<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Twilio-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/twilio-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Twilio-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/twilio-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build a Twilio SMS &#43; Microsoft Teams Integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13877/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13877/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.twilio.com/blog/feed&#34;&gt;Twilio Engineering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.twilio.com/en-us/blog/developers/tutorials/integrations/build-twilio-sms-microsoft-teams-integration&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to run Automated AMD Tests and Fine-Tune Twilio AMD for Accurate Voice Automation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13876/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13876/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.twilio.com/blog/feed&#34;&gt;Twilio Engineering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.twilio.com/en-us/blog/developers/best-practices/automated-amd-tests-voice&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Holiday Magic: Twilio Powers Real-Time Calls for ‘NORAD Tracks Santa’</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13478/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13478/</guid>
      <description>This December, Twilio joins the NORAD Tracks Santa program, a cherished tradition for over 70 years. 🎅✨ Twilio&amp;rsquo;s WebRTC technology will facilitate real-time calls, connecting children worldwide with volunteers tracking Santa&amp;rsquo;s journey on Christmas Eve. Exciting times ahead as we enhance holiday joy! 🎄📞 #Twilio #NORADTracksSanta #HolidayMagic #WebRTC #SantaTracker</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Week 2025: Setting New Standards for Intelligent Engagement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13477/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13477/</guid>
      <description>Cyber Week 2025 saw impressive engagement powered by Twilio&amp;rsquo;s APIs. Over 75.1 billion emails, 6.99 billion messages, and 1.07 billion calls were processed, setting new benchmarks for communication. These figures highlight the importance of intelligent engagement in driving customer interactions. 📧📱📞 #CyberWeek2025 #Twilio #Engagement #APIs #Communication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a SendGrid MCP Server for AI Email Workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13479/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13479/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn how to build a SendGrid MCP Server for AI email workflows! This guide offers insights on setting up a scalable email platform, utilizing Twilio&amp;rsquo;s APIs for efficient communication. Discover best practices and tips for enhancing your email capabilities in the AI landscape. #SendGrid #AIWorkflows #Twilio #EmailMarketing #TechTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Twilio &#43; Zoho CRM SMS Integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13414/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13414/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn how to enhance your Zoho CRM experience! This tutorial guides you through building a PHP application that sends SMS notifications to meeting participants. Stay updated on new meetings or any changes with the Twilio and Zoho CRM integration. Perfect for developers looking to streamline communication! 📲💼 #Twilio #ZohoCRM #SMSIntegration #Developers #TechTutorial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use RabbitMQ in Go</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13523/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13523/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn how to integrate RabbitMQ into your Go applications with this step-by-step guide. The article outlines the process of building a resilient application using RabbitMQ, a powerful messaging broker. Key topics include installation, setup, and best practices for effective message handling. Dive into the world of messaging in Go! 🐇📦 #RabbitMQ #GoLang #ProgrammingTips #SoftwareDevelopment #Messaging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Authenticate with Magic Links in Go</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13415/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13415/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to authenticate users with magic links in Go! 📱✨ This tutorial guides you through building an application that uses Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Programmable Messaging API to send magic links via SMS for user authentication. Discover the step-by-step process and enhance your app&amp;rsquo;s login experience! #GoLang #Twilio #WebDevelopment #MagicLinks #Authentication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 reasons why email marketing is important in 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13287/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13287/</guid>
      <description>Email marketing proves its value with a staggering ROI of 3,600% to 4,500%. 📈 This direct communication channel allows businesses to connect with customers effectively, cutting through the noise of social media and other platforms. ✉️ As trends evolve, email remains a reliable method for tailored messaging and customer engagement. Discover more reasons why email marketing is vital in 2026! #EmailMarketing #ROI #CustomerEngagement #DigitalMarketing #MarketingTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying AI at Scale Without Sacrificing Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13286/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13286/</guid>
      <description>Deploying AI securely is a complex task that involves more than just one decision. It requires a disciplined approach that focuses on three key elements: &lt;strong&gt;People&lt;/strong&gt;: Training and awareness are crucial for effective AI deployment. &lt;strong&gt;Process&lt;/strong&gt;: Establishing clear protocols helps in maintaining security. &lt;strong&gt;Practice&lt;/strong&gt;: Continuous evaluation and improvement of practices ensure ongoing protection. Understanding these interconnected elements is essential for organizations looking to scale AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What you should know about Australia&#39;s new SMS Sender ID Register</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13131/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13131/</guid>
      <description>Australia has introduced a new SMS Sender ID Register to enhance transparency and security in messaging. 📲 This register requires businesses to register their SMS sender IDs, helping to reduce spam and protect consumers from scams. Compliance with the new regulations is essential for companies using SMS for communication. Stay informed on these developments to ensure your messaging practices align with the new requirements. 🔒 #SMS #SenderID #Australia #Regulations #BusinessCompliance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Smart QA ChatOps Assistant with Playwright, Twilio WhatsApp, LLMs, and MCP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13082/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13082/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of ChatOps with a Smart QA Assistant! 🤖✨ This article guides developers on integrating Playwright, Twilio WhatsApp, LLMs, and MCP to enhance quality assurance processes. Learn how these tools work together to streamline communication and automate testing. Explore innovative solutions for efficient development! #ChatOps #QualityAssurance #Twilio #Playwright #Automation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checking it twice: How to spot a fake in your inbox and stay safe this holiday season</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13026/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13026/</guid>
      <description>This holiday season, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to be vigilant about email safety. 📧 Twilio&amp;rsquo;s latest article offers practical tips for identifying fake emails. It emphasizes checking sender addresses, looking for spelling errors, and avoiding suspicious links. 🛡️ Stay informed and protect yourself from scams this festive season! 🎄 #EmailSafety #CyberSecurity #HolidayTips #Twilio #StaySafe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Builder: Stefany Millstein, Director of Sales, Commercial</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12932/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12932/</guid>
      <description>Meet Stefany Millstein, Director of Sales at Twilio. In a recent blog post, she shares insights into her role and the importance of cloud communications. Stefany emphasizes the value of building scalable voice and SMS applications using Twilio&amp;rsquo;s APIs. Her experiences highlight the innovative trends shaping the industry today. Explore more about her journey and the impact of Twilio&amp;rsquo;s technology! 🌟📱 #Twilio #CloudCommunications #SalesLeadership #APIs #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launch WhatsApp faster with Twilio: Senders API GA, plus Typing Indicators, Flows, and a smoother ISV experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12880/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12880/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Twilio enhances WhatsApp integration with the launch of the Senders API, now in GA. This update introduces Typing Indicators and Flows, improving communication efficiency. Additionally, the onboarding process for ISVs has been streamlined, allowing businesses to connect with customers more quickly and effectively. #Twilio #WhatsApp #APIs #BusinessGrowth #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Know if Your Voice AI Agents are Working?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12827/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12827/</guid>
      <description>Are your Voice AI agents performing effectively? 🤖 The Twilio blog discusses key indicators to assess their performance. It emphasizes checking if they are production-ready and whether they address your business needs. Understanding these factors can help ensure your Voice AI agents deliver value. #VoiceAI #TechInsights #BusinessSolutions #Twilio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Create a Magic Link in Laravel with Twilio SMS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12826/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12826/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of seamless user authentication! 🔑 This tutorial guides you through the process of creating a magic link in Laravel using Twilio SMS. It covers step-by-step instructions to help developers implement this feature effectively. Enhance your application&amp;rsquo;s user experience today! 🚀📱 #Laravel #Twilio #WebDevelopment #SMS #Authentication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2026 guide to create ads that click to WhatsApp with Twilio</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12745/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12745/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to effectively create ads that link directly to WhatsApp using Twilio. 📱 This guide provides step-by-step instructions for developers, focusing on best practices, integration tips, and user engagement strategies. Enhance your advertising approach and connect with your audience more directly. #Twilio #WhatsApp #DigitalMarketing #AdTech #DeveloperTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Guide to Core Latency in AI Voice Agents (Cascaded Edition)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12744/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12744/</guid>
      <description>Understanding core latency in AI voice agents is crucial for developers. This article outlines the baseline delays that occur during conversations and offers tips for managing these delays effectively. It also discusses important tradeoffs to consider when optimizing performance. Explore how to enhance user experience by addressing core latency. 📈🤖 #AI #VoiceTechnology #Latency #Developers #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Send Timely SMS in Adobe Journey Optimizer Using Twilio Programmable Messaging</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12743/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12743/</guid>
      <description>Discover how to enhance customer engagement by integrating Twilio Programmable Messaging with Adobe Journey Optimizer. 📲 This integration allows businesses to send timely and personalized SMS notifications, improving communication and customer satisfaction. For developers looking to streamline messaging, this guide offers practical steps for implementation. #AdobeJourneyOptimizer #Twilio #SMSMarketing #CustomerEngagement #Integration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Trust in the Age of AI: Why Identity Is the Foundation of Customer Engagement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-11527/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-11527/</guid>
      <description>Twilio plans to acquire Stytch, an identity platform aimed at enhancing AI agent capabilities for developers. This move highlights the importance of identity in building trust and improving customer engagement in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. Stay tuned for how this acquisition may impact the future of AI interactions! 🤖🔐 #AI #CustomerEngagement #Twilio #Stytch #DigitalTrust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Conversational AI Revolution: What 5,000&#43; Consumers and Businesses Told Us</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12162/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12162/</guid>
      <description>Discover insights from Twilio&amp;rsquo;s report on the impact of conversational AI in sales and support. Based on feedback from over 5,000 consumers and businesses, the report highlights the growing role of AI in enhancing customer interactions. Key trends show how businesses are adopting these technologies to improve efficiency and satisfaction. 🤖📈 #ConversationalAI #CustomerExperience #TechTrends #AIInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VoIP texting: What it is and how to do it right</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12122/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12122/</guid>
      <description>📱 Did you know your VoIP number can be used for texting? VoIP texting allows businesses to send and receive SMS through the internet, maintaining their existing phone identity. This method offers high engagement rates, with SMS having an open rate of 98%. It&amp;rsquo;s a cost-effective way to interact with customers globally. Learn how to leverage VoIP texting for your business and integrate it with tools like Twilio for better communication. #VoIPTexting #BusinessCommunication #CustomerEngagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing General Availability of  for Voice Recording</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12123/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12123/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news from Twilio! The new TwiML for voice call recording is now generally available. This feature allows developers to capture 100% of inbound and outbound call audio, enhancing communication capabilities. Explore the potential of this tool for your projects! 🎤💻 #Twilio #VoiceRecording #TechNews #Developers #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrating Twilio and Zendesk for SMS Messaging</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12124/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12124/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to integrate Twilio and Zendesk for SMS messaging in this informative tutorial. 📲 The article outlines the use of webhooks to facilitate this integration, enhancing communication capabilities for businesses. Explore the step-by-step process to streamline SMS interactions with customers. #Twilio #Zendesk #SMSIntegration #TechTutorials #CustomerService</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIGNAL Sydney 2025: A Sold‑out Debut on the Harbour</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12125/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12125/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Twilio SIGNAL made its debut in Sydney in 2025, bringing together 283 customers, partners, and industry leaders. This sold-out event highlighted innovation and collaboration within the tech community. Attendees engaged in discussions about the future of communication and technology. Stay tuned for more updates from SIGNAL! 🌏💡 #Twilio #SIGNAL2025 #TechEvents #Sydney #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Email Logs: Search, Filter, and Troubleshoot Email Events</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11848/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11848/</guid>
      <description>📣 Exciting news from Twilio SendGrid! Email Logs are now Generally Available. This new feature allows users to search event data, troubleshoot bounces, and validate email delivery effectively. Enhancing your email deliverability has never been easier. Stay informed and take advantage of this powerful tool! 📧✅ #EmailMarketing #TwilioSendGrid #EmailLogs #Deliverability #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting iOS 26 Call Screening and Leaving Voicemail​: ​How Twilio AMD and Real-Time Transcriptions Make It Possible</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11686/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11686/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Discover how to detect Apple iOS 26 Call Screening effectively! This article explores the use of Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Answer Machine Detection (AMD) alongside real-time transcriptions. These tools enable developers to identify when a call is screened and ensure that voicemails can be left accurately. Stay updated on the latest tech advancements! 📱💬 #Twilio #iOS26 #CallScreening #TechNews #Developers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Twilio Flex and Microsoft Dynamics 365 with Zing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11684/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11684/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Enhance your customer experience by integrating Twilio Flex with Microsoft Dynamics 365! Zing offers a blueprint for seamless real-time data synchronization and improved agent productivity. This integration can help streamline operations and deliver better service to customers. Discover the benefits today! #CustomerExperience #TwilioFlex #MicrosoftDynamics #ZingIntegration #AgentProductivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Twilio and ZenDesk Voice Integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11685/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11685/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of your customer support with the Twilio and ZenDesk Voice integration! 📞✨ This guide outlines the steps to quickly activate and customize the integration, enhancing communication and efficiency. Discover how to streamline your customer interactions and improve support workflows easily. #Twilio #ZenDesk #CustomerSupport #VoiceIntegration #TechTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 ways Twilio’s infrastructure ensures reliability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11526/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11526/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Discover how Twilio&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure enhances reliability for global communications. The article outlines eight key strategies that ensure secure and real-time interactions for customers. These strategies focus on maintaining uptime and optimizing performance across various platforms. Learn how Twilio supports developers and businesses in delivering consistent customer engagement. 🌍📞 #Twilio #Reliability #CloudCommunications #CustomerEngagement #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Trust in the Age of AI: Why Identity Is the Foundation of Customer Engagement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11527/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11527/</guid>
      <description>Twilio plans to acquire Stytch, an identity platform aimed at enhancing AI agent capabilities for developers. This move highlights the importance of identity in building trust and improving customer engagement in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. Stay tuned for how this acquisition may impact the future of AI interactions! 🤖🔐 #AI #CustomerEngagement #Twilio #Stytch #DigitalTrust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber Week 2025 preparation: Key insights and best practices for retail success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11561/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11561/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cyber Week 2025 is approaching, and preparation is key for retail success! Experts from Twilio emphasize the importance of personalized customer experiences during this busy period. In 2024, digital sales hit $76 billion in the US, highlighting the scale businesses must manage. Best practices include starting preparations early to ensure smooth operations. #CyberWeek #RetailSuccess #CustomerExperience #Ecommerce #BusinessStrategy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of BPO in the Age of AI and Automation: A Conversational Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11474/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11474/</guid>
      <description>Discover insights from our recent webinar on the future of BPO in an era shaped by AI and automation. 🤖 Industry leaders discussed the impact of intelligent automation, the need for upskilling, and the role of hyper-personalization. They emphasized that human empathy and adaptability remain crucial for success. As BPOs face digital transformation, the conversation highlighted what’s next for the industry. 🌐 #BPO #AI #Automation #DigitalTransformation #FutureOfWork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October 2025 Fraud Update: How ISVs can Prepare for the Holiday Season</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11475/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11475/</guid>
      <description>As the holiday season approaches, ISVs need to focus on account security. The October 2025 Fraud Update highlights rising trends in AIT and webform abuse. It outlines essential steps ISVs can take to protect their platforms and respond to potential threats effectively. Stay informed and prepare to safeguard your business! 🔒🎄 #FraudPrevention #CyberSecurity #ISVs #HolidaySeason #AIT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making Alt Text Fast: How Twilio Scaled Docs Accessibility with Automation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11328/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11328/</guid>
      <description>Twilio has successfully implemented prompt-driven automation to enhance accessibility in their documentation. By generating alt text and filenames automatically, they have streamlined the process, saving valuable time. This approach not only improves efficiency but also ensures better accessibility for users. Learn more about their innovative strategy! ✨📄 #Accessibility #Automation #Twilio #TechInnovation #Documentation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulatory &amp; Compliance Corner – October 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11390/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11390/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The latest edition of the Regulatory &amp;amp; Compliance Corner highlights key telecom policy changes globally. 📜 It provides an overview of new regulations impacting the industry, ensuring companies stay informed and compliant. Stay updated on how these changes could affect your operations. #Telecom #Regulations #Compliance #IndustryInsights #PolicyChanges</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Twilio Voice &#43; ElevenLabs Agents Integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11241/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11241/</guid>
      <description>Discover how to integrate Twilio Voice with ElevenLabs agents in your applications. This tutorial guides you through the process of building scalable voice solutions using Twilio&amp;rsquo;s APIs. Learn about cloud communication trends and customer success stories while enhancing your development skills. 🌐💻📞 #Twilio #VoiceIntegration #Developers #TechTutorials #CloudCommunications</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Builder: Cesar Hernandez, Manager, Personalized Support</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11242/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11242/</guid>
      <description>Meet Cesar Hernandez, Manager of Personalized Support at Twilio. His journey highlights the importance of timely referrals and leading with empathy. 🌍 Cesar is dedicated to personal growth and giving back to his community in Bogotá, showcasing how professional development can align with social responsibility. 🤝 Read more about his inspiring story! #Leadership #Community #Twilio #Empathy #ProfessionalGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Manage Your Twilio Verify Safe List in Laravel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11047/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11047/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to effectively manage your Twilio Verify Safe List using Laravel in this informative tutorial. The article provides step-by-step guidance on integrating the Twilio Safe List API, ensuring smooth user verification processes. Enhance your development skills and streamline your application today! 📱💻✨ #Twilio #Laravel #WebDevelopment #API #Tutorial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sending SMS Messages with Twilio and Zapier</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11053/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11053/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Explore how to send SMS messages using Twilio and Zapier! This article provides a comprehensive guide for developers looking to integrate SMS capabilities into their applications. It highlights the benefits of using Twilio&amp;rsquo;s APIs alongside Zapier&amp;rsquo;s automation tools to streamline communication processes. Learn about key features and practical applications to enhance user engagement. #Twilio #Zapier #SMSIntegration #Developers #TechTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take command of your customer data with the latest Twilio platform releases</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10972/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10972/</guid>
      <description>Twilio recently shared updates on their platform aimed at enhancing customer data management. The article highlights trends in cloud communications, offers customer success stories, and provides tips for developing scalable voice and SMS applications using Twilio&amp;rsquo;s APIs. Stay informed on how these tools can benefit your business. 📊💬 #Twilio #CustomerData #CloudCommunications #APIs #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Global Impact Week Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10973/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10973/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Twilio recently shared insights from their 2025 Global Impact Week. The recap highlights cloud communications trends, showcasing customer stories and providing tips for developing scalable voice and SMS applications using Twilio&amp;rsquo;s APIs. Stay updated on the latest in tech and communication! 📱💬 #CloudCommunications #Twilio #TechTrends #APIs #VoiceAndSMS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Builder’s Arcade at SIGNAL Sydney 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10974/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10974/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Discover the Builder’s Arcade at SIGNAL Sydney 2025! This interactive space showcases innovative experiences designed for developers. Attendees can engage with various activations highlighting the latest in technology and collaboration. Join us to explore and connect with industry leaders, enhancing your skills and insights! #SIGNALSydney2025 #Developers #TechEvent #Innovation #Networking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Brand Builders Need Most Right Now? Smarter Data, Real-Time Personalization, and AI That Actually Works | AdWeek 2025 Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10919/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10919/</guid>
      <description>In the AdWeek 2025 recap, key insights for brand builders were shared. The focus is on the importance of smarter data, emphasizing the need for real-time personalization to enhance customer engagement. Additionally, the article highlights the value of effective AI tools that can genuinely support marketing efforts. Stay updated on these trends to improve brand strategies! 📊✨🤖 #AdWeek2025 #BrandBuilding #AI #MarketingTrends #Personalization</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Write Better Reminder Emails (Template &#43; Examples)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10975/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10975/</guid>
      <description>Improve your reminder emails with key strategies for better engagement! 📧✨ Most reminders can be ignored or deleted. However, effective emails can be helpful nudges that keep business running smoothly. Focus on timing, tone, and clarity. Important components include a clear subject line, engaging preview text, personalized greetings, and essential logistical details. Learn more about crafting effective reminder emails in our comprehensive guide! #EmailMarketing #BusinessCommunication&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senders Gain Access to More Data with Yahoo ‘Insights’</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10628/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10628/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo Mail has introduced Yahoo Insights, a new feature that provides users with access to sender data. This tool aims to enhance user experience by offering detailed information about senders. With Yahoo Insights, senders can better understand their audience and improve communication strategies. This update could be beneficial for both personal and business users. Stay informed about advancements in email technology! 📧🔍 #YahooInsights #EmailMarketing #TechUpdates #UserExperience #DataAnalytics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Traffic Jams to Green Lights: Faster, Smarter Messaging with Twilio’s Traffic Optimization Engine</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10523/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10523/</guid>
      <description>Twilio introduces its Traffic Optimization Engine, designed to enhance messaging efficiency. This new feature aims to reduce delays and improve delivery rates for developers. By analyzing message traffic, the engine optimizes routes, ensuring smoother communication. This advancement is expected to significantly benefit businesses relying on timely messaging. 🚦📱💬 #Twilio #Messaging #TechInnovation #BusinessSolutions #TrafficOptimization</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scheduling SMS in Laravel with Twilio</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10547/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10547/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of timely reminders! 📅 This tutorial guides developers on how to schedule SMS notifications using Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Programmable Messaging API with Laravel. It simplifies the process, ensuring you can set up reminders efficiently. Learn to enhance your application’s communication features today! 📲 #Twilio #Laravel #SMS #WebDevelopment #Coding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use a TwiML Application to Connect your Voice AI Agent to a Twilio Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10524/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10524/</guid>
      <description>🔗 Connect your Voice AI Agent to a Twilio Conference using a TwiML Application! This article provides a step-by-step guide on integrating Voice AI with Twilio&amp;rsquo;s conferencing features. It covers the necessary setup and coding to streamline communication effectively. For developers looking to enhance interactions, this tutorial is a valuable resource. #VoiceAI #Twilio #TwiML #DeveloperTutorial #TechIntegration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build an AI Chatbot with Facebook Messenger, OpenAI, and Twilio Programmable Messaging using Python</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10479/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10479/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to create your own AI chatbot? The Twilio blog provides a step-by-step guide on building a chatbot using Facebook Messenger, OpenAI, and Twilio Programmable Messaging with Python. This tutorial covers essential integration techniques and highlights key tools to enhance your development process. Explore the world of AI and messaging! 🤖💬 #AIChatbot #Twilio #PythonDevelopment #TechTutorials #OpenAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Customer Intelligence for Advertisers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10474/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10474/</guid>
      <description>Unlock enhanced ad performance with Customer Intelligence for Advertisers! 📈 The article discusses how Segment CDP can improve targeting, attribution, and return on ad spend (ROAS) across various channels. By leveraging smarter data, advertisers can optimize their campaigns more effectively. Explore the benefits of integrating advanced data solutions into your advertising strategy! 💡 #CustomerIntelligence #Advertising #DataDriven #ROAS #SegmentCDP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twilio Segment Unify: Expert Answers to Profiles, Journeys, and Secure Activation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10478/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10478/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Missed the Twilio Segment Unify webinar? Catch up on key insights about real-time profiles and how Journeys integrates with your CRM. Learn about securely activating warehouse audiences using Reverse-ETL. Stay informed to enhance your data strategy! #Twilio #DataIntegration #CRM #Webinar #MarketingInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book Appointments With Laravel, Twilio and SendGrid</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10342/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10342/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn how to create an efficient appointment management system using Laravel, Twilio, and SendGrid! This tutorial guides developers through the process of building a robust booking system. It covers essential steps and integrations, making it easier to manage appointments effectively. Explore the potential of these powerful tools! 📅📲✉️ #Laravel #Twilio #SendGrid #TechTutorial #AppointmentSystem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Secure Signup API in .NET that Filters Emails and Verifies with Twilio SendGrid</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10345/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10345/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how to create a Secure Signup API in .NET! This tutorial guides developers on filtering emails and verifying them using Twilio SendGrid. Enhance your email campaign productivity with a robust system for user registration. Learn the steps to streamline your signup process today! 📧🔒 #DotNet #Twilio #EmailVerification #APIDevelopment #TechTutorial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gmail to Retire Domain &amp; IP Reputation in Postmaster Tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10344/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10344/</guid>
      <description>Gmail is set to retire the domain and IP reputation scores in its Postmaster Tools. This change will impact how senders monitor their email performance. Senders should be aware of this shift and consider alternative methods for tracking their email reputation. Stay informed and adapt to these changes for better email strategies. 📧🔍 #Gmail #EmailMarketing #PostmasterTools #EmailReputation #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Validate Twilio Event Streams Webhooks in Go</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10343/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10343/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to validate Twilio Event Streams webhooks in Go with a straightforward tutorial. This guide utilizes Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Go Helper Library to ensure proper webhook validation, essential for maintaining secure integrations. Perfect for developers looking to enhance their Twilio experience! 📊🔒💻 #Twilio #GoProgramming #Webhooks #DeveloperTutorial #Coding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The RCS holiday messaging playbook: Turn texts into branded experiences</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10427/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10427/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of your holiday messaging with RCS! 🎉 This playbook highlights how to transform standard texts into engaging shopping experiences. Use rich visuals, interactive replies, and verified brand markers to capture attention effectively. Enhance your customer interactions this holiday season! 📱💬 #RCS #HolidayMarketing #CustomerEngagement #BrandExperience #Messaging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ConversationRelay and the AI Agent Builder Dify: A Multimodal Example with Voice</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10238/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10238/</guid>
      <description>Discover how to create a multimodal experience using Twilio&amp;rsquo;s ConversationRelay and the open-source AI Agent Builder, Dify. This guide provides developers with step-by-step instructions to integrate voice capabilities into their applications effectively. Enhance user interactions with this innovative approach! 🎤🤖 #Twilio #Dify #AI #VoiceTechnology #DeveloperTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Partners for the AI Era: Twilio AI Certification Program</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10237/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10237/</guid>
      <description>Twilio has launched its AI Certification Program aimed at empowering partners in the AI landscape. This initiative showcases certified partners and highlights Twilio&amp;rsquo;s commitment to AI innovation. The program serves as a key element of Twilio’s AI strategy, reinforcing its ecosystem investments. Explore how this certification can enhance partner capabilities and drive growth. 🌐🤖 #Twilio #AICertification #Partnerships #Innovation #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Twilio Docs Support for llms.txt and Markdown</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10182/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10182/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news from Twilio! Twilio Docs now support the llms.txt standard and Markdown. This enhancement allows customers to seamlessly integrate Twilio context into their LLM-powered tools. This update aims to improve user experience and accessibility for developers working with Twilio. #Twilio #LLM #TechNews #Developers #Markdown</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building an OmniChannel Experience: Context Aware Interactions using Salesforce Integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10181/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10181/</guid>
      <description>Building an OmniChannel Experience is essential for effective customer interactions. The article discusses how integrating Salesforce can enhance context-aware interactions. It highlights the importance of seamless communication across various channels to improve customer satisfaction. Developers can leverage Twilio’s tools in this integration. Read more about optimizing your customer experience! 📞💻✨ #OmniChannel #SalesforceIntegration #CustomerExperience #Twilio #DeveloperInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twilio named to the IDC FinTech Rankings 2025 Enterprise Top 50</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10183/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10183/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news! Twilio has been recognized in the IDC FinTech Rankings 2025 as one of the Top 50 Enterprises. This acknowledgment highlights Twilio&amp;rsquo;s influence in cloud communications and its role in supporting scalable voice and SMS applications through its APIs. Learn more about the trends and customer stories that showcase this achievement. #Twilio #FinTech #CloudCommunications #APIs #IDC2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the builder: Tanise Love, Senior Employee Impact Manager</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10117/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10117/</guid>
      <description>Meet Tanise Love, Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Senior Employee Impact Manager! 🌟 In her role, Tanise emphasizes the importance of values that shape Twilio’s giving culture. She actively works to bring this culture to life, demonstrating how corporate responsibility can impact communities and employees alike. Discover more about her insights and contributions in the full article. #Twilio #EmployeeSpotlight #CorporateResponsibility #GivingCulture #Leadership</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage a List of Safe Phone Numbers in PHP with Twilio Verify&#39;s Safe List API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9956/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9956/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to integrate a Safe List into your PHP applications using Twilio Verify&amp;rsquo;s Safe List API. This tutorial provides step-by-step instructions on managing a list of safe phone numbers, enhancing security in your applications. Explore the features and benefits of implementing this API today! 📱🔒 #Twilio #PHP #APIs #WebDevelopment #Security</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upstream Data Orchestration:  The Key to Real-Time, 1:1 Personalization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-10044/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-10044/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking real-time, personalized experiences is vital for businesses today. Twilio emphasizes the importance of upstream data orchestration in achieving 1:1 personalization. The article discusses how leveraging data effectively can enhance customer interactions and drive engagement. Learn how Twilio&amp;rsquo;s APIs support scalable voice and SMS applications for better communication strategies. #DataOrchestration #RealTimePersonalization #Twilio #CustomerEngagement #APIs 📊📱✨</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the Monolith: How We Used the Strangler Fig Pattern to Transform Segment’s Notification Architecture</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9896/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9896/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in notification architecture! Segment has adopted the Strangler Fig pattern to modernize its alerts and notifications. This approach promotes modularity, reliability, and reusability in workflows. Learn how this transformation enhances the overall system performance. #TechInnovation #SoftwareDevelopment #Notifications #StranglerFig #ModularDesign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build 2-Way Conversational Email Experiences Using SendGrid Inbound Parse</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9957/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9957/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Explore how to create a 2-way conversational email system using Twilio SendGrid’s Inbound Parse! This tutorial guides developers in integrating SendGrid with AWS Bedrock and Serverless Lambda for effective email communication. Boost your email capabilities and streamline interactions. 📧💡 #Twilio #SendGrid #EmailMarketing #AWS #Developers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Generative AI Email Experiences using SendGrid Inbound Parse</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9958/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9958/</guid>
      <description>Discover how to create a generative AI email system using Twilio SendGrid’s Inbound Parse. This guide integrates AWS Bedrock and Serverless Lambda for enhanced email experiences. Learn the step-by-step process to build automated email agents that respond intelligently to incoming messages. This approach leverages powerful cloud technologies for efficiency. 📧💻✨ #Twilio #SendGrid #GenerativeAI #EmailAutomation #AWS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Enable MMS Messaging &amp; Fix Download Issues on Android</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-10045/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-10045/</guid>
      <description>Struggling with MMS messaging on your Android device? 📱💬 This article provides a step-by-step guide on how to enable MMS messaging and troubleshoot download issues. It covers common problems and solutions to help you get your messaging back on track. Check it out for practical tips! #AndroidTips #MMS #TechHelp #MessagingIssues</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-service in the age of AI: Virtual agents that actually resolve</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9895/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9895/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Tired of ineffective chatbots? Explore AI virtual agents that provide real solutions across various channels. These agents not only enhance customer satisfaction (CSAT) but also relieve your support team from repetitive tasks. Learn how self-service is evolving in the age of AI! 🤖✨ #AI #CustomerSupport #SelfService #VirtualAgents #Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use ConversationRelay with the Open Source Agent Builder Flowise: A Multi-Agent Example with Voice</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9897/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9897/</guid>
      <description>Explore how to integrate ConversationRelay with the open-source agent builder Flowise to create a multi-agent voice experience. This guide provides insights on using Twilio Voice alongside Flowise for enhanced voice interactions. Perfect for developers looking to elevate user engagement through voice technology! 📞🔧 #Twilio #Flowise #VoiceTech #Developers #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Holiday Email Marketing Best Practices for 2025 (and Beyond)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9852/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9852/</guid>
      <description>Get ready for the holiday season with effective email marketing strategies! 🎄✉️ This article offers essential tips for planning, optimizing, and managing your email campaigns before, during, and after the holidays. It includes templates and examples to streamline your efforts. Key highlights include planning ahead, adapting to changes in your audience, and strategies to tackle post-holiday churn. #EmailMarketing #HolidayCampaigns #MarketingTips #2025Goals</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Changes Are Coming to the Gmail Inbox</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9841/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9841/</guid>
      <description>📧 Big updates are on the way for Gmail users! The platform will introduce relevancy sorting for promotional emails, enhancing how users view their inbox. Additionally, a new purchases tab will help organize transaction-related emails more effectively. These changes are significant for email marketers to consider in their strategies. #GmailUpdates #EmailMarketing #DigitalTrends #InboxChanges #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Siloes to Platforms: New Data on How Security Teams Are Closing the Fraud Gap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9758/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9758/</guid>
      <description>New research from Liminal and Twilio highlights the convergence of authentication and fraud prevention. It reveals that multi-signal platforms can effectively reduce risk while minimizing user friction. This shift helps security teams tackle fraud more efficiently. Stay informed about the evolving landscape of security! 🔍🔒 #FraudPrevention #CyberSecurity #Authentication #DataSecurity #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Smart Inventory Chatbot on WhatsApp with LangChain, LangGraph, OpenAI, and Flask</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9757/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9757/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Interested in building a smart inventory chatbot? Check out the latest guide on creating one using WhatsApp, LangChain, LangGraph, OpenAI, and Flask. The article provides step-by-step instructions and insights into leveraging these technologies for efficient communication. Enhance your customer interactions today! #ChatbotDevelopment #WhatsApp #OpenAI #LangChain #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to schedule a text message on iPhone and Android</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9842/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9842/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Want to send a text at the perfect moment? This guide covers how to schedule text messages on both iPhone and Android. Learn step-by-step methods to ensure your messages reach recipients at the right time, even if you&amp;rsquo;re busy. Never miss an important moment again! 📱💬 #TextMessage #iPhone #Android #TechTips #Communication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe Coding with an Agent and Twilio SMS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9759/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9759/</guid>
      <description>Discover how to vibe code using Anthropic Claude and build a Twilio SMS application with .NET! This article provides a step-by-step guide for developers looking to integrate AI capabilities with SMS services. It covers essential tools and techniques for effective implementation. Enhance your coding skills and explore new possibilities in app development! 🚀💻📱 #Twilio #Coding #AI #Developers #TechTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Real-Time Support Chat with Go and Twilio Conversations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9712/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9712/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn how to create a real-time support chat using Go and Twilio Conversations! This tutorial provides step-by-step guidance for developers looking to enhance customer support systems. It covers the integration of Twilio&amp;rsquo;s powerful messaging capabilities with the Go programming language. For those interested in improving support interactions, this is a great resource! #GoLang #Twilio #RealTimeSupport #Developers #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP-Based .NET Micro-Weather Wisdom SMS Service Using Twilio &amp; OpenAI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9760/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9760/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how to build a lightweight SMS service that delivers personalized weather tips! This tutorial guides you through using Twilio and OpenAI to fetch forecasts and provide actionable advice on clothing and activities. Users can receive tips on a schedule or on-demand via SMS. Learn more about integrating these technologies for effective weather communication! 📅🌦️ #Twilio #OpenAI #WeatherService #SMS #TechTutorial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say Hello to SIP Code 603&#43;: The FCC’s New Standard for Analytics-based Blocked Calls</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9671/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9671/</guid>
      <description>The FCC has introduced SIP Code 603+, a new standard for analytics-based blocked calls. This code aims to enhance call blocking and improve the accuracy of call completion. By utilizing analytics, the new standard helps reduce unwanted calls, providing a better experience for users. Stay informed about this significant development in communication technology! 📞🔒 #FCC #CallBlocking #Telecom #Communication #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yahoo Mail’s Storage Limit Change Impacts Senders</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9713/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9713/</guid>
      <description>Yahoo Mail has recently reduced its storage limit, which affects how senders can interact with recipients. This change may lead to issues with email delivery and storage for users. It’s important for both senders and recipients to be aware of this update to manage their email effectively. Stay informed and adjust your email practices accordingly! 📧📉 #YahooMail #EmailUpdates #TechNews #StorageLimit #EmailManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redesigning Twilio’s Onboarding Experience: What’s New</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9595/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9595/</guid>
      <description>Twilio has revamped its onboarding experience to enhance user engagement. The new design focuses on personalized experiences tailored for developers. These updates aim to streamline the onboarding process, allowing users to build faster with improved developer tools. Explore the new features and how they can benefit your workflow. 🚀👩‍💻 #Twilio #UserOnboarding #DeveloperTools #TechUpdates #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twilio’s 2025 Heightened Awareness Period: Ensuring Reliable Messaging for Peak Season</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9596/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9596/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Twilio is gearing up for its 2025 Heightened Awareness Period, focusing on reliable messaging during peak seasons. The company shares insights on cloud communication trends and offers customer stories that highlight the effectiveness of its APIs for scalable voice and SMS applications. Stay informed for tips on optimizing your messaging strategies! 📩💡 #Twilio #CloudCommunications #SMS #VoiceApplications #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Heartfelt Thanks to Our Community of Builders</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9496/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9496/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to announce that Twilio has been named one of Fast Company&amp;rsquo;s 2025 Best Workplaces for Innovators! 🎉 This recognition highlights our commitment to fostering a creative culture and empowering innovation within our community of builders. Thank you to everyone who contributes to this vibrant environment! 🙌 #Twilio #Innovation #BestWorkplaces #Community #Gratitude</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The End of the Emergency Plan-as-Usual</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9539/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9539/</guid>
      <description>Humanitarian organizations and governments are transforming crisis readiness strategies. They are implementing scalable, people-first communication systems to enhance response during weather-related disasters. These advancements aim to save lives and improve coordination in emergencies. Stay informed about these critical changes. 🌍📞✨ #CrisisManagement #HumanitarianAid #DisasterResponse #CommunicationSystems #WeatherPreparedness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perform a Warm Transfer to a Human Agent from the OpenAI Realtime API using Twilio Programmable SIP and TypeScript</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9497/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9497/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn how to seamlessly connect OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s Realtime SIP Connector with Twilio’s Programmable SIP. This guide covers the process of interacting with an AI Agent and performing a warm transfer to a human agent using TypeScript. Enhance your communication solutions effectively! 🔗 Check out the full tutorial for detailed steps. #Twilio #OpenAI #SIP #TypeScript #Developers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calculating Character Count of RCS Messages</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7770/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7770/</guid>
      <description>Understanding RCS message character count is crucial for effective customer engagement. 📱 This article delves into the differences in message length and encoding between RCS and SMS. It highlights the importance of these factors in communication strategies. For developers, these insights can optimize message delivery and enhance user experiences. #RCS #SMS #CustomerEngagement #TechInsights #Messaging</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compliance Toolkit: AI-powered support for SMS compliance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7713/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7713/</guid>
      <description>Twilio&amp;rsquo;s new Compliance Toolkit leverages AI and machine learning to enhance SMS compliance. This tool proactively identifies and mitigates potential regulatory violations, helping businesses maintain compliance and avoid penalties. Explore how AI can support your compliance efforts! 📲🤖 #Compliance #AI #SMS #Twilio #Regulations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laravel Queries: Learn by Building a Data Table</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7649/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7649/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into Laravel with a hands-on tutorial! Learn how to effectively use Laravel&amp;rsquo;s Query Builder through practical examples. The article guides you step-by-step to build a functional data table, enhancing your development skills. Perfect for developers looking to sharpen their database query techniques! #Laravel #WebDevelopment #Coding #Programming #DataTables</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Email Marketing: Tools, Benefits &amp; Best Practices in 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7772/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7772/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of AI in email marketing! 🚀 AI tools analyze subscriber behavior in real-time, optimizing send times and personalizing content for better engagement. This means no more one-size-fits-all newsletters; instead, you can craft tailored emails for each recipient. 📧 Discover how AI can help your email marketing team understand what works best, from subject lines to send times. It enhances communication without replacing marketers. #EmailMarketing #AI #MachineLearning&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guide to Apple Mail Privacy Protection (MPP) &amp; iOS 18 (2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7771/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7771/</guid>
      <description>Apple&amp;rsquo;s Mail Privacy Protection (MPP) has evolved since its launch in 2021. The feature aims to enhance user data control but presents challenges for email marketers. 📧 As we head into 2025 with iOS 18, expect changes like AI-generated previews and new inbox categories that impact email visibility. 📊 Tracking remains complex due to masked IP addresses and stripped tracking parameters, making campaign attribution more difficult. 📉 Marketers need to adapt their strategies to thrive in this&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Check Phone Usage and Time Spent on Phone</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-31-7714/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-31-7714/</guid>
      <description>📱 Want to monitor your phone usage? This article guides Android and iPhone users on how to check the time spent on apps and websites. It details the steps needed to access usage statistics, helping you understand your digital habits. Stay informed about your screen time! ⏳ #PhoneUsage #DigitalWellness #ScreenTime #TechTips #Smartphone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMS Verification: What It Is, How It Works, &amp; Sending Codes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-30-7715/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-30-7715/</guid>
      <description>🔒 SMS verification enhances security by sending unique codes to your phone. This process adds an extra layer of protection for users, ensuring that only authorized individuals can access accounts. Businesses can easily implement SMS verification to safeguard sensitive information and improve user trust. Learn more about how this system works and its benefits! 📱✅ #SMSVerification #CyberSecurity #UserTrust #BusinessSafety #Twilio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect the OpenAI Realtime SIP Connector with Twilio Elastic SIP Trunking</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7558/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7558/</guid>
      <description>🔗 Learn how to connect the OpenAI Realtime SIP Connector with Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Elastic SIP Trunking. This integration enables communication with an AI Agent, enhancing your application&amp;rsquo;s capabilities. The article provides a step-by-step guide tailored for developers looking to implement this technology. For more details, check out the full tutorial! #Twilio #OpenAI #SIPTrunking #Developers #TechIntegration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Twilio’s Real-Time Transcriptions Service in Node.js</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7557/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7557/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to implement Twilio’s Real-Time Transcriptions service in your Node.js application. 🖥️ This tutorial guides developers on streaming voice call transcripts through webhooks, enhancing communication and accessibility in applications. Explore the step-by-step process to integrate this feature into your projects. 📞 #Twilio #NodeJS #RealTimeTranscription #Webhooks #DevTutorials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an AI Voice Assistant with Twilio Voice, OpenAI’s Realtime API, and Node.js</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7524/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7524/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how to create an AI voice assistant using Twilio Voice and OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s Realtime API with Node.js! This tutorial guides you through building a conversational assistant that allows fluid, human-like interactions. The new Speech to Speech (S2S) capabilities enhance latency and improve dialogue flow. Learn to set up a Twilio Media Stream server to process audio and deliver real-time responses. Let’s dive into building your own assistant! 🤖💬 #AI #VoiceAssistant #Twilio #OpenAI #NodeJS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an AI Voice Assistant with Twilio Voice, OpenAI’s Realtime API, and Python</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7526/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7526/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! A new tutorial teaches how to build an AI voice assistant using Twilio Voice and OpenAI’s Realtime API with Python and FastAPI. This integration allows for direct Speech to Speech (S2S) functionality, enhancing conversation fluidity. By setting up a Twilio Media Stream server, you can enable your assistant to respond to calls with real-time audio. Explore the possibilities of creating interactive AI experiences! #AI #VoiceAssistant #Twilio #OpenAI #Python</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an AI Voice Assistant with Twilio Voice, the OpenAI Realtime Agents SDK, and Node.js</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7522/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7522/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into the world of AI! This article outlines how to build an AI voice assistant using Twilio Voice, the OpenAI Realtime Agents SDK, and Node.js. It offers practical tips for tool calling and appointment scheduling. Enhance your development skills and explore the integration possibilities. #AI #VoiceAssistant #Twilio #OpenAI #NodeJS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Multimodal Conversational AI Experiences with Twilio and the OpenAI Realtime API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7523/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7523/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of multimodal Voice AI by integrating Twilio APIs with OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s Realtime API. This collaboration enhances customer interactions through practical tutorials and sample projects. Explore how to elevate your conversational AI experiences effectively. #AI #VoiceTech #Twilio #OpenAI #CustomerExperience 🌐🤖💬📈</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Outgoing Calls with Twilio Voice and the OpenAI Realtime API and Node.js</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7525/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7525/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to enhance your calling experience? This article explains how to create an AI-driven voice assistant that can make outbound calls using Twilio Voice and the OpenAI Realtime API with Node.js. It covers essential prerequisites including setting up Node.js, Twilio, and OpenAI accounts. The tutorial also provides demo code for dialing a phone number and handling call interactions. Learn more about building your own voice assistant today! 📞💻 #AI #Twilio #OpenAI #NodeJS #VoiceAssistant</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Outgoing Calls with Twilio Voice, the OpenAI Realtime API, and Python</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7559/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7559/</guid>
      <description>📞 Learn how to build an AI-driven voice assistant that can make outbound calls using Twilio Voice and the OpenAI Realtime API with Python. This tutorial guides you through the process of setting up your Python environment, ensuring you have the required accounts and tools, including Twilio and OpenAI API access. Follow along as you create a filter function to check phone numbers and initiate calls. Once connected, the OpenAI Realtime API will start the conversation! #AI #Twilio #Python&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMTP Port 587 vs 465: Which Port Should You Use?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7716/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7716/</guid>
      <description>📧 Confused about SMTP ports? Here&amp;rsquo;s a quick guide! For email submission, use &lt;strong&gt;SMTP port 587&lt;/strong&gt; with StartTLS. It&amp;rsquo;s the current standard, well-supported, and ensures both secure and non-secure connections run smoothly. &lt;strong&gt;Port 465&lt;/strong&gt; is an option, but it has a complicated history and is generally not recommended unless absolutely necessary. Choose wisely to avoid troubleshooting! 🔧 #SMTP #EmailConfiguration #TechTips #CyberSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Call Center: What It Is, How It Works, &amp; Top Solutions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7717/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7717/</guid>
      <description>Discover the essentials of cloud call centers in our latest guide! ☁️📞 Learn what cloud call centers are, how they operate, and the advantages they hold over traditional systems. The article also highlights top solutions and best practices for implementation. Stay informed about the future of customer communication! #CloudCallCenter #CustomerService #TechTrends #BusinessSolutions #Twilio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCS is now generally available: Increase engagement and ROI with zero code changes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7244/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7244/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for businesses! RCS is now generally available through Twilio. Engage your customers with rich content on a branded channel without any code changes to your existing messaging solutions. This update aims to enhance customer engagement and improve return on investment. #RCS #Twilio #CustomerEngagement #Messaging #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 contact center technologies and trends to support your agents and customers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7245/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7245/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Contact center technologies are rapidly evolving. Staying updated on these trends is essential for supporting both agents and customers. 📈 The article highlights 12 key technologies that are shaping the future of contact centers. These advancements aim to enhance efficiency and improve user experiences. Explore the latest in contact center innovation to ensure your operations remain competitive and effective. #ContactCenter #TechTrends #CustomerSupport #Innovation #BusinessSolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Vibe Coding to Alter a Twilio Code Exchange Template</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7190/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7190/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Are you a non-developer wanting to customize Twilio Code Exchange templates? This article introduces &amp;ldquo;vibe coding,&amp;rdquo; a method to enhance templates using AI tools without manual coding. It guides you through using OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT to expand a Node.js application that tracks email events in SendGrid. Create your account on OpenAI to get started and explore how AI can assist in developing your ideas. #Twilio #OpenAI #VibeCoding #NoCode #TechForEveryone</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19&#43; tips to stop your emails from going to spam in 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-24-7246/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-24-7246/</guid>
      <description>Struggling with your emails landing in the spam folder? 📧 Here are key tips to improve your email deliverability: - Build your own email list and use double opt-in methods. - Regularly clean your email list and monitor your sender reputation. - Ensure compliance with privacy laws and provide an email preference center. Stay informed and keep your messages in the inbox! 📨 #EmailMarketing #SpamFilters #EmailTips #DigitalMarketing #InboxSuccess</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>List-Unsubscribe Header: What It Is &amp; How to Use It</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-7773/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-7773/</guid>
      <description>📧 A list-unsubscribe header is a helpful email feature that allows recipients to easily opt out of future communications without marking emails as spam. This option appears directly in the email client interface, streamlining the process for users. Major providers like Gmail and Outlook support this feature, making it a best practice for businesses. Implementing list-unsubscribe headers not only enhances user experience but also helps businesses maintain compliance and a healthy email list&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Email Authentication: How to Authenticate Email in 5 Steps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-7774/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-7774/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Email authentication is crucial for ensuring your messages are recognized as genuine by providers like Gmail and Yahoo. With new 2024 sender requirements, it&amp;rsquo;s no longer optional. Use SPF, DKIM, and DMARC to build trust and improve deliverability. Follow five simple steps to authenticate your email and keep your messages out of spam folders. #EmailAuthentication #SPF #TrustInEmail #EmailDeliverability #Cybersecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Prevent Race Conditions in Laravel with Atomic Locks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5136/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5136/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to prevent race conditions in Laravel with atomic locks! 🔒 This article outlines the importance of using Laravel’s locking mechanisms to ensure data integrity and manage concurrent processes effectively. Discover practical steps and examples to implement these techniques in your projects. Stay informed and enhance your development skills! 💻✨ #Laravel #WebDevelopment #CodingTips #RaceConditions #AtomicLocks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to boost business with affiliate email marketing programs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5137/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5137/</guid>
      <description>Boost your business with affiliate email marketing! 📧✨ Successful companies expand their reach by identifying target markets and building connections. One effective strategy is partnering with affiliate marketers who promote your products through their own networks. These marketers communicate with audiences that already trust them, increasing the likelihood of conversions. Compensation structures in affiliate programs vary, typically rewarding based on performance. Tracking links help&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulatory and Compliance Corner - August &amp; September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5138/</guid>
      <description>🌍 This month&amp;rsquo;s Regulatory and Compliance Corner highlights significant telecom policy changes worldwide. Key updates include new regulations aimed at enhancing data privacy and security for users. Additionally, several countries are revising rules to promote competition in the telecom sector. Stay informed about these important shifts in the industry! 📡✉️ #Telecom #Regulations #DataPrivacy #IndustryInsights #Compliance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A CDP is the Best Contextual Data Layer for Agentic Systems</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5140/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5140/</guid>
      <description>AI agents thrive on accurate, real-time context. A Customer Data Platform (CDP) like Twilio Segment plays a crucial role in delivering this data. It provides clean, consented information tailored to the agents&amp;rsquo; needs. This enables more informed, efficient, and secure decision-making, ultimately enhancing customer experiences. #AI #CustomerExperience #DataManagement #Twilio #CDP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices for OTP Input Forms in Android</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5139/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5139/</guid>
      <description>Creating effective OTP input forms in Android is crucial for user verification. This article by Twilio discusses best practices for design and implementation. It highlights troubleshooting tips to enhance user experience and security. Developers can benefit from these insights to improve their applications. Explore more to ensure your OTP forms are user-friendly and effective! 🔐📱 #AndroidDevelopment #OTPSecurity #UserExperience #Twilio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Insert a GIF into Emails in 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-7718/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-7718/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Want to enhance your email marketing? Consider adding GIFs! GIFs can capture attention and engage customers effectively. This article provides a concise tutorial on inserting GIFs into emails using platforms like Gmail and Outlook. 🖼️ Key steps include copying a GIF link from sites like Giphy, pasting it into your email, and ensuring the entire animation displays correctly. For detailed methods and insights on using GIFs in your campaigns, check out the full article! #EmailMarketing #GIFs&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Twilio Support for Meta’s WhatsApp Marketing Messages Lite API on Private Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5144/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5144/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for businesses! Twilio now supports Meta’s WhatsApp Marketing Messages Lite API, enhancing the delivery of high-volume marketing campaigns. 📈 The MM Lite API is designed to improve message deliverability and reduce errors, all managed through the Twilio platform. Key features include optimized delivery, TTL control, and ROI tracking. 🔗 With Twilio, businesses gain a reliable communication platform that simplifies the management of multiple channels while ensuring compliance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the builder: Kate Molony, Software Engineer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5141/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5141/</guid>
      <description>Meet Kate Molony, a Software Engineer at Twilio! 🚀 In our latest #BehindTheBuilder feature, Kate discusses her career journey, starting as an intern and progressing to a full-time role on the Operational Insights team. Her experience highlights the growth and opportunities available at Twilio. Learn more about her insights and contributions! 💡 #Twilio #SoftwareEngineering #CareerJourney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices for OTP Input Forms in iOS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5142/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5142/</guid>
      <description>🔑 Building effective OTP input forms in iOS is crucial for security. This article outlines best practices for developers, focusing on user experience and testing methods. It emphasizes the importance of clear design and error handling to enhance usability. Learn how to create secure and efficient OTP forms that meet industry standards. #iOSDevelopment #OTPSecurity #UserExperience #BestPractices #Twilio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Businesses Need to Know About iOS 26</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5143/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5143/</guid>
      <description>📱 Businesses should be aware of the recent changes in Apple iOS 26. These updates may significantly affect how companies utilize SMS, MMS, RCS messaging, and voice calls to communicate with customers. Understanding these implications is crucial for maintaining effective customer engagement strategies. Stay informed to adapt your communication approaches accordingly! #iOS26 #BusinessCommunication #CustomerEngagement #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Developer Evangelist Anni Chen</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-5145/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-5145/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Anni Chen, Twilio&amp;rsquo;s new Developer Evangelist! Anni brings a passion for AI, food, and productivity to her role. She shares insights from her journey into developer evangelism, aiming to connect with the developer community and enhance user experiences. Stay tuned for more updates and insights from Anni! #DeveloperEvangelism #Twilio #TechCommunity #AI #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to clean your email list: your step-by-step scrub guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-5146/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-5146/</guid>
      <description>Cleaning your email list is crucial for effective marketing. 🧹 Inactive subscribers and invalid addresses can hurt your engagement rates and sender reputation. Regular maintenance can help you maintain a high-performing email database. Key steps include removing bad addresses, identifying inactive subscribers, and segmenting your audience. 📊 Remember, it&amp;rsquo;s an ongoing process, not just a one-time task. #EmailMarketing #ListCleaning #DigitalMarketing #Engagement #MarketingTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to test Twilio Verify without getting rate limited</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4790/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4790/</guid>
      <description>Struggling with Twilio Verify testing? This article offers solutions to common issues like rate limits and expired verifications. It also shares best practices for effective verification testing. Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to set up a testing dashboard to streamline your process. #Twilio #API #Testing #DevTips #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>19 Best Email Fonts That Won&#39;t Let You Down in 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5149/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5149/</guid>
      <description>Discover the 19 best email fonts for 2025 that ensure your messages stand out! This guide highlights email-safe fonts that work seamlessly in platforms like Gmail and Outlook. It covers key topics such as the benefits of choosing the right font, top recommendations for email signatures, newsletters, and marketing campaigns. Optimize your email communications for better engagement! ✉️📈 #EmailMarketing #DesignTips #EmailFonts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deliver Secure and Reliable OTPs with Twilio Verify and PingOne</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5147/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5147/</guid>
      <description>PingOne now integrates directly with Twilio Verify, enhancing OTP delivery and reducing fraud risks. 🔒✨ This integration improves multi-factor authentication by utilizing Twilio&amp;rsquo;s global sender management and intelligent fallback systems. 📲 The guide provides a step-by-step configuration, requiring no extra tools. Learn more about securing user access effectively! #CyberSecurity #MultiFactorAuthentication #TwilioVerify #PingOne #FraudPrevention</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why RCS messaging is the future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5148/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5148/</guid>
      <description>RCS messaging is transforming customer engagement by providing interactive and visual experiences directly within messaging apps. 📱✨ Unlike SMS and MMS, RCS offers features like tap-to-buy buttons and branded profiles, enhancing communication between brands and consumers. Businesses adopting RCS are seeing improved response rates and increased customer loyalty. Explore how RCS can elevate your customer experience. #RCS #CustomerEngagement #DigitalMarketing #MessagingInnovation #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern messaging with RCS: Your webinar recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5150/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5150/</guid>
      <description>Discover the potential of Rich Communication Services (RCS) in engaging customers! 📱 In a recent webinar, Twilio experts highlighted how RCS transforms customer communication. With 89% of consumers preferring messaging, brands can now leverage RCS for a more interactive experience. RCS offers features like verified sender IDs, multimedia content, and secure messaging, enhancing trust and engagement. Learn how to utilize these advancements for your business! 🌟 #RCS #CustomerEngagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Send an MMS With Rust</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-5151/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-5151/</guid>
      <description>📱 Learn how to send an MMS using Rust with Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Programmable Messaging API! This tutorial builds on a previous SMS guide, introducing the Multimedia Messaging Service (MMS), which allows sending images, audio, and more. While Rust lacks a dedicated SDK from Twilio, you can utilize Crates like Reqwest and Serde to simplify the process. You&amp;rsquo;ll need Rust, a Twilio account, and a mobile device. Ready to get started? #Rust #MMS #Twilio #Programming #Coding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure CakePHP with One-Time Password Verification Using  WhatsApp</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-5152/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-5152/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your CakePHP security with One-Time Password (OTP) verification via WhatsApp! 📱🔒 This tutorial guides you through the process of integrating the Twilio WhatsApp Business API for user authentication. Learn to create login and verification pages that streamline user access while boosting security. Prerequisites include PHP 8.3+, a Twilio account, and basic CakePHP knowledge. #WebDevelopment #CakePHP #Twilio #UserSecurity #WhatsApp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 things to know about RCS business messaging</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-5153/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-5153/</guid>
      <description>RCS business messaging is transforming brand-consumer interactions. This advanced protocol enables the exchange of rich, interactive content like images, videos, and buttons. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering moving from SMS or MMS, understanding RCS is essential. Twilio hosted a webinar to discuss RCS&amp;rsquo;s significance and how to begin using it. Check it out for insights! 📱💬 #RCS #BusinessMessaging #Twilio #DigitalCommunication #Marketing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What does looping in email mean?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-5154/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-5154/</guid>
      <description>📧 Looping in email can be confusing, but it’s important to understand the difference. Email looping is the practice of adding someone to an existing conversation, enhancing communication and transparency. However, it’s wise to seek consent to avoid unwanted notifications. On the other hand, looping mail refers to automated emails continuously sent between systems, which can lead to spam and affect email marketing performance. Understanding these concepts can improve your email practices&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>21 Types of Emails Explained (With Tips &amp; Examples)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-02-5155/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-02-5155/</guid>
      <description>Discover the 21 types of emails you can use to enhance your marketing strategy. 📧 From welcome emails that create strong first impressions to promotional emails that boost sales, knowing when to use each type is key. Explore email categories like product, event, privacy, educational, and promotional with helpful tips and examples. Experiment to find what resonates with your audience! #EmailMarketing #DigitalCommunication #MarketingStrategy #EmailTypes #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMTP Relay Service: What Is SMTP Relay &amp; How Does It Work?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-02-5156/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-02-5156/</guid>
      <description>Discover the role of SMTP relay services in email delivery! 📧 These services ensure your marketing emails reach inboxes effectively. They route messages through dedicated servers, helping manage high-volume sending and maintain sender reputation. Learn more about how SMTP relay servers work and their importance for reliable email communication. #EmailMarketing #SMTPRelay #EmailDelivery #DigitalCommunication #MarketingTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>23 Rules for Writing Website Copy in 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-5157/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-5157/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Looking to improve your website copy? Check out these 23 essential rules for writing effective web content in 2025. From headlines to calls-to-action, the right words can engage and convert visitors. Mastering elements like body copy and subheaders is crucial for a better user experience. Learn how to make your website a powerful tool for your brand! 🖥️✍️ #WebsiteCopy #ContentWriting #DigitalMarketing #SEO #WebDesign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Rules in Spain: Don’t Let Your Calls Get Ghosted</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5158/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5158/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New telecom regulations in Spain are now in effect! Spanish mobile numbers cannot be used for unsolicited marketing or customer service calls. This means calls may get flagged or blocked, especially if using Transit-Caller-ID. 📞 To stay compliant, consider switching to Spanish landline or toll-free numbers. Review your number strategy to avoid disruptions in communication. Stay informed and keep your calls connected! #Telecom #Spain #Compliance #Twilio #Communication</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
