<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineering-at-Meta on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/engineering-at-meta/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engineering-at-Meta on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/engineering-at-meta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OCP Summit 2025: The Open Future of Networking Hardware for AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10879/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10879/</guid>
      <description>🌐 At the OCP Summit 2025, Meta outlined advancements in network fabrics tailored for AI training clusters. 📈 The company expanded its hardware portfolio, introducing new disaggregated network platforms to enhance collaboration within the Open Compute Project. 🔧 Meta emphasized the importance of open hardware in driving innovation and improving data center efficiency. Key milestones include the evolution of Disaggregated Scheduled Fabric and the launch of the Ethernet for Scale-Up Networking&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the React Foundation: The New Home for React &amp; React Native</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10511/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 18:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10511/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for the React community! Meta has announced the formation of the React Foundation, aimed at supporting React and React Native. This transition will formalize governance and ensure independent technical direction, with a board including representatives from major companies like Amazon and Microsoft. Meta is committing over $3 million and five years of support to help with this transition. The foundation will maintain infrastructure, organize events, and foster collaboration&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing OpenZL: An Open Source Format-Aware Compression Framework</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10459/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10459/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing OpenZL, a new open source compression framework designed for structured data. OpenZL offers lossless compression with performance comparable to specialized compressors while maintaining the simplicity of a single executable binary. You can start using OpenZL today! Check out the Quick Start guide and GitHub repository for more details. #OpenZL #DataCompression #OpenSource #TechInnovation #StructuredData</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Candle Subsea Cable, Updates to Our Asia-Pacific Connectivity Projects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10435/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 02:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10435/</guid>
      <description>🌊 Exciting news in connectivity! Meta has introduced Candle, a new submarine cable set to connect East and Southeast Asia. This cable will be the largest capacity system in the region, enhancing connectivity for over 580 million people by 2028. Additionally, updates on the Bifrost cable system have been shared, alongside progress on the Echo and Apricot cables. These initiatives aim to support the growing demand for robust internet infrastructure in the Asia-Pacific region. #Connectivity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating our Android apps with Baseline Profiles</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10330/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10330/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in Android app performance at Meta! We&amp;rsquo;ve leveraged Android’s Baseline Profiles to enhance app efficiency, addressing user needs that have become more complex over time. 📈 By using user data and fine-tuning our approach, we&amp;rsquo;ve improved performance metrics by up to 40%. This helps tackle slow startups and responsiveness issues, ensuring a smoother experience for billions of users. Learn more about our infrastructure and the challenges we faced! #AndroidDevelopment #Meta&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs Are the Key to Mutation Testing and Better Compliance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10301/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10301/</guid>
      <description>Meta is advancing software testing with its Automated Compliance Hardening (ACH) tool, powered by large language models (LLMs). This tool automates compliance adherence and enhances developer efficiency. By using LLMs, Meta simplifies risk assessments, reduces developer workload, and fosters continuous compliance, creating safer online environments. Meta also invites the community to engage in challenges like the JiTTest Challenge, exploring new opportunities in software testing. #Meta&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AssetGen: Generating 3D Worlds With AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10206/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10206/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting developments in AI and VR were highlighted at Meta Connect. Mark Zuckerberg shared a vision of creating 3D virtual worlds easily using AI prompts. The new Meta Horizon Studio aims to empower creators with this technology. On the Meta Tech Podcast, experts discussed AssetGen, a model designed to generate 3D assets from simple text, showcasing the future of immersive experiences. 🎧 Listen to the episode on your favorite podcast platform! #AI #VR #MetaConnect #3DWorlds #MetaTech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meta’s Infrastructure Evolution and the Advent of AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10207/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10207/</guid>
      <description>Meta has transformed over 21 years from a small social network to a global platform serving 3.4 billion users. 🌍 The company’s infrastructure has evolved significantly, addressing challenges through innovative solutions, especially with the rise of AI. This evolution requires advancements at all levels, from hardware to data centers. Meta remains committed to open-source principles, sharing developments with the engineering community. #Meta #AI #Infrastructure #OpenSource #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networking at the Heart of AI — @Scale: Networking 2025 Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10161/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10161/</guid>
      <description>🌐 AI is transforming networking, and this year&amp;rsquo;s @Scale:Networking event highlighted its critical role. Engineers from major tech companies gathered to discuss the infrastructure needed for AI advancements. 🔍 Key topics included significant investments in AI infrastructure, with companies planning extensive builds and renewable energy initiatives. 📈 Additionally, the evolution of AI models and workloads was a focus, showcasing rapid growth and increasing demands on network performance&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Video Streaming With the AV1 Video Codec in Mobile Devices</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9965/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 08:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9965/</guid>
      <description>📢 Today, Meta, Vodafone, and Google released a white paper on the benefits of the AV1 video codec for mobile streaming. The document advises core processor vendors to consider adopting AV1 hardware or, if not feasible, to implement software-based AV1 decoders. This is crucial as video content makes up 70-80% of mobile data traffic. 📱 AV1 can enhance video quality in low- and mid-tier devices, matching premium handsets while optimizing network capacity. Collaboration between content providers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read Meta’s 2025 Sustainability Report</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9619/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9619/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Meta has released its 2025 Sustainability Report, outlining its commitment to environmental responsibility. The report details strategies for reducing carbon emissions and promoting renewable energy use across its operations. Key initiatives and progress updates reflect Meta’s ongoing efforts to enhance sustainability and accountability. #Sustainability #Meta2025 #ClimateAction #RenewableEnergy #CorporateResponsibility 🌱</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Ranking Framework for Better Notification Quality on Instagram</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7650/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7650/</guid>
      <description>Meta is enhancing Instagram notifications using machine learning and diversity algorithms. A new framework aims to reduce uniformity, offering a varied mix of notifications while lowering overall volume. This approach boosts engagement rates by ensuring users discover diverse content and creators. The goal is to balance personalization with a richer notification experience, avoiding overexposure to the same authors. #InstagramUpdates #MachineLearning #UserExperience #Diversity #SocialMedia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Kotlin incremental compilation on Buck2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7256/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7256/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Kotlin developers! Meta has integrated the Kotlin incremental compiler into Buck2, enhancing speed and efficiency. This incremental approach reduces compilation time by focusing on changed files, a significant improvement as codebases grow. Some modules now build up to 3x faster! Learn more about the integration process and its impact on developer productivity. #Kotlin #Buck2 #IncrementalCompilation #Meta #DeveloperProductivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating AI agent solutions for warehouse data access and security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4966/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 22:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4966/</guid>
      <description>Meta is evolving its data warehouse to enhance productivity and security for both human users and AI agents. 🤖🔒 We are developing AI agents to streamline data access requests, helping users find the data they need while assisting data owners in maintaining security. Guardrails, such as auditing and feedback systems, are also being implemented to ensure safe operations. As the scale and complexity of data access grow, our focus is on minimizing security risks while improving efficiency. This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federation Platform and Privacy Waves: How Meta distributes compliance-related tasks at scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4855/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4855/</guid>
      <description>Meta is enhancing privacy compliance with its Federation Platform and Privacy Waves program. These tools manage compliance tasks effectively and ensure accountability across teams. 🌐 The Federation Platform breaks down compliance initiatives into manageable tasks, while Privacy Waves organizes these tasks into monthly batches for better planning. 📅 Together, they improve user data protection and streamline operations, managing over 100,000 tasks annually. This approach is expanding into&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diff Risk Score: AI-driven risk-aware software development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4160/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 17:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4160/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing the Diff Risk Score (DRS) from Meta! This AI-driven technology predicts the likelihood of code changes causing production incidents, enhancing software development processes. By analyzing code changes and metadata, DRS generates risk scores, allowing developers to identify potentially risky code. 🛠️ DRS has notably reduced code freezes during critical periods, boosting productivity while maintaining user experience. For instance, during a key event in 2024, over 10,000 code&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a human-computer interface for everyone</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 14:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-11/</guid>
      <description>Discover how Meta&amp;rsquo;s Reality Labs is advancing human-computer interaction with wrist-worn devices using surface electromyography (sEMG). 🤖 Their research focuses on creating a universal input device that adapts to different users. Generalization remains a key challenge, as existing models often cater to individual gestures. Listen to the latest episode of the Meta Tech Podcast to learn more about this innovative approach! 🎧✨ #HumanComputerInteraction #TechInnovation #MetaTech #sEMG #Podcast</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
