<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engineering@Microsoft on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/engineering@microsoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engineering@Microsoft on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:07:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/engineering@microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Diagnosing instability in production-scale agent reinforcement learning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-28-14984/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:07:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-28-14984/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Hugging Face has integrated the Post-Training Toolkit into TRL, enhancing diagnostics for production-scale reinforcement learning (RL) systems. This integration allows for better monitoring and control in long-running agent systems. It helps identify late-phase instability that can develop gradually, often going unnoticed until recovery options are limited. 📈 The article discusses a specific issue with tool-using agents trained using on-policy methods, revealing that traditional metrics can&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Interaction Changes Everything: Treating AI Agents as Collaborators, Not Automation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13389/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 01:46:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13389/</guid>
      <description>At Microsoft Ignite 2025, the focus was on transforming AI agents into collaborators rather than just automation tools. Amanda Silver and Karl Piteira discussed how this shift enhances engineering workflows, allowing developers to work alongside intelligent agents like GitHub Copilot. One case study highlighted how a complex migration project was completed in under 2 hours with 80-90% accuracy, compared to the usual 4-6 weeks. This success stemmed from treating AI as a partner, not just a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
