<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spotify-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/spotify-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spotify-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:00:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/spotify-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shuffle: Making Random Feel More Human</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12129/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12129/</guid>
      <description>🎶 Spotify has revamped its Shuffle feature to enhance user experience! For years, listeners felt Shuffle wasn&amp;rsquo;t truly random, often hearing the same tracks repeatedly. In response to feedback, Spotify introduced a new system called &amp;ldquo;Fewer Repeats,&amp;rdquo; which prioritizes freshness while maintaining randomness. This means your favorite songs won&amp;rsquo;t dominate the queue, allowing for a more varied listening experience. Premium users will now find this updated Shuffle as the default option. For those&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500&#43; PRs Later: Spotify’s Journey with Our Background Coding Agent (Part 1)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11962/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11962/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://engineering.atspotify.com/feed/&#34;&gt;Spotify Engineering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://engineering.atspotify.com/2025/11/spotifys-background-coding-agent-part-1/&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Winning: Spotify’s Experiments with Learning Framework</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9923/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 11:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9923/</guid>
      <description>Spotify has developed the Confidence platform to enhance product decision-making across numerous teams. The focus has shifted from simply increasing experiment velocity to improving quality and insights through the Experiments with Learning (EwL) metric. This approach emphasizes understanding failures, which helps guide better product decisions. With an aim to foster a culture of experimentation, Spotify has expanded its team involvement from 40 to around 300. This initiative includes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
