<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Spotify-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/spotify-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Spotify-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:41:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/spotify-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why We Use Separate Tech Stacks for Personalization and Experimentation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14308/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 14:41:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14308/</guid>
      <description>At Spotify, personalization enhances user experience by tailoring content to individual preferences. This is achieved through advanced models that analyze user characteristics and behaviors. 🎧 Experimentation complements personalization by testing and improving these systems. By using a separate tech stack for each, Spotify can optimize both areas effectively. Learn more about the rationale behind this separation and its benefits. #Personalization #Experimentation #SpotifyEngineering&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Background Coding Agents: Context Engineering (Part 2)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12989/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:20:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12989/</guid>
      <description>In Part 2 of our series on context engineering for background coding agents, we delve into effective migration prompts and necessary tools. Spotify has developed a coding agent to enhance our Fleet Management system, capable of editing code, running builds, and automating pull requests. However, guiding this agent effectively has proven challenging. We initially explored open-source options like Goose and Aider but faced difficulties in scaling them for large migrations. This led us to create&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shuffle: Making Random Feel More Human</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12129/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12129/</guid>
      <description>🎶 Spotify has revamped its Shuffle feature to enhance user experience! For years, listeners felt Shuffle wasn&amp;rsquo;t truly random, often hearing the same tracks repeatedly. In response to feedback, Spotify introduced a new system called &amp;ldquo;Fewer Repeats,&amp;rdquo; which prioritizes freshness while maintaining randomness. This means your favorite songs won&amp;rsquo;t dominate the queue, allowing for a more varied listening experience. Premium users will now find this updated Shuffle as the default option. For those&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1,500&#43; PRs Later: Spotify’s Journey with Our Background Coding Agent (Part 1)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11962/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11962/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://engineering.atspotify.com/feed/&#34;&gt;Spotify Engineering&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://engineering.atspotify.com/2025/11/spotifys-background-coding-agent-part-1/&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Winning: Spotify’s Experiments with Learning Framework</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9923/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 11:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9923/</guid>
      <description>Spotify has developed the Confidence platform to enhance product decision-making across numerous teams. The focus has shifted from simply increasing experiment velocity to improving quality and insights through the Experiments with Learning (EwL) metric. This approach emphasizes understanding failures, which helps guide better product decisions. With an aim to foster a culture of experimentation, Spotify has expanded its team involvement from 40 to around 300. This initiative includes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
