<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HashiCorp-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/hashicorp-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HashiCorp-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/hashicorp-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>15 questions to ask your cloud security team</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11220/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11220/</guid>
      <description>Navigating security in multi-cloud and hybrid environments presents unique challenges for organizations. 🌩️ To enhance compliance and risk management, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to ask the right questions. Key points include: 1️⃣ How are security vulnerabilities proactively addressed? 2️⃣ Are cloud environments built to meet security standards? 3️⃣ How consistent are security policies across providers? These questions can guide teams in strengthening their security posture and avoiding costly breaches. 🔒&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do cloud wrong: 7 red flags your strategy needs a reset</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11221/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11221/</guid>
      <description>Is your cloud strategy facing challenges? 🚩 Recognizing early warning signs can prevent major issues down the line. Key indicators include escalating bills, too many tools, and manual processes that consume time. According to the 2025 Cloud Complexity Report, 52% of organizations view hybrid cloud complexity as a major hurdle. Addressing these red flags early can help streamline operations. Stay proactive! 🛠️💡 #CloudStrategy #HybridCloud #InfrastructureManagement #CloudComplexity #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Day 2 infrastructure management with Terraform actions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11124/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11124/</guid>
      <description>🌐 In the evolving landscape of hybrid and multi-cloud environments, managing infrastructure is becoming increasingly complex. 🔍 An article discusses how Terraform actions can standardize Day 2 workflows, ensuring effective long-term infrastructure management. It highlights that most risks occur post-deployment, making ongoing maintenance crucial. ⚙️ Day 0 involves provisioning, Day 1 focuses on configuration, and Day 2+ is about management and optimization. Common challenges include&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solutions to secret sprawl: A 4-part framework</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11028/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Secret sprawl can increase vulnerability to data breaches for organizations. A new article outlines a 4-part framework to enhance secrets management. 🔑 Key strategies include: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Centralized secrets management&lt;/strong&gt; to store and protect all secrets. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Cross-platform synchronization&lt;/strong&gt; for unified management. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Secret scanning&lt;/strong&gt; to detect leaks across infrastructure. 4. &lt;strong&gt;Access controls and encryption&lt;/strong&gt; to safeguard secrets. Adopting these practices can help organizations manage their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to write and rightsize Terraform modules</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11002/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11002/</guid>
      <description>🔧 Designing effective Terraform modules involves careful consideration of key areas: scope, code strategy, security, and testing. Rene Schach, a Senior Cloud Consultant, emphasizes the importance of understanding your module&amp;rsquo;s purpose and audience. Engaging with users helps identify their needs and streamline workflows. Modules should maintain clear functional separation and avoid tight coupling to ensure flexibility and maintainability. Group related resources and separate by volatility for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fannie Mae’s process for developing policy as code with Terraform Enterprise and Sentinel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10959/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10959/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Fannie Mae is leading the way in policy as code with Terraform Enterprise and Sentinel, streamlining compliance in regulated environments. By automating cloud infrastructure provisioning, they mitigate security risks while adhering to IT regulations. Their approach includes over 450 Sentinel policies that act as guardrails for AWS services. This strategy allows for version control, automated testing, and early compliance checks, shifting responsibility to developers for proactive risk&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20% of Singapore in 2 years: Trust Bank’s 4 keys to coding with speed and security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10906/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10906/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Trust Bank has made significant strides in Singapore&amp;rsquo;s fintech landscape, capturing 20% of the population in just two years. Their success is rooted in a balance of speed and security, as emphasized by CIO Rajay Rai. Key strategies include a solid infrastructure philosophy, where security is integrated from the start, and opting to buy rather than build for non-essential tools. With a focus on efficiency, customers can now open accounts in just minutes! #Fintech #Innovation #TrustBank&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prevent secret exposure across IT: 4 tools and techniques</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10873/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10873/</guid>
      <description>Preventing the exposure of sensitive information is crucial for cybersecurity. 🔒 The average data breach cost is projected to reach $4.4M by 2025. A significant number of attacks involve compromised credentials, highlighting the need for proactive measures. HashiCorp offers tools that integrate security checks into development workflows. One notable method is credential injection, which automates the management of sensitive credentials, reducing the risk of exposure. Explore how these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riverty automates hybrid cloud to deliver faster, safer financial infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10603/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10603/</guid>
      <description>Riverty has transformed its infrastructure by implementing a fully automated hybrid cloud platform. This shift enhances developer efficiency and significantly reduces security risks. By using HashiCorp Cloud Platform (HCP) tools like Terraform and Vault, Riverty achieved a 90% reduction in deployment time. The new system allows for self-service infrastructure requests, cutting down approval time by 80%. 🌐✨ This modernization also standardizes provisioning across multiple cloud environments,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform introduces organizational control for user token generation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10604/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10604/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Terraform users! HashiCorp has introduced organizational control for user API tokens in HCP Terraform, enhancing access management. This feature allows organization owners to enable or disable user tokens, improving security and collaboration. Users can now manage three types of API tokens: user, team, and organization tokens. The new settings help enforce the least privilege principle and simplify permissions management. For more details, check out Terraform’s API Tokens&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do cloud right: What successful enterprises are getting right about cloud strategy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10558/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10558/</guid>
      <description>Transformative organizations are leveraging AI-driven automation to enhance cloud success, with 56% planning to infuse AI into their operations. In contrast, only 46% of tactical firms are adopting similar strategies, risking a widening gap in cloud management. 🌐🤖 A recent report highlights that 97% of organizations face cloud infrastructure challenges, with hybrid cloud complexity being the top concern for 52%. Tactical companies rely on manual processes, which hampers efficiency and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From key sprawl to scalable control: Rethinking SSH access</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10514/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10514/</guid>
      <description>Access sprawl and security issues are growing concerns with static SSH keys. 🚨 These keys, widely used for secure connections, become unmanageable as organizations scale, leading to risks like shared access and lack of audit trails. Transitioning to SSH certificates can enhance security and manageability, providing better auditability and automatic revocation. This move addresses the challenges of static keys, especially in dynamic environments. 🔑 #CyberSecurity #SSH #AccessManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud migration strategy for insurance: Lessons from an industry leader</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10466/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10466/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloud migration is transforming the insurance industry! A leading insurer shares insights on overcoming challenges to drive ROI from cloud strategies. 📊 Despite migrating over 50% of its applications to the cloud, the company faces pressure to modernize legacy systems due to rising insurtech competition and changing customer expectations. 🔑 To foster innovation, they&amp;rsquo;re adopting a phased approach, exploring new models like embedded travel insurance and IoT solutions. Key strategies include&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow Catalog for Terraform adds approval workflow integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10385/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10385/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Terraform users! The latest update to the ServiceNow Service Catalog for Terraform now features a native approval workflow. This integration adds a vital layer of governance to self-service infrastructure provisioning, ensuring all requests are reviewed before any resources are created. 🛠️ With version 2.9, organizations can now streamline their approval processes, reducing the complexity of custom solutions. Users can easily configure items to require approval, providing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why traditional secret scanning tools fail to address today&#39;s secret management crisis</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10400/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10400/</guid>
      <description>Traditional secret scanning tools face significant challenges in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced development landscape. 🚀 Recent research shows over 18,000 exposed API secrets last year, with many categorized as highly critical. Despite using secret scanning, organizations struggle with credential leaks and sensitive data exposure. 🔑 The shift to microservice architectures and cloud deployments has increased the number of secrets to manage, outpacing older scanning methods. These tools often produce high&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HCP Terraform and Waypoint in Europe now generally available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10268/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10268/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for European customers! HCP Terraform and HCP Waypoint are now available locally, enhancing geographic service locality and supporting GDPR compliance. 🌍 With these services running in European data centers, customers can expect reduced latency and secure data storage. However, some data may still be transferred outside Europe for operational needs, with strict access controls in place. 🔒 Explore the benefits of automated workflows and secure infrastructure management with HCP&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 years of HashiConf: A bold leap into AI-powered infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10158/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10158/</guid>
      <description>🚀 HashiConf 2025 marked a decade of innovation in cloud automation, emphasizing the future of infrastructure as automated and secure. This year, HashiCorp, now part of IBM, highlighted The Infrastructure Cloud, designed for comprehensive management of infrastructure and security. Attendees shared valuable insights, including customer success stories and strategies for implementing AI-ready automation across operations. Catch up on key sessions and announcements on our YouTube channel! 📹&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building intelligent infrastructure automation with HashiCorp</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10157/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10157/</guid>
      <description>🌐 HashiConf 2025 introduces a new era for HashiCorp as an IBM Company, focusing on AI-driven infrastructure and security. The goal is to address common pain points in infrastructure management, such as fragmented visibility and overwhelming security risks. A unified lifecycle management platform aims to streamline operations across hybrid cloud environments. Key challenges include managing skills gaps and complex regulations. The push for intelligent operations emphasizes the need for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scale infrastructure with new Terraform and Packer features at HashiConf 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10128/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10128/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates at HashiConf 2025! HashiCorp introduced new features for Terraform and Packer aimed at simplifying hybrid cloud infrastructure management. These tools address challenges like fragmented workflows and compliance issues, enhancing developer productivity and cost control. Key announcements include: - &lt;strong&gt;Terraform Stacks&lt;/strong&gt;: Now available for easier infrastructure management. - &lt;strong&gt;Terraform search&lt;/strong&gt;: Improve resource discovery and import efficiency. - **Integration with Azure&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthen security with Vault, Boundary, and Radar features at HashiConf 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10129/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10129/</guid>
      <description>🚀 HashiCorp unveiled new features at HashiConf 2025 to enhance security in development workflows. Key updates include: - &lt;strong&gt;Vault Enterprise 1.21&lt;/strong&gt;: Introducing secrets to Kubernetes pods without persistent storage and improved identity management. - &lt;strong&gt;HCP Vault Radar&lt;/strong&gt;: New tools for real-time secrets detection and monitoring in VSCode and Jira. - &lt;strong&gt;HCP Boundary&lt;/strong&gt;: Passwordless access to Windows hosts to streamline developer experience. These enhancements aim to strengthen security across&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform &amp; Ansible: Unifying infrastructure provisioning and configuration management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10130/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10130/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Terraform and Ansible are transforming how we manage infrastructure in hybrid and multi-cloud environments. As the demand for cloud applications rises, organizations face increasing complexity in infrastructure management. Terraform excels in provisioning resources, while Ansible specializes in configuration management. Together, they streamline Day 2 operations, ensuring infrastructure remains healthy over time. Introducing Terraform actions aims to unify these workflows, reducing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform Stacks, explained</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10131/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10131/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Terraform Stacks streamline resource management and provisioning at scale. They tackle challenges like managing dependencies and reducing run time by allowing users to organize Terraform modules into manageable pieces. Key benefits include simplified management and improved productivity, enabling rapid creation of consistent infrastructure setups. Common use cases involve deploying applications as single units and managing Kubernetes workloads efficiently. #Terraform #InfrastructureAsCode&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public beta of RDP credential injection now available in Boundary 0.20</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10132/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10132/</guid>
      <description>🚀 HashiCorp Boundary 0.20 has launched a public beta for RDP credential injection! This update enables passwordless and secure access to Windows environments, addressing the security risks associated with traditional RDP workflows. With automatic credential injection, users no longer have to handle sensitive information manually. This feature significantly reduces the chances of credential theft while ensuring a smooth user experience. #HashiCorp #Boundary #RDP #Cybersecurity #PasswordlessAccess</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why secrets management is incomplete without secret scanning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7745/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7745/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Secrets management is vital for safeguarding API keys, passwords, and certificates. However, it often only covers known secrets, leaving gaps in security. 💻 Secrets can be scattered across code, pipelines, and tools, creating hidden risks. Recent research shows that leaked secrets can take 94 days to remediate, increasing vulnerability to attacks. 🔐 Secret scanning complements management by providing visibility and real-time detection of hidden secrets. This proactive approach integrates&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 security wins from Booking.com&#39;s hybrid cloud migration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7701/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7701/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Booking.com has made significant strides in their hybrid cloud migration by enhancing security with HashiCorp Vault. They developed a unified secrets management system, allowing consistent access across various platforms, including AWS and GCP. This central security bridge mitigates risks of misconfigurations. By migrating to JWT authentication, they simplified their authentication processes, reducing complexity and improving oversight. Additionally, Vault&amp;rsquo;s secrets sync will provide&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 tips for credential management across multi-cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7645/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7645/</guid>
      <description>Managing credentials in multi-cloud environments can be complex. Lino Telera from InfoCert shares five essential tips to streamline secret management: 1️⃣ Use dynamic secrets instead of static API keys to minimize risk. 2️⃣ Automate runtime secret management to eliminate manual errors. 3️⃣ Implement workspace sandboxing to enforce zero trust principles. These practices help improve security and efficiency in development. #CredentialManagement #CloudSecurity #DevOps #InfoSec #HashiCorp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Policy as code, explained</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7484/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7484/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Policy as code is transforming IT operations by automating compliance checks in infrastructure deployments. This approach allows for quick verification of stakeholder requirements, moving away from slow, error-prone manual processes. With customizable policy languages, organizations can effectively manage security, compliance, and architecture. Learn more about how companies like Fannie Mae and Wayfair are implementing this strategy. #PolicyAsCode #ITOperations #Infrastructure #Automation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform provider for Google Cloud 7.0 is now GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7288/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7288/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Terraform users! The Terraform provider for Google Cloud has reached general availability with version 7.0. This release introduces new ephemeral resources and write-only attributes to enhance security when managing sensitive data. The community&amp;rsquo;s feedback has played a crucial role in this improvement. With over 1.4 billion downloads, the provider now supports 800+ resources and 300+ data sources. #Terraform #GoogleCloud #CloudSecurity #DevOps #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret sprawl is costing you more than you think</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7172/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7172/</guid>
      <description>🛡️ Secret sprawl is significantly impacting organizations, costing them millions annually through lost productivity and increased security overhead. Developers often waste time on preventable secret management tasks, leading to an estimated $936,000 annual loss for a typical 50-person team. This includes hunting down exposed credentials and managing compromised keys. Moreover, security teams face a burden from false positives, costing around $520,000 each year due to unnecessary&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why default secret detection rules don&#39;t work (and how to fix it)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6312/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6312/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Many organizations face challenges with default secret detection rules. Studies indicate that up to 80% of security alerts are false positives, leading to overlooked real threats. 📊 Generic detection tools often miss unique credentials like proprietary API keys. This can result in significant security incidents if not addressed. 💡 HCP Vault Radar offers a solution with customizable detection patterns and severity-based workflows. This approach helps teams focus on genuine threats while&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to enable developer self-service at scale with Terraform and Waypoint</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5111/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5111/</guid>
      <description>Unlock developer self-service at scale with HCP Waypoint! 🚀 Learn how to streamline Terraform workflows and empower your teams. With Waypoint, platform teams can create reusable modules, simplifying complex processes for developers. This approach reduces bottlenecks and enhances productivity. Waypoint integrates seamlessly with existing tools, offering a user-friendly interface that maintains security and compliance. Explore how to build effective workflows and facilitate efficient&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 lessons from Moneybox’s Terraform journey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5112/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5112/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Moneybox, a UK fintech, shares insights from their transition to HCP Terraform. They faced challenges as their infrastructure grew, shifting from Terraform Community Edition to streamline workflows. Key lessons include: 1️⃣ Start simple, but scale when needed. 2️⃣ Design infrastructure for growth. 3️⃣ Build self-service modules for teams. 4️⃣ Integrate governance into workflows. These changes improved efficiency and team collaboration. 🌐💼 #Fintech #Infrastructure #Terraform #CloudComputing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform now supports assigning agent pools at the project level</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5113/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5113/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for HCP Terraform and Terraform Enterprise users! You can now assign default agent pools at the project level. This update simplifies the management of self-hosted agents, enhancing security and scalability. With this feature, project owners can easily set a default agent pool for future workspaces, promoting consistency across projects. Existing workspaces maintain their current settings, ensuring a smooth transition. Get started today and streamline your infrastructure&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving secret zero with Vault and OpenShift Virtualization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5114/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5114/</guid>
      <description>Discover how Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization and HashiCorp Vault can address the secret zero problem in virtualized environments. Organizations face challenges in establishing machine identity as they adopt identity-based security. Traditional virtualization solutions often lack inherent machine identity, leading to reliance on initial credentials for secure communication with Vault. Red Hat OpenShift Virtualization offers a solution by enabling virtual machines to leverage Kubernetes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software provenance: Why visibility into your software supply chain matters</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4954/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4954/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Understanding software provenance is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s complex software supply chain. This concept emphasizes tracking the creation, modification, and ownership of software artifacts throughout their lifecycle. As cyber threats rise, maintaining visibility is essential for security and compliance. Challenges include limited visibility, pipeline complexity, and compliance risks. Organizations must prioritize comprehensive documentation to address these issues. Stay informed and secure! 🔒🛡️&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform embraces Arm: More choice, greater flexibility</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4955/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4955/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Terraform has expanded support for Arm architecture, giving customers more options for their IT investments. With the rise of Arm&amp;rsquo;s popularity for its cost savings and performance benefits, Terraform now allows running Terraform Enterprise and HCP Terraform agents on Arm-based platforms like AWS Graviton. This change enables customers to optimize their setups for both performance and cost. One user shared that they moved to 100% Graviton CPUs, enhancing efficiency in their operations. Learn&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 key questions about designing a secure cloud environment</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4708/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4708/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Designing a secure cloud environment is crucial for organizations to avoid risks and enhance innovation. Here are 10 key questions leaders should ask their teams: 1. Do we have full visibility into our cloud infrastructure? 2. Are we embedding security throughout the development lifecycle? 3. Can we enforce security policies at scale? These discussions are essential for reducing risk and maintaining compliance. 🌐 For more insights on cloud security, check the full article. #CloudSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing Ansible Automation Platform (AAP) credentials at scale with Vault</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4761/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4761/</guid>
      <description>🔑 Managing SSH credentials at scale just got easier! This article explores how HashiCorp Vault and Red Hat Ansible Automation Platform (AAP) work together to automate SSH certificate retrieval. By issuing short-lived credentials, organizations can enhance security and streamline operations. Static SSH keys pose risks, making secure and scalable management a challenge. Vault&amp;rsquo;s integration allows AAP to request dynamic SSH certificates on demand, simplifying access to remote hosts. Learn more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the transition to IBM means for HashiCorp customers: Greater value, same commitment</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4052/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4052/</guid>
      <description>🚀 HashiCorp is transitioning to IBM starting September 1, 2025. This move aims to enhance customer value while maintaining the trust you&amp;rsquo;ve built with HashiCorp. 🔧 Key updates include changes to product naming conventions, aligning with IBM’s portfolio, but no alterations to features. Customers using legacy products will benefit from upgrades at current pricing. 💼 Billing operations will also shift to IBM, with new customer numbers issued. PAYG customers will see no changes. For more details,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doing hybrid cloud right: Taking the complexity out of infrastructure management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-1995/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-1995/</guid>
      <description>Navigating hybrid cloud management can be challenging. As AI adoption increases, organizations must modernize their cloud infrastructure for effective governance and management. 🌐 Gartner predicts that by 2027, 90% of organizations will embrace hybrid cloud models, yet many face complexities due to fragmented tools and inconsistent processes. 🚧 To improve efficiency, organizations should empower platform teams to standardize workflows and enhance collaboration between infrastructure and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HCP Terraform introduces Hold Your Own Key (HYOK)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-1996/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-1996/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for HCP Terraform customers! The new Hold Your Own Key (HYOK) feature is now available, providing enhanced control over sensitive data in Terraform artifacts. HYOK allows organizations to manage their encryption keys, ensuring that secrets in state and plan files are securely handled. This is crucial for those migrating to the cloud and needing compliance with strict security standards. 🔒 With HYOK, customers can encrypt their Terraform artifacts before uploading them,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
