<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AMD-Developer-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/amd-developer-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AMD-Developer-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/amd-developer-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ONNX and DirectML execution provider guide - part 1</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11490/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11490/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of AMD hardware for neural network inference with the ONNX Runtime and DirectML execution provider. 🚀 This guide discusses optimizing performance by minimizing data transfer between CPU and GPU. It highlights the importance of establishing a native inference pipeline using DirectX 12 to enhance efficiency. Setting up the ONNX Runtime with DirectX 12 involves creating a shared context for pre- and post-processing, allowing smoother operations. #MachineLearning #ONNX #DirectML&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONNX and DirectML execution provider guide - part 2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11491/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11491/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into the latest guide on optimizing neural network inference on AMD hardware using ONNX Runtime with DirectML! This second part focuses on integrating DirectML into DirectX 11 applications. It addresses resource sharing challenges between DirectX 11 and 12, emphasizing the need for efficient data pipelines. Key points include: - Importance of sharing textures without mipmaps. - Conditions for successful resource sharing with DirectX APIs. Explore the potential of your applications! 💻🔧&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Topaz Labs brings generative AI video enhancement to AMD Radeon GPUs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11228/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11228/</guid>
      <description>Topaz Labs and AMD have teamed up to enhance video processing using generative AI on AMD Radeon GPUs. This collaboration enables real-time performance and improved workflows for users. The new diffusion-based video enhancement feature runs on AMD Ryzen processors and RDNA architecture, maximizing processing efficiency. The innovative Project Starlight transforms low-res video to HD, achieving seamless motion across frames. This technology is optimized for AMD devices, offering up to 3.3x&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sim-to-real in AMD Schola</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10361/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10361/</guid>
      <description>Discover the process of sim-to-real in the latest guide using AMD Schola! This article explains how to replicate the SunFounder PiCar-X device in Unreal® Engine and train it with reinforcement learning. The goal is to teach the agent to follow a line on the floor using simulated color sensors. The training leverages the Stable Baselines3 library with the PPO algorithm, achieving strong results after 2 million steps. #ReinforcementLearning #SimToReal #UnrealEngine #Robotics #AMDSchola 🚗💻🎮</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sim-to-real in AMD Schola</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10361/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10361/</guid>
      <description>Discover the process of sim-to-real in the latest guide using AMD Schola! This article explains how to replicate the SunFounder PiCar-X device in Unreal® Engine and train it with reinforcement learning. The goal is to teach the agent to follow a line on the floor using simulated color sensors. The training leverages the Stable Baselines3 library with the PPO algorithm, achieving strong results after 2 million steps. #ReinforcementLearning #SimToReal #UnrealEngine #Robotics #AMDSchola 🚗💻🎮</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A beginner&#39;s guide to deploying LLMs with AMD on Windows using PyTorch</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10033/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10033/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Interested in deploying AI models on your Windows PC? Check out this beginner&amp;rsquo;s guide on using PyTorch with AMD graphics hardware. No need for dedicated AI infrastructure; just a modern AMD GPU or APU will do! The public preview of PyTorch for Windows supports several AMD models, enabling efficient AI workload execution. Perfect for developers, this guide walks you through setup, configuration, and execution of Large Language Models (LLMs). 🖥️✨ #AI #PyTorch #AMD #MachineLearning #TechGuide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Animating geometry with AMD DGF</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9929/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9929/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The AMD DGF SDK has been updated, introducing new features, including an animation-aware encoding pipeline. The Dense Geometry Format (DGF) allows for a cache-friendly representation of compressed triangles. This update offers improvements and bug fixes, making it easier to create animations in ray tracing applications. For a complete list of changes, refer to the release notes. #AMD #DGF #Animation #GraphicsProgramming #RayTracing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD FSR 4 now available in over 85 games</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9437/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9437/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Exciting news for gamers! AMD has launched FidelityFX™ Super Resolution 4 (FSR 4), now available in over 85 games. This advanced neural rendering technology enhances graphics quality using machine learning, resulting in clearer visuals without compromising performance. To experience FSR 4, simply update your AMD Software: Adrenalin Edition driver and enable it in supported games. Explore enhanced gaming today! 🌟 #AMD #FSR4 #GamingTech #Graphics #GameOn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD FidelityFX SDK 2.0 launches our neural rendering technologies for developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5018/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AMD has launched the FidelityFX SDK 2.0, introducing new machine learning-based rendering technologies for developers. This update simplifies integration of FidelityFX features, starting with AMD FSR 4 upscaling. It allows for automatic upgrades in supported games without needing separate updates. Developers will need to use specific DLLs for the new technologies, ensuring compatibility with the latest AMD hardware. #AMDFidelityFX #GamingTech #GameDevelopment #FSR4 #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD FidelityFX Super Resolution 4 now available on GPUOpen</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5022/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for gamers! AMD has launched FidelityFX Super Resolution 4 (FSR 4), now available on GPUOpen. This new machine learning-based upscaler significantly enhances image quality compared to FSR 3.1. FSR 4 utilizes AMD Instinct GPUs and RDNA 4 architecture for optimal performance. It improves temporal stability, detail preservation, and reduces ghosting on moving objects. Upgrade your gaming experience today! 🎮✨ #AMD #FSR4 #GamingTechnology #GameDev #Graphics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD FidelityFX Super Resolution 4 Unreal Engine plugin guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5027/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5027/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for game developers! The AMD FidelityFX Super Resolution 4 (FSR 4) plugin is now available for Unreal Engine 5.1 to 5.6. This plugin enhances framerates with a machine learning upscaler and frame generation. 🎮 FSR 4 combines advanced upscaling algorithms with AMD RDNA 4 architecture for improved performance. It also includes the FSR4MovieRenderPipeline for efficient rendering. For optimal results, developers should review recommendations and known issues specific to their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get ready for FSR Redstone with AMD FSR 3.1.4 and our new UE 5.6 plugin</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4713/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4713/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for game developers! AMD has released FidelityFX™ Super Resolution 3.1.4, enhancing framerates with improved upscaling and frame generation. This version also features a signed DLL for easy upgrades to future FSR technologies, including FSR Redstone. The updated Unreal Engine 5.6 plugin simplifies integration, allowing developers to prepare for upcoming ML-powered features like Neural Radiance Caching and ML Frame Generation. Get ready to elevate your game’s performance! 🎮✨&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD releases Vulkan support for Dense Geometry Format</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4091/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4091/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AMD has announced a provisional Vulkan® extension for its Dense Geometry Format (DGF), a block-based geometry compression technology. This extension, VK_AMDX_dense_geometry_format, allows DGF data to be directly used in building acceleration structures, enhancing performance and reducing memory costs. With native DGF support, developers can expect improved build times and lower memory usage for BLAS. #AMD #Vulkan #GameDev #Graphics #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD TressFX 5.0 for Unreal Engine 5 is now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-200/</guid>
      <description>🌟 AMD has launched TressFX 5.0 for Unreal Engine 5.4, enhancing realistic hair and fur simulation. Key updates include support for Lumen ray tracing, deep shadow approximation, and continuous LOD. This version is designed for seamless integration into your Unreal projects. To install, ensure you are a registered Unreal developer and follow the simple integration steps. #AMD #UnrealEngine #TressFX #GameDev #Simulation</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
