<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Salesforce-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/salesforce-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Salesforce-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:04:07 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/salesforce-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Code Reviews: Adapting to a Surge in AI-Generated Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-29-15016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 16:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-29-15016/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The article &amp;ldquo;Scaling Code Reviews: Adapting to a Surge in AI-Generated Code&amp;rdquo; highlights how Salesforce Engineering is addressing challenges in code review processes due to AI tools. As AI-assisted coding increases code volume by 30%, traditional review methods struggle to keep up. Large pull requests often lead to superficial reviews, risking code quality and trust. Salesforce responds by re-architecting the review system with Prizm, aiming to preserve developer intent and maintain&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Salesforce Edge: Automating Global Rollback for 1.5 Trillion Requests in 10 Minutes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-27-14968/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 14:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-27-14968/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the latest article, Salesforce highlights the work of Sanjeev Chhabria and his team in automating global rollback processes. 🌐 Their efforts have cut rollback time from hours to just 10 minutes, allowing Salesforce Edge to manage 1.5 trillion requests monthly with improved reliability. 🔧 Key innovations include re-architecting Kubernetes deployments and automating traffic cutover to maintain high availability. #Salesforce #Engineering #Innovation #Automation #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Agentforce, Data, and Apps Turned the Salesforce Stack into Agentforce 360</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14781/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:37:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14781/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In a recent Engineering Energizers Q&amp;amp;A, Muralidhar Krishnaprasad (MK), President and CTO of C360 Platform, shared insights on unifying Salesforce’s core platform layers into Agentforce 360. 🛠️ MK’s team focuses on integrating data, agents, and applications to create a cohesive architecture. This transformation aims to enhance real-time, AI-driven experiences for enterprise applications. 🌐 The unified data layer is key, harmonizing signals and ensuring consistent context across applications&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Agentforce Runs Secure AI Agents at 11 Million Calls Per Day</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14748/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14748/</guid>
      <description>Meet Sahil Sobti, Lead Software Engineer at Salesforce, who oversees the Developer Access team for Agentforce. 💻 His team manages over 11 million daily agent calls, ensuring secure and reliable interactions. They focus on implementing a robust access layer that protects sensitive data while enabling growth and innovation. 🔒 Sahil emphasizes the importance of coordinating multiple teams to maintain security and functionality as Agentforce evolves. 🚀 #Salesforce #AI #Cybersecurity #Engineering&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Agentforce Runs Secure AI Agents at 11 Million Calls Per Day</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-21-14748/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:52:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-21-14748/</guid>
      <description>Meet Sahil Sobti, Lead Software Engineer at Salesforce, who oversees the Developer Access team for Agentforce. 💻 His team manages over 11 million daily agent calls, ensuring secure and reliable interactions. They focus on implementing a robust access layer that protects sensitive data while enabling growth and innovation. 🔒 Sahil emphasizes the importance of coordinating multiple teams to maintain security and functionality as Agentforce evolves. 🚀 #Salesforce #AI #Cybersecurity #Engineering&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a Mock LLM Service Cut $500K in AI Benchmarking Costs, Boosted Developer Productivity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14588/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 22:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14588/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A recent article highlights how Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s internal LLM mock service has transformed AI benchmarking. By simulating LLM behavior, the team saved over $500K annually on costs while improving developer productivity. This mock service allows for performance validation without relying on live LLM providers, reducing variability and external dependencies. The approach enhances scalability and reliability, enabling engineers to focus on system improvements. #Salesforce #AI #Benchmarking&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Agentforce Enabled Conversational Recommendations with AI-Driven Intent on Data 360</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14547/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 23:20:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14547/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in AI-driven personalization! Bhumika Sethi, a senior software engineer at Salesforce, discusses how the Data 360 team enhances Agentforce. They focus on unifying customer profiles and engagement signals to deliver real-time, intent-based recommendations. The team addresses the challenge of understanding user intent in conversations, moving beyond traditional web-based personalization methods. This approach ensures agents provide relevant responses based on user&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migration at Scale: Moving Marketing Cloud Caching from Memcached to Redis at 1.5M RPS Without Downtime</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14279/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 06:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14279/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting engineering developments at Salesforce! In the latest Engineering Energizers Q&amp;amp;A, the Marketing Cloud Caching team&amp;rsquo;s journey is highlighted as they successfully migrated from Memcached to Redis without any downtime. This transition handled 1.5 million cache events per second across 50+ applications. Key focus areas included maintaining performance and security, while ensuring seamless user experiences. The shift to Redis Cluster addressed previous limitations and improved system&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migration at Scale: Moving Marketing Cloud Caching from Memcached to Redis at 1.5M RPS Without Downtime</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14279/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14279/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting engineering developments at Salesforce! In the latest Engineering Energizers Q&amp;amp;A, the Marketing Cloud Caching team&amp;rsquo;s journey is highlighted as they successfully migrated from Memcached to Redis without any downtime. This transition handled 1.5 million cache events per second across 50+ applications. Key focus areas included maintaining performance and security, while ensuring seamless user experiences. The shift to Redis Cluster addressed previous limitations and improved system&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Sales Agents: Engineering Next-Gen AI for the Enterprise Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14307/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:21:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14307/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in AI for sales are on the horizon! In a recent Q&amp;amp;A, Shweta Joshi, Software Engineering Architect at Salesforce, discusses the evolution of the Engagement Agent. This generative-AI system automates personalized sales outreach, now scaling to support over 1 million actions monthly. The team transitioned from a single-agent model to a multi-agent architecture, enhancing reliability and efficiency. Key innovations include a smart queuing system and fairness algorithms to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Agentforce Enabled Incident Response Automation to Cut Common Resolution Time by 70 – 80%</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-29-14178/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 22:24:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-29-14178/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in incident response at Salesforce! Deborah Donoghue, VP of Centralized Incident Response, shares how her team cut resolution time for major incidents by 70-80% through automation and AI. The team tackled human-driven bottlenecks and improved decision-making with Agentforce, transforming the incident response process into a more efficient, predictive system. Their goal is to enhance detection, understanding, and mitigation of issues, ultimately ensuring a smoother&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shattering AWS’s 250K-IP Ceiling: How Data 360 Reached 1 Million IPs with Zero-Downtime Migration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14119/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 23:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14119/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In a recent Engineering Energizers Q&amp;amp;A, Shirel Vaiman from Salesforce discussed how Data 360 achieved a remarkable milestone of 1 million IPs without downtime. The team tackled AWS&amp;rsquo;s 250,000-IP limit by employing prefix delegation and custom observability tools. Their focus was on expanding network capacity while ensuring reliability and security for hyperscale data workloads. Key challenges included AWS’s strict limits, increased workload demands, and Hyperforce&amp;rsquo;s architectural&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI-Enabled Tooling Boosted Code Output 30% — While Keeping Quality and Deployment Safety Intact</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13912/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13912/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s Chief Availability Officer, Darryn Dieken, shares insights on boosting engineering productivity. His team has unified tools across diverse runtimes, enhancing code output by 30% while maintaining quality and safety. 🔍 They support 200,000 changes weekly across 25 Hyperforce regions, focusing on developer efficiency and operational excellence through AIOps and automated workflows. 💡 By adopting a portfolio approach to AI tools, engineers can choose what fits their needs while&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Agentforce Achieved 3–5x Faster Response Times While Solving Enterprise-Scale Architectural Complexity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13292/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 04:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13292/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting progress in AI! Krista Hardebeck and her team at Salesforce have successfully implemented the Agentforce service for a major retailer, achieving response times 3–5x faster. They optimized complex architectures while integrating brand-specific conversational AI. Key improvements included reducing reasoning latency by 20 seconds and ensuring reliability in high-volume order interactions. The project emphasized a strong technical foundation, enabling expansion across multiple brands&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI-Driven Refactoring Cut a 2-Year Legacy Code Migration to 4 Months</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13181/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:12:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13181/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in code migration! In a recent article, Lilach Nachmias, Senior Manager of Software Engineering at Salesforce, shared insights on migrating the Own Archive package into Salesforce’s Core infrastructure. This process transformed a two-year effort into just four months through AI-driven refactoring. The migration tackled challenges like undocumented legacy Apex patterns and deep dependency chains, ensuring a fully native product that enhances security and reliability&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Tools Accelerated Building and Adopting Cloud-Agnostic SDK Tasks From Months to Weeks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12988/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:47:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12988/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in cloud technology! Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s Claudia Santoro highlights the development of MultiCloudJ, a cloud-agnostic Java SDK. This tool allows seamless deployment across AWS, GCP, and Alibaba Cloud without provider-specific code. AI tools like Claude and Cursor have reduced development time from months to weeks, enabling faster onboarding. The three-layer architecture of MultiCloudJ addresses cloud provider differences, simplifying API interactions. #CloudComputing #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Real-Time AI Classification for Agentforce: How Single-Token Prediction Delivers 30x Faster Agent Responses</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12910/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 18:44:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12910/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In a recent Q&amp;amp;A, Salesforce engineers Shiva Kumar Pentyala and James Zhu discuss the development of HyperClassifier for Agentforce. This specialized small language model classifies data 30 times faster than general-purpose models using single-token prediction. It addresses latency issues in real-time voice interactions and ensures accurate responses. The focus is on creating efficient AI tailored to specific tasks, enhancing user experiences. Continuous model improvement drives reliability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI-Powered Migration Tools: Compressing 4 Sprints Into 3 Days with Cursor, Windsurf, and Claude</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12725/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12725/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in AI-powered migration tools at Salesforce! Tripti Sheth, Senior Director of Software Engineering, leads a team focused on migrating 4.3 million daily alert notifications to Hyperforce. Their innovative approach transformed outdated spreadsheets into dynamic AI dashboards in just three days. This shift empowers backend engineers to create advanced UI tools and implement automated validation frameworks, significantly speeding up project timelines. MNM (Monitoring Cloud&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Agentforce Deployments: From 6 Months to 3 Weeks Across 150&#43; Enterprises</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12186/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:15:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12186/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Enterprise AI deployments often face challenges like architectural complexity and governance issues. Mukul Singh, Director of Forward Deployed Engineering at Agentforce, helps streamline these processes. With his guidance, deployment timelines have reduced from six months to just three weeks across 150+ enterprises. This efficiency allows teams to scale significantly. The FDE team focuses on overcoming technical blockers and ensuring customers can manage their own implementations&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Zero-Trust Infrastructure Powering Agentforce 360 Platform: Protecting 20 Trillion Transactions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12126/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12126/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Meet Meir Amiel, Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s President and Chief Infrastructure Officer, who leads the development of the Hyperforce Infrastructure. His team powers the Agentforce 360 Platform, ensuring a trusted infrastructure for Salesforce products like Data 360 and MuleSoft. This foundation supports secure operations across various regulated environments. 🔐 Discover how they have secured 20 trillion transactions annually across 17 countries through a robust zero-trust infrastructure, addressing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Data 360 Vector Search Delivers Near Real-Time Intelligence on 90% of Enterprise Data</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11668/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:59:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11668/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in data management! Geeta Singh and her team at Salesforce have enhanced Data 360&amp;rsquo;s vector search capabilities. They transform up to 90% of unstructured data—like documents and media—into actionable insights in near real-time. This advancement addresses the challenges of processing diverse data formats efficiently. Utilizing GPU acceleration, they achieved a significant 51-fold reduction in transcription costs and improved their development cycle by 60% with AI tools&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architecting Multi-System Production Platform: Event Processing Driving $400M&#43; Across 15,000&#43; Orgs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11367/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:42:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11367/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in Salesforce! Madhura Kasinadhuni, Senior Director of Software Engineering, led the creation of Digital Wallet, a platform that provides real-time consumption-based pricing visibility. Since its launch in July 2024, it has reached over 15,000 organizations and generated $400M+ in annual contract value. 💰 The platform focuses on transparency, self-service management, proactive support, and intelligent insights. It aims to enhance customer decision-making and optimize&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Table Predictions in Data Cloud: Enabling Machine Learning Across Related Data Objects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11272/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:39:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11272/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in machine learning are here! Lovi Yu, a Senior Software Engineer at Salesforce, discusses the new multi-DMO support in Data Cloud Model Builder. This feature allows users to build predictions across multiple related data objects, enhancing decision-making. The team focused on balancing functionality and performance while ensuring a user-friendly interface. This development addresses customer needs for more complex data analysis. Discover how predictive modeling can&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Table Predictions in Data Cloud: Enabling Machine Learning Across Related Data Objects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11272/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 20:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11272/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in machine learning are here! Lovi Yu, a Senior Software Engineer at Salesforce, discusses the new multi-DMO support in Data Cloud Model Builder. This feature allows users to build predictions across multiple related data objects, enhancing decision-making. The team focused on balancing functionality and performance while ensuring a user-friendly interface. This development addresses customer needs for more complex data analysis. Discover how predictive modeling can&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentforce’s Agent Graph: Toward Guided Determinism with Hybrid Reasoning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11089/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 22:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11089/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in enterprise AI! In a recent Q&amp;amp;A, Phil Mui, SVP of Agentforce Software Engineering, discusses Agent Graph, the technology behind hybrid reasoning. This approach focuses on externalizing reasoning into design-time graphs, enhancing reliability while maintaining natural conversations. The team addresses common &amp;ldquo;drop-off&amp;rdquo; issues in enterprise applications, aiming for consistency and control in LLMs. A General Availability release is expected later this year. Learn more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Data Cloud One: Enterprise Metadata Synchronization Across 850&#43; Orgs in Days, Not Weeks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10961/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10961/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Salesforce! Hari Priyanka Nunna, Director of Software Engineering, led the development of Data Cloud One. This solution connects multiple Salesforce orgs to a single Data Cloud instance, cutting down on implementation time. The team achieved strong transactional consistency using an outbox pattern architecture and managed to scale from zero to over 850 connections in just nine months. 🌐 Data Cloud One simplifies metadata synchronization, helping enterprise customers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Data Cloud’s New Unstructured Data Governance: Automated PII Detection at Enterprise Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10909/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10909/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in data governance are underway at Salesforce! In the latest “Engineering Energizers” Q&amp;amp;A, Lead Software Engineer Bhargava Ravali Koganti discusses the development of Data Cloud’s first unstructured security system. This innovative system automatically detects and masks sensitive information in enterprise documents. The team tackled the challenge of processing large volumes of unstructured data using Spark pipelines and machine learning models. Their efforts focus on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Real-Time Multimodal AI Pipelines: Scaling File Processing to 50M Daily Uploads</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10637/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 23:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10637/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in AI at Salesforce! Vaibhav Raizada, a Senior Software Engineer, is leading the development of multimodal AI capabilities for Salesforce Prompt Builder. This innovation unlocks file-based data, enhancing AI&amp;rsquo;s ability to process previously invisible information. Key challenges addressed include real-time file processing and integrating diverse data sources. This allows for automated document field extraction and improved customer support through efficient case&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Apache Phoenix DynamoDB Compatibility: Zero-Code Multi-Cloud Database Migrations at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10501/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 13:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10501/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in multi-cloud database migration! Viraj Jasani, a Principal Software Engineer at Salesforce, led the creation of DynamoDB-compatible REST services on Apache Phoenix. This innovation allows teams to migrate across cloud platforms without changing application code. The team tackled significant challenges, including reverse-engineering Amazon’s database APIs and ensuring reliability across multiple clouds like AWS and GCP. This effort prevents vendor lock-in and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing Data Cloud: Unleashing the Power of the New ML Recommendations System</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10271/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10271/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s Data Cloud! Andrew Patti and his team have launched the first Data Cloud-native ML recommendations system. This innovative system utilizes a flexible schema and a unique multi-cluster architecture to enhance personalization capabilities. Their mission ensures seamless migration for customers transitioning from legacy systems, maintaining high performance and availability. With a focus on scalability and ethical ML use, they are set to meet evolving&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Tools Cut Customer Escalation Time: From Days of Manual Work to Minutes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10191/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10191/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI is transforming customer escalations at Salesforce! Kristin Foss, VP of Software Engineering for Customer Centric Engineering, leads a team that has reduced escalation resolution time significantly. By utilizing AI agents and automation, they&amp;rsquo;ve shifted from manual data collection to efficient problem-solving. Their focus is on addressing customer issues quickly, allowing engineers to spend less time gathering data and more time resolving problems. This approach enhances productivity and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Tools Cut Customer Escalation Time: From Days of Manual Work to Minutes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-28-10191/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 19:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-28-10191/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI is transforming customer escalations at Salesforce! Kristin Foss, VP of Software Engineering for Customer Centric Engineering, leads a team that has reduced escalation resolution time significantly. By utilizing AI agents and automation, they&amp;rsquo;ve shifted from manual data collection to efficient problem-solving. Their focus is on addressing customer issues quickly, allowing engineers to spend less time gathering data and more time resolving problems. This approach enhances productivity and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebuilding Heroku on Kubernetes: Platform Modernization, Operational Complexity, and Technical Debt Resolution</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10037/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10037/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements at Heroku! Jillian Wilmarth, Director of Platform Engineering, led the team in a major overhaul, transitioning the platform to Kubernetes. This shift addresses operational complexities and modernizes infrastructure to enhance user experience. Key improvements include IPv6 support and expanded Dyno sizing options. The move ensures Heroku remains competitive and adaptable in a fast-evolving tech landscape. 🌐 #Heroku #Kubernetes #PlatformEngineering #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trust Foundation: How Unified Agentforce Platform’s Operational Excellence Unlocks Rapid AI Adoption</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9891/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9891/</guid>
      <description>Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s Unified Agentforce Platform (UAP) has achieved a 94% adoption rate for AI tools by focusing on operational trust and productivity. The platform connects various sales, service, and marketing functions, integrating advanced AI and data capabilities. In 2024, a strategic &amp;ldquo;Trust Moratorium&amp;rdquo; addressed operational challenges, leading to a Safe Change Program that automated deployment processes, enhancing security and reliability. This initiative resulted in significant improvements,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Cost Reduction Through Hyperforce Optimization: Re-routing Traffic, Slashing $20M</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9794/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9794/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in cost optimization are happening at Salesforce! In a recent Q&amp;amp;A, Tanya Shukla, Senior Product Manager on the Hyperforce team, shared how they improved cost-to-serve economics for Salesforce’s Hyperforce platform. By redesigning key components, they successfully migrated over 90% of traffic while saving $20M. 💰 The team focused on optimizing the egress gateway, crucial for outbound customer connections. They tackled challenges with traffic routing and developed&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending 20 Trillion Transactions: How Hyperforce’s Trusted Perimeter Stops DDoS Attacks with AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9686/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9686/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s Hyperforce team has developed the Trusted Perimeter, a robust platform that protects over 4.5 million domains from DDoS attacks. 🛡️ This system can handle attacks up to 1.6 terabytes per second, ensuring seamless security and performance globally. 🔍 It integrates AI for real-time threat detection and supports 20 trillion transactions annually, allowing businesses to focus on operations without security concerns. #CyberSecurity #DDoSProtection #Salesforce #AI #TrustedPerimeter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Sustainable Enterprise AI Adoption: Cultural Strategies That Achieved 95% Developer Engagement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9435/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9435/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In our latest &amp;ldquo;Engineering Energizers&amp;rdquo; Q&amp;amp;A, Scott Yancey, EVP of Software Engineering, shares his insights on driving AI adoption at Salesforce. His team achieved a remarkable 95% engagement from developers despite facing technical challenges. They focused on breaking cultural barriers and enhancing the development process through AI. Key examples include AI in log analysis, UI accessibility scanning, and issue triaging, all aimed at reducing manual effort. Scott emphasizes that AI is not&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating 70% of Dependency &amp; Vulnerability Management with Renovate and CI/CD</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7556/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 23:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7556/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in security automation at Salesforce! Sai Saketh Nakkina and his team transformed vulnerability management for AI features on the Agentforce platform. By automating 70% of the process with Renovate and CI/CD, they significantly reduced manual responses to vulnerabilities. Their mission focuses on maintaining secure ML pipelines and delivering AI features efficiently while ensuring platform integrity. This approach addresses security threats and enhances customer trust&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking AI Testing Barriers: Dynamic Assertions and AI Automation Deliver 1000%&#43; Productivity Gains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7448/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 19:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7448/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how Gayathri Rajan and her team at Salesforce are revolutionizing AI quality testing! Their innovative approach tackles non-deterministic AI responses and complex integration challenges. By implementing dynamic assertions, they enhance validation processes and boost productivity by over 1000%. Their mission is to ensure reliable AI experiences, empowering teams while transforming quality into a competitive advantage. #AI #QualityTesting #Salesforce #Innovation #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI-Native Engineer: How Salesforce’s Next Generation is Redefining Software Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6349/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6349/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Salesforce Engineering is transforming software development through AI adoption. Key changes include enhanced hiring practices, improved knowledge flow, and a shift in mentorship dynamics. New hires now adapt quickly, using intelligent tools that streamline onboarding. Junior developers are stepping up, showcasing new skills and reshaping traditional mentorship roles. #Salesforce #SoftwareDevelopment #AI #Innovation #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Hyperforce Service Mesh: Blast Radius Reduction, Scale Optimization, and Open Source Innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5162/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5162/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the latest &amp;ldquo;Engineering Energizers&amp;rdquo; Q&amp;amp;A, we spotlight Pratima Nambiar, a Distinguished Architect at Salesforce. She has been pivotal in developing the service mesh architecture for the Hyperforce platform. 🔍 This architecture secures communication among thousands of services, addressing challenges like blast radius reduction and scale optimization. The team leverages open source tools like Envoy and Istio to enhance service connectivity. 💡 The shift to public cloud infrastructure has&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cursor AI Cut Legacy Code Coverage Time by 85%</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5163/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5163/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in software engineering at Salesforce! Rachna Singh and her team tackled the challenge of achieving 80% code coverage on legacy systems. By utilizing Cursor AI, they reduced unit test development time from 26 days to just 4! 📉 This innovative approach not only met the coverage requirement but also improved feature delivery and code quality across multiple repositories. #Salesforce #AI #SoftwareEngineering #CodeCoverage #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Salesforce Delivers Reliable, Low-Latency AI Inference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4854/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4854/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Meet Nilesh Salpe, an engineer at Salesforce focusing on the AI Metadata Service (AIMS). This service offers tenant-specific configurations for AI inferences, crucial for applications like Agentforce. 🔧 His team developed a multi-layered caching system to address a 400ms latency issue, enhancing performance to sub-millisecond levels while ensuring reliability against backend outages. 🌐 AIMS plays a key role in managing diverse AI models and configurations across Salesforce’s multi-cloud&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Boosted Performance Engineering Productivity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2183/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2183/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the latest &amp;ldquo;Engineering Energizers&amp;rdquo; Q&amp;amp;A, we spotlight Zak Zimmerman, Director of Software Engineering at Salesforce. Zak leads the Data Cloud Performance Engineering team, enhancing how they analyze performance data and automate systems using AI tools. The team focuses on ensuring performance, scalability, and reliability within Data Cloud, addressing challenges from massive data influxes. They employ AI to streamline data processing and visualize insights more effectively. Learn how AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
