<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Salesforce-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/salesforce-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Salesforce-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:40:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/salesforce-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building Data Cloud One: Enterprise Metadata Synchronization Across 850&#43; Orgs in Days, Not Weeks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10961/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:40:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10961/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Salesforce! Hari Priyanka Nunna, Director of Software Engineering, led the development of Data Cloud One. This solution connects multiple Salesforce orgs to a single Data Cloud instance, cutting down on implementation time. The team achieved strong transactional consistency using an outbox pattern architecture and managed to scale from zero to over 850 connections in just nine months. 🌐 Data Cloud One simplifies metadata synchronization, helping enterprise customers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Data Cloud’s New Unstructured Data Governance: Automated PII Detection at Enterprise Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10909/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10909/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in data governance are underway at Salesforce! In the latest “Engineering Energizers” Q&amp;amp;A, Lead Software Engineer Bhargava Ravali Koganti discusses the development of Data Cloud’s first unstructured security system. This innovative system automatically detects and masks sensitive information in enterprise documents. The team tackled the challenge of processing large volumes of unstructured data using Spark pipelines and machine learning models. Their efforts focus on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Real-Time Multimodal AI Pipelines: Scaling File Processing to 50M Daily Uploads</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10637/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 23:43:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10637/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in AI at Salesforce! Vaibhav Raizada, a Senior Software Engineer, is leading the development of multimodal AI capabilities for Salesforce Prompt Builder. This innovation unlocks file-based data, enhancing AI&amp;rsquo;s ability to process previously invisible information. Key challenges addressed include real-time file processing and integrating diverse data sources. This allows for automated document field extraction and improved customer support through efficient case&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Apache Phoenix DynamoDB Compatibility: Zero-Code Multi-Cloud Database Migrations at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10501/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 13:52:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10501/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in multi-cloud database migration! Viraj Jasani, a Principal Software Engineer at Salesforce, led the creation of DynamoDB-compatible REST services on Apache Phoenix. This innovation allows teams to migrate across cloud platforms without changing application code. The team tackled significant challenges, including reverse-engineering Amazon’s database APIs and ensuring reliability across multiple clouds like AWS and GCP. This effort prevents vendor lock-in and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing Data Cloud: Unleashing the Power of the New ML Recommendations System</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10271/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10271/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s Data Cloud! Andrew Patti and his team have launched the first Data Cloud-native ML recommendations system. This innovative system utilizes a flexible schema and a unique multi-cluster architecture to enhance personalization capabilities. Their mission ensures seamless migration for customers transitioning from legacy systems, maintaining high performance and availability. With a focus on scalability and ethical ML use, they are set to meet evolving&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Tools Cut Customer Escalation Time: From Days of Manual Work to Minutes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10191/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10191/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI is transforming customer escalations at Salesforce! Kristin Foss, VP of Software Engineering for Customer Centric Engineering, leads a team that has reduced escalation resolution time significantly. By utilizing AI agents and automation, they&amp;rsquo;ve shifted from manual data collection to efficient problem-solving. Their focus is on addressing customer issues quickly, allowing engineers to spend less time gathering data and more time resolving problems. This approach enhances productivity and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Tools Cut Customer Escalation Time: From Days of Manual Work to Minutes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-28-10191/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 19:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-28-10191/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI is transforming customer escalations at Salesforce! Kristin Foss, VP of Software Engineering for Customer Centric Engineering, leads a team that has reduced escalation resolution time significantly. By utilizing AI agents and automation, they&amp;rsquo;ve shifted from manual data collection to efficient problem-solving. Their focus is on addressing customer issues quickly, allowing engineers to spend less time gathering data and more time resolving problems. This approach enhances productivity and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebuilding Heroku on Kubernetes: Platform Modernization, Operational Complexity, and Technical Debt Resolution</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10037/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 17:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10037/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements at Heroku! Jillian Wilmarth, Director of Platform Engineering, led the team in a major overhaul, transitioning the platform to Kubernetes. This shift addresses operational complexities and modernizes infrastructure to enhance user experience. Key improvements include IPv6 support and expanded Dyno sizing options. The move ensures Heroku remains competitive and adaptable in a fast-evolving tech landscape. 🌐 #Heroku #Kubernetes #PlatformEngineering #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trust Foundation: How Unified Agentforce Platform’s Operational Excellence Unlocks Rapid AI Adoption</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9891/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:15:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9891/</guid>
      <description>Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s Unified Agentforce Platform (UAP) has achieved a 94% adoption rate for AI tools by focusing on operational trust and productivity. The platform connects various sales, service, and marketing functions, integrating advanced AI and data capabilities. In 2024, a strategic &amp;ldquo;Trust Moratorium&amp;rdquo; addressed operational challenges, leading to a Safe Change Program that automated deployment processes, enhancing security and reliability. This initiative resulted in significant improvements,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Cost Reduction Through Hyperforce Optimization: Re-routing Traffic, Slashing $20M</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9794/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9794/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in cost optimization are happening at Salesforce! In a recent Q&amp;amp;A, Tanya Shukla, Senior Product Manager on the Hyperforce team, shared how they improved cost-to-serve economics for Salesforce’s Hyperforce platform. By redesigning key components, they successfully migrated over 90% of traffic while saving $20M. 💰 The team focused on optimizing the egress gateway, crucial for outbound customer connections. They tackled challenges with traffic routing and developed&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending 20 Trillion Transactions: How Hyperforce’s Trusted Perimeter Stops DDoS Attacks with AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9686/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 14:29:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9686/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s Hyperforce team has developed the Trusted Perimeter, a robust platform that protects over 4.5 million domains from DDoS attacks. 🛡️ This system can handle attacks up to 1.6 terabytes per second, ensuring seamless security and performance globally. 🔍 It integrates AI for real-time threat detection and supports 20 trillion transactions annually, allowing businesses to focus on operations without security concerns. #CyberSecurity #DDoSProtection #Salesforce #AI #TrustedPerimeter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Sustainable Enterprise AI Adoption: Cultural Strategies That Achieved 95% Developer Engagement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9435/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9435/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In our latest &amp;ldquo;Engineering Energizers&amp;rdquo; Q&amp;amp;A, Scott Yancey, EVP of Software Engineering, shares his insights on driving AI adoption at Salesforce. His team achieved a remarkable 95% engagement from developers despite facing technical challenges. They focused on breaking cultural barriers and enhancing the development process through AI. Key examples include AI in log analysis, UI accessibility scanning, and issue triaging, all aimed at reducing manual effort. Scott emphasizes that AI is not&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating 70% of Dependency &amp; Vulnerability Management with Renovate and CI/CD</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7556/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 23:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7556/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in security automation at Salesforce! Sai Saketh Nakkina and his team transformed vulnerability management for AI features on the Agentforce platform. By automating 70% of the process with Renovate and CI/CD, they significantly reduced manual responses to vulnerabilities. Their mission focuses on maintaining secure ML pipelines and delivering AI features efficiently while ensuring platform integrity. This approach addresses security threats and enhances customer trust&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking AI Testing Barriers: Dynamic Assertions and AI Automation Deliver 1000%&#43; Productivity Gains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7448/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 19:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7448/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how Gayathri Rajan and her team at Salesforce are revolutionizing AI quality testing! Their innovative approach tackles non-deterministic AI responses and complex integration challenges. By implementing dynamic assertions, they enhance validation processes and boost productivity by over 1000%. Their mission is to ensure reliable AI experiences, empowering teams while transforming quality into a competitive advantage. #AI #QualityTesting #Salesforce #Innovation #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI-Native Engineer: How Salesforce’s Next Generation is Redefining Software Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6349/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6349/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Salesforce Engineering is transforming software development through AI adoption. Key changes include enhanced hiring practices, improved knowledge flow, and a shift in mentorship dynamics. New hires now adapt quickly, using intelligent tools that streamline onboarding. Junior developers are stepping up, showcasing new skills and reshaping traditional mentorship roles. #Salesforce #SoftwareDevelopment #AI #Innovation #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Hyperforce Service Mesh: Blast Radius Reduction, Scale Optimization, and Open Source Innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5162/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5162/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the latest &amp;ldquo;Engineering Energizers&amp;rdquo; Q&amp;amp;A, we spotlight Pratima Nambiar, a Distinguished Architect at Salesforce. She has been pivotal in developing the service mesh architecture for the Hyperforce platform. 🔍 This architecture secures communication among thousands of services, addressing challenges like blast radius reduction and scale optimization. The team leverages open source tools like Envoy and Istio to enhance service connectivity. 💡 The shift to public cloud infrastructure has&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cursor AI Cut Legacy Code Coverage Time by 85%</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5163/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:32:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5163/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in software engineering at Salesforce! Rachna Singh and her team tackled the challenge of achieving 80% code coverage on legacy systems. By utilizing Cursor AI, they reduced unit test development time from 26 days to just 4! 📉 This innovative approach not only met the coverage requirement but also improved feature delivery and code quality across multiple repositories. #Salesforce #AI #SoftwareEngineering #CodeCoverage #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Salesforce Delivers Reliable, Low-Latency AI Inference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4854/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4854/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Meet Nilesh Salpe, an engineer at Salesforce focusing on the AI Metadata Service (AIMS). This service offers tenant-specific configurations for AI inferences, crucial for applications like Agentforce. 🔧 His team developed a multi-layered caching system to address a 400ms latency issue, enhancing performance to sub-millisecond levels while ensuring reliability against backend outages. 🌐 AIMS plays a key role in managing diverse AI models and configurations across Salesforce’s multi-cloud&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Boosted Performance Engineering Productivity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2183/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2183/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the latest &amp;ldquo;Engineering Energizers&amp;rdquo; Q&amp;amp;A, we spotlight Zak Zimmerman, Director of Software Engineering at Salesforce. Zak leads the Data Cloud Performance Engineering team, enhancing how they analyze performance data and automate systems using AI tools. The team focuses on ensuring performance, scalability, and reliability within Data Cloud, addressing challenges from massive data influxes. They employ AI to streamline data processing and visualize insights more effectively. Learn how AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
