<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/docker-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/docker-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Hype: How to Use AI to Actually Increase Your Productivity as a Dev</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12944/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12944/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Incorporating AI tools into your development workflow can be challenging at first. Many, including the author, experienced initial frustration with productivity gains. 🔑 Key insights suggest breaking work into manageable chunks, understanding problems before solutions, and refining your approach with AI tools. 🛠️ Effective AI coding involves a cycle: Prompting, Planning, Producing, and Refining. This structured method helps maintain context and improves code quality. Stay adaptable and keep&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Model Runner Integrates vLLM for High-Throughput Inference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12891/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12891/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Docker Model Runner now integrates the vLLM inference engine, enhancing high-throughput AI inference capabilities. This integration allows seamless scaling of AI workloads across various Nvidia hardware while maintaining the familiar Docker workflow. 🖥️ vLLM optimizes performance with advanced algorithms and supports popular models like GPT-OSS and Llama 3, ensuring efficient deployment for production-grade applications. Start exploring today with simple&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I joined Docker: security at the center of the software supply chain</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12854/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12854/</guid>
      <description>Mark Lechner, CISO at Docker, emphasizes the need for security at the core of the software supply chain. As threats evolve, they exploit interconnected systems rather than isolated ones. He reflects on his decade-long experience in diverse sectors, highlighting the shift from controlled environments to open systems where trust must be proven. Docker’s role is crucial; with containers as the standard unit of compute, ensuring security now can reshape software development. 🔍🔐💻 #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 Must-Have MCP Servers (and How to Use Them)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12845/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12845/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of AI with the Model Context Protocol (MCP)! 🚀 In a recent article, Oleg Šelajev highlights six essential MCP servers that enhance developer productivity. These servers connect AI agents to external tools, streamlining workflows. Key servers include Context7 for coding accuracy, Obsidian for smarter note-taking, and DuckDuckGo for search capabilities. Each server offers unique benefits to improve your development process. 💻✨ Explore how these tools can transform your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker &#43; Unsloth: Build Custom Models, Faster</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12782/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 17:57:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12782/</guid>
      <description>Running AI models locally can be challenging due to dependency issues and inconsistencies. Docker and Unsloth are collaborating to simplify the process of building and running custom models. This partnership aims to enhance model creation, optimization, and execution. With Docker Model Runner, developers can easily launch models across different systems, streamlining the workflow. Explore more about this innovative solution! 🚀🖥️ #AI #Docker #Unsloth #MachineLearning #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launch a Chat UI Agent with Docker and the Vercel AI SDK</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12766/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12766/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Launching a Chat UI Agent is now simpler with Docker and the Vercel AI SDK! By using Docker, you can maintain a consistent environment across different machines. The Vercel AI SDK streamlines the creation of conversational interfaces with tools for streaming responses and multi-turn interactions. Get started by cloning the Next.js AI Chatbot template and configuring your API keys. With just one command, your Chat UI goes live! #ChatUI #Docker #Vercel #AI #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making the Most of Your Docker Hardened Images Trial – Part 1</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12176/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:04:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12176/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover Docker Hardened Images! These minimal base images are designed to enhance application security by eliminating unnecessary packages and proactively patching vulnerabilities. 🔍 With a 30-day trial, you can evaluate if these images reduce your security risks without extra operational burden. 📊 Expect to measure CVE counts and engineering effort during the trial to see real results. Get started with the DHI catalog and experience the benefits firsthand! #Docker #CyberSecurity #DevOps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating the Great AI Productivity Divide: Why Are Some Developers 5x Faster?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12171/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12171/</guid>
      <description>AI developer tools promise increased productivity but results vary widely. 🚀 While some developers report boosts of 3-5x, others experience no benefits or even losses of up to 19%. In 2025, 84% of developers plan to use these tools, yet trust in their accuracy is declining. Awareness of this divide in experiences is crucial for developers. #AIDevelopment #Productivity #TechTrends #SoftwareEngineering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cagent Comes to Docker Desktop with Built-In IDE Support through ACP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12101/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12101/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Docker Desktop now includes cagent, allowing you to build AI agents without any extra installations. Cagent is an open-source tool that simplifies AI agent development using YAML files. You can define behaviors and tools, while cagent manages execution. To get started, update Docker Desktop to version 4.49.0 or later and create your first agent with ease. Existing users can continue using their current installations for flexibility. Additionally, cagent now&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The WhatsApp Data Exfiltration Attack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12102/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12102/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Part 5 of our MCP Horror Stories series highlights a serious security threat: the WhatsApp Data Exfiltration Attack. This vulnerability allows attackers to steal entire message histories by leveraging a clever exploit within WhatsApp. It bypasses traditional security measures, making it difficult to detect. Understanding these threats is crucial for developers to enhance AI security. #CyberSecurity #AIThreats #DataProtection #WhatsApp #MCP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop 4.50: Indispensable for Daily Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12103/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12103/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker Desktop 4.50 is here, enhancing how development teams build and ship software. This update focuses on faster debugging, improved security controls, and AI integration. It aims to streamline daily workflows for developers, reducing friction and enhancing productivity. Key features include free Docker Debug for all users and deeper IDE integration for smoother troubleshooting. The new Compose to Kubernetes capabilities help bridge local development with production environments&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Engine v29: Foundational Updates for the Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12104/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12104/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker Engine v29 is here, focusing on foundational updates for Linux users running the Community Edition. This release enhances maintainability and developer experience with important changes, including an updated minimum API version to 1.44 and the Containerd image store as the default for new installations. Additionally, Docker has migrated to Go modules and offers experimental support for NFTables, improving interoperability across the container ecosystem. For Docker Desktop users, no&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect to Remote MCP Servers with OAuth in Docker</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12105/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 13:53:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12105/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The Docker MCP Catalog now supports remote MCP servers with OAuth, making it easier to connect securely to various tools like Notion and Linear. 🔗 With over 60 new remote servers added, you can enhance your workflows without manual token juggling. Just two simple commands are all you need to get started! 💻 Enjoy seamless integration and quick access to essential services right from your Docker environment. #Docker #MCP #OAuth #RemoteServers #DeveloperTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help Define the Future of Development – Take the Docker State of Application Development Survey 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12106/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12106/</guid>
      <description>📢 Join the Docker community by participating in the fourth annual State of Application Development survey! Your feedback is vital for shaping the future of application development. It takes just 20 minutes to share your insights on current trends and challenges. 🛍️ Complete the survey for a chance to win prizes, including a MacBook Pro, PlayStation 5, and Amazon gift cards! 🕒 The survey runs from November 10 to December 10, 2025. Be among the first 300 respondents to receive exclusive Docker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most DevSecOps Advice Is Useless without Context—Here’s What Actually Works</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11943/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11943/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.docker.com/blog/feed/&#34;&gt;Docker Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.docker.com/blog/context-aware-devsecops-what-works/&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic MCPs with Docker: Stop Hardcoding Your Agents’ World</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11944/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11944/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.docker.com/blog/feed/&#34;&gt;Docker Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.docker.com/blog/dynamic-mcps-stop-hardcoding-your-agents-world/&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Multimodal AI Models With Docker Model Runner</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11655/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 13:20:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11655/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of multimodal AI! 🌐 This article discusses how multimodal models can process various inputs like text, images, and audio, enhancing AI capabilities. You can now ask models to describe images or transcribe audio clips for more intuitive interaction. Learn how to utilize these models with Docker Model Runner, from choosing the right model to practical examples. The CLI and API provide options for experimentation and integration into applications. #AI #Multimodal #Docker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Doesn’t Have to Hurt</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11536/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11536/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Security teams and employees often find themselves at odds over the tools needed to get work done. Tools like AI for documentation can be blocked, causing frustration for everyone involved. 💻 Shadow IT emerges as a solution, but it creates tension between innovation and security compliance. Employees seek flexibility, while security teams strive to maintain oversight. 🤝 There’s a call for collaboration to shift security focus towards compromise and efficiency, allowing for better tool&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Bones: A Pirate-Voiced Halloween Chatbot Powered by Docker Model Runner</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11537/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 12:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11537/</guid>
      <description>🎃 Meet Mr. Bones, the interactive Halloween chatbot! Mike Coleman from Docker transformed a Home Depot skeleton into a pirate-voiced AI that chats with kids. Using Docker Model Runner, he created a local LLM that handles conversations seamlessly. Key benefits include no API costs, low latency, and easy model switching. Curious about how it works? Kids talk to the skeleton, and a Raspberry Pi processes their questions before Mr. Bones responds in pirate voice! 🏴‍☠️👻 #Halloween #AI #Docker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>theCUBE Research economic validation of Docker’s development platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11485/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 11:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11485/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The recent study by theCUBE Research highlights Docker&amp;rsquo;s significant role in enhancing developer productivity and software supply chain security. 🔍 Nearly 400 IT and AppDev leaders reported that Docker streamlines agentic AI development, reducing setup time by over 25% for 87% of organizations. 🛡️ Docker&amp;rsquo;s integrated security features help maintain compliance, with 95% of respondents noting improved vulnerability identification. For more insights, check out the full report! 📊 #Docker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>theCUBE Research economic validation of Docker’s development platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11501/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 11:46:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11501/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A recent study by theCUBE Research explores Docker&amp;rsquo;s influence on developer productivity and AI development. Nearly 400 IT leaders from global enterprises shared insights on how Docker enhances software supply chain security and reduces costs. Key findings indicate that 87% of organizations have cut AI setup time by over 25%, while 80% report a 26% faster AI time-to-market. Docker integrates security seamlessly, with 95% of respondents noting improved vulnerability management. For a deeper&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Connect MCP Servers to Claude Desktop with Docker MCP Toolkit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11323/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11323/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of Claude Desktop with the Docker MCP Toolkit! 🚀 This integration allows Claude to function as a development partner, executing tasks securely without affecting your local machine. With the Model Context Protocol (MCP), Claude can connect to tools and APIs, enabling actions like container deployment and data analysis. 🛠️ The Docker MCP Toolkit creates a safe environment for these processes, ensuring security and efficiency. Automate tasks that once took hours down to just&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Hub Incident Report – October 20, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11274/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 23:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11274/</guid>
      <description>🚨 &lt;strong&gt;Docker Hub Incident Report&lt;/strong&gt; 🚨 On October 20, 2025, Docker experienced a significant outage due to issues in AWS’s US-East-1 region. This affected services like Docker Hub and Build Cloud, disrupting workflows for developers globally. The outage began at 06:48 UTC, leading to complete service interruption by 08:01 UTC. Partial recovery started around 09:40 UTC, with full restoration achieved by 09:42 UTC on October 21. We are monitoring our systems closely to ensure stability moving&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Org, Your Tools: Building a Custom MCP Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11270/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 19:07:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11270/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in AI tooling! Mike Coleman from Docker discusses the importance of implementing guardrails for AI adoption in enterprises. Many organizations seek tighter control over the tools available to developers through Docker’s Model Context Protocol (MCP) tooling. The article provides a guide on how to create a custom MCP catalog by forking Docker’s official catalog, hosting images in a private registry, and using the MCP Gateway to manage server connections. Learn more about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Guide to the Galaxy: MCP Toolkit and Gateway, Explained</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11257/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11257/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into Docker&amp;rsquo;s MCP Toolkit and Gateway! In a recent discussion, Jim Clark explained how the MCP Toolkit helps users discover and manage MCP servers seamlessly. It leverages Docker containers for installation and orchestration, ensuring consistency and governance. The MCP Gateway unifies server access for clients, enhancing security with OAuth support and provenance checks. For official details, check out the Docker MCP Catalog. #Docker #MCPToolkit #MCPGateway #TechTalk #SoftwareEngineering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why More People Are Taking Control of Their Digital Lives with Self-Hosted Alternatives</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11256/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11256/</guid>
      <description>🌐 More people are choosing self-hosted alternatives for their digital tools, moving away from cloud services that come with subscription fees and data privacy concerns. 💾 Self-hosting allows individuals to control their data and avoid reliance on third-party providers. Many open-source options exist for those looking to manage their own software. 🔍 The article explores the rise of self-hosting, its benefits, and beginner-friendly software options. #SelfHosting #DataPrivacy #OpenSource&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker &#43; E2B: Building the Future of Trusted AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11197/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11197/</guid>
      <description>🛠️ The era of AI agents is evolving, but trust remains a significant challenge. Docker, with over 20 million developers, is enhancing its tools for building and securing AI agents. 🔒 Recently, Docker partnered with E2B to provide secure cloud sandboxes for developers. This collaboration aims to give fast and secure access to numerous real-world tools. 🤖 With new capabilities and a focus on safety, Docker is setting the standard for how agents connect and act in a secure manner. #Docker #E2B&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Offload: Automating Everyday Workflows with Docker</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11152/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11152/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Developers often face limitations with their local machines when handling heavy tasks like AI training or large code compilations. Docker Offload addresses this by allowing users to extend their existing Docker workflows to the cloud, maintaining the familiar commands while leveraging powerful cloud resources. This service is perfect for executing resource-intensive builds, enhancing development speed, and managing complex applications without the need for hardware upgrades. Getting started&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing a Richer ”docker model run” Experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11110/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:26:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11110/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for Docker users! The latest upgrade to the Docker Model Runner enhances the interactive chat experience. It now features a readline-style prompt with keyboard shortcuts for smoother navigation and editing. Key improvements include: - New keyboard shortcuts for efficient text management. - Ability to stop model responses anytime using “Ctrl + c”. - Better multi-line support and command history for easier experimentation. Enhance your AI workload management today! #Docker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Model Runner Meets Open WebUI: A Simpler Way to Run Local AI Models</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11069/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11069/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the AI community! Sergei Shitikov has developed a new Docker extension that simplifies running local AI models using Docker Model Runner and Open WebUI. This tool makes local LLMs accessible to everyone, even those without a tech background. With just a few clicks, you can set up your own AI assistant, enjoying a rich chat experience while maintaining privacy. No complex configurations required! Learn more about this powerful duo and how to get started. #AI #Docker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to add MCP Servers to OpenAI’s Codex with Docker MCP Toolkit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11043/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:12:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11043/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of AI coding with OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s Codex and the Docker MCP Toolkit! 🔗 The Model Context Protocol (MCP) Toolkit connects Codex to over 200 MCP servers, enabling efficient interaction with specialized tools. This post demonstrates how to link Codex with Neo4j, showcasing a fun project that visualizes Pokémon species data. 📊 The Docker MCP Toolkit simplifies data modeling, allowing developers to focus on building knowledge graphs without the usual setup hassles. Discover how this&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I Still Use jQuery</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11029/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11029/</guid>
      <description>jQuery has been a staple in web development since its launch in 2006. Initially, it simplified tasks like DOM manipulation and event handling across different browsers, which was a challenge at the time. 🌐 Despite the rise of modern frameworks, jQuery remains popular, with around 195 million websites using it as of August 2025. Some developers, including the article&amp;rsquo;s author, still find it useful for specific tasks. 🔧 The article discusses when to choose jQuery over other tools, emphasizing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debug Docker Builds with Visual Studio Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10989/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10989/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Building Docker images is vital for modern application delivery. However, debugging Dockerfiles can be complex and time-consuming. To enhance this process, recent updates to Docker Build clients and the VS Code Docker extension now introduce Build Debugging. This allows developers to inspect build stages, variables, and even open a shell in the image being built. 🐳 To get started, ensure you have the latest Docker DX extension and Docker Desktop. Create a launch configuration in VS Code to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Hardened Images: crafted by humans, protected by AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10960/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10960/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At Docker, we&amp;rsquo;re committed to building hardened images with meticulous human craftsmanship and enhanced by AI. This dual approach ensures better security for our users. Our AI guardrail recently caught a critical bug during an nginx-exporter update, preventing potential issues from reaching customers. This highlights the importance of layered safeguards in software development. By addressing issues upstream, we maintain clean images and support the broader open-source community. #Docker #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to add MCP Servers to Gemini CLI with Docker MCP Toolkit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10947/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10947/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the future of AI-assisted development with the powerful duo of Google’s Gemini CLI and Docker&amp;rsquo;s MCP Toolkit! 🚀 This combination simplifies browser testing and performance analysis, allowing for automation with just a few commands. A setup that takes only 5 minutes can save developers significant time on each test. ⏱️ Learn how to connect Gemini CLI with Docker and automate tasks like issue creation and performance reporting—all from your terminal. With over 220 pre-built MCP servers,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Multi-Agent System in 5 Minutes with cagent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10895/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10895/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in AI models like GPT-5 and Gemini are leading developers to explore multi-agent systems. These systems consist of various agents—researchers, writers, planners—working together to tackle complex tasks. However, building these systems can be challenging due to integration issues. cagent is an open-source tool designed to simplify this process. It allows users to create and manage multi-agent systems easily, using a single YAML file for configuration. With cagent, you&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join Us in Rebooting the Docker Model Runner Community!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10896/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10896/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for the Docker Model Runner community! The project has transitioned from Limited Beta to General Availability, now accessible on all Docker versions with added Vulkan support for broader GPU compatibility. We&amp;rsquo;ve streamlined the contribution process by consolidating repositories and enhancing documentation, making it easier for all contributors. Join us in shaping the future of AI models with Docker! 👉 Star, fork, and contribute to our repo. Spread the word! #Docker #OpenSource&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Model Runner on the new NVIDIA DGX Spark: a new paradigm for developing AI locally</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10881/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10881/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI developers! NVIDIA DGX Spark now supports Docker Model Runner, enhancing local model development. With DGX Spark&amp;rsquo;s powerful Grace Blackwell GB10 Superchip, you can efficiently prototype and fine-tune large models right on your machine. 🖥️ Docker Model Runner simplifies this process, providing a secure environment for running AI models without cloud dependency. Unboxing and setup are straightforward, allowing for quick integration into your workflow. #NVIDIA #Docker #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100% Transparency and Five Pillars</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10878/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10878/</guid>
      <description>Container security is crucial as workloads increasingly rely on containers. However, many organizations misrepresent their container security capabilities. According to a recent article, there are five essential elements for achieving maximum container security: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Minimal Attack Surface&lt;/strong&gt;: Only essential software should be included. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Complete Software Bills of Materials (SBOM)&lt;/strong&gt;: Accurate inventory is necessary. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Verifiable Build Provenance&lt;/strong&gt;: Establishes a clear chain of custody&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Add MCP Servers to Claude Code with Docker MCP Toolkit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10621/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10621/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI coding assistants have advanced significantly, but tools like Claude Code still require manual interaction with your environment. The Model Context Protocol (MCP) and Docker MCP Toolkit bridge this gap, enabling seamless integration with your tools and databases. This guide outlines how to set up and connect Claude Code with Docker MCP Toolkit, configure servers for Jira and GitHub, and automate tech debt tracking. With over 200 pre-built servers and one-click deployment, developers can&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LoRA Explained: Faster, More Efficient Fine-Tuning with Docker</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10579/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:58:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10579/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of language models with LoRA! 🚀 This article explores how to fine-tune models efficiently using Docker. By focusing on specific skills, like masking personally identifiable information (PII), we can enhance model performance without extensive resources. LoRA (Low-Rank Adaptation) allows you to teach new tasks while preserving the model’s core knowledge. It involves adding small adapter layers to the pre-trained model, making the process faster and less resource-intensive. The&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From the Captain’s Chair: Pradumna Saraf</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10535/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10535/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Meet Pradumna Saraf, a Docker Captain and Open Source Developer passionate about DevOps! In our latest &amp;ldquo;From the Captain’s Chair&amp;rdquo; interview, Pradumna shares his journey from learning about MongoDB to embracing Docker. He values community involvement and aims to create more technical content while engaging in international talks. He highlights Docker Compose as a favorite feature, especially for managing AI models. Read more to discover his insights and experiences in the Docker community!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Local AI on Any GPU: Docker Model Runner Now with Vulkan Support</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10536/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 11:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10536/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI enthusiasts! Docker Model Runner now supports Vulkan, allowing GPU-accelerated inferencing on a wider range of hardware, including AMD and Intel GPUs. This update simplifies running large language models locally with just one command. 🖥️ No special setup is needed; the tool automatically detects compatible Vulkan hardware. Try it out today! For collaboration and contributions, visit the GitHub repo. #Docker #AI #Vulkan #OpenSource #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powered by Docker: How Open Source Genius Cut Entropy Debt with Docker MCP Toolkit and Claude Desktop</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10490/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10490/</guid>
      <description>Open Source Genius faced a challenge with increasing document chaos, termed &amp;ldquo;entropy debt,&amp;rdquo; while managing multiple AI projects. 📄 Instead of hiring more staff or adding SaaS tools, they developed an AI-powered file automation agent using Docker’s MCP Toolkit and Claude Desktop. This solution saves each team member two hours weekly! ⏳ With the goal of creating over $100M in small business value by 2027, OSG effectively streamlined their processes and improved productivity. 💡 #OpenSource&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Granite 4.0 Models Now Available on Docker Hub</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10472/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 21:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10472/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IBM has launched its Granite 4.0 language models on Docker Hub! Developers can now easily discover and run these open-source models, enabling quick prototyping and scalable AI applications. The Granite 4.0 family combines strong performance with a lightweight design. With features like a hybrid architecture and support for long context lengths, these models are designed for efficiency and flexibility. Explore the capabilities of Granite 4.0 today! #IBM #Granite40 #DockerHub #AI #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlimited access to Docker Hardened Images: Because security should be affordable, always</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10473/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 21:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10473/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in software security! Docker has launched unlimited access to its Hardened Images catalog, aiming for near-zero CVEs at an affordable price. This change allows teams to access secure, up-to-date container images without premium costs. These images are built from source, continuously patched, and smaller in size, reducing potential vulnerabilities. The catalog supports various platforms, making it easy for developers to adopt. Discover the impact of secure software development&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker at AI Engineer Paris: Build and Secure AI Agents with Docker</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10446/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10446/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Last week, Docker participated in the inaugural AI Engineer Paris conference, highlighting the evolution of AI application development. Key discussions emphasized that true innovation requires rigorous engineering, not just &amp;ldquo;AI dust.&amp;rdquo; The focus is on creating robust AI agents through standardized practices. Docker&amp;rsquo;s Tushar Jain led a keynote on making AI agent development accessible to all developers. A hands-on workshop followed, teaching attendees how to build collaborative multi-agent&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Llama.cpp Gets an Upgrade: Resumable Model Downloads</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10447/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 11:55:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10447/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for the llama.cpp community! The latest update introduces &lt;strong&gt;resumable downloads&lt;/strong&gt; for GGUF model files. No more starting over if your connection drops! This new feature allows downloads to resume from where they left off, improving efficiency and user experience. Additionally, the update ensures smarter management of model versions and prevents file corruption during downloads. For optimal model management, consider using &lt;strong&gt;Docker Model Runner&lt;/strong&gt; to streamline workflows and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Shell Scripts to Science Agents: How AI Agents Are Transforming Research Workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10386/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10386/</guid>
      <description>🔬 AI agents are revolutionizing research workflows by automating complex tasks in scientific studies. Instead of relying on manual scripts, researchers can now describe their goals, and these intelligent systems handle tasks like data parsing and literature searching. These autonomous agents, like those developed by CrewAI, work together to improve efficiency and reproducibility in research. The future of science is here! 🌟 #AIinResearch #ScienceAgents #Automation #Innovation #ResearchEfficiency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Tuning Local Models with Docker Offload and Unsloth</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10387/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:46:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10387/</guid>
      <description>Exploring local models has its challenges, but the potential is significant. 🌟 Models like Gemma 3 270M can run on common hardware, offering benefits like privacy and offline capabilities. However, achieving high performance for complex tasks remains difficult. The Unsloth project is a game-changer for fine-tuning, providing a ready-to-use Docker image to streamline the process. 🚀 With Docker Offload, users can access cloud GPU resources, enhancing their local workflow. Stay tuned for a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expanding Docker Hardened Images: Secure Helm Charts for Deployments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10229/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10229/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Development teams are facing increased pressure to secure their software supply chains. Docker has introduced Helm charts in the Docker Hardened Images (DHI) Catalog to streamline Kubernetes deployments while enhancing security. These charts ensure safe configurations and clear traceability, meeting the needs of teams concerned about compliance. With changes from Broadcom affecting Bitnami&amp;rsquo;s distribution, Docker offers a reliable alternative for secure deployments. Join the beta program to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker MCP Toolkit: MCP Servers That Just Work</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10203/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10203/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover the Docker MCP Toolkit! This free feature in Docker Desktop offers access to over 200 MCP servers, making it simple and secure to run local servers for your AI projects. With just a few clicks, you can configure servers, environment variables, and API keys. The toolkit also supports integrations with tools like LM Studio and Claude Desktop. Build advanced workflows by connecting feedback from Notion to GitHub Issues. Check out the demo for practical examples! 📊💻 #Docker #MCPToolkit&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trust Paradox: When Your AI Gets Catfished</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10139/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10139/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Hackers are exploiting trust relationships to catfish your AI. Attacks aren&amp;rsquo;t about technical skills; they manipulate familiar systems designers and developers rely on. From altered npm packages to deceptive documentation, AI tools can be misled to introduce vulnerabilities. The good news? Solutions exist that don&amp;rsquo;t hinder development. #CyberSecurity #AI #TrustParadox #MCP #InfoSec</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Docker Premium Support and TAM service</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10098/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:19:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10098/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Docker! They&amp;rsquo;ve launched the Premium Support and Technical Account Management (TAM) service, providing 24/7 support for developers. Key features include high-priority responses, advanced incident analysis, and guidance from Docker experts. This service aims to enhance resilience and support across the entire Docker ecosystem. Ideal for enterprises navigating complex software development challenges. For more info, check the Docker website! #Docker #PremiumSupport #TAM&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run, Test, and Evaluate Models and MCP Locally with Docker &#43; Promptfoo</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10058/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 11:32:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10058/</guid>
      <description>Explore the power of Promptfoo and Docker Model Runner for evaluating LLM apps! Promptfoo is an open-source CLI that simplifies the evaluation of AI models. With Docker Model Runner, users can easily manage and deploy these models. The Docker MCP Toolkit serves as a local gateway for running containerized MCP servers, enhancing connectivity with AI agents. These tools enable users to compare models and assess MCP servers directly from their development environment. #AI #Docker #Promptfoo&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The Drive-By Localhost Breach</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9917/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9917/</guid>
      <description>🚨 MCP Horror Stories: Drive-By Localhost Breach 🚨 Part 4 of our series highlights a critical vulnerability, CVE-2025-49596, found in MCP Inspector. This issue allows attackers to compromise developer machines simply by visiting a malicious website. With a CVSS score of 9.4, this flaw turns a trusted debugging tool into an attack vector, showcasing the real-world risks in AI development environments. Learn how Docker MCP Gateway can help protect against these sophisticated threats&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Silent Component Updates &amp; Redesigned Update Experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9821/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:07:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9821/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker Desktop 4.46 introduces automatic component updates and a redesigned update experience. With these changes, updates happen in the background, ensuring zero interruption to your workflow. Key tools like Docker Scout and Compose will always be up-to-date without manual input. 🔒 The new update experience features clearer messaging and reduced notification fatigue. Users also have the option to manage updates in their settings. Learn more about these enhancements! #Docker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Containers: llama.cpp Now Pulls GGUF Models Directly from Docker Hub</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9822/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 12:01:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9822/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in local AI! llama.cpp now supports pulling GGUF models directly from Docker Hub, simplifying the process for developers. This integration allows for rock-solid versioning, centralized model storage, and streamlined workflows. With just a command, you can easily manage models without the hassle of manual downloads. 🎉 Explore how this feature enhances reproducibility and efficiency in your projects! #AI #DockerHub #llamaCpp #MachineLearning #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build and Distribute AI Agents and Workflows with cagent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9791/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9791/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing cagent, an open-source project from Docker that simplifies the creation and sharing of AI agents without any coding! By defining your agent&amp;rsquo;s behavior, tools, and persona in a single YAML file, you can easily build personalized AI assistants. 🌐 cagent not only streamlines agent creation but also facilitates community sharing through OCI registries. Explore practical use cases, like a GitHub Task Tracker, to see how cagent can enhance your workflows! #AI #OpenSource #Docker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker and CNCF: Partnering to Power the Future of Open Source</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9792/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9792/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Docker! They&amp;rsquo;ve announced an official partnership with the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF). This collaboration strengthens their commitment to open source, enhancing support for developers and maintainers in the cloud-native ecosystem. Key benefits include unlimited image pulls and access to Docker&amp;rsquo;s extensive resources. With Docker Hub hosting over 14 million images and 22 billion downloads monthly, this partnership aims to improve project visibility and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Model Runner General Availability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9773/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9773/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Docker Model Runner is now generally available! Originally launched in April 2025 as a Beta, it has rapidly evolved to provide developers with a reliable tool for managing and running local AI models, specifically large language models (LLMs). Docker Model Runner integrates smoothly with existing infrastructure, allowing developers to use familiar Docker commands while ensuring security and compliance. Key features include GPU acceleration, OpenAI-compatible APIs, and support&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build Secure AI Coding Agents with Cerebras and Docker Compose</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9740/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9740/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Explore how to build secure AI coding agents using Cerebras and Docker Compose! The article highlights the process of creating portable and secure AI environments. It covers essential steps, from cloning the GitHub repository to configuring the .env file with your Cerebras API key. Learn about the architecture, including the Agentic Loop and MCP Tools, which are crucial for the agent&amp;rsquo;s functionality. For detailed guidance, check out the full article! #AICoding #Cerebras #DockerCompose&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Security: A Developer’s Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9685/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9685/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Model Context Protocol (MCP) has quickly gained traction since its launch by Anthropic in November 2024. It serves as a vital link between AI agents and various tools, APIs, and data. 🔍 However, this flexibility comes with security challenges. Research indicates that 43% of analyzed MCP servers have command injection vulnerabilities, which could lead to serious risks if misconfigured. 🛡️ This guide offers developers insights into MCP security, highlighting risks and best practices for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nine Rules of AI PoC Success: How to Build Demos That Actually Ship</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9649/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9649/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A recent article challenges the claim that &amp;ldquo;95% of AI POCs fail,&amp;rdquo; arguing that the real issue lies in how teams design their proofs of concept. Many POCs are built as disposable demos for presentations, not for real-world use. This leads to failures when they encounter actual users or scale demands. To improve success rates, the article outlines nine essential rules for creating effective POCs. Key strategies include starting small, designing for production from day one, and optimizing for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Hallucinations to Prompt Injection: Securing AI Workflows at Runtime</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9516/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9516/</guid>
      <description>Developers are facing new challenges as AI workflows become potential attack surfaces. With AI tools like LLMs generating code, issues can arise only at runtime, leading to serious risks such as data loss or unauthorized commands. ⚠️ Prompt injections and misuse of AI outputs are significant threats. Recent incidents have shown how AI-generated scripts can unintentionally delete databases or expose sensitive information. 📉 To tackle these risks, integrating runtime security directly into&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Acquisition of MCP Defender Helps Meet Challenges of Securing the Agentic Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7786/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7786/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker, Inc. has acquired MCP Defender to enhance security for AI applications. As AI evolves rapidly, new security challenges arise for software development. 🔍 The current AI security landscape reflects early container adoption, marked by innovation but also uncertainty about risks. Organizations must now focus on real-time monitoring and dynamic threat detection. 🔒 Docker aims to embed security into AI infrastructure from the start, ensuring seamless integration into development&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Acquisition of MCP Defender Helps Meet Challenges of Securing the Agentic Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-8131/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-8131/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker, Inc. has announced its acquisition of MCP Defender to enhance security for AI applications. As AI technology evolves, so do the security challenges it presents. 🚧 Companies are urged to shift towards real-time monitoring and proactive threat detection to safeguard their AI infrastructure. Docker aims to integrate security into AI development from the start, ensuring a seamless experience for developers. 🔐 #Docker #AIsafety #Cybersecurity #TechNews #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid AI Isn’t the Future — It’s Here (and It Runs in Docker)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7731/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7731/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Hybrid AI is revolutionizing how we utilize AI models! Running large models in the cloud can lead to high costs, while local models help maintain privacy and control expenses. However, local models often lack capability. The hybrid approach combines cloud and local strengths, offering a cost-effective, efficient solution. Using Docker, developers can easily deploy systems that balance performance and affordability. Explore how this innovative model works! 🖥️💡 #HybridAI #Docker #AIModels&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hybrid AI Isn’t the Future — It’s Here (and It Runs in Docker)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-8132/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-8132/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Hybrid AI is reshaping how we utilize AI models. By merging powerful cloud models with efficient local models, it balances performance, cost, and privacy. This allows developers to achieve high quality without overspending. 💡 The Minions protocol exemplifies this, using local &amp;ldquo;minions&amp;rdquo; for routine tasks while a remote supervisor handles complex reasoning. Docker facilitates simple and secure deployments. 🐳 Explore the advantages of Hybrid AI, including cost reduction, scalability, and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You are Doing MCP Wrong: 3 Big Misconceptions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7692/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7692/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Understanding the Model Context Protocol (MCP) is crucial for developers. Many mistakenly view MCP as just another API, which can disrupt agent designs and execution reliability. MCP is designed for LLM tool use, not replacing RPC but enhancing it. Another common misconception is that tools are agents. While tools execute tasks, agents plan and evaluate until goals are met. For effective use, define tool preconditions, validate inputs, and maintain clear logs. #ModelContextProtocol #MCP&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcom’s New Bitnami Restrictions? Migrate Easily with Docker</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-30-7564/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 23:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-30-7564/</guid>
      <description>Bitnami has been crucial in simplifying application deployment for developers. However, significant changes are coming to their distribution model. Starting September 29, access to most versioned images will require a paid subscription under Bitnami Secure Images. Only the :latest tags will remain free, while older images will move to a legacy archive without updates. Docker offers alternatives with their Official Images and Hardened Images, providing robust options for teams facing these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boost Your Copilot with SonarQube via Docker MCP Toolkit and Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7536/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7536/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the age of AI copilots, ensuring code quality is crucial. SonarQube helps identify bugs, test coverage, and security issues but can interrupt workflow due to feedback loops. 🔧 The solution? Integrate SonarQube directly into your IDE using the Sonar MCP server and Docker MCP Toolkit. This allows AI agents like GitHub Copilot to access code quality metrics seamlessly. 🛠️ The Docker MCP Toolkit simplifies the setup, enabling developers to focus on coding without distractions. For hands-on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure by Design: A Shift-Left Approach with Testcontainers, Docker Scout, and Hardened Images</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7465/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7465/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s software development landscape, speed should not compromise security. 🛡️ This article discusses a shift-left approach using tools like Testcontainers and Docker to enhance security early in the development lifecycle. It highlights how developers can conduct reliable integration tests while maintaining high quality. A practical example features a Node.js Movie Catalog API, demonstrating how Testcontainers can streamline testing against a PostgreSQL database. 📦 Learn how modern&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop Accelerates Innovation with Faster Release Cadence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7231/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7231/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news from Docker! Starting with release 4.45.0 on August 28, Docker Desktop will shift to a new update schedule, moving from monthly to bi-weekly releases, aiming for weekly updates by 2025. This change is in response to user requests for quicker access to new features and urgent updates. 🚀 Enhancements include smarter component updates that occur silently without interrupting your workflow and clearer update information within the app. Enterprise users will retain control over&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prototyping an AI Tutor with Docker Model Runner</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5115/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5115/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exploring how AI can enhance developer learning is exciting! A recent article discusses the creation of an interactive AI tutor using Docker Model Runner. This tool aims to streamline the learning process by embedding AI assistance directly into the development environment. The tutor helps users run their first &amp;ldquo;hello-world&amp;rdquo; container without the hassle of switching between various resources, maintaining context, and ensuring privacy. #AITutoring #Docker #DeveloperExperience #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supply Chain Paradox: When “Hardened” Images Become a Vendor Lock-in Trap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5116/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5116/</guid>
      <description>The demand for pre-hardened container images is rapidly rising as companies seek immediate security solutions with low operational effort. These images offer minimal dependencies, allowing teams to focus on application development. However, this trend may lead to unintended vendor lock-in. Organizations could become overly reliant on a single vendor&amp;rsquo;s systems and processes, complicating operations and potentially weakening security. Additionally, deviations from mainstream distributions can&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamline NGINX Configuration with Docker Desktop Extension</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5117/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:13:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5117/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Enhance your NGINX configuration with Docker Desktop! This article highlights how the NGINX Development Center simplifies server management and boosts workflow efficiency. It offers user-friendly tools for easier configuration, multi-server management, and improved debugging. With over 51,000 downloads, it integrates seamlessly with Docker Desktop to streamline app and web server development. #Docker #NGINX #WebDevelopment #DevOps #Containerization</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI Agents with Docker MCP Toolkit: A Developer’s Real-World Setup</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5118/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:59:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5118/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Building AI agents requires more than just model calls. The article explores using the Docker MCP Toolkit to create an agent that interacts with GitHub repositories. This agent can answer questions about code, such as summarizing modules or locating specific functions. 🛠️ The Docker MCP Toolkit streamlines setup and integration, making development faster and more efficient. By using Docker Compose, the environment remains consistent across all stages of development. #AI #Docker #MCPToolkit&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker @ Black Hat 2025: CVEs have everyone’s attention, here’s the path forward</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5119/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At Black Hat 2025, CVEs were a hot topic, highlighting the need for effective vulnerability management. The focus is shifting from just scanning to eliminating security debt before it enters the software supply chain. Hardened images and compliance-ready tools are becoming essential. Key themes included the importance of secure starting points, customization for enterprises, and the demand for FedRAMP-ready solutions. Thanks to everyone who joined the Docker community at our booth and the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A practitioner’s view on how Docker enables security by default and makes developers work better</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5120/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5120/</guid>
      <description>Docker Captains share their experiences on how Docker enhances security and developer efficiency. Security in distributed systems is crucial, and Docker provides a strong framework for developers and security teams. Key areas of focus include managing artifacts, code quality, and vulnerability management. For more insights on becoming a Docker Captain, visit the Docker Captains’ website! 🛠️🔒 #Docker #Security #DevOps #ContainerSecurity #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop 4.44: Smarter AI Modeling, Platform Stability, and Streamlined Kubernetes Workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5121/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5121/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker Desktop 4.44 introduces key updates for developers. The new Docker Model Runner allows users to inspect AI inference requests and responses directly, enhancing transparency and debugging. This feature aids in troubleshooting workflows, especially for AI/LLM applications. Real-time resource checks are now available to prevent system slowdowns when running multiple models. Additionally, Goose and Gemini CLI are supported as MCP clients, streamlining connections to over 140 MCP servers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The GitHub Prompt Injection Data Heist</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5122/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5122/</guid>
      <description>🚨 In Part 3 of the MCP Horror Stories series, we explore the GitHub Prompt Injection Data Heist. This incident highlights critical vulnerabilities in AI security, revealing how attackers can manipulate AI assistants through malicious GitHub issues. When developers request help, they risk exposing sensitive data from locked repositories. Learn how these attacks exploit broad GitHub tokens and bypass traditional access controls. Docker’s MCP Toolkit offers solutions to protect against such&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GPT-5 Launch Broke the AI Internet (And Not in a Good Way)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4956/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4956/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The launch of GPT-5 by OpenAI caused significant disruption in the AI app ecosystem. Many applications failed overnight due to the unexpected removal of older APIs. Developers are reminded that relying too heavily on a single provider or model can lead to system failures. The interconnected nature of AI applications means that even small changes can have wide-reaching impacts. As the landscape evolves, it’s crucial to build resilient systems. Developers should prepare for sudden changes by&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI agents made easy with Goose and Docker</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4957/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4957/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Building AI agents can be simplified with the right tools and frameworks. Key components include selecting an AI backend, configuring accessible tools, and integrating business logic for specific use cases. This article explores using Goose, Docker, and the MCP protocol to create an agent that summarizes YouTube videos. With Docker Model Runner, you can run AI locally for enhanced privacy. For more details, check the GitHub repository: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/shelajev/hani&#34;&gt;https://github.com/shelajev/hani&lt;/a&gt;. #AIAgents #Docker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tooling ≠ Glue: Why changing AI workflows still feels like duct tape</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4852/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4852/</guid>
      <description>Modern AI development presents a contradiction. While we have advanced tools and frameworks like LangChain and Hugging Face, replacing components often leads to system failures. 🔧 The expectation was for modular workflows, but instead, we face a fragmented landscape. Each tool has different assumptions, making integration challenging and time-consuming. 🕒 Abstractions often leak, complicating even simple tasks. What should be seamless can turn into complex issues, leaving developers to write&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remocal and Minimum Viable Models: Why Right-Sized Models Beat API Overkill</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-09-4802/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-09-4802/</guid>
      <description>💡 Discover a new approach to AI development with Remocal and Minimum Viable Models! Many businesses face high costs and latency issues from API-dependent AI. For example, a simple sentiment analyzer can cost $847/month and take 2.3 seconds per review. Remocal combines local and cloud resources, allowing developers to work efficiently without the hassle of complex cloud setups. This method makes AI development more affordable and speeds up iteration. Minimum Viable Models (MVM) focus on using&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Recipe AI Agent with Koog and Docker</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4762/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:23:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4762/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into the world of AI with Philippe Charriere’s latest blog post on building a recipe AI agent using JetBrains’ Koog and Docker. He details the integration of Koog with Docker Model Runner for creating a specialized agent for ratatouille recipes. Key tools include Docker Compose and the Docker MCP Gateway. For those interested in hands-on learning, the post outlines project setup using IntelliJ IDEA, Gradle, and Docker configurations. Explore the details to enhance your AI skills! 🍳📦&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The Supply Chain Attack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4763/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4763/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Part 2 of our MCP Horror Stories series highlights a critical supply chain attack affecting AI development environments. The article discusses CVE-2025-6514, where a vulnerability in mcp-remote led to credential compromise and remote code execution. This incident impacted nearly 437,000 environments, including major platforms like Cloudflare and Hugging Face. Learn about the attack techniques used, the importance of containerized MCP servers, and practical steps to secure your AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating FedRAMP Compliance with Docker Hardened Images</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4147/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4147/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Navigating FedRAMP compliance can be costly and time-consuming, often taking 12-18 months and over $2 million. Competitors are already moving ahead while you manage security controls. Docker has introduced Hardened Images (DHI) to streamline this process. These pre-configured images support FIPS 140 compliance, simplifying cryptographic requirements. With DHI, companies can reduce compliance costs and speed up time-to-market for cloud services. 💻🔒 #FedRAMP #Docker #CloudCompliance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Next Evolution of Docker Hardened Images: Customizable, FedRAMP Ready, AI Migration Agent, and Deeper Integrations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4148/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4148/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker Hardened Images (DHI) have seen rapid adoption since their launch in May, helping organizations achieve near-zero CVEs and secure their software supply chains. 🔒 The latest enhancements include a broader image catalog, customizable options, and an AI migration agent. These updates will be showcased at Black Hat 2025. 🛠️ DHI now supports full-stack systems with trusted, production-ready images, ensuring security without hindering developer speed. #Docker #Cybersecurity #DevOps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone’s a Snowflake: Designing Hardened Image Processes for the Real World</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2015/</guid>
      <description>Hardened container images and distroless software are gaining traction among startups and established companies. While they promise a smaller attack surface and operational simplicity, challenges arise in real-world applications. The unique needs of development teams often clash with rigid security measures, leading to frustration and workarounds. This &amp;lsquo;Snowflake Problem&amp;rsquo; highlights how no two environments are the same, complicating the balance between usability and security. Flexibility is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Docker MCP Toolkit Works with VS Code Copilot Agent Mode</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 20:10:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2016/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of your development workflow! 🚀 The article explores how Docker&amp;rsquo;s Model Context Protocol (MCP) Toolkit integrates with VS Code’s GitHub Copilot Agent Mode. This combination enhances productivity by allowing autonomous coding workflows with improved security and automation. Key features of the MCP Toolkit include modular components for various tasks and strict access controls for security. 🛡️ For a step-by-step setup guide, check out the article to get started with these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Questions: What You Should Really Be Asking Your Hardened Image Provider Before You Press the Buy Button</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2017/</guid>
      <description>When considering hardened image providers, it’s essential to go beyond buzzwords like &amp;ldquo;zero-CVE.&amp;rdquo; Understanding their update and patch management processes is crucial. Ask how quickly they can respond to serious vulnerabilities and their SLAs on updates. Also, inquire about their modification processes. Knowing how to adjust images without compromising security is vital for maintaining your workflows. For more insights on essential questions to ask, check the full article. 🔍💻 #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GenAI vs. Agentic AI: What Developers Need to Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2018/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Generative AI (GenAI) is transforming how developers create applications, focusing on content generation like text and images. In contrast, a new form, agentic AI, enables planning, reasoning, and multi-step actions, paving the way for intelligent, goal-driven systems. 💻 The article discusses the differences between GenAI and agentic AI, including their construction, challenges, and use cases. It highlights how developers can utilize Docker for building AI applications, offering insights on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The Security Issues Threatening AI Infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2019/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New Series Alert: MCP Horror Stories! 🚨 The first issue dives into the security vulnerabilities within the Model Context Protocol (MCP) ecosystem. MCP enables AI agents to communicate with various services, but this connectivity brings significant security risks. While MCP aims to streamline integrations, it has raised concerns about potential data breaches and system compromises due to malicious servers. Stay informed about the challenges in AI infrastructure! #AI #CyberSecurity #MCP&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
