<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NYT-Open-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/nyt-open-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in NYT-Open-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:30:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/nyt-open-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Designing a Digital New York Times Museum</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10966/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10966/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting project alert! Five interns from The New York Times designed a virtual museum to connect remote employees with the company&amp;rsquo;s rich history. They created a guided and interactive experience based on a real museum tour, highlighting key artifacts. Using 3D technology, they ensured users can navigate freely while learning about significant pieces of journalism. This innovative project earned them the 2025 iF Design Award and IDEA Bronze Prize! #DigitalDesign #NYTimes #VirtualMuseum&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling subscriptions at The New York Times with real-time causal machine learning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10413/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 15:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10413/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The New York Times has advanced its subscription strategy by implementing real-time causal machine learning algorithms. These algorithms enhance decision-making for paywalls and registration walls, optimizing access based on user behavior. This dynamic approach allows for personalized experiences, improving both subscription and registration rates. The collaboration between data science and business leadership is key to this success. 📈 #MachineLearning #DigitalMedia #NYTimes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New York Times Games’ Path to Dark Mode</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10079/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:25:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10079/</guid>
      <description>The New York Times Games team has been working on a much-requested Dark Mode feature, aimed at improving player experience, especially for nighttime gameplay. 🌙 Designing Dark Mode involved more than just inverting colors; it required careful consideration of accessibility and brand consistency across various games. The process revealed years of design complexities that needed addressing. To streamline development, the team focused on the Games app first, ensuring a cohesive user experience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
