<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Supabase-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/supabase-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Supabase-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 07:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/supabase-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introducing TRAE SOLO integration with Supabase</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-08-14297/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-08-14297/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! TRAE IDE now integrates seamlessly with Supabase. This integration allows users to manage their backend infrastructure directly within the IDE, streamlining workflows and reducing context switching. TRAE has gained over 6 million users globally and supports the full software development lifecycle. Explore how TRAE SOLO’s AI capabilities can enhance your coding experience! #TRAE #Supabase #DevCommunity #AI #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supabase Security Retro: 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14352/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14352/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://supabase.com/feed.xml&#34;&gt;Supabase Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://supabase.com/blog/supabase-security-2025-retro&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sync Stripe data to your Supabase database in one click</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14080/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14080/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Supabase now offers official support for the Stripe Sync Engine. With a simple one-click integration, you can sync your Stripe data directly into your Supabase database. This includes customers, subscriptions, invoices, and payments, all accessible via standard SQL. This integration is a result of collaboration between Supabase and Stripe, featuring enhancements like incremental sync and flexible JSONB storage. Syncing Stripe data allows for better revenue&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building ChatGPT Apps with Supabase Edge Functions and mcp-use</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13970/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13970/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover the new potential of ChatGPT with the Apps SDK! This article explains how to build a ChatGPT app that connects to a Supabase database using mcp-use and Edge Functions. Learn to create interactive widgets for exploring database schemas, viewing data, and running SQL queries. Transform your ChatGPT experience by integrating custom interfaces and external services! #ChatGPT #Supabase #AppDevelopment #TechInnovation #MCPUse</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Own Your Observability: Supabase Metrics API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13686/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13686/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Streamline your database monitoring with Supabase&amp;rsquo;s new Metrics API! You can now export your Supabase database telemetry into any Prometheus-compatible observability stack. This includes popular platforms like Grafana Cloud and Datadog. The API allows full control over monitoring, visualization, and alerting, enhancing your overall observability. 📊 Say goodbye to siloed metrics! Correlate API latency with database performance effortlessly. #Supabase #MetricsAPI #Observability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Supabase for Platforms</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13490/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13490/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Supabase has launched &amp;ldquo;Supabase for Platforms,&amp;rdquo; a white-label solution that allows platforms to manage backends for their users seamlessly. This initiative aims to simplify the development process for full-stack applications. Leading platforms like Lovable and Bolt.new are already utilizing this solution, enabling users to create millions of projects effortlessly. Supabase for Platforms is designed for any tool looking to offer managed backends. #Supabase&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Async Streaming to Postgres Foreign Data Wrappers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13426/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13426/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Supabase Wrappers is enhancing Postgres Foreign Data Wrappers (FDWs) by introducing asynchronous streaming! This update allows more efficient, memory-safe queries for large analytical workloads. Traditionally, FDWs operated synchronously, fetching all results or fixed-size batches, which could block the Postgres backend. With this new approach, users can expect improved performance in querying external databases. #Postgres #DataStreaming #Supabase #ForeignDataWrappers #DatabasePerformance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build &#34;Sign in with Your App&#34; using Supabase Auth</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13427/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13427/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Supabase Auth has expanded its capabilities! It&amp;rsquo;s now equipped with OAuth 2.1 and OpenID Connect, allowing your project to serve as an identity provider. This means AI agents can authenticate through your app using the Model Context Protocol (MCP), enhancing security and integration. Developers can now build on your platform easily, enabling secure API access and enterprise single sign-on. Explore the new possibilities with Supabase! 🔑✨ #Supabase #Auth #IdentityProvider #APISecurity #OAuth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Seven New Email Templates for Supabase Auth</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13382/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13382/</guid>
      <description>🔔 Exciting news for Supabase users! We have launched 7 new email notification templates for Supabase Auth. These templates aim to enhance account security by informing users about critical changes on their accounts. Users will receive alerts for actions such as password changes, email updates, and linked identities. Stay informed and safe! 🔒✉️ #Supabase #AccountSecurity #EmailNotifications #UserSafety #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new Supabase power for Kiro</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13383/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13383/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The latest update brings Supabase powers to Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Kiro IDE, enhancing your ability to build full-stack applications efficiently. With Kiro&amp;rsquo;s deep integration, you get access to your Supabase database schema, edge functions practices, and security guidelines for Row Level Security (RLS). This update allows for streamlined management of database schemas and offers one-click access to essential development tasks. Two new powers are available: one for hosted&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Analytics Buckets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13228/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13228/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Supabase has launched Analytics Buckets to enhance data storage for analytical workloads. These specialized storage options are built on Apache Iceberg and Amazon S3, using columnar Parquet format. They are designed for efficient data scans, aggregations, and time-series queries. Analytics Buckets enable cost-effective storage, offering savings of 30-90% compared to traditional database storage. They also support open table formats and allow for schema evolution without data rewriting&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Supabase ETL</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13229/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13229/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Supabase ETL! This new change-data-capture pipeline allows you to replicate Postgres tables to analytical destinations like Analytics Buckets and BigQuery in near real time. It captures changes including inserts, updates, and deletes seamlessly. Setup is quick via the Supabase Dashboard, and it&amp;rsquo;s open source on GitHub. Discover how separating OLTP and OLAP can improve data analytics performance! #SupabaseETL #DataAnalytics #OpenSource #BigQuery #Postgres</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Vector Buckets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13161/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13161/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Supabase! They have launched &lt;strong&gt;Vector Buckets&lt;/strong&gt;, a new storage option that combines durability with built-in similarity search. This feature offers an efficient way to manage large datasets, catering to modern app needs like semantic search and recommendations. You can now choose between &lt;strong&gt;pgvector&lt;/strong&gt; for smaller datasets or &lt;strong&gt;Vector Buckets&lt;/strong&gt; for storing millions of vectors seamlessly. Explore the potential of Vector Buckets today! 🌐🔍 #Supabase #VectorStorage&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supabase Launch Week 15 Hackathon Winner Announcement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5292/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5292/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Supabase Launch Week 15 has concluded, and we are excited to announce the winners of our Hackathon! The event showcased remarkable innovation from participants, demonstrating their technical skills. The standout project, &amp;ldquo;Figma AI Tickets&amp;rdquo; by vickywane, is a plugin that converts design tasks into actionable user stories using OpenAI’s GPT-4. Congratulations to all participants for their impressive submissions! 👏 #Supabase #Hackathon #Innovation #Figma #GPT4</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supabase Auth: Build vs. Buy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5293/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5293/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Understanding authentication is key for developers. While it’s essential in almost every app, it&amp;rsquo;s often not the main focus. Supabase Auth provides a ready-made solution, integrating directly with your Postgres database. It offers JWT-based security and seamless Row Level Security integration. Building your own authentication can lead to hidden costs, such as time and maintenance, which can divert resources from core development. Consider your options carefully! 🔒💻 #Supabase #Authentication&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
