<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Palantir-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/palantir-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Palantir-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:51:33 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/palantir-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Founder Mode: Mission Mode</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11027/</guid>
      <description>In the discussion of startup management, Noam Perski argues that &amp;ldquo;Mission Mode&amp;rdquo; is essential for addressing critical problems. Unlike Paul Graham&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Founder Mode,&amp;rdquo; which emphasizes founder involvement, mission mode prioritizes organizing around customer needs. It requires every team member to work with urgency, focusing on meaningful outcomes. Perski highlights that companies like Palantir have successfully employed this approach for two decades, tackling complex challenges by embedding&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10626/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10626/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Palantir Technologies provides software platforms for data and AI, assisting various sectors including defense, healthcare, and finance. 🛡️ The company emphasizes privacy, ensuring clients maintain full ownership and control over their data. Palantir is not a data broker and does not sell or use client data for its own purposes. 📊 With advanced security and governance tools, Palantir helps organizations optimize operations while adhering to global regulations. For more information, visit&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the AIPCon 8 Demos Redefining the Future of Enterprise AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10393/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 21:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10393/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AIPCon 8 showcased transformative AI applications across various industries, highlighting real-world solutions at Palantir&amp;rsquo;s recent conference. From healthcare to motorsport, demos featured innovations like Andretti&amp;rsquo;s RaceOS for rapid data-driven decisions and Nebraska Medicine&amp;rsquo;s automated documentation for efficient revenue cycle management. These advancements illustrate how AI can solve operational challenges and enhance efficiency. #EnterpriseAI #AIPCon8 #Innovation #Healthcare #Motorsport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Palantir’s Strategic Privacy Investments Enable Future Customer Success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10080/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10080/</guid>
      <description>Palantir is enhancing customer success through strategic privacy investments in its software platforms. Their tools, like granular access controls and data lineage, ensure sensitive data is handled securely. A key feature, Checkpoints, allows users to provide purpose justification for sensitive actions, improving compliance and governance. Checkpoints integrate with over 60 actions, helping organizations meet regulatory requirements and manage AI workflows effectively. Learn how these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>À propos de Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9973/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9973/</guid>
      <description>Palantir Technologies, fondée en 2003 et basée à Denver, fournit des plateformes de gestion de données et d&amp;rsquo;intelligence artificielle. 🤖 Les logiciels de Palantir sont utilisés dans plus de 50 secteurs, aidant des clients dans le public et le privé, comme des agences gouvernementales et des entreprises. Ils intègrent des données variées dans un environnement sécurisé. 🔒 Palantir s&amp;rsquo;engage à respecter la confidentialité et la sécurité des données de ses clients, qui conservent le contrôle total&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defensive Databases: Optimizing Index-Refresh Semantics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9936/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 16:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9936/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Palantir&amp;rsquo;s Foundations team is enhancing Elasticsearch (ES) to boost stability without forking the source code. This post discusses how they customize ES by optimizing indexing refresh semantics to avoid bad access patterns. With over 300 ES clusters in various environments, maintaining reliability is crucial. The team aims to share insights with the Elastic community for potential improvements in the mainline offering. 🔗 Read more about their approach and solutions in the full article!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correcting the Record: Response to the Recent American Conservative Article on Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9710/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 20:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9710/</guid>
      <description>Palantir addresses recent allegations from the American Conservative questioning its commitment to privacy and civil liberties. The response clarifies that Palantir is not a surveillance company and does not engage in or promote unlawful surveillance practices. The article misrepresents Palantir&amp;rsquo;s work with intelligence agencies, particularly regarding claims related to the NSA&amp;rsquo;s XKEYSCORE tool. Palantir emphasizes its dedication to privacy laws and governance safeguards, ensuring that its&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5052/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5052/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Interested in Palantir? Here’s a quick overview! Palantir Technologies, founded in 2003 and headquartered in Denver, offers software for data operations and AI infrastructure. Their solutions support organizations in various sectors, including defense, healthcare, and finance. Their platforms integrate diverse data sources to enhance decision-making, while ensuring customer data remains secure and controlled. Notably, Palantir does not act as a data collector or broker. For more insights,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling On-Prem Security at Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5053/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5053/</guid>
      <description>Palantir emphasizes security in its on-premises solutions, tailoring approaches for various environments. 🌐 The Insight tool enhances security by automating checks on server configurations, ensuring compliance with rigorous standards. It allows users to run scans and generate reports easily. 📊 With the integration of Foundry and Apollo, Palantir streamlines the review process, improving visibility and collaboration. 🔍 Learn more about how Palantir maintains security across thousands of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America’s AI Action Plan</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-500/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-500/</guid>
      <description>🚀 On July 23, 2025, the White House released &amp;ldquo;Winning the AI Race: America’s AI Action Plan,&amp;rdquo; aiming to boost U.S. leadership in AI through 90+ federal policy actions. Key focuses include: - Promoting commercial AI solutions in federal procurement, especially for the DoD. - Streamlining processes for AI system approvals and leveraging existing platforms like Maven and Army Vantage. The plan emphasizes the role of testbeds for efficient AI deployment, ensuring systems meet mission-critical&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
