<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Palantir-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/palantir-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Palantir-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:38:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/palantir-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Correcting the Record: Response to the EFF January 15, 2026 Report on Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-27-14924/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 17:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-27-14924/</guid>
      <description>Palantir addresses claims made by the Electronic Frontier Foundation (EFF) regarding its work with Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE) in a recent blog post. The response highlights that EFF&amp;rsquo;s report contains misleading statements and inaccuracies about Palantir&amp;rsquo;s role and practices. Palantir emphasizes its commitment to transparency and clarifies that it does not manage a master database for surveillance purposes. The company invites further dialogue to correct misconceptions and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Managing and Securing VS Code Extensions at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-23-14802/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 15:33:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-23-14802/</guid>
      <description>Palantir&amp;rsquo;s InfoSec team discusses their approach to managing VS Code extensions securely. They highlight the security risks posed by extensions, which enhance productivity but can also lead to vulnerabilities. Their journey began with insights from browser extension management and emphasizes the need for careful oversight without hindering developer workflows. Key findings revealed many users were unaware of their installed extensions, prompting the need for better visibility and security&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Agents in Production (Agentic Runtime, #1)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14760/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14760/</guid>
      <description>🔍 The first article in the series about Palantir AIP&amp;rsquo;s Agentic Runtime explores how it secures agents in critical operations. Key points include: - &lt;strong&gt;Secure Access:&lt;/strong&gt; The design ensures stable performance and access control for various large language models. - &lt;strong&gt;Orchestrated Execution:&lt;/strong&gt; Agent orchestration is isolated and managed through a secure infrastructure. - &lt;strong&gt;Policy Enforcement:&lt;/strong&gt; Granular policies govern memory types and tool usage. - &lt;strong&gt;Real-Time Monitoring:&lt;/strong&gt; Comprehensive&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publikacja fałszywych twierdzeń nt. Palantira i Rządu Szwajcarskiego przez czasopismo Die Republik</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14318/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 16:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14318/</guid>
      <description>📢 Recently, the magazine Die Republik published claims about Palantir&amp;rsquo;s relationship with the Swiss government. Palantir clarified that these assertions misrepresent its interactions, stating it never submitted formal offers for government contracts. The company emphasizes the absence of any official assessment of its software by Swiss authorities. Palantir encourages open dialogue to address concerns and promote transparency in technology discussions. 🤝💻 #Palantir #Switzerland #Technology&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Era of Defense Innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14065/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 17:21:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14065/</guid>
      <description>The U.S. defense industrial base is on the brink of significant change. The Trump administration and Congress are addressing issues in defense procurement, aiming to enhance military efficiency and innovation. The recently passed FY2026 National Defense Authorization Act (NDAA) introduces major reforms, focusing on a Commercial-First Procurement Framework. This approach prioritizes commercial products to improve competition and access to technology for our warfighters. Key reforms also&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Korrektur: Wie das Online-Magazin Die Republik einen Regierungsbericht zu Palantir verdrehte</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:47:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14013/</guid>
      <description>An article in Republik misrepresents Palantir&amp;rsquo;s engagement with the Swiss government, suggesting a failed campaign for contracts. Palantir clarifies that it never submitted formal bids and was not contacted during the report&amp;rsquo;s creation. The piece raises concerns about ethics and technology without direct evaluation of Palantir’s capabilities. It emphasizes the need for factual discourse to avoid misconceptions about technology procurement. For accurate information on Palantir&amp;rsquo;s role and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Palantir and L3Harris</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13649/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:55:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13649/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Palantir and L3Harris are collaborating to enhance America&amp;rsquo;s defense capabilities through AI-driven production. Since 2023, their partnership has focused on rebuilding the defense industrial base to ensure rapid reindustrialization. Key initiatives include AI-powered tools like MRPSpeed for efficient production of night vision goggles and AI-enabled supply chain resilience. These innovations aim to optimize operations and decision-making at all levels. Their joint efforts extend to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Trust at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13438/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 14:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13438/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Palantir introduces “audit.3,” a next-generation audit logging system enhancing transparency and accountability across its platforms. This evolution aims to provide quicker, structured logs, vital for organizations managing sensitive data. Comprehensive audit logging helps security teams investigate incidents and ensures compliance. 📊 The new system improves log accessibility and consistency, allowing for real-time data analysis, boosting trust in the handling of sensitive information&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Infrastructure and Ontology</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11377/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11377/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from NVIDIA and Palantir! They have announced a partnership to integrate NVIDIA models with Palantir&amp;rsquo;s AI platform, enhancing enterprise decision-making. Key offerings include the NVIDIA Nemotron Super model and the NeMo Retriever, which support advanced AI applications. This collaboration aims to improve operations across industries, with Lowe’s already benefiting from enhanced supply chain optimization. The integration also promises to accelerate scientific research,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the AIPCon 8 Demos Transforming Manufacturing, Insurance, and Construction</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11254/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11254/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AIPCon 8 showcased how AI is reshaping manufacturing, insurance, and construction. 🌟 Companies like Ursa Major are transforming traditional workflows into automated, intelligent systems that enhance efficiency and accuracy. 📈 From automated insurance underwriting to streamlined construction operations, these implementations highlight the power of enterprise AI in real-world applications. 🔍 Discover how organizations are building new operating models tailored to their specific needs! #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Acerca de Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11239/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:18:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11239/</guid>
      <description>Palantir Technologies, fundada en 2003, es una empresa de software con sede en Denver que ofrece plataformas para la gestión de datos e inteligencia artificial. Su software es utilizado en más de 50 sectores, incluyendo el público y privado. 🏢💻 Colaboran con organismos como el Departamento de Defensa de EE. UU. y ONGs, ayudando a integrar y analizar datos de manera segura y eficiente. Palantir enfatiza la privacidad y el control de datos, asegurando que los clientes mantengan la propiedad de&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Founder Mode: Mission Mode</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11027/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11027/</guid>
      <description>In the discussion of startup management, Noam Perski argues that &amp;ldquo;Mission Mode&amp;rdquo; is essential for addressing critical problems. Unlike Paul Graham&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Founder Mode,&amp;rdquo; which emphasizes founder involvement, mission mode prioritizes organizing around customer needs. It requires every team member to work with urgency, focusing on meaningful outcomes. Perski highlights that companies like Palantir have successfully employed this approach for two decades, tackling complex challenges by embedding&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10626/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10626/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Palantir Technologies provides software platforms for data and AI, assisting various sectors including defense, healthcare, and finance. 🛡️ The company emphasizes privacy, ensuring clients maintain full ownership and control over their data. Palantir is not a data broker and does not sell or use client data for its own purposes. 📊 With advanced security and governance tools, Palantir helps organizations optimize operations while adhering to global regulations. For more information, visit&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the AIPCon 8 Demos Redefining the Future of Enterprise AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10393/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 21:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10393/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AIPCon 8 showcased transformative AI applications across various industries, highlighting real-world solutions at Palantir&amp;rsquo;s recent conference. From healthcare to motorsport, demos featured innovations like Andretti&amp;rsquo;s RaceOS for rapid data-driven decisions and Nebraska Medicine&amp;rsquo;s automated documentation for efficient revenue cycle management. These advancements illustrate how AI can solve operational challenges and enhance efficiency. #EnterpriseAI #AIPCon8 #Innovation #Healthcare #Motorsport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Palantir’s Strategic Privacy Investments Enable Future Customer Success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10080/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10080/</guid>
      <description>Palantir is enhancing customer success through strategic privacy investments in its software platforms. Their tools, like granular access controls and data lineage, ensure sensitive data is handled securely. A key feature, Checkpoints, allows users to provide purpose justification for sensitive actions, improving compliance and governance. Checkpoints integrate with over 60 actions, helping organizations meet regulatory requirements and manage AI workflows effectively. Learn how these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>À propos de Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9973/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:15:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9973/</guid>
      <description>Palantir Technologies, fondée en 2003 et basée à Denver, fournit des plateformes de gestion de données et d&amp;rsquo;intelligence artificielle. 🤖 Les logiciels de Palantir sont utilisés dans plus de 50 secteurs, aidant des clients dans le public et le privé, comme des agences gouvernementales et des entreprises. Ils intègrent des données variées dans un environnement sécurisé. 🔒 Palantir s&amp;rsquo;engage à respecter la confidentialité et la sécurité des données de ses clients, qui conservent le contrôle total&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defensive Databases: Optimizing Index-Refresh Semantics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9936/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 16:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9936/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Palantir&amp;rsquo;s Foundations team is enhancing Elasticsearch (ES) to boost stability without forking the source code. This post discusses how they customize ES by optimizing indexing refresh semantics to avoid bad access patterns. With over 300 ES clusters in various environments, maintaining reliability is crucial. The team aims to share insights with the Elastic community for potential improvements in the mainline offering. 🔗 Read more about their approach and solutions in the full article!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correcting the Record: Response to the Recent American Conservative Article on Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9710/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 20:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9710/</guid>
      <description>Palantir addresses recent allegations from the American Conservative questioning its commitment to privacy and civil liberties. The response clarifies that Palantir is not a surveillance company and does not engage in or promote unlawful surveillance practices. The article misrepresents Palantir&amp;rsquo;s work with intelligence agencies, particularly regarding claims related to the NSA&amp;rsquo;s XKEYSCORE tool. Palantir emphasizes its dedication to privacy laws and governance safeguards, ensuring that its&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5052/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5052/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Interested in Palantir? Here’s a quick overview! Palantir Technologies, founded in 2003 and headquartered in Denver, offers software for data operations and AI infrastructure. Their solutions support organizations in various sectors, including defense, healthcare, and finance. Their platforms integrate diverse data sources to enhance decision-making, while ensuring customer data remains secure and controlled. Notably, Palantir does not act as a data collector or broker. For more insights,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling On-Prem Security at Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5053/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5053/</guid>
      <description>Palantir emphasizes security in its on-premises solutions, tailoring approaches for various environments. 🌐 The Insight tool enhances security by automating checks on server configurations, ensuring compliance with rigorous standards. It allows users to run scans and generate reports easily. 📊 With the integration of Foundry and Apollo, Palantir streamlines the review process, improving visibility and collaboration. 🔍 Learn more about how Palantir maintains security across thousands of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America’s AI Action Plan</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-500/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-500/</guid>
      <description>🚀 On July 23, 2025, the White House released &amp;ldquo;Winning the AI Race: America’s AI Action Plan,&amp;rdquo; aiming to boost U.S. leadership in AI through 90+ federal policy actions. Key focuses include: - Promoting commercial AI solutions in federal procurement, especially for the DoD. - Streamlining processes for AI system approvals and leveraging existing platforms like Maven and Army Vantage. The plan emphasizes the role of testbeds for efficient AI deployment, ensuring systems meet mission-critical&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
