<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Auth0-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/auth0-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Auth0-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/auth0-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FastAPI Best Practices</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-23-14820/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-23-14820/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of FastAPI with essential best practices! 🚀 This article explores architectural patterns and testing strategies to transform a simple script into a scalable FastAPI application. It highlights the framework&amp;rsquo;s rise due to its ease of use and powerful features. Understanding REST API design and correct HTTP verbs is crucial for consistency and usability. For developers ready to elevate their skills, check out the official documentation and advanced security examples! 🔍💻&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Broken Access Control Still Dominates the OWASP Top 10 in 2026?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14769/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14769/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Broken Access Control (BAC) remains the top security risk in the OWASP Top 10 for web applications, as confirmed in recent reports. This issue persists due to its nature as a logical vulnerability, making it difficult for automated tools to detect. Unlike technical vulnerabilities, BAC and Broken Object Level Authorization (BOLA) involve semantic flaws in how access is managed. Effective solutions require understanding these complexities and implementing best practices for access control&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Third-Party Tool Calling in LlamaIndex Using Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-21-14721/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-21-14721/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Learn how to securely call third-party tools in LlamaIndex using Auth0 Token Vault. This method allows applications to act on behalf of users without exposing sensitive tokens. The article outlines two calling types: system-level and user-level. User-level calling is enhanced by OAuth 2.0, enabling access to user-specific resources like emails and messages. 📧 Discover how to integrate these features into applications like “Teacher’s Aide,” which helps teachers manage classes and students&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Auth0 Tenant Access Control List Empowers Customers Under Fire</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-20-14677/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-20-14677/</guid>
      <description>In September 2025, Auth0 launched the Tenant Access Control List (ACL), a feature designed to manage and filter traffic to its services. One Auth0 customer effectively used Tenant ACL to combat a fake signup attack that generated over 21 million illegitimate requests. Initially, the customer blocked malicious traffic with help from Auth0 support. However, the attackers quickly adapted, leading to interruptions for legitimate users. By leveraging Tenant ACL, the customer was able to respond&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Did My Auth0 Bill Change? A Guide to Proration, Discounts, and Upgrades</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14621/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14621/</guid>
      <description>Understanding unexpected changes in your Auth0 bill? Here’s a quick overview: 🔍 &lt;strong&gt;Three-Month Rule&lt;/strong&gt;: Auth0 auto-upgrades your plan if you exceed usage limits for three consecutive months, ensuring uninterrupted access. 📊 &lt;strong&gt;Mid-Cycle Changes&lt;/strong&gt;: Upgrading or adding features mid-cycle results in prorated charges, reflecting your usage. To manage your billing, regularly audit your user volume, traffic, and integrations. #Auth0 #Billing #CloudServices #UsageAudit #TechFinance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The API Authorization Hierarchy of Needs: Why You Aren’t Ready for AI Agents Yet</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14568/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14568/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking AI agents in your application isn’t as simple as it seems. 🛠️ The article outlines the API Authorization Hierarchy of Needs, emphasizing the importance of a mature authorization system before integrating AI. Level 1 focuses on application-level authorization for humans, ensuring data isolation and granular roles. Level 2 introduces service accounts for machine-to-machine interactions, allowing automated tasks. Understanding these levels is crucial for secure agentic workflows. 🔐 #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Brand Identity Simplified with Auth0 Multiple Custom Domains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14519/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14519/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Managing multiple brands just got easier with Auth0&amp;rsquo;s Multiple Custom Domains feature! This tool allows businesses to streamline user experiences across various applications from a single tenant. It enables efficient management of distinct custom domains while maintaining a unified user store. With MCD, brands can customize user experiences and maintain brand integrity during login processes. Learn more about simplifying multi-brand identity management! 🔑✨ #Auth0 #IdentityManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Implement Google One Tap in React with Auth0 and FedCM</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14476/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14476/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn how to integrate Google One Tap in your React app using Auth0 and FedCM! This guide covers setting up Sign-in with Google, providing a simple authentication method for your users. Google One Tap allows easy sign-in with just one tap, enhancing user experience on both mobile and desktop. FedCM is a key component, offering a privacy-focused method for identity federation without relying on third-party cookies. For detailed steps, check out the full article! #GoogleOneTap #React #Auth0&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming P99s in OpenFGA: How We Built a Self-Tuning Strategy Planner</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-09-14375/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-09-14375/</guid>
      <description>🚀 OpenFGA has significantly reduced P99 latency by 98% using a self-tuning strategy planner! Initially, static rules were used for graph traversals, but the need for a dynamic solution became clear. The new planner adapts to real-time data, selecting the best traversal strategies based on individual graph complexities. This evolution allows continuous updates and improves performance as data distributions change. #OpenFGA #LatencyReduction #GraphTraversal #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fact or Fiction: Eight Myths About Auth0 For B2B</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-08-14356/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-08-14356/</guid>
      <description>Explore the truth behind common myths about Auth0 for B2B applications! 🛠️ This article addresses eight misconceptions related to multi-tenancy, SSO, and security features. Many assumptions stem from outdated information, leading to misunderstandings about Auth0&amp;rsquo;s capabilities. Key points include that Auth0 was built for B2B use and supports true multi-tenancy without custom solutions. Companies transitioning from B2C can easily adapt to B2B by leveraging its infrastructure. 📈 Stay informed&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model Context Protocol Nov 2025 Specification Update: CIMD, XAA, and Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14305/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14305/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The November 2025 update to the Model Context Protocol (MCP) introduces key changes aimed at enhancing AI agent security. 📄 Client Identity Metadata Documents (CIMD) streamline how clients identify themselves to servers, replacing manual registrations with a cleaner URL-based approach. This shift enhances trust through DNS and HTTPS. 🔒 Additionally, Cross App Access (XAA) allows organizations to manage authorization centrally, reducing user consent fatigue and improving security visibility&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an AI Assistant with LangGraph, Next.js, and Auth0 Connected Accounts</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14066/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14066/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Enhance your AI assistant with LangGraph, Next.js, and Auth0! This article guides you through integrating Slack and GitHub using Auth0’s Connected Accounts feature. You’ll learn to list channels, interact with workspaces, and access GitHub repositories. Make sure you have the necessary tools and access before starting! #AI #LangGraph #NextJS #Auth0 #TechTutorials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why MCP’s Move Away from Server-Sent Events Simplifies Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14057/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14057/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Model Context Protocol (MCP) has deprecated Server-Sent Events (SSE) in favor of Streamable HTTP. This decision aims to enhance security for developers, especially in Identity and Security fields. 🔒 SSE&amp;rsquo;s persistent connections posed risks, allowing traffic to flow without ongoing checks. Streamable HTTP simplifies communication, using a single endpoint and improving authentication practices. 💻 This shift supports stronger CORS policies and secure session management, making it a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulletproof Hosting Defense: Mitigating the Proxy Threat with Threat Intelligence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14024/</guid>
      <description>Bulletproof Hosting (BPH) providers pose significant risks by offering infrastructure that abusers exploit. They allow attackers to mask their origins, making it easier to conduct credential stuffing attacks on IAM systems. The Joint Ransomware Task Force (JRTF) has released a guide to help network defenders manage traffic from these providers. Importantly, this information can aid IAM teams in protecting applications from fraud. Auth0 leverages its extensive experience in securing billions&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 My Account API: Let Users Manage Their Own Account</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14003/</guid>
      <description>🔑 The Auth0 My Account API allows users to manage their accounts directly, simplifying self-service actions like profile updates and Multi-Factor Authentication enrollment. By using access tokens from the standard login process, it eliminates the need for complex server-side components, enhancing security and streamlining development. To start using the API, it must be activated in the Auth0 dashboard. #Auth0 #UserManagement #APISecurity #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Authorization Testing: FGA, GitHub Actions, and CI/CD</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13941/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13941/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Explore how to maintain consistent authorization confidence in your applications! This article discusses the importance of automating testing in CI/CD pipelines using OpenFGA and GitHub Actions. As authorization models grow complex, manual checks become inefficient and error-prone. It outlines defining OpenFGA test files and integrating them into your workflow to ensure secure code changes before production. Learn about the core components of OpenFGA and how to structure your authorization&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAPI for Developers: Here Is Your Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13826/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13826/</guid>
      <description>📢 A new ebook, &amp;ldquo;A Developer’s Guide to FAPI,&amp;rdquo; is now available! This resource explains the importance of FAPI for regulated industries and how it enhances security beyond OAuth bearer tokens. FAPI introduces rigorous security protocols that help protect high-stakes data, shifting from a passive to an active identity verification model. It emphasizes secure access tokens through Mutual TLS (mTLS) and Demonstration of Proof-of-Possession (DPoP). Learn more about implementing these standards for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Accessible Guide to WCAG 3.3.9: Going for Gold</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13827/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 10:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13827/</guid>
      <description>WCAG 3.3.9 enhances web accessibility by removing exceptions from WCAG 3.3.8. While 3.3.8 set minimum standards for accessible authentication, 3.3.9 eliminates cognitive tests like object recognition and personal content selection. This aims to support users with severe cognitive impairments more effectively. Understanding these levels is crucial: Level AA compliance is a legal baseline, while Level AAA represents a gold standard for accessibility. #WebAccessibility #WCAG #InclusiveDesign&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Honeypots: A Simple Trap for Spam Registration Bots</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13562/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13562/</guid>
      <description>🚫 Spam registrations can distort user analytics and disrupt experiences. To combat this issue, the article highlights the use of honeypots as a simple yet effective defense. By implementing a honeypot trap with Auth0 Universal Login, you can deter spam bots without compromising user experience. The Swiss Cheese Model emphasizes a layered defense approach to mitigate risks from automated threats. With bad bots now making up 37% of internet traffic, a proactive strategy is essential. Explore&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Auth0 ASP.NET SDK to Secure Your API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13496/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13496/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for ASP.NET developers! Auth0 has launched its new ASP.NET Core Authentication SDK, designed to enhance API security. This SDK simplifies the integration of token validation and authorization, making it easier to secure your services. Key features include: - Full JWT Bearer functionality - Built-in DPoP support for improved security - Flexible configuration options - Zero lock-in for seamless updates Get started today by downloading the SDK from NuGet! #APISecurity #Auth0&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Add Sign in with Vercel to Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13446/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13446/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Integrating &amp;ldquo;Sign in with Vercel&amp;rdquo; to Auth0 enhances user login experiences by allowing seamless access using existing Vercel identities. 🔑 This article outlines the steps to implement this feature, starting with setting up the Vercel app and obtaining necessary credentials. 📜 A custom OAuth2 connection is utilized, culminating in a “Continue with Vercel” button on the Auth0 Universal Login page. #Auth0 #Vercel #OAuth2 #UserExperience #WebDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Startups can Leverage Auth0’s B2B Capabilities</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13386/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13386/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Startups can enhance their B2B SaaS offerings by leveraging Auth0’s capabilities. The Auth0 for Startups program provides tools like multi-tenancy, which allows distinct user management for each business customer. This ensures a tailored experience with features such as Single Sign-On and custom branding. Key benefits include support for up to 100,000 active users, inbound SCIM, and more. Explore how you can secure and customize access for your business clients! 🔒✨ #B2B #SaaS #Startups&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next.js 16: What’s New for Authentication and Authorization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13175/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Next.js 16 introduces key updates for authentication and authorization, enhancing security for developers. The framework now features a renamed middleware file, changing from middleware.ts to proxy.ts. This change clarifies its role as a routing layer, streamlining request interception. With the new proxy.ts, developers can implement lightweight authentication checks effectively. However, complex session management and authorization should be handled closer to data. #Nextjs16&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 MAU Explained: How to Calculate and Optimize Your Costs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13126/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13126/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Auth0’s Monthly Active Users (MAU) is key for optimizing costs. An MAU is defined as a user who logs in or refreshes a token within a month. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that MAUs are calculated per tenant, meaning a user across multiple tenants counts as multiple MAUs. To manage your MAU count effectively, consider these tips: 1️⃣ Optimize automated testing strategies 2️⃣ Implement Single Sign-On (SSO) 3️⃣ Use account linking Maximize the value of your current plan! 💻🔍 #Auth0&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying OAuth Security: State vs. Nonce vs. PKCE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13094/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13094/</guid>
      <description>Understanding OAuth security is essential for secure authentication. This article explains the differences between key parameters: state, nonce, and PKCE. Each plays a unique role in protecting against various attacks, like CSRF and code interception. The state parameter ensures the response is legitimate, while nonce and PKCE add additional layers of security. Learn how these components work together to safeguard your applications. 🔐💻 #OAuth #Cybersecurity #WebDevelopment #Authentication #PKCE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiding Prompts in Plain Sight: A New AI Security Risk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13071/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13071/</guid>
      <description>🔍 AI is transforming our web interactions, but with this advancement comes new security risks. Prompt injection vulnerabilities are now a top concern, especially with the rise of AI browsers. These can occur directly through manipulated inputs or indirectly via hidden queries in external content. As AI becomes more autonomous, indirect prompt injections pose significant threats that may go unnoticed until it&amp;rsquo;s too late. 🌐🔒 #AISecurity #PromptInjection #Cybersecurity #AIBrowsers #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Client ID Metadata Documents Are the Future of MCP Client Registration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13003/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13003/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Model Context Protocol (MCP) is shifting from Dynamic Client Registration (DCR) to Client ID Metadata Documents (CIMD) for enhanced security. DCR has proven complex and burdensome for large-scale systems. The new CIMD approach simplifies client-server connections by eliminating the need for stateful registration, addressing operational challenges effectively. This transition aims to streamline processes and improve security in open ecosystems. 🌐🔒 #CyberSecurity #MCP #ClientRegistration&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Auth0 Security Against Identity Attacks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12942/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12942/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Dive into our guide on enhancing Auth0 security against identity attacks! This resource highlights key areas to focus on, including misconfigurations, account fraud, MFA bypass, and token hijacking. It emphasizes the importance of proper configurations and proactive detection measures to safeguard your identity systems. Explore strategies to fortify your defenses and stay ahead of automated threats. #Auth0 #Cybersecurity #IdentityProtection #SecurityBestPractices #MFA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Your AI Agents: The Power is Already in Your Auth0 Plan</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12900/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12900/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Secure your AI agents with Auth0! Auth0 for AI Agents enhances your existing plan, enabling faster and secure AI authentication. This solution addresses gaps in traditional security, protecting against data leaks and compliance risks. With Auth0, focus on innovation while we manage security complexity. Enjoy seamless integration with popular AI frameworks like LangChain and Vercel AI SDK. #AI #Auth0 #DataSecurity #Innovation #TechSolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 for AI Agents is Now Generally Available (GA)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12852/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12852/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Auth0 for AI Agents is now generally available. This solution empowers developers to build secure AI agents while ensuring user data safety. It allows for user identification, controlled access to data, and human approval for key actions. Start integrating security into your AI projects today! 🔒🤖 #Auth0 #AI #DataSecurity #Innovation #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proactive Auth0 Security Posture via Real-Time Audit of Management API Logs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12169/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12169/</guid>
      <description>Stay ahead of security threats with proactive monitoring of your Auth0 Management API logs. 📊 Real-time audits help detect changes to critical defenses like MFA and Attack Protection, preventing configuration drift and maintaining a strong security posture. Auth0 Logs enable this essential threat detection, complementing tools like Checkmate for ongoing security monitoring. Learn how immediate awareness of modifications can protect your identity security. 🔒 #Auth0 #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 CLI: Leveling Up Your Developer Workflow with Powerful Enhancements</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12170/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12170/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates to the Auth0 CLI are here! The latest enhancements focus on usability and provide deeper API coverage. Developers can now manage Auth0 resources directly from the terminal with improved features. 🔍 Key updates include: - Complete configuration for Universal Login - Enhanced debugging with interactive logs - Streamlined user management - Support for CI/CD and Infrastructure as Code These improvements were influenced by community feedback, ensuring they address real developer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET 10: What’s New for Authentication and Authorization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12083/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12083/</guid>
      <description>🌟 .NET 10 introduces significant updates for authentication and authorization, designed to enhance application security. Key features include support for passkeys in ASP.NET Core Identity, offering a phishing-resistant alternative to passwords. This integration is aimed at improving user experience and security. Developers can easily configure passkey options to tailor the implementation to their needs. Discover the enhancements and how they can benefit your projects! 🔐💻 #DotNet10&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Three Laws of AI Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11930/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11930/</guid>
      <description>The article discusses adapting Asimov&amp;rsquo;s Three Laws of Robotics for modern AI security. As AI agents become more autonomous, they face new security challenges, particularly regarding data control and tool access. Unlike traditional programs, AI&amp;rsquo;s non-deterministic nature makes it unpredictable, raising concerns about reliability. Key questions emerge about granting AI tools access to sensitive information and actions without clear oversight. #AISecurity #AI #Asimov #DataProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trusting AI Output? Why Improper Output Handling is the New XSS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11931/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11931/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Are you trusting AI output? 🚨 Improper output handling can lead to serious vulnerabilities like XSS, SQL injection, and RCE. As developers integrate AI, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember: never trust the outputs from Large Language Models (LLMs) without proper validation. The OWASP Top 10 highlights this issue with LLM05, emphasizing that treating LLMs as trusted components can lead to significant security risks. Stay informed and safeguard your applications! 🔒 #CyberSecurity #AI #OWASP #LLM&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling Third-Party Access Tokens Securely in AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11708/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11708/</guid>
      <description>🔐 AI Agents are revolutionizing how we manage tasks by interacting with services like Google and GitHub. However, this opens up new security challenges. Developers must implement secure-by-design strategies to protect sensitive data and manage third-party access tokens effectively. This involves ensuring proper user authentication and securely storing access tokens. Maintaining high security while providing easy integration is essential. #AISecurity #DataProtection #TokenManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Log Detections for Credential Stuffing and MFA Exploit Prevention</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11547/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11547/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your security with eight crucial log detections for credential stuffing and MFA exploit prevention from Auth0. These detections are part of the Auth0 Detection Catalog, offering real-time insights and customizable monitoring for your SIEM. Key features include tracking abnormal login patterns and identifying sophisticated bot activity. Stay ahead of potential threats and protect your systems! 🔒🛡️ #CyberSecurity #Auth0 #CredentialStuffing #MFA #SecurityMonitoring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 for Scaling Apps: Advanced Security and Authentication</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11496/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11496/</guid>
      <description>Is your app outgrowing its authentication setup? 🚀 Auth0 identifies three key signs that indicate it&amp;rsquo;s time for an upgrade. 1️⃣ Stronger security is needed as your user base grows. Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) can enhance security without sacrificing user experience. 2️⃣ If you&amp;rsquo;re creating workarounds for user groups, consider Auth0 Organizations for a streamlined solution. Explore how Auth0 can help scale your app effectively. 🔐 #Auth0 #AppDevelopment #UserSecurity #Authentication&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MS Agent Framework and Python: Use the Auth0 Token Vault to Call Third-Party APIs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11446/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 11:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11446/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Explore how to build a secure AI-powered help desk application using Python! This article guides you through using the Microsoft Agent Framework, FastAPI, and Auth0 for authentication. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn to connect to the Gmail API for sending email notifications securely. Key prerequisites include Python 3.12+, an OpenAI API key, Google OAuth 2.0 access, and an Auth0 account. #Python #AI #FastAPI #Auth0 #GmailAPI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing AI Agents: Mitigate Excessive Agency with Zero Trust Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11314/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11314/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI agents are reshaping application development, offering powerful capabilities in task management. However, security risks like Excessive Agency pose significant challenges. Excessive Agency occurs when AI systems are given too many permissions, leading to unintended actions. This vulnerability is on the OWASP Top 10 list for LLMs and can lead to severe consequences in sensitive environments. To mitigate these risks, adopting a Zero Trust security model is crucial. This approach ensures AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social or Enterprise: Which Connection is Right?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11123/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11123/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the choice between Social and Enterprise Connections can be challenging for developers. 🤔 Social Connections enable users to log in with existing accounts from providers like Google and Facebook, ideal for B2C applications. They enhance user convenience and streamline sign-ups. In contrast, Enterprise Connections cater to B2B needs, allowing users to manage both personal and corporate accounts effectively. Understanding the right connection type is crucial for your app&amp;rsquo;s success! 🔑&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing CheckMate for Auth0: A New Auth0 Security Tool</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11077/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11077/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing CheckMate for Auth0! This new open-source tool helps developers and security teams assess and enhance the security of their Auth0 tenant configurations. CheckMate analyzes your setup against security best practices, providing insights to identify vulnerabilities. 🛡️ Key features include checks for misconfigured applications, password policies, MFA settings, and more. It streamlines security reviews, making it easier to maintain a secure environment. 🔍 #Auth0 #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 FGA Logging API: A Complete Audit Trail for Authorization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11034/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11034/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Auth0! The new Fine-Grained Authorization (FGA) Logging API is now available. This dedicated endpoint provides a complete audit trail for every interaction with the FGA system. Developers, security engineers, and compliance officers can now easily access authorization logs for auditing, troubleshooting, and monitoring. Key features include: - Immutable logs for compliance - Detailed filtering for efficient debugging - Proactive security monitoring Learn more about how&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September 2025 in Auth0: Advanced Security Controls and Auth0 for AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11012/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 19:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11012/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Auth0 for September 2025! The latest features include &lt;strong&gt;Auth0 for AI Agents&lt;/strong&gt;, set to be generally available in October, announced during Oktane 25. This aims to enhance secure AI interactions. 🔒 &lt;strong&gt;Tenant Access Control List&lt;/strong&gt; is now available, allowing custom access management to boost security for tenant environments. 🛠️ Developers will benefit from the &lt;strong&gt;Dry Run for Auth0 Deploy CLI&lt;/strong&gt;, enabling a preview of deployment changes before implementation. Stay updated on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding ReBAC and ABAC Through OpenFGA and Cedar</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10944/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10944/</guid>
      <description>Explore the differences between Relationship-based Access Control (ReBAC) and Attribute-based Access Control (ABAC) in the latest blog post. The article discusses how both models fit under the umbrella of policy-based access control (PBAC), highlighting their unique approaches to permissions. OpenFGA represents ReBAC, focusing on relationships, while Cedar exemplifies ABAC, emphasizing attributes. These frameworks help shape your authorization systems effectively. 🔑🔍📊 #ReBAC #ABAC&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Your Business Ready for AI Agents? The Ultimate AI Security Checklist for Customer Identity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10620/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10620/</guid>
      <description>Is your business prepared for AI agents? 🤖 As AI technology becomes part of everyday life, security concerns are rising. A recent report shows that 60% of users worry about AI&amp;rsquo;s impact on their digital identities. Our AI Security Checklist outlines the essential steps for assessing your identity environment. 📝 Strengthening your strategy is crucial to ensuring customer trust and data protection. Stay secure as you implement AI solutions! #AI #Cybersecurity #CustomerTrust #DataProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 Token Vault: Secure Token Exchange for AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10601/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10601/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Auth0 Token Vault enhances AI agents by enabling secure, delegated access through OAuth 2.0 Token Exchange. AI agents can now perform tasks like scheduling meetings or posting updates without exposing sensitive refresh tokens. This method addresses the risks associated with traditional token storage and API keys. By applying federated identity, users can seamlessly authenticate with trusted providers, ensuring better control and security. Discover how Auth0 is paving the way for safer AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refresh Token Security: Detecting Hijacking and Misuse with Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10570/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10570/</guid>
      <description>Enhancing refresh token security is vital for modern applications. 🔐 This article discusses methods to detect hijacking and misuse using Auth0&amp;rsquo;s Detection Catalog. Refresh tokens help maintain user experience but pose security risks, especially if compromised. Key strategies include: - Storing tokens in secure HTTP-Only cookies - Enabling refresh token rotation - Automatic reuse detection These measures can help mitigate risks and protect sensitive data. 💻🛡️ #Cybersecurity #Auth0&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying JOSE, the JWT Family: JWS, JWE, JWA, and JWK Explained</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10489/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10489/</guid>
      <description>Understanding the JWT Family: JOSE, JWS, JWE, JWK, and JWA. 🔍 This article clarifies these terms, which are essential in modern authentication. JOSE is a framework for securely transferring claims, while JWS ensures data integrity and authenticity through signatures. JWE deals with encrypted messages, JWK provides keys, and JWA outlines the algorithms used. Together, they create a cohesive system for secure data exchange. 🔑📦 #Cybersecurity #JWT #DataIntegrity #SecureData #JOSE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity That Helps You Sell: Introducing Auth0 for B2B Enhancements</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10380/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10380/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for B2B companies! Auth0 is enhancing identity management with new features that streamline onboarding and improve security. Key updates include self-service onboarding workflows, Group Provisioning with SCIM, and Universal Logout. These tools aim to reduce reliance on support tickets and improve operational efficiency. With these enhancements, B2B companies can speed up deployment and manage identities more securely, ensuring a smoother experience for both customers and IT&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure a .NET RAG System with Auth0 FGA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10311/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10311/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Discover how to secure your .NET Blazor AI chatbot with the Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) pattern. This guide emphasizes the importance of user-level permissions to prevent sensitive data leaks. Simply authenticating users isn&amp;rsquo;t enough; the retrieval mechanism must also enforce access control. Learn to build and secure your RAG-powered chatbot using Auth0 for both user authentication and document-level authorization. #AI #Chatbots #Security #Auth0 #DotNet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Auth0 for AI Agents: Powering the Future of AI, Securely</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10053/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10053/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Oktane! Auth0 for AI Agents is now set to be generally available this October. This complete authentication solution is designed for secure AI agent development, addressing the unique challenges they present. Many organizations are eager to adopt AI but face concerns about data security and trust. Traditional identity tools often fall short for AI agents, which can access and act on behalf of users across multiple platforms. Auth0 offers a solution, allowing companies to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Signup Fraud: 3 Ways to Use Auth0 Logs to Protect Your Business</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10035/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10035/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Fraudulent signups can harm businesses significantly. Auth0 provides tools to help detect and prevent these threats. Key indicators of signup fraud include: 1️⃣ High-volume signups from specific IP addresses. 2️⃣ Use of disposable email addresses. 3️⃣ Unverified accounts. By leveraging Auth0 Logs, businesses can identify these patterns and take action to protect themselves. 🛡️ #FraudPrevention #Auth0 #CyberSecurity #BusinessSafety #SignUpFraud</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopify &#43; Auth0: A New Era for Retail Customer Identity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9943/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9943/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Shopify has partnered with Auth0 to enhance the online shopping experience! The integration allows merchants to upgrade their login systems with features like passwordless options, multi-factor authentication, and more, improving security and customization. Shopify&amp;rsquo;s new Customer Accounts now support Auth0, offering a modern approach to customer identity management. Key benefits include enterprise-grade security and better user experiences. #Shopify #Auth0 #Ecommerce #CustomerExperience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Transaction Metadata for Auth0 Actions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9901/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9901/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Auth0! They&amp;rsquo;ve introduced Actions Transaction Metadata, a new feature aimed at improving authentication flows. This tool allows developers to store and pass custom variables more efficiently, reducing the need for workarounds that increase API usage. Previously, developers relied on Auth0 Actions Cache and Profile Metadata for local storage, which often led to complications. The new Transaction Metadata streamlines this process, enhancing performance and reliability&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing DPoP with Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9766/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9766/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Implementing DPoP with Auth0 enhances security for your Single-Page Applications (SPA) and APIs. This guide explains how DPoP binds access tokens to clients, using public key cryptography to protect against token replay attacks. Auth0 SDKs simplify the process, allowing easy integration with minimal configuration. Learn how to enable DPoP in your application and API effectively. #DPoP #Auth0 #WebSecurity #API #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oktane Online 2025: The AI Security Event You Can’t Miss</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9833/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9833/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Join us for Oktane Online, streaming live on September 25-26, 2025! With over 40 sessions on AI, identity, and security, this free event is designed for IT leaders, security professionals, and anyone interested in the future of technology. Expect keynotes from industry leaders, real-time Q&amp;amp;As, and even entertainment from guests like Jeremy Renner! Plus, earn up to 13.5 CPE credits. Don’t miss out—secure your spot today! #OktaneOnline #AISecurity #TechEvent #CPEcredits #IdentityInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Your Product Hitting Its Limits? A Guide to Upgrading Your Auth0 Plan</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9770/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9770/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Is your product ready for the next step? If you&amp;rsquo;re using the Auth0 Free plan, you may soon encounter limitations as your business grows. Signs to consider upgrading include hitting roadblocks in user management, increased security needs, and the importance of trust in attracting clients. Upgrading enhances your security, ensures compliance, and allows for scalability. Features like advanced multi-factor authentication and log streaming can support your growth journey. #Auth0 #ProductGrowth&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing DPoP with Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9766/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9766/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Implementing DPoP with Auth0 enhances security for your Single-Page Applications (SPA) and APIs. This guide explains how DPoP binds access tokens to clients, using public key cryptography to protect against token replay attacks. Auth0 SDKs simplify the process, allowing easy integration with minimal configuration. Learn how to enable DPoP in your application and API effectively. #DPoP #Auth0 #WebSecurity #API #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Identity Security Essentials for a Trusted AI Agent Strategy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9683/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9683/</guid>
      <description>Is your AI agent strategy secure? 🤖🔒 As companies integrate AI agents, consumer trust is crucial. A recent report shows that while 37% of consumers use GenAI tools, 70% still prefer human interaction due to privacy concerns. To build trust, robust customer identity and access management (CIAM) is essential. Here are four key practices: 1️⃣ Ensure strong authentication before AI actions. 2️⃣ Securely manage data access to protect user information. Investing in CIAM can enhance security and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Your Auth0 Secured Remote MCP Server in ChatGPT Developer Mode</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9591/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9591/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of ChatGPT by connecting your Auth0-secured Model Context Protocol (MCP) server! 🔗✨ This new capability allows for secure read and write actions, enhancing your AI assistant&amp;rsquo;s functionality. Learn how to enable Developer Mode, configure custom connectors, and authorize connections with Auth0 Universal Login. Ensure you follow security best practices while integrating. For a comprehensive guide, check the steps outlined in the article. #ChatGPT #Auth0 #MCP #DeveloperMode&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against AI-Powered CLI Supply Chain Attacks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9514/</guid>
      <description>🚨 AI-powered CLI supply chain attacks are becoming a serious threat to developers. These attacks exploit trusted command-line tools, turning them into insider threats that can steal sensitive data. A recent example involves an attacker exploiting a developer&amp;rsquo;s credentials to publish a malicious update, compromising systems and stealing secrets. To defend against these threats, an identity-first strategy is essential for securing developer environments and preventing data exfiltration. Stay&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>August 2025 in Auth0: Non-Unique Emails, DPoP, and TLS Fingerprints</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9489/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9489/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Auth0 for August 2025! This month, they introduced flexibility with passwordless connection switching on Universal Login, allowing users to choose their login method easily. They also launched early access to Non-Unique Emails, enabling multiple accounts to share the same email, benefiting various business scenarios. Additionally, enhanced security features like DPoP and TLS Fingerprints have been added to protect users from token theft. #Auth0 #ProductUpdate&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Configure the Auth0 MCP Server in VS Code for AI Assistant Integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9450/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn to set up the Auth0 MCP Server in VS Code for AI assistant integration! This guide offers step-by-step instructions to help you analyze logs and manage identity operations directly from your IDE. The MCP Server allows natural language interactions, simplifying tasks like user management and log analysis. Make sure you have an Auth0 account, VS Code, and npx ready to get started! #Auth0 #VSCODE #AIIntegration #IdentityManagement #TechGuide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Authorization in ASP.NET Core with Auth0 FGA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7766/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7766/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of Fine-Grained Authorization (FGA) in your ASP.NET Core applications with Auth0 FGA! 🔑 This article provides a step-by-step guide to implementing relationship-based permissions in a minimal API. Instead of relying on static roles, users&amp;rsquo; actions are based on their specific relationships to resources, like file ownership. Learn how to enhance your API for file and folder management using the OpenFGA SDK to enforce these permissions effectively. Get started with the right&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Accessible Guide to WCAG 3.3.8: Authentication Without Frustration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7699/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7699/</guid>
      <description>Navigating login processes can be challenging for users with cognitive disabilities. WCAG Success Criterion 3.3.8, &amp;ldquo;Accessible Authentication,&amp;rdquo; aims to simplify this experience. It highlights that no cognitive function tests should be required unless alternatives are provided. Common pitfalls include standard username/password fields and transcription-based 2FA, which can create barriers. By addressing these issues, developers can create a more inclusive login experience for everyone. 🔑💻✨&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API Keys and AI Agents: Four Common Risks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7639/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7639/</guid>
      <description>Building AI agents can be thrilling, but it comes with serious security risks when using API keys. 🚨 Pasting keys everywhere can lead to exposure through public repositories, logs, or client-side applications. This increases the chance of automated attacks, especially if the keys have broad permissions. 🔑 Managing these keys is crucial to ensure data security and compliance, particularly in regulated industries. Consider solutions like Auth0&amp;rsquo;s Token Vault to safeguard your integrations. 🔒 #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Asynchronous Human-in-the-Loop Authorization in Python with LangGraph and Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7518/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7518/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to implement asynchronous authorization in your LangGraph application using Auth0 and the CIBA flow. This tutorial covers using a secondary device for secure permissions, allowing actions like financial transactions or order approvals with human oversight. Discover the importance of keeping humans in the loop for responsible AI actions. For more insights on CIBA, check out the linked blog post! 🔐📱🤖 #AsynchronousAuth #LangGraph #Auth0 #CIBA #ResponsibleAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Python MCP Server to Consult a Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7455/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7455/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Want to enhance your AI assistant&amp;rsquo;s capabilities? Check out this guide on building a Python MCP server to create a searchable knowledge base from your blog. Learn how to connect your AI, like Claude, to your blog content seamlessly without interrupting your workflow. Discover the benefits of the Model Context Protocol (MCP) for secure data access and efficient information retrieval. #AI #Python #KnowledgeBase #MCP #TechGuide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level Up Your Security Posture with the Auth0 Security Detection Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7228/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7228/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for security professionals! Auth0 has launched the &lt;strong&gt;Security Detection Catalog&lt;/strong&gt; on GitHub, an open-source resource aimed at enhancing your security posture. It offers actionable intelligence and proactive threat updates to help you stay ahead of emerging threats. Each detection includes threat descriptions and recommended prevention strategies, ensuring a swift response. The catalog is designed for compatibility with Sigma rules, allowing for quick deployment across various&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Step-by-Step Guide to Securing Amazon Bedrock Agents with Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7188/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7188/</guid>
      <description>Enhance the security of your Amazon Bedrock agents with Auth0 for GenAI! 🔐 This guide outlines how to implement secure authentication and authorization, allowing agents to act on users&amp;rsquo; behalf without static credentials. Key features include secure login, identity-based API access, and authorization-aware actions. Learn how to build robust, identity-aware AI applications with these essential capabilities. #AmazonBedrock #GenAI #Auth0 #AI #Security</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect Your Access Tokens with DPoP (Demonstrating Proof of Possession)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6332/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6332/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Protect your applications with DPoP! This article explains how Demonstrating Proof-of-Possession enhances security for access tokens by ensuring they can only be used by the intended application. Unlike traditional bearer tokens, DPoP binds tokens to a specific client instance, mitigating risks of token theft. Learn about the benefits, security threats it addresses, and how to implement DPoP in your applications using Auth0. #Security #DPoP #OAuth2 #AccessTokens #ApplicationSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Third-Party Tool Calling: A Guide to LangGraph Tool Calling and Secure AI Integration in Python</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6308/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6308/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how to integrate third-party APIs securely using LangGraph in Python! This guide builds on the previous article about the Zoo AI, focusing on tool calling on behalf of users while maintaining security. Learn how to implement LangChain with FastAPI and Auth0 to access protected resources safely. Enhance your application while ensuring proper authorization for each user action. 🦁🐾 #LangChain #APISecurity #Python #FastAPI #AIIntegration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Financial Services Demands a New Trust Layer: Why Identity Security Is the Answer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5100/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5100/</guid>
      <description>As AI transforms financial services, new risks arise with autonomous AI agents accessing sensitive data. Traditional identity security is becoming insufficient. Financial institutions must now consider not just who the user is, but also what operates on their behalf. A shift to advanced identity solutions, like Auth for GenAI, is essential for secure innovation. 🚀🔐 Explore more insights from the Auth0 Customer Identity Trends Report 2025. #AI #FinancialServices #IdentitySecurity #Innovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Trust in AI: A Developer&#39;s Identity Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5009/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5009/</guid>
      <description>🔐 In the evolving landscape of AI, security is essential for building user trust. Developers face challenges like signup attacks, account takeovers, and poor password hygiene, which can erode confidence in digital platforms. The Auth0 Customer Identity Trends Report 2025 reveals that 46.1% of new registrations may be fraudulent, while 16.9% of login attempts show malicious intent. To foster trust, developers must prioritize robust identity management, as 74% of users value a company’s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Access Control in the Era of AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4945/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4945/</guid>
      <description>AI agents are evolving, performing complex tasks and making API calls autonomously. This shift poses new security challenges, particularly in access control. The article discusses the history of AI agents and highlights the risks they bring, emphasizing the need for fine-grained access control. Traditional models like RBAC and ABAC struggle under the dynamic nature of AI systems, often requiring additional engineering for effective management. Explore how to adapt access control as AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 Product Updates (July 2025): New Security Features, Global Regions, and Developer Previews</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4946/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4946/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Auth0 this July! We&amp;rsquo;re introducing enhanced security features like PII masking in logs, which helps protect sensitive data. Improvements in bot detection will ensure smoother experiences for genuine users. Additionally, new global cloud regions are now available, including Mexico 🇲🇽 and Hong Kong 🇭🇰, expanding our reach. Stay tuned for more features aimed at empowering developers! #Auth0 #Security #DeveloperUpdates #CloudExpansion #IdentityManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earn Customer Trust in the AI Era: A Guide for Businesses</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4947/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4947/</guid>
      <description>🌐 In the AI era, building customer trust is crucial for businesses. A recent report reveals that 37% of consumers frequently interact with AI. Yet, 70% prefer humans for assistance, valuing empathy over efficiency. 🤝 As customers define AI&amp;rsquo;s role, they see it as a tool for tasks but hesitate to trust it with complex decisions. The key question remains: &amp;ldquo;Can I trust you with my data?&amp;rdquo; With 23% of users avoiding AI entirely, addressing this concern is essential for fostering trust. 🔑&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Can&#39;t I Just Use an API? Because Your AI Agent Needs MCP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4849/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4849/</guid>
      <description>Understanding the limitations of traditional APIs for AI agents is crucial. 🤖 The article discusses how APIs can confuse AI agents due to excessive choices and the need for manual translation of information. This often hampers performance and adaptability. Introducing the Model Context Protocol (MCP), which streamlines AI reasoning by providing high-level capabilities instead of overwhelming details. MCP enhances the agent&amp;rsquo;s ability to focus on tasks efficiently. #AI #MCP #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Healthcare Is AI-Powered and Secure: How CIAM Builds Trust</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4850/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4850/</guid>
      <description>The integration of AI in healthcare is reshaping the industry, promising enhanced efficiency and personalized treatment. However, the security of sensitive patient data is a major concern. Customer Identity and Access Management (CIAM) solutions play a crucial role in ensuring that only authorized users access AI systems, supporting compliance and security. As the healthcare IAM market is projected to grow significantly, establishing trust becomes vital. Patients prioritize trust over&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Myths About JWTs Debunked</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4707/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4707/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Understanding JSON Web Tokens (JWTs) is crucial for secure application and API management. This article debunks five common myths about JWTs, highlighting misconceptions that can lead to vulnerabilities. One key point is that JWTs are not just another type of token; they are structured and self-contained, offering stateless validation. Learn more about JWTs and their proper usage to enhance your security practices. #JWT #WebSecurity #APIProtection #TechMyths #Cybersecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) with Auth0 FGA and FastAPI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4756/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4756/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking tenant-level permissions is essential for application growth. This article delves into implementing Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) using Auth0 FGA and FastAPI. RBAC simplifies user management by assigning permissions to roles rather than individuals, making administration easier. Auth0 FGA provides a scalable solution for handling authorization decisions. Learn how to design a coarse-grained RBAC model tailored for multi-tenant applications. This approach enables efficient&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing AI Agents: Retail&#39;s Next Big Challenge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4706/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4706/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence is transforming the retail industry, offering new ways to engage customers and streamline operations. 🚀 While 90% of retailers are already using or evaluating AI, concerns about data privacy and security remain significant. 60% of retailers worry about data privacy, highlighting the need for secure AI adoption. 🔒 Current AI applications include hyper-personalized shopping experiences, virtual try-ons, and real-time customer service assistance. The future holds even&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAPI 2.0: The Future of API Security for High-Stakes Customer Interactions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4133/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4133/</guid>
      <description>🚀 FAPI 2.0 is redefining API security for critical customer interactions. Originally created for financial services, it now offers advanced protections applicable across industries. This new version focuses on enhancing end-to-end security and privacy for sensitive actions like payments and data sharing. Key benefits include clear specifications, thorough conformance tests, and a standards-based approach for better security. Discover how FAPI 2.0 can help protect your organization. 🔒🌐&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Auth0 Mitigates OWASP’s Agentic AI Threats</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-1965/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-1965/</guid>
      <description>🌐 AI-powered agents are transforming industries, but they also bring significant security risks. Auth0 addresses these challenges highlighted by OWASP&amp;rsquo;s recent report on Agentic AI threats. Key risks include data breaches and regulatory non-compliance, which can erode customer trust. Traditional security measures often fall short for autonomous AI. Organizations must implement robust security from the start when developing GenAI applications. 🔐 #CyberSecurity #AI #GenAI #Auth0 #OWASP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Connect Auth0 with Shopify: A Tech Quick Start Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-1966/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-1966/</guid>
      <description>Unlock enhanced security for your Shopify store by integrating Auth0! 🔐 This guide details how to connect Auth0 with Shopify customer accounts using OpenID Connect (OIDC). The integration allows for better login options, including social logins and multifactor authentication (MFA). Learn how to set up Auth0, configure your Shopify store, and customize your authentication flow, all while ensuring a secure and personalized experience for your customers. #Shopify #Auth0 #Ecommerce #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an AI Assistant with LangGraph and Next.js: Use Your APIs and Google Calendar as Tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-1967/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-1967/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to enhance your AI assistant? This article guides you in building a tool-calling AI agent using LangGraph and Next.js. 🔧 You&amp;rsquo;ll learn to integrate your APIs, utilize Google Calendar, and manage authorization with Auth0. 📚 Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to check previous posts for foundational knowledge on tool calling in AI agents. #AIAssistant #LangGraph #NextJS #TechTutorial #Auth0</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Cloudflare Agents with Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-1968/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-1968/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of Cloudflare Agents with Auth0! 🌐 This article explores how to implement Auth0 for secure authentication and authorization of AI running on Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s edge network. It provides a starter kit and detailed deployment instructions to ensure your AI operates efficiently and securely. Discover how these agents can capture user input, execute complex workflows, and interact with external systems—all while maintaining robust security. 🔐🤖 #Cloudflare #AI #Auth0 #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
