<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Auth0-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/auth0-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Auth0-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/auth0-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Signup Fraud: 3 Ways to Use Auth0 Logs to Protect Your Business</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10035/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10035/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Fraudulent signups can harm businesses significantly. Auth0 provides tools to help detect and prevent these threats. Key indicators of signup fraud include: 1️⃣ High-volume signups from specific IP addresses. 2️⃣ Use of disposable email addresses. 3️⃣ Unverified accounts. By leveraging Auth0 Logs, businesses can identify these patterns and take action to protect themselves. 🛡️ #FraudPrevention #Auth0 #CyberSecurity #BusinessSafety #SignUpFraud</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopify &#43; Auth0: A New Era for Retail Customer Identity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9943/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9943/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Shopify has partnered with Auth0 to enhance the online shopping experience! The integration allows merchants to upgrade their login systems with features like passwordless options, multi-factor authentication, and more, improving security and customization. Shopify&amp;rsquo;s new Customer Accounts now support Auth0, offering a modern approach to customer identity management. Key benefits include enterprise-grade security and better user experiences. #Shopify #Auth0 #Ecommerce #CustomerExperience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Transaction Metadata for Auth0 Actions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9901/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9901/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Auth0! They&amp;rsquo;ve introduced Actions Transaction Metadata, a new feature aimed at improving authentication flows. This tool allows developers to store and pass custom variables more efficiently, reducing the need for workarounds that increase API usage. Previously, developers relied on Auth0 Actions Cache and Profile Metadata for local storage, which often led to complications. The new Transaction Metadata streamlines this process, enhancing performance and reliability&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing DPoP with Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9766/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9766/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Implementing DPoP with Auth0 enhances security for your Single-Page Applications (SPA) and APIs. This guide explains how DPoP binds access tokens to clients, using public key cryptography to protect against token replay attacks. Auth0 SDKs simplify the process, allowing easy integration with minimal configuration. Learn how to enable DPoP in your application and API effectively. #DPoP #Auth0 #WebSecurity #API #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oktane Online 2025: The AI Security Event You Can’t Miss</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9833/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9833/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Join us for Oktane Online, streaming live on September 25-26, 2025! With over 40 sessions on AI, identity, and security, this free event is designed for IT leaders, security professionals, and anyone interested in the future of technology. Expect keynotes from industry leaders, real-time Q&amp;amp;As, and even entertainment from guests like Jeremy Renner! Plus, earn up to 13.5 CPE credits. Don’t miss out—secure your spot today! #OktaneOnline #AISecurity #TechEvent #CPEcredits #IdentityInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Your Product Hitting Its Limits? A Guide to Upgrading Your Auth0 Plan</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9770/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9770/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Is your product ready for the next step? If you&amp;rsquo;re using the Auth0 Free plan, you may soon encounter limitations as your business grows. Signs to consider upgrading include hitting roadblocks in user management, increased security needs, and the importance of trust in attracting clients. Upgrading enhances your security, ensures compliance, and allows for scalability. Features like advanced multi-factor authentication and log streaming can support your growth journey. #Auth0 #ProductGrowth&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing DPoP with Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9766/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 10:36:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9766/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Implementing DPoP with Auth0 enhances security for your Single-Page Applications (SPA) and APIs. This guide explains how DPoP binds access tokens to clients, using public key cryptography to protect against token replay attacks. Auth0 SDKs simplify the process, allowing easy integration with minimal configuration. Learn how to enable DPoP in your application and API effectively. #DPoP #Auth0 #WebSecurity #API #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Identity Security Essentials for a Trusted AI Agent Strategy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9683/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9683/</guid>
      <description>Is your AI agent strategy secure? 🤖🔒 As companies integrate AI agents, consumer trust is crucial. A recent report shows that while 37% of consumers use GenAI tools, 70% still prefer human interaction due to privacy concerns. To build trust, robust customer identity and access management (CIAM) is essential. Here are four key practices: 1️⃣ Ensure strong authentication before AI actions. 2️⃣ Securely manage data access to protect user information. Investing in CIAM can enhance security and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Your Auth0 Secured Remote MCP Server in ChatGPT Developer Mode</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9591/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9591/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of ChatGPT by connecting your Auth0-secured Model Context Protocol (MCP) server! 🔗✨ This new capability allows for secure read and write actions, enhancing your AI assistant&amp;rsquo;s functionality. Learn how to enable Developer Mode, configure custom connectors, and authorize connections with Auth0 Universal Login. Ensure you follow security best practices while integrating. For a comprehensive guide, check the steps outlined in the article. #ChatGPT #Auth0 #MCP #DeveloperMode&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against AI-Powered CLI Supply Chain Attacks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9514/</guid>
      <description>🚨 AI-powered CLI supply chain attacks are becoming a serious threat to developers. These attacks exploit trusted command-line tools, turning them into insider threats that can steal sensitive data. A recent example involves an attacker exploiting a developer&amp;rsquo;s credentials to publish a malicious update, compromising systems and stealing secrets. To defend against these threats, an identity-first strategy is essential for securing developer environments and preventing data exfiltration. Stay&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>August 2025 in Auth0: Non-Unique Emails, DPoP, and TLS Fingerprints</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9489/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9489/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Auth0 for August 2025! This month, they introduced flexibility with passwordless connection switching on Universal Login, allowing users to choose their login method easily. They also launched early access to Non-Unique Emails, enabling multiple accounts to share the same email, benefiting various business scenarios. Additionally, enhanced security features like DPoP and TLS Fingerprints have been added to protect users from token theft. #Auth0 #ProductUpdate&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Configure the Auth0 MCP Server in VS Code for AI Assistant Integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9450/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9450/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn to set up the Auth0 MCP Server in VS Code for AI assistant integration! This guide offers step-by-step instructions to help you analyze logs and manage identity operations directly from your IDE. The MCP Server allows natural language interactions, simplifying tasks like user management and log analysis. Make sure you have an Auth0 account, VS Code, and npx ready to get started! #Auth0 #VSCODE #AIIntegration #IdentityManagement #TechGuide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained Authorization in ASP.NET Core with Auth0 FGA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7766/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7766/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of Fine-Grained Authorization (FGA) in your ASP.NET Core applications with Auth0 FGA! 🔑 This article provides a step-by-step guide to implementing relationship-based permissions in a minimal API. Instead of relying on static roles, users&amp;rsquo; actions are based on their specific relationships to resources, like file ownership. Learn how to enhance your API for file and folder management using the OpenFGA SDK to enforce these permissions effectively. Get started with the right&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Accessible Guide to WCAG 3.3.8: Authentication Without Frustration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7699/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7699/</guid>
      <description>Navigating login processes can be challenging for users with cognitive disabilities. WCAG Success Criterion 3.3.8, &amp;ldquo;Accessible Authentication,&amp;rdquo; aims to simplify this experience. It highlights that no cognitive function tests should be required unless alternatives are provided. Common pitfalls include standard username/password fields and transcription-based 2FA, which can create barriers. By addressing these issues, developers can create a more inclusive login experience for everyone. 🔑💻✨&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API Keys and AI Agents: Four Common Risks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7639/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7639/</guid>
      <description>Building AI agents can be thrilling, but it comes with serious security risks when using API keys. 🚨 Pasting keys everywhere can lead to exposure through public repositories, logs, or client-side applications. This increases the chance of automated attacks, especially if the keys have broad permissions. 🔑 Managing these keys is crucial to ensure data security and compliance, particularly in regulated industries. Consider solutions like Auth0&amp;rsquo;s Token Vault to safeguard your integrations. 🔒 #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Asynchronous Human-in-the-Loop Authorization in Python with LangGraph and Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7518/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7518/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to implement asynchronous authorization in your LangGraph application using Auth0 and the CIBA flow. This tutorial covers using a secondary device for secure permissions, allowing actions like financial transactions or order approvals with human oversight. Discover the importance of keeping humans in the loop for responsible AI actions. For more insights on CIBA, check out the linked blog post! 🔐📱🤖 #AsynchronousAuth #LangGraph #Auth0 #CIBA #ResponsibleAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Python MCP Server to Consult a Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7455/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7455/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Want to enhance your AI assistant&amp;rsquo;s capabilities? Check out this guide on building a Python MCP server to create a searchable knowledge base from your blog. Learn how to connect your AI, like Claude, to your blog content seamlessly without interrupting your workflow. Discover the benefits of the Model Context Protocol (MCP) for secure data access and efficient information retrieval. #AI #Python #KnowledgeBase #MCP #TechGuide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level Up Your Security Posture with the Auth0 Security Detection Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7228/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7228/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for security professionals! Auth0 has launched the &lt;strong&gt;Security Detection Catalog&lt;/strong&gt; on GitHub, an open-source resource aimed at enhancing your security posture. It offers actionable intelligence and proactive threat updates to help you stay ahead of emerging threats. Each detection includes threat descriptions and recommended prevention strategies, ensuring a swift response. The catalog is designed for compatibility with Sigma rules, allowing for quick deployment across various&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Step-by-Step Guide to Securing Amazon Bedrock Agents with Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7188/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7188/</guid>
      <description>Enhance the security of your Amazon Bedrock agents with Auth0 for GenAI! 🔐 This guide outlines how to implement secure authentication and authorization, allowing agents to act on users&amp;rsquo; behalf without static credentials. Key features include secure login, identity-based API access, and authorization-aware actions. Learn how to build robust, identity-aware AI applications with these essential capabilities. #AmazonBedrock #GenAI #Auth0 #AI #Security</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect Your Access Tokens with DPoP (Demonstrating Proof of Possession)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6332/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6332/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Protect your applications with DPoP! This article explains how Demonstrating Proof-of-Possession enhances security for access tokens by ensuring they can only be used by the intended application. Unlike traditional bearer tokens, DPoP binds tokens to a specific client instance, mitigating risks of token theft. Learn about the benefits, security threats it addresses, and how to implement DPoP in your applications using Auth0. #Security #DPoP #OAuth2 #AccessTokens #ApplicationSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Third-Party Tool Calling: A Guide to LangGraph Tool Calling and Secure AI Integration in Python</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6308/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6308/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how to integrate third-party APIs securely using LangGraph in Python! This guide builds on the previous article about the Zoo AI, focusing on tool calling on behalf of users while maintaining security. Learn how to implement LangChain with FastAPI and Auth0 to access protected resources safely. Enhance your application while ensuring proper authorization for each user action. 🦁🐾 #LangChain #APISecurity #Python #FastAPI #AIIntegration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Financial Services Demands a New Trust Layer: Why Identity Security Is the Answer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5100/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5100/</guid>
      <description>As AI transforms financial services, new risks arise with autonomous AI agents accessing sensitive data. Traditional identity security is becoming insufficient. Financial institutions must now consider not just who the user is, but also what operates on their behalf. A shift to advanced identity solutions, like Auth for GenAI, is essential for secure innovation. 🚀🔐 Explore more insights from the Auth0 Customer Identity Trends Report 2025. #AI #FinancialServices #IdentitySecurity #Innovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Trust in AI: A Developer&#39;s Identity Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5009/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5009/</guid>
      <description>🔐 In the evolving landscape of AI, security is essential for building user trust. Developers face challenges like signup attacks, account takeovers, and poor password hygiene, which can erode confidence in digital platforms. The Auth0 Customer Identity Trends Report 2025 reveals that 46.1% of new registrations may be fraudulent, while 16.9% of login attempts show malicious intent. To foster trust, developers must prioritize robust identity management, as 74% of users value a company’s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Access Control in the Era of AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4945/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4945/</guid>
      <description>AI agents are evolving, performing complex tasks and making API calls autonomously. This shift poses new security challenges, particularly in access control. The article discusses the history of AI agents and highlights the risks they bring, emphasizing the need for fine-grained access control. Traditional models like RBAC and ABAC struggle under the dynamic nature of AI systems, often requiring additional engineering for effective management. Explore how to adapt access control as AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 Product Updates (July 2025): New Security Features, Global Regions, and Developer Previews</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4946/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4946/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Auth0 this July! We&amp;rsquo;re introducing enhanced security features like PII masking in logs, which helps protect sensitive data. Improvements in bot detection will ensure smoother experiences for genuine users. Additionally, new global cloud regions are now available, including Mexico 🇲🇽 and Hong Kong 🇭🇰, expanding our reach. Stay tuned for more features aimed at empowering developers! #Auth0 #Security #DeveloperUpdates #CloudExpansion #IdentityManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Earn Customer Trust in the AI Era: A Guide for Businesses</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4947/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4947/</guid>
      <description>🌐 In the AI era, building customer trust is crucial for businesses. A recent report reveals that 37% of consumers frequently interact with AI. Yet, 70% prefer humans for assistance, valuing empathy over efficiency. 🤝 As customers define AI&amp;rsquo;s role, they see it as a tool for tasks but hesitate to trust it with complex decisions. The key question remains: &amp;ldquo;Can I trust you with my data?&amp;rdquo; With 23% of users avoiding AI entirely, addressing this concern is essential for fostering trust. 🔑&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Can&#39;t I Just Use an API? Because Your AI Agent Needs MCP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4849/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4849/</guid>
      <description>Understanding the limitations of traditional APIs for AI agents is crucial. 🤖 The article discusses how APIs can confuse AI agents due to excessive choices and the need for manual translation of information. This often hampers performance and adaptability. Introducing the Model Context Protocol (MCP), which streamlines AI reasoning by providing high-level capabilities instead of overwhelming details. MCP enhances the agent&amp;rsquo;s ability to focus on tasks efficiently. #AI #MCP #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Healthcare Is AI-Powered and Secure: How CIAM Builds Trust</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4850/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4850/</guid>
      <description>The integration of AI in healthcare is reshaping the industry, promising enhanced efficiency and personalized treatment. However, the security of sensitive patient data is a major concern. Customer Identity and Access Management (CIAM) solutions play a crucial role in ensuring that only authorized users access AI systems, supporting compliance and security. As the healthcare IAM market is projected to grow significantly, establishing trust becomes vital. Patients prioritize trust over&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Myths About JWTs Debunked</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4707/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4707/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Understanding JSON Web Tokens (JWTs) is crucial for secure application and API management. This article debunks five common myths about JWTs, highlighting misconceptions that can lead to vulnerabilities. One key point is that JWTs are not just another type of token; they are structured and self-contained, offering stateless validation. Learn more about JWTs and their proper usage to enhance your security practices. #JWT #WebSecurity #APIProtection #TechMyths #Cybersecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) with Auth0 FGA and FastAPI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4756/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4756/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking tenant-level permissions is essential for application growth. This article delves into implementing Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) using Auth0 FGA and FastAPI. RBAC simplifies user management by assigning permissions to roles rather than individuals, making administration easier. Auth0 FGA provides a scalable solution for handling authorization decisions. Learn how to design a coarse-grained RBAC model tailored for multi-tenant applications. This approach enables efficient&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing AI Agents: Retail&#39;s Next Big Challenge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4706/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4706/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence is transforming the retail industry, offering new ways to engage customers and streamline operations. 🚀 While 90% of retailers are already using or evaluating AI, concerns about data privacy and security remain significant. 60% of retailers worry about data privacy, highlighting the need for secure AI adoption. 🔒 Current AI applications include hyper-personalized shopping experiences, virtual try-ons, and real-time customer service assistance. The future holds even&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAPI 2.0: The Future of API Security for High-Stakes Customer Interactions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4133/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4133/</guid>
      <description>🚀 FAPI 2.0 is redefining API security for critical customer interactions. Originally created for financial services, it now offers advanced protections applicable across industries. This new version focuses on enhancing end-to-end security and privacy for sensitive actions like payments and data sharing. Key benefits include clear specifications, thorough conformance tests, and a standards-based approach for better security. Discover how FAPI 2.0 can help protect your organization. 🔒🌐&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Auth0 Mitigates OWASP’s Agentic AI Threats</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-1965/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-1965/</guid>
      <description>🌐 AI-powered agents are transforming industries, but they also bring significant security risks. Auth0 addresses these challenges highlighted by OWASP&amp;rsquo;s recent report on Agentic AI threats. Key risks include data breaches and regulatory non-compliance, which can erode customer trust. Traditional security measures often fall short for autonomous AI. Organizations must implement robust security from the start when developing GenAI applications. 🔐 #CyberSecurity #AI #GenAI #Auth0 #OWASP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Connect Auth0 with Shopify: A Tech Quick Start Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-1966/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-1966/</guid>
      <description>Unlock enhanced security for your Shopify store by integrating Auth0! 🔐 This guide details how to connect Auth0 with Shopify customer accounts using OpenID Connect (OIDC). The integration allows for better login options, including social logins and multifactor authentication (MFA). Learn how to set up Auth0, configure your Shopify store, and customize your authentication flow, all while ensuring a secure and personalized experience for your customers. #Shopify #Auth0 #Ecommerce #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an AI Assistant with LangGraph and Next.js: Use Your APIs and Google Calendar as Tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-1967/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-1967/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to enhance your AI assistant? This article guides you in building a tool-calling AI agent using LangGraph and Next.js. 🔧 You&amp;rsquo;ll learn to integrate your APIs, utilize Google Calendar, and manage authorization with Auth0. 📚 Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to check previous posts for foundational knowledge on tool calling in AI agents. #AIAssistant #LangGraph #NextJS #TechTutorial #Auth0</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Cloudflare Agents with Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-1968/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-1968/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of Cloudflare Agents with Auth0! 🌐 This article explores how to implement Auth0 for secure authentication and authorization of AI running on Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s edge network. It provides a starter kit and detailed deployment instructions to ensure your AI operates efficiently and securely. Discover how these agents can capture user input, execute complex workflows, and interact with external systems—all while maintaining robust security. 🔐🤖 #Cloudflare #AI #Auth0 #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
