<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Event on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/categories/event/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Event on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello Developer: January 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14281/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14281/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for developers in January 2026! This edition highlights a special SwiftUI activity in Cupertino and offers new ways to engage with Liquid Glass. Check out a quick video recap of Apple design resources and explore the all-new Develop in Swift Tutorials. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the article on maximizing foundation models! #AppleDevelopers #SwiftUI #TechUpdates #LiquidGlass #FoundationModels</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – January 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14254/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14254/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Happy New Year! Welcome to the January 2026 edition of Java Annotated Monthly! This month features Neha Sardana, a VP at Morgan Stanley, sharing her insights on Java technology and open-source software. She discusses Project Valhalla, highlighting its potential to enhance Java&amp;rsquo;s performance by treating data more efficiently. This could significantly benefit frameworks and libraries we use daily. For more details, check out the full article! #Java #ProjectValhalla #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games made with Unity: 2025 in review</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14292/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14292/</guid>
      <description>2025 has been a notable year for the Unity community, showcasing a variety of new titles. Noteworthy releases include &lt;em&gt;Jump Space&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Megabonk&lt;/em&gt;, and the highly anticipated &lt;em&gt;Hollow Knight: Silksong&lt;/em&gt;. The IGF Awards celebrated several Unity games, with &lt;em&gt;Consume Me&lt;/em&gt; winning three awards. The community was engaged through events like the Unity Awards Steam Sale. For a comprehensive list of Unity games launched in 2025, visit our Steam Curator page. 🎮✨ #Unity #GameDevelopment #IndieGames&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nick Lucchesi Takes Helm at The New Stack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14230/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:30:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14230/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for The New Stack readers! Nick Lucchesi has been appointed as the new editor-in-chief. Nick brings extensive experience from his previous role at Laptop Magazine. He aims to uphold TNS&amp;rsquo;s commitment to clarity in technology while preparing for an AI-driven future. Expect a mix of in-depth journalism and timely insights as he leads TNS forward. #NewLeadership #TechNews #TheNewStack #AI #Journalism</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year! AWS Weekly Roundup: 10,000 AIdeas Competition, Amazon EC2, Amazon ECS Managed Instances and more (January 5, 2026)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14234/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 17:10:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14234/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Happy New Year! As we kick off 2026, AWS is launching exciting initiatives. Join the next cohort of the &amp;ldquo;Become a Solutions Architect&amp;rdquo; program focusing on &amp;ldquo;Agentic AI on AWS,&amp;rdquo; starting February 21, 2026. This free mentoring opportunity helps advance careers in cloud and AI. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the chance to enter the Global 10,000 AIdeas Competition by January 21 for a shot at $250,000 in prizes and AWS credits. Key AWS updates include: - New EC2 M8gn and M8gb instances with improved performance. -&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linus Torvalds Gets Candid About Windows, Workflows, and AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-04-14215/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2026 14:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-04-14215/</guid>
      <description>Linus Torvalds recently appeared on Linus Tech Tips, engaging in a casual discussion about Linux and technology. 🎥 He shared insights into building a perfect Linux PC and emphasized the importance of reliable hardware, noting that many issues attributed to Windows may stem from hardware instability. 💻 Torvalds also reflected on his workflow, stating that after 20 years, Linux operates with an almost flawless process, contributing to a stress-free work environment. Catch the full interview for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games made with Unity: December 2025 in review</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-02-14210/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-02-14210/</guid>
      <description>🎮 December 2025 wrapped up with notable achievements at The Game Awards and the 17th Unity Awards. Congratulations to award winners like Silksong and Umamusume: Pretty Derby! 🏆 A highlight from the IGF Awards was &amp;ldquo;Consume Me,&amp;rdquo; which won three awards. Check out the latest games made with Unity launched this month, including titles like &lt;em&gt;Terminator 2D: NO FATE&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Rhythm Doctor&lt;/em&gt;. For a full list and more details, visit our Steam Curator page! #UnityGames #GameAwards #IndieGames #Unity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new era of Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-30-14185/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-30-14185/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Stack Overflow! At WeAreDevelopers, the team introduced a new vision and mission for the platform, emphasizing their commitment to serving the tech community. This year marks significant changes, including the launch of OverflowAI and new user engagement features. With a focus on the evolving tech landscape, Stack Overflow aims to adapt to the AI era. Stay tuned for more developments! #StackOverflow #WeAreDevelopers #TechCommunity #AI #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Donald Knuth’s 2025 Christmas Lecture: The Knight’s Tours</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-25-14152/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-25-14152/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Donald Knuth recently delivered his annual Christmas lecture at Stanford, celebrating over 30 years of this tradition. Approaching his 88th birthday, he continues to work on &amp;ldquo;The Art of Computer Programming.&amp;rdquo; This year, Knuth explored the classic graph theory question: &amp;ldquo;Can a knight cover all cells of a chessboard without revisiting?&amp;rdquo; Through this, he emphasized the beauty found in math and computer science. He also shared updates on his adventures, including his 64th wedding anniversary&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruby Turns 30: A Celebration of Code, Community, and Creativity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-25-14151/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-25-14151/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Ruby celebrates 30 years of making coding more human and enjoyable! Created by Yukihiro “Matz” Matsumoto, Ruby&amp;rsquo;s design emphasizes intuitive syntax and object-oriented principles. As part of the anniversary, RubyMine is now free for non-commercial use, supporting new developers. Over the years, Ruby has introduced key tools like Bundler, RSpec, and RuboCop, shaping a vibrant community focused on craftsmanship. #Ruby30 #Programming #DeveloperCommunity #RubyMine #CodeCraftsmanship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Portraits: AI generated trading cards</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14081/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14081/</guid>
      <description>🎉 At the Next.js Conf and Ship AI events, we launched an innovative activation combining technology and nostalgia. Attendees had the chance to create their own AI-generated trading cards during the online registration process. This initiative aimed to enhance their experience and set the stage for real-world interactions at the events. Discover more about this unique blend of tech and fun! #AI #NextjsConf #TradingCards #TechInnovation #EventExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the gap: bitsIO wins Splunkie Award for data and AI-powered nonprofit solutions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14113/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 21:35:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14113/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! bitsIO has been awarded the Splunkie Award for Social Impact Partner of the Year. This marks their third win, highlighting their commitment to bridging the data divide for nonprofits. 💻 Nonprofits often face complex challenges but lack the resources of larger enterprises. bitsIO provides AI-powered Splunk services tailored to these organizations, offering support from setup to ongoing maintenance. 🌍 Their mission is to empower nonprofits to manage sensitive data and enhance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code in Rust: Winners and Highlights</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14114/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14114/</guid>
      <description>🎉 A big thank you to all who participated in Advent of Code 2025 in Rust! It was great to see the community come together to solve puzzles during the holiday season. Before the event, Vitaly Bragilevsky shared tips on using AI effectively in the challenges. Over 12 days, daily features in the RustRover Advent Calendar highlighted useful tools for Rust developers. 🏆 Congratulations to our top winners: 1. Duro 2. JohnX4321 3. MaRcR11 4. Giacomo Stevanato 5. Agnibha Chakraborty Additionally,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel Portraits: AI generated trading cards</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14081/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14081/</guid>
      <description>🎉 At the Next.js Conf and Ship AI events, we launched an innovative activation combining technology and nostalgia. Attendees had the chance to create their own AI-generated trading cards during the online registration process. This initiative aimed to enhance their experience and set the stage for real-world interactions at the events. Discover more about this unique blend of tech and fun! #AI #NextjsConf #TradingCards #TechInnovation #EventExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kickstart Your 2026 Security Strategy: Master Automation at the DevNet Ignite Security Workshop</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14079/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14079/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to enhance your cybersecurity strategy for 2026? Join the DevNet Ignite Security Workshop, featuring hands-on sessions in nine global cities. Learn to automate security and reduce manual workloads. Key tracks include Security Automation, Network Security, and Cloud Protection, focusing on real-world applications. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to elevate your skills! #Cybersecurity #DevNetIgnite #SecurityAutomation #TechTraining #2026Strategy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the pitch: Meet the students proposing bold ways to use Cisco technology for good</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14074/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 22:16:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14074/</guid>
      <description>At Cisco&amp;rsquo;s first Empower &amp;amp; Connect Summit, students showcased innovative ways to use technology for social good. 🌍💡 Five finalist teams presented ideas aimed at addressing community challenges, reflecting a deep understanding of local needs. The event highlighted the potential of technology to create opportunities. Arizona State University&amp;rsquo;s DinéLink team won first place, earning $10,000 for their impactful proposal. #Cisco #EmpowerAndConnect #Innovation #SocialImpact #TechnologyForGood</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From the Captain’s Chair: Igor Aleksandrov</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14058/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14058/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Meet Igor Aleksandrov, a Docker Captain and CTO of JetRockets! In the latest &amp;ldquo;From the Captain’s Chair&amp;rdquo; series, Igor shares his journey from dealing with dependency issues in Rails to embracing Docker for a unified approach in development. His team prioritized consistency, implementing Docker in production first to tackle challenges effectively. 🛠️ Igor aims to engage more with the Atlanta tech community and speak at conferences to share his insights on containerization and Rails best&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last week in AWS re:Invent with Corey Quinn</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14040/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14040/</guid>
      <description>Last week at AWS re:Invent, Ryan Donovan spoke with Corey Quinn, Chief Cloud Economist at Duckbill. They explored the impact of AI agents and the focus on large enterprises by AWS. Corey highlighted the challenges faced by startups and independent developers in this landscape, noting a shift towards more inclusive technology offerings. For more insights, check Ryan’s recap on our blog! #AWS #CloudComputing #AI #TechTrends #StartupInsights 🚀💻📊</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdTour 2026: Securing the AI Era Together</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14083/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14083/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The AI era is transforming cybersecurity as organizations adopt AI for innovation while adversaries enhance their attack methods. CrowdTour 2026 aims to unite industry experts to discuss these changes. This global roadshow will feature insights on AI-driven defense, real-world customer stories, and collaborative strategies to prevent breaches. Key themes include: 1️⃣ Defeating AI-accelerated adversaries 2️⃣ Transforming Security Operations Centers (SOCs) 3️⃣ Governing and securing AI across&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Innovation: How Atlassian Williams Racing Drives Success with Rovo</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13979/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 22:42:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13979/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian Williams Racing is transforming teamwork with Rovo, enhancing their System of Work. 🏎️💡 Data silos in Formula 1 can hinder performance, but Rovo centralizes engineering knowledge for quicker insights. This tool allows teams to find and act on critical data efficiently. By using Confluence for documentation, engineers can track experiments and share insights, maximizing the value of their simulations. Discover how Rovo amplifies expertise and improves collaboration. #Atlassian&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deck the halls with Webex calls: How Cisco technology brings holiday cheer to hospitals</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13950/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:59:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13950/</guid>
      <description>Cisco’s Connected Santa program uses Webex technology to bring holiday cheer to children in hospitals. 🎄 For 17 years, Cisco volunteers have enabled virtual visits from Santa, reaching thousands of kids across the U.K., Ireland, and beyond. This year, over 300 children in 15 hospitals participated. Joanne Bugg, a dedicated volunteer for 13 years, leads the initiative in the U.K. 🎅 #ConnectedSanta #Cisco #HolidayCheer #Webex #CommunitySupport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industry Leaders on the KotlinConf’25 Stage: What Global Brands Built With Kotlin</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13929/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 10:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13929/</guid>
      <description>🌍 KotlinConf 2025 showcased how global brands like Meta, AWS, Duolingo, and Uber utilize Kotlin for real-world engineering challenges. Developers shared insights on navigation, performance, and cross-platform architecture. Key talks included AWS&amp;rsquo;s massive multiplatform project, Duolingo&amp;rsquo;s productivity with Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP), and Google Workspace&amp;rsquo;s deployment experiences. Join KotlinConf 2026 to connect with industry leaders! #KotlinConf #Kotlin #SoftwareEngineering #TechCommunity #KMP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the winners of the inaugural Databricks Free Edition Hackathon</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13832/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13832/</guid>
      <description>🚀 We are thrilled to announce the winners of the inaugural Databricks Free Edition Hackathon! Participants showcased their innovative solutions using Databricks, demonstrating impressive skills and creativity. The event highlighted the power of collaboration and the potential of data analytics. Congratulations to all the winners! 🏆✨ #Databricks #Hackathon #DataAnalytics #Innovation #Winners</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Cisco at NRF 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13604/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 16:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13604/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Cisco at NRF 2026! Join us in New York City from January 11-13, 2026, for Retail’s Big Show. This year&amp;rsquo;s theme, &amp;ldquo;Welcome to the next now,&amp;rdquo; highlights the transformative changes in retail powered by Cisco technology. Learn how we’re helping retailers enhance their operations through AI-ready infrastructure. Our booth will feature Cisco Store technology and insightful theater sessions. Don’t miss this opportunity to see how we’re shaping the future of retail! #NRF2026 #Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your 2025 Stacked: A year of knowledge, community, and impact</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13864/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13864/</guid>
      <description>🚀 2025 was a significant year for Stack Internal! Your 2025 Stacked is now available, showcasing the collective achievements of your community. This summary highlights key contributions, including top contributors and popular posts that shaped your year. From engaging questions to impactful articles, see how knowledge sharing drove your organization forward. Explore this year&amp;rsquo;s highlights and celebrate your team&amp;rsquo;s efforts! 🌟📈 #StackInternal #KnowledgeSharing #CommunityImpact #YearInReview&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live from re:Invent…it’s Stack Overflow!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13865/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13865/</guid>
      <description>📢 Live from AWS re:Invent! Ryan Donovan hosts Stack Overflow&amp;rsquo;s CEO Prashanth Chandrasekar and Director of Data Science Michael Foree. They discuss key themes from the event, including AI agents and the enterprise&amp;rsquo;s trust issues regarding AI. Prashanth highlights the growing interest in AI, emphasizing the need for trust in its adoption. For more insights, check out the full recap on our blog! #AWS #AI #TechTrends #StackOverflow #reInvent2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building the Future Together: Introducing the Twilio Partner Advisory Board</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13983/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13983/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Twilio has announced the formation of its Partner Advisory Board, aimed at collaborating with top system integrators and tech partners. This initiative is set to influence product strategy and enhance offerings in global markets starting in 2026. Stay tuned for updates as they work together to shape the future! #Twilio #Partnerships #TechInnovation #ProductStrategy #AdvisoryBoard</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At AWS re:Invent, the news was agents, but the focus was developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13866/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13866/</guid>
      <description>AWS re:Invent brought together around 60,000 developers in Las Vegas for four days of innovation and networking. Key announcements focused on AI agents, including Kiro developer, security, and DevOps agents. These autonomous agents aim to enhance application efficiency and security. AWS also introduced AWS Transform, aimed at reducing tech debt, and discussed the importance of policy guardrails for agent collaboration. Additionally, AI Factories were announced to cater to entities needing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apply to present at Unreal Fest Chicago 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13676/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13676/</guid>
      <description>📣 Calling all creators! Unreal Fest Chicago 2026 is seeking speakers to share their projects and technical insights. If you have experience with Epic tools and want to showcase your work, now is the time to submit your session proposal! Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the opportunity to contribute to this exciting event. #UnrealFest #EpicGames #GameDev #SpeakersWanted #Chicago2026</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating excellence: Unity Awards 2025 winners.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-09-13489/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-09-13489/</guid>
      <description>🏆 The Unity Awards 2025 recognized outstanding achievements across various fields. 📅 This year&amp;rsquo;s ceremony highlighted individuals and organizations committed to promoting unity and excellence in their communities. 👏 Winners were honored for their innovative contributions and dedication to positive change. Join us in celebrating their success! #UnityAwards2025 #Excellence #CommunityImpact #CelebratingSuccess</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating excellence: Unity Awards 2025 winners.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-09-13495/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-09-13495/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Celebrating excellence at the 17th Unity Awards 2025! This year saw over 700 project submissions, with 14,000 voters casting more than 36,000 votes. The competition was intense, with many categories decided by narrow margins, showcasing exceptional talent in the Unity community. A big thank you to all nominees and to everyone who joined the live showcase! 🙌 #UnityAwards #Creativity #Innovation #GameDevelopment #Community</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Gets an AI Conformance Program — and VMware Is Already On Board</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13570/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 20:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13570/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Cloud Native Computing Foundation has launched the Certified Kubernetes AI Conformance Program to tackle fragmentation in AI workloads. VMware’s vSphere Kubernetes Service is among the first to achieve certification, enhancing interoperability across platforms. Experts emphasize the importance of portability for seamless application movement between public and private clouds. Learn more about this initiative from KubeCon + CloudNativeCon! 🌐 #Kubernetes #AI #CloudComputing #VMware #CNCF</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS re:Invent keynote recap, on-demand videos, and more (December 8, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13566/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:05:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13566/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The week following AWS re:Invent is a great opportunity to explore key announcements and their potential impact. One highlight was Rafi Quisumbing receiving the Now Go Build Award for his commitment to community building in the Philippines. 🎉 Keynotes emphasized the evolving role of developers and the rise of AI agents, with insights from AWS leaders on security, performance, and innovation. Watch the keynotes and sessions on-demand! 📹 #AWS #CloudComputing #AI #DeveloperCommunity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>See what Forge developers are building for Codegeist 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13520/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:28:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13520/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Codegeist 2025 is here, with Atlassian offering up to $120,000 in prizes! I reviewed early submissions and found three innovative apps addressing common challenges. 🔹 &lt;strong&gt;SimpleDesk&lt;/strong&gt; simplifies Jira project management, offering a cleaner interface for teams needing less complexity. 🔹 &lt;strong&gt;Monkey SQL&lt;/strong&gt; integrates SQL queries into the Atlassian ecosystem, enhancing productivity with transparent AI capabilities. 🔹 &lt;strong&gt;Forge Secure Notes&lt;/strong&gt; provides encrypted storage for sensitive information within&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How etcd Solved Its Knowledge Drain With Deterministic Testing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13512/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13512/</guid>
      <description>The article discusses how etcd addressed knowledge loss when maintainers left the project. Lead maintainer Marek Siarkowicz highlighted that turnover led to reliability issues and critical bugs in new releases. To tackle this, the team implemented &amp;ldquo;robustness testing&amp;rdquo; and developed a framework inspired by Jepson. They aimed for linearizability in distributed systems, a significant challenge. Collaborating with Antithesis on deterministic simulation testing helped them better manage bugs and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Kaggle Grandmasters Win Artificial General Intelligence Competition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13502/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13502/</guid>
      <description>🏆 NVIDIA researchers have secured a significant victory in the Kaggle ARC Prize 2025 competition, a key indicator of advancements in artificial general intelligence (AGI). Ivan Sorokin and Jean-Francois Puget, part of the Kaggle Grandmasters of NVIDIA, topped the leaderboard with a score of 27.64%. Their team, NVARC, fine-tuned a 4B model variant that excelled against larger models at a low cost. The ARC-AGI benchmark tests AI&amp;rsquo;s ability to perform abstract reasoning with minimal examples,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks Wins Seven 2025 AWS Partner of the Year Awards</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13474/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 01:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13474/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks has achieved a remarkable milestone by winning seven AWS Partner of the Year Awards for 2025. These awards recognize Databricks&amp;rsquo; contributions to cloud data and machine learning solutions. This achievement highlights their strong partnership with AWS and commitment to innovation in technology. #Databricks #AWSPartner #Awards2025 #CloudComputing #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello Developer: December 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13460/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13460/</guid>
      <description>📅 In the December 2025 edition of Hello Developer, the App Store Award winners are highlighted. 🎨 You can sign up for new design and Liquid Glass activities starting in the new year. 🎥 Explore the latest videos added to the expanding video library. 📚 Discover the team behind the sticker-centric language-learning app, CapWords. 📝 Don’t miss updates to documentation and HIG. #HelloDeveloper #AppStoreAwards #LanguageLearning #DesignActivities #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Store Award winners announced</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13450/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 13:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13450/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Exciting news! The App Store has announced its award winners, highlighting the exceptional talent of developers globally. These awards recognize innovative apps that have made a significant impact. Join us in celebrating their achievements! 🌍👏 #AppStoreAwards #Developers #Innovation #TechCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Live Melbourne 2025 Reflections: Transforming Cisco Customer Experience with AI and Human Expertise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13421/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 13:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13421/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Reflecting on Cisco Live Melbourne 2025, Jacqui Guichelaar emphasized the importance of human connections in enhancing customer experiences. Keynote highlights focused on resilience and simplicity, introducing Cisco IQ, which offers personalized insights and automation. Feedback from customers and partners indicated strong support for this innovation. The event showcased successful partnerships, particularly with LTIMindtree, highlighting the impact of Cisco’s integrated approach on their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over 20 Unreal Engine titles nominated in The Game Awards 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13440/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13440/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news from The Game Awards 2025! Over 20 developers using Unreal Engine have received nominations this year. Notably, nearly a third of all nominated games were created with this powerful engine. Check out the complete list of nominees and celebrate the creativity in gaming! 🎮🏆 #GameAwards2025 #UnrealEngine #GamingCommunity #GameDevelopment #Nominees</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Us Anything During JetBrains AMA Week</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13372/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 11:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13372/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join JetBrains for AMA Week on Reddit from December 9–12! Our product teams will engage directly with developers to discuss your experiences with our tools. This is a great opportunity to share your feedback and influence future developments. Check the schedule for session times and participate! 💬 #JetBrains #AMAWeek #DeveloperCommunity #FeedbackMatters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Stories Of Developers Using JetBrains Rider to Create, Collaborate, and Have Fun</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13373/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 09:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13373/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains Rider has introduced a free non-commercial license, encouraging developers to explore coding without financial constraints. Recently, they shared inspiring stories from users who embraced this opportunity. From a cloud architect creating a digital board game to a self-taught programmer developing a productivity app, curiosity drives innovation. These narratives highlight the joy of coding beyond commerce. #JetBrains #CodingCommunity #CuriosityDriven #DeveloperStories&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GovWare 2025 Security Operations Centre</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13293/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 06:03:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13293/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The GovWare 2025 Security Operations Centre, a collaboration with Cisco, aims to enhance security for the upcoming conference. Key missions include: - &lt;strong&gt;Protect&lt;/strong&gt;: Safeguarding the network from various threats. - &lt;strong&gt;Educate&lt;/strong&gt;: Offering SOC tours and informative content for attendees. - &lt;strong&gt;Innovate&lt;/strong&gt;: Advancing security through new tech and AI. Attendees can join the secure network while following best practices. #GovWare2025 #CyberSecurity #Innovation #Cisco #TechEvent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Time2Give Led Me to Africa — and to New Lessons in Leadership and Inclusion</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13214/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13214/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Last fall, Susan C. shared her transformative experience through Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Time2Give program, which led her to Zimbabwe. She met Dr. Tererai Trent, who inspired her with her mission to empower girls and build sustainable futures. This motivated Susan to volunteer with Tererai Trent International, utilizing her communications skills. After discussing a potential trip to Zimbabwe, Susan received swift approval from her manager to pursue this opportunity. 🌍✈️ #Leadership #Inclusion #Volunteer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking Attacks With Cisco XDR at the GovWare SOC</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13295/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13295/</guid>
      <description>🚨 During GovWare, Cisco XDR played a crucial role in detecting and responding to security incidents. The SOC team identified 39 incidents, with 12 posing direct threats to security. Cisco XDR&amp;rsquo;s integration with various tools allowed for swift analysis, reducing response times significantly. Key incidents were reported to the GovWare NOC for further action. #CyberSecurity #CiscoXDR #GovWare #IncidentResponse #ThreatDetection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Splunk SOAR in Action at the GovWare: Zero-Touch Clear Text Password Response</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13296/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13296/</guid>
      <description>At GovWare 2025, the Cisco Security Operations Centre showcased how they automated the incident response process using Splunk SOAR and Splunk Enterprise Security (ES). 🔒 Their goals included protecting the conference network, educating attendees about security risks, and driving innovation. A previous dashboard identified vulnerabilities from clear text credentials in network traffic. 📊 The integration of ES with Splunk SOAR transformed their manual response process into an automated system,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GovWare Captive Portal: (Splash Page)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13297/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13297/</guid>
      <description>Cisco partnered with GovWare 2025 to create a click-through captive portal for the conference. This marked the first time attendees had access to a wireless network. The project faced challenges due to compliance issues at the Marina Bay Sands. Cisco pivoted from using a firewall to the Identity Services Engine (ISE) for better management of attendee connections. Ultimately, a solution was found using DHCP option 114, allowing the portal to be advertised effectively. #GovWare2025 #Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clair Obscur: Expedition 33: autonomy, creativity, and community key to Sandfall Interactive’s success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13226/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13226/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting insights from Tom Guillermin of Sandfall Interactive on the development of the acclaimed game Clair Obscur: Expedition 33. He shares his journey with Unreal Engine and highlights how UE5 contributed to the game&amp;rsquo;s success. Check out the full interview for more details! 🎮✨ #GameDevelopment #UnrealEngine #ClairObscur #GOTY #IndieGames</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Live for You: Migration to Cisco Secure Firewall</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13153/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:04:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13153/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to simplify your firewall migration? At Cisco Live APJC, Principal Engineer Raghu Kulkarni shared insights on transitioning to Cisco Secure Firewall without the usual downtime fears. He highlighted that 95% of the migration can be staged in advance. Key points included tools for migration, essential pre-checks, and strategies for existing Firepower device configurations. Preparation is key: identify stakeholders and ensure your environment is ready for a smooth transition. #CiscoLive&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Live for You: AIOps for Cisco Secure Firewall</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13154/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13154/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco Live APJC highlighted the importance of AIOps for Cisco Secure Firewall in enhancing operational efficiency and security. Gayathri Nagarajan explained the complexities of firewall management, emphasizing the need for quick issue resolution to prevent costly downtimes, which can average $300,000 per hour. AIOps simplifies troubleshooting with features like single-click issue identification and proactive insights, reducing both detection and remediation times significantly. For firewall&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks at NeurIPS 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13190/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13190/</guid>
      <description>Databricks is excited to be a platinum sponsor at NeurIPS 2025! 🎉 The conference will showcase advancements in AI and machine learning, bringing together experts and enthusiasts from around the world. Join us to explore innovative solutions and engage in insightful discussions. Stay tuned for updates! #NeurIPS2025 #Databricks #AI #MachineLearning #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Livestream: Engineers Talk About Spring Boot 4, Life, and Other Stuff</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13159/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13159/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join us for an insightful livestream featuring the Spring team and Evgeny Borisov! 🗓️ Date: December 11, 2025 🕓 Time: 4:00–5:00 pm UTC We&amp;rsquo;ll dive into the latest updates in Spring Boot 4, explore how they enhance developer productivity, and discuss migration considerations. The session will also cover community insights and more. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to learn from the experts! #SpringBoot #JavaDevelopment #IntelliJIDEA #Livestream #TechTalks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Decade of Defense: Celebrating Grab&#39;s 10th Year Bug Bounty Program</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13140/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13140/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Celebrating 10 years of Grab&amp;rsquo;s Bug Bounty Program with HackerOne! From a small group of 23 researchers, we&amp;rsquo;ve grown into a global community of over 850 security experts. Together, we protect 187 million users across Southeast Asia. Our program adapts to new threats and includes initiatives like mobile security and exclusive global campaigns to enhance collaboration. Here’s to continued partnerships and a secure digital future! 🌏🔐 #Cybersecurity #BugBounty #Collaboration #Grab #HackerOne</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025’s ‘Advent of Code’ Event Chooses Tradition Over AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-30-13137/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 14:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-30-13137/</guid>
      <description>🎉 The countdown to the 2025 &amp;ldquo;Advent of Code&amp;rdquo; event begins! This year marks a significant change as the number of puzzles has been reduced from 25 to 12. Event creator Eric Wastl aims to make the challenge more accessible for participants. Despite advancements in AI, the coding community&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm for this holiday tradition remains strong. Last year, over 284,000 people engaged in the event, showcasing its popularity. Get ready for another exciting coding adventure! 🧑‍💻🎄 #AdventOfCode&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Cloud Native To AI Native: Where Are We Going?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13130/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 20:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13130/</guid>
      <description>Panelists at KubeCon + CloudNativeCon discussed the shift from cloud native to AI native technology. Jonathan Bryce emphasized the importance of inference in AI development beyond chatbots. He noted the need for robust models and an inference layer to effectively utilize large datasets. Kate Goldenring highlighted WebAssembly&amp;rsquo;s role in rapid inferencing, emphasizing security through sandboxing. The conversation reflects the evolving landscape of AI technology. #AINative #CloudNative&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Amazon Prepares for Black Friday: Predictive Modeling</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-28-12850/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 16:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-28-12850/</guid>
      <description>Amazon engineers discussed their strategies for handling Black Friday traffic during a recent keynote at Kubecon + CloudNativeCon NA. 📈 They emphasized that merely reacting to demand isn&amp;rsquo;t enough. Instead, Amazon uses predictive modeling to prepare for peak traffic surges, ensuring a smooth shopping experience for customers. With Black Friday approaching, these insights could benefit other retailers facing similar challenges. 🛒 #Amazon #BlackFriday #Ecommerce #TechInsights #Kubecon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2025: A Kotlin Playground</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 15:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13123/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Join us for Advent of Code 2025 from December 1–5! Participate in five days of Kotlin livestreams featuring experts and special guests. Solve puzzles, learn tips, and engage with the Kotlin community in Slack. 🛠️ Climb the leaderboards for a chance to win prizes and share your solutions on GitHub. Happy coding! 🚀 #AdventOfCode #Kotlin #CodingCommunity #Programming #LiveStream</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Went to BazelCon 2025 – Here’s Everything You Need to Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13089/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13089/</guid>
      <description>🎉 BazelCon 2025 took place at the Omni Atlanta Hotel, celebrating Bazel&amp;rsquo;s tenth anniversary. The event coincided with KubeCon, creating a vibrant atmosphere filled with tech discussions. JetBrains participated, providing insights on the Bazel for CLion plugin, gathering valuable user feedback. Key announcements included the deprecation of the WORKSPACE file and the introduction of Bzlmod as the default. Bazel 9 will disable autoloads, requiring explicit load statements in BUILD files for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KServe Joins CNCF To Standardize AI Model Serving on Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13080/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 20:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13080/</guid>
      <description>🚀 KServe has officially joined the Cloud Native Computing Foundation (CNCF) as an incubating project at KubeCon+CloudNativeCon North America. This move highlights KServe’s role in standardizing AI model serving on Kubernetes, providing a scalable platform for enterprises. It aims to address the complexities of modern AI workloads. KServe focuses on multinode inference for large language models, enhancing efficiency in cloud-native AI infrastructure. Developed by industry leaders like Google&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building the future: highlights from Dropbox’s 2025 summer intern class</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13081/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13081/</guid>
      <description>This summer, Dropbox welcomed 43 interns as part of the 2025 Camp Dropbox Intern Program. 🌍 They came from 27 colleges, including six international institutions. Over 12 weeks, interns worked on impactful projects, especially related to Dropbox Dash, our AI-powered search tool. They received over 6,000 hours of mentorship and participated in various community-building events. 🤝 Interns shared their experiences, highlighting technical achievements and personal growth throughout their time at&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8th Global Partner Innovation Challenge: Celebrating this year’s Partnering for Purpose winners</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13075/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 18:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13075/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The 8th Global Partner Innovation Challenge showcased impressive innovation at the Cisco Partner Summit 2025. This year saw a record 76 submissions in the Partnering for Purpose category, focusing on energy, healthcare, and emergency response. Notably, 76% included AI, highlighting the use of emerging technology for impactful solutions. Congratulations to the four winners who represent the best in purpose-driven innovation! 🎉 #InnovationChallenge #PartneringForPurpose #TechForGood #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon CTO Werner Vogels’ Predictions for 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13034/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 16:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13034/</guid>
      <description>Amazon&amp;rsquo;s CTO, Werner Vogels, shared key insights at AWS re:Invent, marking a shift in his approach. This year, he provided predictions ahead of the event, hinting it might be his last keynote. His predictions focus on AI and its societal effects, including redefining companionship, quantum-safe encryption, and the fast transition of military tech to consumer products. Vogels emphasized the need for younger voices in tech, reflecting on his 21 years at Amazon. #AWS #WernerVogels&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Together – How Cisco, the NFL and Real Madrid Brought the First-Ever NFL Game to Spain</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13032/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 11:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13032/</guid>
      <description>🏟️ Historic moments unfolded at Bernabéu Stadium as the NFL played its first game in Spain, thanks to Cisco&amp;rsquo;s collaboration with Real Madrid. This event showcased the seamless integration of technology and sports, highlighting Cisco&amp;rsquo;s commitment to enhancing fan experiences. The partnership between Cisco, the NFL, and Real Madrid exemplifies the power of teamwork in the sports industry. #NFLinSpain #Cisco #RealMadrid #SportsInnovation #Partnerships</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: How to join AWS re:Invent 2025, plus Kiro GA, and lots of launches (Nov 24, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13018/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting updates from AWS! Join us next week for AWS re:Invent from Dec. 1-5, 2025, in Las Vegas. Whether attending in person or tuning in via livestream, be ready for the latest AWS news and insights. Check the agenda and session catalog before you arrive! Kiro, the AI coding tool, is now generally available with new features, including property-based testing and centralized management for enterprise teams. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss other recent launches, including Amazon EC2 P6-B300 instances and new&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepnote CEO: Why Notebooks Are the ‘Perfect User Interface’ for AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12993/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:19:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12993/</guid>
      <description>Deepnote CEO Jakob Jurových discusses the evolution of data tools and the role of notebooks in AI. He identifies a gap between simple tools like spreadsheets and advanced solutions that require extensive learning. Deepnote aims to bridge this gap by enhancing collaboration in data exploration. Jurových announces Deepnote&amp;rsquo;s transition to open source, highlighting its innovative format designed for cloud and AI integration. 📊💻✨ #Deepnote #AI #OpenSource #DataScience #Collaboration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building the Future of AI Agents and Intelligence Apps: Celebrating 4 years of Databricks Seattle R&amp;D</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13005/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 18:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13005/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Celebrating 4 years of innovation at Databricks Seattle R&amp;amp;D! Since opening in November 2021, the team has focused on developing AI agents and intelligence applications. Their efforts have significantly advanced AI technology, contributing to various sectors. Stay tuned for more updates on their groundbreaking work! #AI #Innovation #Databricks #Seattle #ResearchAndDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Six ways Cisco is Powering Intelligent Transportation for a Better Future.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12996/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12996/</guid>
      <description>🚦 At the recent ITS World Congress, Cisco highlighted its role in transforming Intelligent Transportation Systems (ITS) for a safer and smarter future. 🌍 Key challenges include integrating diverse vendor technologies. Cisco addresses this by promoting an open, standards-based networking approach, enabling seamless communication among different ITS devices. 💡 The event featured discussions on AI, sustainability, and vehicle safety, aiming to tackle global transportation issues such as traffic&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the 2025 EMEA GitLab Partner Award winners</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12979/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12979/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Proud to announce the 2025 EMEA GitLab Partner Award winners! This year, exceptional partners in the EMEA region were recognized for their DevSecOps expertise and contributions. Key awards include: 🏆 &lt;strong&gt;Regional Partner of the Year&lt;/strong&gt;: - &lt;strong&gt;Central Europe&lt;/strong&gt;: cc cloud GmbH - &lt;strong&gt;Northern Europe&lt;/strong&gt;: Adaptavist - &lt;strong&gt;Southern Europe&lt;/strong&gt;: knowmad mood - &lt;strong&gt;Meta Region&lt;/strong&gt;: Digital Future - &lt;strong&gt;Emerging Markets&lt;/strong&gt;: Cloudfresh 🏅 &lt;strong&gt;Best Technical Solution&lt;/strong&gt;: D|OPS Digital 🏅 &lt;strong&gt;Most Certified Partner&lt;/strong&gt;: Devoteam 🏅&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rising Importance of Governance at SwampUP Berlin 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12962/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 22:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12962/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Docker team participated in JFrog SwampUP Berlin 2025 from November 12-14, engaging in technical sessions and discussions. Key insights included the rise of software supply chain attacks, where malicious actors are using AI to exploit open-source packages. 🔒 Governance plays a crucial role in preventing these attacks by controlling entry points in the software lifecycle. Tools must enhance interoperability to detect risks effectively. Additionally, discussions highlighted the importance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Excellence: Cisco Customer Achievement Awards APJC 2025 Winners Announced!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12949/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:11:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12949/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Exciting news from Cisco Live 2025 in Melbourne! The winners of the Cisco Customer Achievement Awards: APJC 2025 have been announced. These awards honor organizations and individuals who have showcased outstanding innovation and leadership in the Asia Pacific, Japan, and Greater China regions. The winners are recognized for driving digital transformation and creating meaningful outcomes through technology. A heartfelt congratulations to all finalists for their dedication to excellence!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktoberfest 2025 Comes to a Close</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12950/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12950/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Hacktoberfest 2025 has wrapped up, marking its 12th year of bringing open-source communities together! This year&amp;rsquo;s event welcomed over 56,000 participants from 176 countries, with a new requirement of 6 pull requests to enhance engagement and impact. Participants made 87,929 contributions, showcasing the growth of the community. 🌍✨ In-person hackathons were held in seven cities, and online events supported newcomers in their open-source journey. Digital badges were awarded, including a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Open Source Program: Fall 2025 cohort</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12953/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12953/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news from Vercel! The Fall 2025 cohort of the Open Source Program is here. This initiative supports open-source maintainers with resources, credits, and guidance to enhance their projects. The program showcases innovative work in AI-native applications, developer infrastructure, and more. Discover the talented creators and their amazing projects today! 🚀💻 #OpenSource #Vercel #Innovation #TechCommunity #Fall2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google’s Web AI Playbook: The Paved Road vs. the Open Field</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12914/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 22:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12914/</guid>
      <description>🖥️ At the recent Google Web AI Summit, the focus was on client-side AI in browsers. Key discussions included Model Context Protocol (MCP) and its web variant, WebMCP, which help developers utilize device hardware more effectively. 💻 Parisa Tabriz from Google emphasized the transformative impact of AI on web development, referring to it as a &amp;ldquo;renaissance of the web.&amp;rdquo; She reassured attendees of Google&amp;rsquo;s commitment to an open and interoperable web, highlighting advancements like WebAssembly and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pulse: Cloudflare takes down half the internet – but shares a great postmortem</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12913/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12913/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare recently experienced a significant outage, impacting thousands of websites, including major platforms like ChatGPT, Dropbox, and Reddit. The outage lasted six hours, highlighting the reliance many services have on Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s content delivery network. In response, Cloudflare released a detailed postmortem to explain the root cause, which stemmed from a database permissions change. Additionally, The Pragmatic Engineer is launching The Pragmatic Summit, aimed at connecting engineers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adam Jacob on Why Scaling Is ‘The Funnest Game’</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12903/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12903/</guid>
      <description>At the Monster Scale Summit 2025, Adam Jacob discussed the complexities of software at scale. He emphasized that while scaling is a thrilling challenge, it can invite criticism. Jacob highlighted the importance of ensuring software remains functional under load. Quality and speed should be balanced, especially in the early stages of development. Join the upcoming Monster SCALE Summit 2026 on March 11-12 for insights from industry experts. #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTalk #Scaling&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevRel newsletter — November 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12894/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12894/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Check out the latest DevRel newsletter from Elastic! This November, we highlight Elastic 9.2, featuring significant updates like agentic workflows in Kibana, AI-assisted log pipelines, and a new on-disk vector index. Explore complimentary on-demand trainings and stay informed on the latest blogs, videos, and upcoming events. #Elastic #DevRel #TechNews #AI #Kibana</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Amazon Prepares for Black Friday</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12850/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12850/</guid>
      <description>Amazon engineers discussed their strategies for handling Black Friday traffic during a recent keynote at Kubecon + CloudNativeCon NA. 📈 They emphasized that merely reacting to demand isn&amp;rsquo;t enough. Instead, Amazon uses predictive modeling to prepare for peak traffic surges, ensuring a smooth shopping experience for customers. With Black Friday approaching, these insights could benefit other retailers facing similar challenges. 🛒 #Amazon #BlackFriday #Ecommerce #TechInsights #Kubecon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Store Award finalists announced</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12846/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 14:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12846/</guid>
      <description>🎉 The App Store Awards are back, honoring apps and games that enhance lives through innovation and design. This year, 49 finalists have been selected for their exceptional contributions and cultural impact. 🌟 Stay tuned as winners will be announced in the coming weeks! #AppStoreAwards #Innovation #Tech #Gaming #AppFinalists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cisco’s Time2Give Connects Careers, Global Strategy, and Local Impact</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12832/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 13:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12832/</guid>
      <description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Time2Give program enables employees to spend 80 hours of paid time off on community service. Marley Pirochta and her team recently restored trails in Acadia National Park, collaborating with the Sierra Club and Friends of Acadia. This initiative links global strategy to local impact, showcasing Cisco&amp;rsquo;s commitment to sustainability. 🌍🌲 #Cisco #Time2Give #CommunityService #Sustainability #AcadiaNationalPark</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highlights from the Unite 2025 Keynote</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12866/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12866/</guid>
      <description>This week, Unity developers gathered in Barcelona for Unite 2025. The Keynote featured key announcements, including new tools for game development and partnerships aimed at enhancing the gaming ecosystem. 🎮 A surprise appearance by Tim Sweeney from Epic Games highlighted collaboration efforts, such as bringing Unity games into Fortnite. New features like the Platform Toolkit and AI Gateway were also introduced to simplify development. 🚀 Unity&amp;rsquo;s commitment to supporting developers continues to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extraordinary Together: From Adoption to Acceleration at Cisco Connect Canada</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12750/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 10:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12750/</guid>
      <description>📅 Join us on November 19 at Cisco Connect Canada in Toronto! This event focuses on bridging the gap between technology deployment and achieving real impact. Attendees will explore how AI is transforming organizational operations and the importance of strong partnerships. Cisco emphasizes the need for tailored support to accelerate outcomes, enabling businesses to maximize their investments. #CiscoConnect #AI #CustomerExperience #TechInnovation #BusinessTransformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Databricks at Microsoft Ignite 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12737/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12737/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Azure Databricks participated as a Visionary-level sponsor at Microsoft Ignite 2025 in San Francisco. They highlighted strategies for organizations to unify data, analytics, and AI on the Azure platform. This collaboration aims to enhance business intelligence and streamline operations. Stay updated on these advancements! #AzureDatabricks #MicrosoftIgnite #DataAnalytics #AI #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Lambda, load balancers, Amazon DCV, Amazon Linux 2023, and more (November 17, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12727/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 17:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12727/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from AWS! In preparation for AWS re:Invent, three new talks will cover Apple Silicon optimization with EC2 Mac, and AI development in Swift. 🎉 Welcome to the new AWS Heroes: Dimple, Rola, and Vivek! The GenAI Loft is now open in Tel Aviv, offering tailored sessions for startups and developers until November 19. 🔧 Key launches include AWS Lambda now supporting Rust and Java 25, along with a new Provisioned Mode for SQS event source mapping. #AWS #CloudComputing #Serverless&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Your Calendars! Qodana Events in November</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 10:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12200/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Mark your calendars for November! The JetBrains Qodana team is hosting events focused on secure workflows and high-quality code. 📅 On November 18, Grigorii Liullin will discuss integrating security into IDEs in JRush Episode 6. 📅 Join the Qodana livestream on November 19 to explore modern enterprise practices for building secure code. 📅 Lastly, don’t miss the meetup in Utrecht on November 26, centered around AI applications. #JetBrains #Qodana #SoftwareDevelopment #SecureCode #AIApplications</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Is Heading to VSLive! Orlando</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-15-12190/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 01:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-15-12190/</guid>
      <description>📢 JetBrains is heading to Visual Studio Live! in Orlando next week! 🎉 Join us at booth #118 in the expo area to explore our .NET tools, including live demos of ReSharper and Rider. Learn about our support for .NET 10 and Visual Studio 2026. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the chance to ask questions, discuss product roadmaps, and grab some JetBrains swag! We will also have special offers for booth visitors. #JetBrains #VSLive #dotNET #OrlandoEvents #TechCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building with Forge: Recap from the Atlassian Builders’ Summit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12118/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12118/</guid>
      <description>📅 Last month, around 150 Atlassian practitioners gathered at the Atlassian Builders’ Summit to explore Forge. The event featured presentations, hands-on workshops, and expert sessions aimed at empowering both admins and non-developers to build impactful apps and enhance security. Key sessions included a keynote by Matt Doar on the relevance of Forge, and practical workshops led by Liz Tanner and Darryl Lee, focusing on app development for non-developers. Tanya Botta concluded with insights on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Physics to the Future: Brian Granger on Project Jupyter in the Age of AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-11977/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 16:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-11977/</guid>
      <description>Brian Granger, co-creator of Project Jupyter, discusses the evolution of Jupyter Notebooks and its impact on open source sustainability. 🌐📊 In an interview at JupyterCon, he shares insights on the project&amp;rsquo;s origins and its adaptability in the age of AI. Granger emphasizes Jupyter&amp;rsquo;s modular design, which allows it to address complex problems effectively. He highlights that Jupyter was not initially meant for software engineering, but rather for fostering human reasoning in challenging&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco at AutoCon 4: AI, Automation, and the Human Side of ‘Ops’</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12005/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 22:13:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12005/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At AutoCon 4, taking place from November 17–21, 2025, in Austin, TX, Cisco will showcase the impact of AI and automation on network operations. 🤖 Network engineers are encouraged to embrace automation, as it is becoming essential in the industry. Those who leverage these tools will have a competitive edge. 🌟 Join the conversation at the Cisco booth to explore effective strategies, tools, and processes that drive success. #Cisco #AutoCon4 #AI #Automation #NetworkEngineering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Summer of Code 2025: What Our Contributors Built</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12037/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 20:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12037/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Congratulations to the contributors and mentors of Google Summer of Code 2025! This year&amp;rsquo;s projects have significantly impacted the Kotlin ecosystem. 🔍 Highlights include the IntelliJ Platform Gradle Plugin, which improved reporting and build speeds, and enhancements to Configuration Cache for faster Gradle builds. Many contributors shared their experiences, emphasizing the value of mentorship and collaboration in their growth. 🌟 Thank you for your dedication and hard work! #GSoC2025&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Our Final AWS Heroes of 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12137/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 20:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12137/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news as we approach AWS re:Invent! We&amp;rsquo;re celebrating three remarkable AWS Heroes: Dimple Vaghela, Rola Dali, and Vivek Velso. Each has made significant contributions to the cloud community through their unique journeys and commitment to knowledge sharing. Dimple leads AWS User Groups in India, empowering women in tech and rural communities. Rola, an expert in AI and data, mentors women and students in Montreal. Vivek specializes in generative AI, sharing his extensive knowledge&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Google Is Shifting AI From the Cloud to Your Browser</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-11987/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-11987/</guid>
      <description>🌐 The recent Google Web AI summit highlighted a shift towards running AI directly in web browsers. Organizer Jason Mayes discussed the transition from “Web ML” to “Web AI,” reflecting industry terminology changes. The focus is now on client-side AI, with technologies like LiteRT.js, designed for efficient inference in the browser. Google aims to enhance deployability and privacy while leaving model training to Python. #WebAI #MachineLearning #GoogleAI #TechTrends #AIInBrowser</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KubeCon: A Terraform Killer Built on Apple’s Pkl</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-11988/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-11988/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A new solution for Infrastructure as Code (IaC) challenges is here! Platform Engineering Labs has introduced Formae, an open-source platform built on Apple’s Pkl language. This aims to simplify IaC and address common pain points like complexity and error-prone YAML files. Attendees at KubeCon+CloudNativeCon can see a demo at Booth No. 2152. #KubeCon #InfrastructureAsCode #OpenSource #TechInnovation #Formae</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parenting Through Chronic Illness: My Journey with Cisco by My Side</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12007/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12007/</guid>
      <description>Angee B. shares her journey of parenting a teenager with chronic kidney disease while working at Cisco. In 2019, a routine illness turned into a life-altering diagnosis. Angee highlights the support and flexibility Cisco provides, allowing her to balance work and her daughter’s needs. It’s a testament to the importance of workplace support for parents. 🤝💼💖 #ChronicIllness #Parenting #WorkplaceSupport #Cisco #HealthJourney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf 2025 Recordings Are Now Live</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12039/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12039/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf 2025 took place on November 5, focusing on plugin development for JetBrains IDEs. 🎥 If you missed it, recordings of all sessions are now available on YouTube. The event gathered over 1,000 viewers and featured 10 speakers sharing insights on various topics, including plugin creation and AI-powered tools. 🙏 A huge thank you to all participants and speakers for making this event successful! #JetBrains #PluginDevelopment #TechConference #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Livestream: Build Visual AI Agents with NVIDIA Cosmos Reason and Metropolis</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 22:22:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12020/</guid>
      <description>Join the upcoming livestream on November 18, where you&amp;rsquo;ll learn to fine-tune the NVIDIA Cosmos Reason VLM to create visual AI agents. 🕕 The session runs from 18:00 to 19:00 (CET). This is a great opportunity for anyone interested in AI and data-driven solutions. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out! #NVIDIA #AI #Livestream #VisualAI #TechEvent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: OpenAI partnership, Jane Goodall Institute research archive, and more (November 10, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12139/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12139/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Excitement builds for AWS re:Invent 2025, happening December 1-5 in Las Vegas! With registration still open, attendees can look forward to keynotes, breakout sessions, and networking opportunities. 🤝 AWS and OpenAI have announced a $38 billion partnership to optimize AI workloads using AWS infrastructure. This includes access to advanced GPU resources for enhanced performance. 📚 Additionally, AWS is investing $1 million to digitize the Jane Goodall Institute’s 65 years of primate research&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help Define the Future of Development – Take the Docker State of Application Development Survey 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12106/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12106/</guid>
      <description>📢 Join the Docker community by participating in the fourth annual State of Application Development survey! Your feedback is vital for shaping the future of application development. It takes just 20 minutes to share your insights on current trends and challenges. 🛍️ Complete the survey for a chance to win prizes, including a MacBook Pro, PlayStation 5, and Amazon gift cards! 🕒 The survey runs from November 10 to December 10, 2025. Be among the first 300 respondents to receive exclusive Docker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIGNAL Sydney 2025: A Sold‑out Debut on the Harbour</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12125/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12125/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Twilio SIGNAL made its debut in Sydney in 2025, bringing together 283 customers, partners, and industry leaders. This sold-out event highlighted innovation and collaboration within the tech community. Attendees engaged in discussions about the future of communication and technology. Stay tuned for more updates from SIGNAL! 🌏💡 #Twilio #SIGNAL2025 #TechEvents #Sydney #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer Experience is Ready to Roll at Cisco Live Melbourne</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-08-11881/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 00:36:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-08-11881/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco Live Melbourne is just around the corner! Join us for insights into Cisco Customer Experience (CX) at the event. Keynote speaker Jacqui Guichelaar will address &amp;ldquo;What’s Next, Starts Now!&amp;rdquo; on November 11. Not attending? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry! Keynotes and sessions will be available via broadcast. Explore how AI is reshaping services in our Centre Stage session. #CiscoLive #CustomerExperience #AIFuture #TechInnovation #Melbourne2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elevating the Future of the Customer Support Experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11883/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:19:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11883/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Cisco Live Melbourne! Buffy Ransom highlights the evolution in customer support at Cisco, focusing on a more personalized and proactive approach. The Technical Assistance Center (TAC) is transforming to meet growing IT demands with AI-driven solutions. Cisco IQ is introduced as a unified digital interface, offering real-time insights and tailored guidance to prevent issues before they arise. This shift aims to enhance the overall customer experience and empower teams&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Excellence: Our 2025 Global Award Winners</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11884/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11884/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Celebrating Excellence in the AI Era! 🌟 Cisco&amp;rsquo;s 2025 Global Award Winners were honored at the Partner Summit for their transformative impact on customer success. These partners showed exceptional innovation, business growth, and alignment with Cisco’s strategy. 🏆 Regional Winners: - APJC: ITOCHU Techno-Solutions Corporation - Americas: World Wide Technology - EMEA: Emircom These partners have co-innovated with Cisco, delivering AI-ready solutions and driving measurable outcomes&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Go Beyond Boundaries: Your CX Journey at Cisco Live Melbourne 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11885/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:50:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11885/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join Cisco Customer Experience at Cisco Live Melbourne 2025 from November 10-13 at the Melbourne Convention and Exhibition Centre! Explore innovative sessions and demos designed to enhance your Cisco investments and navigate the digital landscape. Not attending in person? Catch the Keynotes and sessions via digital broadcast. Discover solutions for digital resilience, future-proof workplaces, and AI-ready data centers. #CiscoLive #CustomerExperience #Innovation #TechEvent #Melbourne2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating partner excellence: The 2025–2026 Elastic Partner Awards</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11421/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11421/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Celebrating excellence in innovation, the 2025–2026 Elastic Partner Awards are underway! These awards honor partners globally for their significant contributions to Elastic&amp;rsquo;s Search AI Platform. Events kicked off in Bengaluru on September 24 and will continue in cities like New York, Amsterdam, and more. Awards are given in seven categories, including Top GenAI Partner and Top Services Partner, with updates provided as winners are announced. 🏆 Stay tuned for more! #ElasticPartnerAwards&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks Free Edition Hackathon: show the world what’s possible in data and AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-05-11854/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-05-11854/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Databricks Free Edition Hackathon is now live! This event encourages developers and students to explore the possibilities in data and AI. Participants can build AI applications, data science projects, and machine learning models using the Free Edition. Join the movement and showcase your skills! 🌍💻 #Databricks #Hackathon #AI #DataScience #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Partners Lead with AI, Everything Changes: Meet Cisco’s 2025 Partner Innovation Challenge Winners</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11829/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 19:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11829/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from the Cisco Partner Summit 2025! This year&amp;rsquo;s Partner Innovation Challenge celebrated groundbreaking AI solutions that address global challenges. With a 40% increase in submissions, partners showcased innovative approaches in areas like student support and sustainable energy. 🌍 The Grand Prize went to erlySense, which transforms student mental health support into a proactive model. The second place winner, Splid.AI, efficiently connects renewable energy with AI computing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HashiCorp at AWS re:Invent: Accelerate every step of your cloud journey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11820/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11820/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting times at AWS re:Invent! HashiCorp is a Diamond Sponsor, bringing hands-on learning and collaboration to Las Vegas from December 1-5. Join us at booth 439 for live product showcases, expert insights, and breakout sessions focused on automation and security in cloud environments. 🛠️ Don&amp;rsquo;t miss our demos on Terraform, Vault, and more! Plus, engage in technical discussions with our experts and collect exclusive swag. Check the AWS Session Catalog for sessions like &amp;ldquo;Run and Scale&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>There’s Never Been a Better Time to Partner with Cisco</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11702/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 14:11:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11702/</guid>
      <description>Exciting developments from the Cisco Partner Summit! 🚀 Tim Coogan highlights how Cisco is addressing the urgent needs of customers in the AI space. With new AI-ready solutions and enhanced partner programs, Cisco empowers partners to support evolving infrastructure demands. Key announcements include the Edge Compute portfolio, enabling AI workloads at the edge, and advancements to the AI-ready secure network architecture, ensuring operational simplicity and robust security for enterprises&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join Us for the Blackwell NVFP4 Kernel Hackathon with NVIDIA and GPU MODE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11673/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11673/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Join the Blackwell NVFP4 Kernel Hackathon! 🌟 This four-part performance challenge is hosted by NVIDIA in collaboration with GPU MODE, with support from Dell and Sesterce. Developers can showcase their skills and push performance limits. For event details and inquiries, reach out to the NVIDIA Developer Community Team. #Hackathon #NVIDIA #GPU #DeveloperCommunity #PerformanceChallenge</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kelsey Hightower on Engineering at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11659/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 18:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11659/</guid>
      <description>Kelsey Hightower emphasizes the importance of personal experience in engineering at scale. 🛠️ During the Monster SCALE Summit, he advised attendees not to rush into scaling without first understanding the challenges involved. His journey spans significant contributions to Puppet, CoreOS, and KubeCon, showcasing the lasting impact of his ideas. Join the upcoming Monster SCALE Summit on March 11-12 for more insights! 🌍💡 #Engineering #Kubernetes #Scaling #TechTalk #MonsterSCALE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Project Rainier online, Amazon Nova, Amazon Bedrock, and more (November 3, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11669/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11669/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Last week at AWS Shenzhen Community Day, Jeff Barr highlighted the global experimentation in generative AI and encouraged local developers to innovate. 👩‍💻 Attendees engaged in discussions on model grounding and applications, showcasing Kiro-themed demos and AI IoT projects. 🌐 Project Rainier, a powerful AI supercomputer, is now operational, utilizing nearly 500,000 Trainium2 chips for advanced model training. 🔍 Key launches include Amazon Nova&amp;rsquo;s new web retrieval tools and enhancements in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busy Plugin Developers Newsletter – Q3 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11665/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11665/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting updates for plugin developers from JetBrains! 📅 Mark your calendars for the JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf on November 5, 2025. This free online event will cover essential topics like plugin creation and the Language Server Protocol. 🧩 New features include resolved reviews that maintain visibility without affecting ratings, and updated requirements for plugin names and descriptions. 🔧 Check out the new IntelliJ Platform Compose Plugin Template for building modern UIs, along with&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Live session] Agentic developer workflows powered by Rovo Dev</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11640/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11640/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join us for a webinar on November 13th, 2025, focused on agentic developer workflows using Jira, Bitbucket, and Rovo Dev. Discover how Rovo Dev—our AI agent—can enhance code generation, reviews, and overall production speed. The session will include demos, getting started tips, and a live Q&amp;amp;A with Atlassian experts. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to transform your workflows! 🔗 Sign up now! #Webinar #AI #DevTools #Atlassian #RovoDev</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join the Unreal Engine simulation team at I/ITSEC 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11653/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11653/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join us at I/ITSEC 2025 to explore the latest in XR-based flight and drone simulator demos. Discover new updates for Unreal Engine focused on AI and robotics workflows. Learn how Epic ecosystem tools like MetaHuman and RealityScan can enhance your simulation projects. 📅 Book your meeting with us today! #IITSEC2025 #UnrealEngine #Simulation #AIFuture #Robotics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Money20/20 USA 2025: Fintech’s inflection point has arrived</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11674/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11674/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Money20/20 USA 2025 highlighted a pivotal moment for fintech, emphasizing the role of trusted data, explainable AI, and resilient infrastructure. The focus has shifted from experimentation to responsible execution. AI is now integral to finance, with leaders prioritizing its governance and scalability. Key discussions included the integration of AI in fraud detection, liquidity optimization, and enhancing customer experience. #Fintech #Money2020 #AI #Data #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Next.js Got Its Snappy Client Navs Back</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11532/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11532/</guid>
      <description>Frontend developer Sam Selikoff recently joined Vercel and questioned the Next.js team about achieving snappy client navigation with React Server Components (RSC). At the Next.js Conference, he highlighted the challenges of using RSCs while maintaining fast navigation, referencing past trends where frameworks moved rendering back to the server for improved performance. Selikoff discussed how companies like Twitter and Netflix have successfully enhanced load times and performance by&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating the magic cycle of research breakthroughs and real-world applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11558/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11558/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements were shared at the recent Research@ event by Google Research, showcasing breakthroughs in earth science, genomics, and quantum computing. These innovations are part of a “magic cycle” where research and real-world applications drive each other forward. Enhanced AI tools and open platforms are accelerating this process, leading to new opportunities in various fields. 🌍🔬 Stay tuned for more updates on how technology is shaping our future! #GoogleResearch #Innovation #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start Your Engines: Codegeist 2025 Hackathon Is Here</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11511/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11511/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Codegeist 2025 is now open! This annual hackathon invites developers to create apps that enhance teamwork and collaboration, inspired by the precision of racing crews. Participants can use Forge to build solutions for Jira and Confluence. With over $120,000 in prizes available, including $15,000 for grand prize winners, there’s plenty to gain. The submission window runs from October 27 to December 22. Join the community and showcase your talent! 💻🏆 #Codegeist2025 #Atlassian #Hackathon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live from the OpenAI forum: Learning to code in the age of AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11504/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11504/</guid>
      <description>Join us for a virtual fireside chat featuring our CEO, Prashanth Chandrasekar, at the OpenAI Forum! 🗣️ The discussion will focus on the evolving role of developers as AI technology advances. Many junior developers are understandably concerned about their future in the field. 🌐 Tune in on November 3 at 3 PM EDT to learn about insights from our 2025 Developer Survey and how we can support the next generation of engineers. 💻 #OpenAI #SoftwareDevelopment #FutureOfWork #AI #TechTalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy birthday, Repo! A look back on our mascot’s first year</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11489/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 12:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11489/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Happy 1st Birthday, Repo! 🎉 This year marked the debut of Repo, our helpful &amp;ldquo;reponaut,&amp;rdquo; who assists developers in managing complex coding challenges. Key events included advancements in Red Hat OpenShift AI and the successful growth of the Quarkus project, highlighting the focus on developer productivity. In 2025, major releases such as Red Hat Enterprise Linux 10 and the Red Hat OpenShift Lightspeed assistant enhanced the developer experience. The community continues to embrace AI and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating partner excellence: The 2025–2026 Elastic Partner Awards</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11421/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11421/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Celebrating excellence in innovation, the 2025–2026 Elastic Partner Awards are underway! These awards honor partners globally for their significant contributions to Elastic&amp;rsquo;s Search AI Platform. Events kicked off in Bengaluru on September 24 and will continue in cities like New York, Amsterdam, and more. Awards are given in seven categories, including Top GenAI Partner and Top Services Partner, with updates provided as winners are announced. 🏆 Stay tuned for more! #ElasticPartnerAwards&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Distributed Systems: Jason Taylor Shows How .NET Aspire Makes the Complex Feel Effortless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11455/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 14:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11455/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025, Jason Taylor showcased how .NET Aspire simplifies building distributed systems. He emphasized that &amp;ldquo;effortless&amp;rdquo; means reducing friction while focusing on delivering user-centric features. With just a few clicks, developers can enhance ASP.NET Core apps with automatic resilience and health checks. The local development experience is notably improved, allowing new team members to onboard quickly with one press of F5. Discover more in the full presentation!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Distributed Systems: Jason Taylor Shows How .NET Aspire Makes the Complex Feel Effortless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11628/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 14:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11628/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025, Jason Taylor, Microsoft MVP, introduced .NET Aspire, a tool aimed at simplifying distributed systems development. He emphasized that “effortless” means focusing effort where it counts, reducing unnecessary complexity. With just a few clicks, developers can enhance applications with features like automatic retry policies and service discovery. Taylor showcased how .NET Aspire improves local development, making onboarding new team members easier and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DroidKaigi 2025 – Koog で広がる Kotlin とAI の可能性</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11632/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 07:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11632/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Recently, I attended the DroidKaigi After Party hosted by KINTO Technologies and JetBrains. The focus was on the session “AI Utilization in Development with Kotlin,” particularly on the Koog framework. 📹 For those interested, you can watch the session video featuring Sebastian Aigner discussing Koog, an OSS Kotlin agent framework. 📚 I also shared insights on how to construct AI workflows using Koog and provided additional resources for further learning. For more details, check out the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of BPO in the Age of AI and Automation: A Conversational Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11474/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11474/</guid>
      <description>Discover insights from our recent webinar on the future of BPO in an era shaped by AI and automation. 🤖 Industry leaders discussed the impact of intelligent automation, the need for upskilling, and the role of hyper-personalization. They emphasized that human empathy and adaptability remain crucial for success. As BPOs face digital transformation, the conversation highlighted what’s next for the industry. 🌐 #BPO #AI #Automation #DigitalTransformation #FutureOfWork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreal Engine Student Showcase 2025 just dropped</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11443/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11443/</guid>
      <description>🎉 The 2025 Unreal Engine Student Showcase has been released! This year&amp;rsquo;s showcase features impressive projects from students in various fields, including games, film and TV, and animation. These creations highlight the talent and creativity of the next generation of developers and artists. Check out the inspiring work that is shaping the future! 🌟 #UnrealEngine #StudentShowcase #GameDevelopment #Animation #CreativeArts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brickster Voices: Meet Maggie Chu, Sr. Manager, Field Engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11461/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11461/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Maggie Chu, Sr. Manager of Field Engineering at Brickster! In the latest Brickster Voices feature, she shares her journey in building and scaling alongside customers. Her insights highlight the importance of collaboration and innovation in the engineering field. Discover more about the experiences that shape our team! #BricksterVoices #FieldEngineering #Leadership #CareerJourney #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Than a Warm-Up: Start KubeCon With a Colocated Event</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11337/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11337/</guid>
      <description>KubeCon + CloudNativeCon is evolving beyond keynotes and pavilions. Colocated events are becoming essential for attendees, offering targeted learning opportunities before the main conference. From newcomers to seasoned pros, there’s something for everyone. 🌟 One highlight is KyvernoCon, focusing on Policy as Code, which aids enterprises in managing Kubernetes efficiently. 🚀 GitOps is also gaining traction with the introduction of FluxCon, emphasizing the growing importance of these practices&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Bonds Beyond Business: How Human Connection Defines Cisco Culture</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11334/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 12:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11334/</guid>
      <description>Cole A. shares his experience in India, attending a teammate&amp;rsquo;s wedding, highlighting Cisco&amp;rsquo;s people-first culture. He reflects on the importance of human connections in achieving success, emphasizing that behind every project are dedicated individuals. His trip enriched his understanding of different cultures and reinforced his philosophy: people come first. 🤝🌍💼 #CiscoCulture #HumanConnection #PeopleFirst #Diversity #Teamwork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Customer Achievement Awards: APJC 2025 Finalists</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11310/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11310/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Cisco! The inaugural Cisco Customer Achievement Awards for the APJC region have been launched to honor organizations driving innovation and digital transformation. These awards expand on the previous CX Customer Hero Awards. Congratulations to the finalists in the AI Infrastructure Innovation Award and CX AI Trailblazer Award categories! 🎉 Stay tuned for the awards ceremony at Cisco Live Melbourne on November 10, 2025. #CiscoAwards #DigitalTransformation #Innovation #APJC&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Modern Enterprise Toolkit for Secure, High-Quality Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11311/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11311/</guid>
      <description>Join JetBrains Qodana on November 19, 2025, for a live session focused on embedding quality, security, and compliance into development workflows. Hosted by Kai Schmithuesen, learn about Qodana&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and how it integrates with DevOps. Key topics include secure code practices, enhanced access control, and insights for managing project health. Mark your calendars and register! 🗓️🔒 #JetBrains #DevOps #Qodana #SecureCoding #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Thompson Recalls Unix’s Rowdy, Lock-Picking Origins</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-26-11284/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 13:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-26-11284/</guid>
      <description>Ken Thompson reflects on the early days of the Unix operating system in a recent oral history at the Computer History Museum. 🎤 At 82, he shares memories of the collaborative environment at Bell Labs, where innovation thrived among a spirited group of tech enthusiasts. 💡 Thompson details his transition from the failed Multics project to the creation of Unix, emphasizing the importance of experimentation and community. He also shares a quirky anecdote about raising a baby alligator at the lab!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why PyTorch Won</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-25-11279/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 20:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-25-11279/</guid>
      <description>During the PyTorch Conference 2025 in San Francisco, I had the opportunity to interview Luca Antiga, a key figure in the PyTorch Foundation. Antiga shared insights on why PyTorch has thrived in the AI landscape. Its user-friendly, &amp;ldquo;pythonic&amp;rdquo; nature has made it a favorite among researchers, who have since transitioned to the tech industry. Moreover, PyTorch has maintained relevance through various AI advancements, including generative AI. It’s now vital for both model training and production,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the AIPCon 8 Demos Transforming Manufacturing, Insurance, and Construction</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11254/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11254/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AIPCon 8 showcased how AI is reshaping manufacturing, insurance, and construction. 🌟 Companies like Ursa Major are transforming traditional workflows into automated, intelligent systems that enhance efficiency and accuracy. 📈 From automated insurance underwriting to streamlined construction operations, these implementations highlight the power of enterprise AI in real-world applications. 🔍 Discover how organizations are building new operating models tailored to their specific needs! #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One night changed everything: Why I sleep out for Covenant House</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11227/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11227/</guid>
      <description>I participated in my sixth Sleep Out for Covenant House, an event raising funds for homeless youth. 🌙 Each year, I learn more about the challenges faced by the 4.2 million young people experiencing homelessness. My first Sleep Out opened my eyes to the urgency of their needs. 🚶‍♂️💧 Join me in supporting this cause and raising awareness. #CovenantHouse #EndYouthHomelessness #SleepOut #SupportYouth #Community</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Affordability, Familiarity, and Novelty: DoorDash’s LLM-assisted personalization framework</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11222/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11222/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DoorDash recently presented at KDD 2025&amp;rsquo;s PARIS Workshop, discussing their LLM-assisted personalization framework for multi-vertical retail. The framework focuses on three key dimensions: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Familiarity&lt;/strong&gt; - highlighting trusted favorites. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Affordability&lt;/strong&gt; - aligning with price preferences. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Novelty&lt;/strong&gt; - introducing new and exciting products. This approach aims to enhance customer discovery, ensuring shopping feels personalized and effortless. #DoorDash #Personalization&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powering Your AI-Ready Campus of the Future: Join us at EDUCAUSE 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11140/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11140/</guid>
      <description>Join Cisco at EDUCAUSE 2025 from October 28-31 in Nashville! Discover how Cisco’s AI-ready solutions empower higher education institutions to harness AI securely. Learn about intelligent assistants and operational insights designed to enhance productivity and campus experiences. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss our lunch and learn session featuring insights from leading universities. #EDUCAUSE2025 #AI #HigherEd #CiscoInnovation #CampusTransformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Builder: Cesar Hernandez, Manager, Personalized Support</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11242/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11242/</guid>
      <description>Meet Cesar Hernandez, Manager of Personalized Support at Twilio. His journey highlights the importance of timely referrals and leading with empathy. 🌍 Cesar is dedicated to personal growth and giving back to his community in Bogotá, showcasing how professional development can align with social responsibility. 🤝 Read more about his inspiring story! #Leadership #Community #Twilio #Empathy #ProfessionalGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic at Money20/20 USA 2025: Powering the next era of financial services</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11157/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11157/</guid>
      <description>Join Elastic at Money20/20 USA 2025 in Las Vegas to explore how cloud and AI are transforming financial services. Key topics include data management, fraud prevention, and compliance. Financial institutions must innovate while maintaining trust. Customers expect seamless digital experiences, while regulators emphasize transparency and security. Elastic Cloud on AWS supports these goals, enhancing efficiency and resilience in the industry. #Money2020 #Fintech #AI #DataManagement #ElasticCloud 🌐💼🔍</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic recognized as a finalist for Innovation in Customer Portals in 2025 TSIA STAR Awards</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11147/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11147/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news! Elastic has been named a finalist in the 2025 TSIA STAR Awards for Innovation in Customer Portals. This recognition highlights our commitment to enhancing digital customer experiences through AI technology. We proudly utilize our own Search AI Platform, demonstrating our dedication to delivering exceptional support. Thank you, TSIA, for acknowledging our efforts! 🙌 #Elastic #CustomerExperience #AIInnovation #TSIA #DigitalSupport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showcasing Innovation and Commitment at NetAcad’s European Partner Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11116/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11116/</guid>
      <description>🌍 At the recent Cisco NetAcad European Partner Conference in Thessaloniki, leaders gathered to discuss the future of workforce training. Cisco aims to equip 1.5 million Europeans with essential digital skills by 2030, focusing on AI readiness. With 3,841 academies supporting 5.1 million students, the commitment to education is strong. AI is reshaping job roles, with 78% of tech positions now needing AI skills. #CiscoNetAcad #AIFuture #DigitalSkills #WorkforceDevelopment #EducationInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Block Got 12,000 Employees Using AI Agents in Two Months</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11082/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11082/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Block has successfully deployed AI agents to its 12,000 employees in just eight weeks, a feat shared at the All Things Open 2025 conference. It began with a single engineer frustrated by limited AI capabilities. After experimenting with OpenAI’s function calling, Block adopted the Model Context Protocol to enhance automation. The team pivoted to focus on user-friendly design, ensuring even non-technical staff could easily access the tools. #AI #Innovation #TechNews #EmployeeEngagement #Block</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Kiro waitlist, EBS Volume Clones, EC2 Capacity Manager, and more (October 20, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11081/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11081/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from the tech world! The global tech community is wrapping up the year with events like the Amazon Q Developer coding challenges in South Africa. The first event in Johannesburg was a success, with more to come in Durban and Cape Town. Key launches include: - &lt;strong&gt;Kiro&lt;/strong&gt;: Open to all developers now, with over 100,000 on the waitlist. - &lt;strong&gt;EC2 Capacity Manager&lt;/strong&gt;: A centralized tool for managing capacity across multiple accounts and regions. - &lt;strong&gt;EBS Volume Clones&lt;/strong&gt;: Create&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering the Course of Wireless Transformation with Cisco and USGA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11026/</guid>
      <description>Cisco played a crucial role in powering the 125th U.S. Open with advanced technology. They deployed 550 access points and used Wi-Fi 7 to ensure seamless connectivity for over 225,000 attendees. This infrastructure supported various digital interactions, from ticketing to social media sharing, enhancing the fan experience. The setup faced challenges of high demand and an outdoor environment, yet Cisco successfully managed the complexities to deliver reliable connectivity. #USOpen #Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf 2025 Is Coming Up Soon!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11010/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news for plugin developers! The JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf is set for November 5. This event features a full day of talks, live Q&amp;amp;A, and in-depth sessions on plugin development. Key topics include creating your first plugin, language plugins, AI-powered testing, and more. Join us live on YouTube or catch up later! #JetBrains #PluginDevelopment #DevConference #SoftwareDevelopment #TechEvent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Igniting our future workforce: Shaping the future in Europe through Cisco Networking Academy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10985/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10985/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The Cisco Networking Academy Partner Conference in Thessaloniki recently gathered educators, government officials, and industry partners to celebrate the past year’s achievements and discuss future goals. 🤝 This event highlighted the importance of collaboration in shaping the future workforce in Europe. The spirit of community and support was evident, emphasizing the shared commitment to education and skill development. #CiscoNetworkingAcademy #FutureWorkforce #Collaboration #Education&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic AI Unleashed: Join the AWS &amp; NVIDIA Hackathon</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10964/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 19:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10964/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to innovate? Join the AWS &amp;amp; NVIDIA Hackathon and build the future of Agentic AI! Create an autonomous application using advanced AI models and scalable infrastructure. This event offers hands-on experience, networking opportunities, and the chance to win prizes. Teams can request $100 in promotional credits to support their projects. Be sure to monitor your usage to maximize your resources! #AI #Hackathon #AWS #NVIDIA #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Livestream] Maximizing TeamCity: New Features in Action and a Look Ahead</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10941/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10941/</guid>
      <description>📅 Join us on October 22, 2025, for a livestream on maximizing TeamCity! TeamCity Solutions Engineers Ricardo Leite and Daniel Gallo will showcase new features and provide a sneak peek at future updates. This session is designed for those looking to enhance their TeamCity experience. Expect hands-on demos, configuration walkthroughs, and insights into licensing changes. 🕓 Don&amp;rsquo;t miss it! #TeamCity #DevOps #Webinar #CI/CD #JetBrains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 years of Cisco Crisis Response: Reflecting on resilience from Hurricane Katrina to Helene</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10923/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 07:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10923/</guid>
      <description>🌍 As we celebrate 20 years of Cisco Crisis Response (CCR), we reflect on resilience from Hurricane Katrina to Hurricane Helene. In 2005, CCR began by restoring communications in disaster-struck areas. Over the years, it has evolved to meet the growing needs of communities affected by crises. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s partnership with BBC StoryWorks highlights CCR&amp;rsquo;s vital role in reconnecting people and rebuilding hope. 👉 Watch the video to learn more about CCR’s impactful work! #CiscoCrisisResponse #Resilience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Taste of P99 CONF: Low Latency With eBPF, Rust and More</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10898/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10898/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Get ready for P99 CONF 2025! This free, virtual event will take place on October 22-23, focusing on performance and low latency engineering. 🗣️ Expect insights from industry leaders like Clickhouse, Arm, NVIDIA, and Disney, among many others. 📚 Don’t miss the chance to watch over 200 on-demand tech talks from P99 CONF 2024, covering essential topics in low latency. 🔍 Stay tuned for detailed sessions on latency management strategies from experts like Pekka Enberg. #P99CONF #LowLatency&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Years Ago, I Took a Chance — Now I’m at Cisco Living the Dream</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10886/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10886/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Two years ago, Jordan B. took a leap from the FinTech industry to Cisco, inspired by its people-first culture. He reflects on his journey of growth and mentorship that led him to a fulfilling role as an Inside Account Executive. Jordan emphasizes the importance of connections and the value of a supportive network. #Cisco #CareerJourney #Mentorship #Growth #PeopleFirst</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCP Summit 2025: The Open Future of Networking Hardware for AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10879/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10879/</guid>
      <description>🌐 At the OCP Summit 2025, Meta outlined advancements in network fabrics tailored for AI training clusters. 📈 The company expanded its hardware portfolio, introducing new disaggregated network platforms to enhance collaboration within the Open Compute Project. 🔧 Meta emphasized the importance of open hardware in driving innovation and improving data center efficiency. Key milestones include the evolution of Disaggregated Scheduled Fabric and the launch of the Ethernet for Scale-Up Networking&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Global Impact Week Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10973/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10973/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Twilio recently shared insights from their 2025 Global Impact Week. The recap highlights cloud communications trends, showcasing customer stories and providing tips for developing scalable voice and SMS applications using Twilio&amp;rsquo;s APIs. Stay updated on the latest in tech and communication! 📱💬 #CloudCommunications #Twilio #TechTrends #APIs #VoiceAndSMS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Builder’s Arcade at SIGNAL Sydney 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10974/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10974/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Discover the Builder’s Arcade at SIGNAL Sydney 2025! This interactive space showcases innovative experiences designed for developers. Attendees can engage with various activations highlighting the latest in technology and collaboration. Join us to explore and connect with industry leaders, enhancing your skills and insights! #SIGNALSydney2025 #Developers #TechEvent #Innovation #Networking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Quick Suite, Amazon EC2, Amazon EKS, and more (October 13, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10875/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10875/</guid>
      <description>This week marked the inaugural AWS AI in Practice meetup hosted by the AWS User Group UK, focusing on AI-assisted software development and agents. Next week, the excitement continues in Italy with sessions on AI agents and context engineering at Codemotion in Milan and an AWS User Group meetup in Rome. 🇮🇹 Notable recent launches include the Amazon Quick Suite for enhanced AI-driven insights, new EC2 instances powered by AMD and Intel processors, and updates to Amazon EKS supporting Kubernetes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILES AND FLOWERS | Award-Winning Animated Short</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10606/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10606/</guid>
      <description>🎬 Exciting news in the animation world! The award-winning short film &amp;ldquo;Miles and Flowers&amp;rdquo; blends drama with humor for an engaging viewing experience. Created entirely in Unreal Engine, the filmmaker worked on this project for two years, focusing on a captivating story. Check it out and experience the unique storytelling! 🌼✨ #Animation #ShortFilm #UnrealEngine #MilesAndFlowers #FilmMaking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything Big Starts Small: Building Open Social Web Apps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10598/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10598/</guid>
      <description>🚀 It&amp;rsquo;s been nearly three years since Elon Musk acquired Twitter, and the fediverse is steadily growing. 🌐 At the recent FediForum, Ben Werdmuller emphasized the importance of starting small for the Open Social Web. He noted that successful platforms often originate from specific community needs. 📢 New projects like AltStore were announced, highlighting the potential of decentralized applications. #Fediverse #OpenSocialWeb #FediForum #CommunityDriven #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Door to More: Unlocking Creativity with AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10605/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10605/</guid>
      <description>Join us on November 6th in San Francisco for an exclusive event with DoorDash marketing leaders! 🚀 Hear from Gina Igwe, Jennifer Richardi, and Shannon Duncan about how AI is transforming creative marketing. This is a great opportunity to learn, network, and enjoy dinner and drinks. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out! RSVP by 10/22. #DoorDash #MarketingInnovation #AI #Networking #CreativeLeadership</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Kotlin Multiplatform Project and Win a Trip to KotlinConf 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10587/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10587/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for students and recent grads! The Kotlin Multiplatform Contest is now open. Build a project using Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP) for a chance to win a trip to KotlinConf 2026 in Munich, Germany! 🏆 Join the dedicated Slack channel for support, share progress, and connect with other participants. Prizes include travel, accommodation, and community recognition. Contest details: - Opens: September 15, 2025 - Deadline: January 12, 2026 - Winners announced: January 22, 2026 For more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting Your KotlinConf Proposal: Expert Tips to  Help You Stand Out</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10557/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10557/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to share your Kotlin expertise at KotlinConf? Here are some expert tips to craft a standout proposal! 1️⃣ Start with a clear and compelling title. First impressions matter! Make sure your title conveys your topic and its benefits to the audience. 2️⃣ Use storytelling in your abstract. Engage your audience by promising a valuable learning experience through a narrative. These insights can boost your chances of acceptance and help you shine at the event! 🌟 #KotlinConf #Kotlin&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charting the Course: Resilience and Innovation at AFCEA TechNet Indo Pacific 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10540/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10540/</guid>
      <description>Join Cisco at AFCEA TechNet Indo Pacific 2025 from October 28-30 in Hawai’i! 🌺 This year&amp;rsquo;s theme, &amp;ldquo;Sword &amp;amp; Shield: Ensuring a Secure, Free, and Prosperous Indo-Pacific,&amp;rdquo; focuses on overcoming challenges in mission connectivity and security. Visit Booth #1222 for demos on digital resiliency and AI-driven NetOps. Discover how Cisco’s solutions help maintain operations in tough environments. 💻✨ #AFCEA2025 #Cisco #Cybersecurity #Innovation #TechEvent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Direct Line to Cisco Automation: Ask Ed Novak About Workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10541/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 13:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10541/</guid>
      <description>📅 Join us on October 8 for a live Q&amp;amp;A with Ed Novak, a Cisco Technical Marketing Engineer! This interactive session will focus on Cisco Workflows, allowing you to ask questions and explore real-world use cases. Prepare your queries and gain insights to enhance your network operations. 🕘 Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to engage directly with an expert! #Cisco #Automation #Workflows #Networking #LiveQandA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Non-Commercial JetBrains Rider Users: Tell Us Your Stories!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10533/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 12:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10533/</guid>
      <description>📣 Attention non-commercial JetBrains Rider users! It’s been nearly a year since Rider became free for non-commercial use. To celebrate, JetBrains is inviting users to share their stories about projects developed with Rider. They are seeking participants for interviews to discuss your experiences, whether it’s for side projects, open-source contributions, or educational endeavors. If interested, contact &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sasha.ivanova@jetbrains.com&#34;&gt;sasha.ivanova@jetbrains.com&lt;/a&gt; for more details. Participants will gain visibility for their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team ’25 Europe: AI that’s changing the game for teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10527/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10527/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Exciting developments at Team ‘25 Europe in Barcelona! AI is reshaping teamwork, with Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s Rovo leading the way. Over three million users benefit from its features, enhancing productivity and collaboration across organizations. Rovo integrates seamlessly with existing systems, transforming workflows and delivering quick answers to users. The rollout continues, with a mobile app on the horizon. Stay tuned for more updates! 🚀 #Team25Europe #AI #Atlassian #Rovo #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From contributor to Elastician: João Neto</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10572/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10572/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Discover the inspiring journey of João Neto, who transitioned from a passionate community contributor to an Elastic employee. His active involvement in the Elastic Contributor Program helped shape his career through knowledge sharing and meaningful connections. João highlights how community engagement and technical expertise paved the way for his dream role at Elastic. Learn more about his experiences and insights! #Elastic #Community #CareerGrowth #Inspiration #TechJourney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet JetBrains at Azure Dev Summit 2025 (Lisbon, Oct 13–16)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10513/</guid>
      <description>🌍 JetBrains is excited to attend the Azure Dev Summit 2025 in Lisbon from October 13–16! Join Max Solovyev, Head of Growth for .NET and GameDev Tools, at our booth to explore how Rider and the dotUltimate suite can enhance your .NET on Azure projects. We will showcase practical demos, discuss Azure App Service, and share insights on performance diagnostics and JetBrains AI features. 📅 Book a brief chat with Max to discuss your goals. #JetBrains #AzureDevSummit #DotNet #Lisbon2025&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Atlas Camp: Amsterdam Call for Speakers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10508/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10508/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The call for speakers is now open for Atlas Camp 2026 in Amsterdam. This flagship Atlassian conference focuses on sharing real stories about platform extensibility, software delivery, and AI-powered solutions. Join a global community and inspire others! Submit your proposal at events.atlassian.com/atlascamp-cfs. #AtlasCamp #Developers #Atlassian #TechCommunity #CallForSpeakers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tech Career That Makes Room for Life — and a Book</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10487/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10487/</guid>
      <description>Discover how Ana N., a Marketing Networking Manager at Cisco, found the balance between her career and personal life. After 20 years in public relations, she turned her dream of writing a book into reality with Cisco&amp;rsquo;s supportive culture. The flexibility allowed her to excel at work while being a mother and a wife. Her journey shows how a positive work environment can help achieve personal goals. 📚💼✨ #Cisco #CareerGrowth #WorkLifeBalance #AuthorJourney #SupportiveCulture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker at AI Engineer Paris: Build and Secure AI Agents with Docker</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10446/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10446/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Last week, Docker participated in the inaugural AI Engineer Paris conference, highlighting the evolution of AI application development. Key discussions emphasized that true innovation requires rigorous engineering, not just &amp;ldquo;AI dust.&amp;rdquo; The focus is on creating robust AI agents through standardized practices. Docker&amp;rsquo;s Tushar Jain led a keynote on making AI agent development accessible to all developers. A hands-on workshop followed, teaching attendees how to build collaborative multi-agent&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the AIPCon 8 Demos Redefining the Future of Enterprise AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10393/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 21:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10393/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AIPCon 8 showcased transformative AI applications across various industries, highlighting real-world solutions at Palantir&amp;rsquo;s recent conference. From healthcare to motorsport, demos featured innovations like Andretti&amp;rsquo;s RaceOS for rapid data-driven decisions and Nebraska Medicine&amp;rsquo;s automated documentation for efficient revenue cycle management. These advancements illustrate how AI can solve operational challenges and enhance efficiency. #EnterpriseAI #AIPCon8 #Innovation #Healthcare #Motorsport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-World IT Sustainability: 3 Case Studies From Green IO London</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10350/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10350/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The recent Green IO conference in London showcased how organizations like HSBC, OVO Energy, and the British government are implementing sustainable tech practices. HSBC shared their open-source tool for measuring software carbon footprints and their commitment to achieving net-zero emissions by 2050. OVO Energy highlighted innovative uses of home boilers for distributed computing. These case studies illustrate the tangible benefits of aligning environmental responsibility with business&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Awareness Month: Become a Champion of Digital Resilience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10355/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10355/</guid>
      <description>🌐 October marks Cybersecurity Awareness Month! This year, Cisco is offering training and certification giveaways to help you enhance your skills in cybersecurity. You can enter the sweepstakes for a chance to win valuable e-learning bundles. 🎓 Additionally, enjoy a 25% discount on cybersecurity learning products from October 13–20, 2025. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to boost your professional journey! 🚀 #CybersecurityAwareness #Cisco #DigitalResilience #CybersecurityTraining #CareerGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the scenes: Supporting engineers and designers during Tech Week 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10347/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10347/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Tech Week 2025 brought together over 1,500 participants for a unique celebration of innovation at LINE Yahoo. Held from June 30 to July 4, the event featured Tech-Verse, a tech conference showcasing nearly 130 sessions, and Hack Day, an internal hackathon for creative projects. Support for presenters included comprehensive guides, expert reviews, and practice sessions, fostering a collaborative environment. Tech Week emphasizes teamwork and encourages sharing ideas, contributing to a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highlights from the Unreal Fest Stockholm opening session</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10372/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10372/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Unreal Fest Stockholm kicked off with an exciting look at Unreal Engine 5.7, showcasing its latest features. 🔧 Developers working on Fortnite can expect new tools designed to enhance their creative process. 🤖 Additionally, the Epic Developer Assistant has expanded, providing even more support for developers. #UnrealFest #UnrealEngine #GameDevelopment #Fortnite #EpicGames</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Maxims for Great Developer Platform Design</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10319/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10319/</guid>
      <description>Russell Miles shared insights on developer platform design at the Devmio International JavaScript Conference. 🎸 He outlined three maxims, starting with the idea that platforms require commitment and resources. If a company isn’t ready to invest, they may not need a platform. He emphasized that every organization already has a platform when they ship code. Understanding internal customers and viewing the platform as a product is crucial for success. #DeveloperPlatforms #JavaScript #Devmio&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Miss Out: Attend the 2025 OCP Global Summit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10322/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10322/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The 2025 OCP Global Summit is just around the corner! Cisco will showcase innovations in AI networking, security, and open networking. Key topics include AI infrastructure, P4 programmability, and SONiC, all aimed at supporting organizations in the AI era. Don’t miss this opportunity to see how Cisco is helping to shape the future of data centers. 🚀 #OCPSummit2025 #Cisco #AINetworking #DataCenter #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside LY Corporation&#39;s &#34;Tech-Verse 2025&#34; conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10303/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10303/</guid>
      <description>🌟 LY Corporation recently held its &amp;ldquo;Tech-Verse 2025&amp;rdquo; conference, focusing on artificial intelligence. The two-day event attracted over 1,200 attendees and featured 131 sessions across 12 categories. Key topics included platform integration post-merger and LY&amp;rsquo;s ambitious AI strategy. CTO Euivin Park outlined the goal of implementing AI across 44 services to enhance user experience. For more insights, check out the presentation slides or archived videos on YouTube! 📊💻 #TechVerse2025&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebexOne 2025: Unlocking the Power of Connected Intelligence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10260/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10260/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Today at WebexOne in San Diego, Cisco unveiled its vision for the future of work, emphasizing the importance of AI in the workplace. 🔑 Key challenges like infrastructure constraints, security threats, and data gaps are being addressed with innovative solutions. Webex is central to this strategy, enhancing communication and collaboration. 🤖 The concept of &amp;ldquo;Connected Intelligence&amp;rdquo; will redefine how we interact—blending human and AI communication seamlessly. #WebexOne #Cisco #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Can Help IT Teams Find the Signals in Alert Noise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10231/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10231/</guid>
      <description>🚨 IT teams face a challenge with alert fatigue as 95-98% of alerts are often noncritical. This overwhelming noise can lead to burnout and decreased productivity. Mandi Walls from PagerDuty emphasized the need for better frameworks using SLOs, automation, and machine learning to improve alert management. Effective solutions can reduce stress and enhance the work environment for developers. #AlertFatigue #DevOps #MachineLearning #ITManagement #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Modern IT Operations Are Becoming More Like Space Travel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10222/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10222/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The ManageEngine user conference in Las Vegas explored the link between IT operations and space travel. Former astronaut Mike Massimino shared insights on teamwork and problem-solving, drawing parallels between astronaut training and IT practices. He highlighted how both fields require trust in tools and collaboration among team members. Massimino&amp;rsquo;s experiences offered a fresh perspective on navigating challenges in IT, especially with the rise of AI. #ITOperations #SpaceTravel #Teamwork&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applications closing for the Airtable AI Incubator</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10225/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10225/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Applications are now open for the Airtable AI Incubator! This program offers builders a chance to transform their ideas into practical solutions with structured mentorship and support. Interested participants must submit their applications by 12pm ET on September 30. Answer key questions to clarify your vision and readiness. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to innovate! #AirtableAI #AIIncubator #Innovation #TechForGood #ApplyNow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 years of helping build a better Internet: a look back at Birthday Week 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10204/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10204/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Celebrating 15 years of Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s mission to build a better Internet! This year&amp;rsquo;s Birthday Week highlighted key themes: promoting new monetization models and enhancing community engagement. Major announcements included plans to hire 1,111 interns in 2026 and support for open-source projects like Ladybird and Omarchy. Cloudflare also opened collaboration hubs in major cities and extended free access to developer tools for non-profits. For more details, check out the blog! #Cloudflare&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience the Power of Connection and AI at Cisco Connect Cancun</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10200/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Cisco Connect is back at the Moon Palace Hotel in Cancun! This event unites 3,000 attendees to explore the latest Cisco innovations and reconnect with peers. The focus is on the “One Cisco” strategy, emphasizing integration across networking, security, and services to create value for customers. AI takes center stage, with discussions on its impact on customer experience. Insights reveal that 93% of global respondents see agentic AI enhancing personalized services by 2028. #CiscoConnect #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktoberfest 2025: How to Participate</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10194/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 07:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10194/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Hacktoberfest 2025 registrations are now open! Join the global celebration of open source this October. To participate, register before October 31 and contribute to projects on GitHub or GitLab with the hacktoberfest topic. Aim for at least 6 accepted pull/merge requests to earn rewards, including digital badges and a limited edition t-shirt for the first 10,000 participants. 👕 Ways to contribute include coding, maintaining projects, or even supporting with documentation and user experience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Digital Event: Open Accelerated Computing Summit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-28-10190/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-28-10190/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Join the Open Accelerated Computing Summit on October 7-8! This digital event will explore new research at the intersection of AI and High-Performance Computing (HPC). Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to gain insights and connect with experts in the field! 🔗 Sign up now: &lt;a href=&#34;https://zoom.us/signup&#34;&gt;Zoom Signup&lt;/a&gt; #OACSummit #AI #HPC #DigitalEvent #Research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networking at the Heart of AI — @Scale: Networking 2025 Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10161/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10161/</guid>
      <description>🌐 AI is transforming networking, and this year&amp;rsquo;s @Scale:Networking event highlighted its critical role. Engineers from major tech companies gathered to discuss the infrastructure needed for AI advancements. 🔍 Key topics included significant investments in AI infrastructure, with companies planning extensive builds and renewable energy initiatives. 📈 Additionally, the evolution of AI models and workloads was a focus, showcasing rapid growth and increasing demands on network performance&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 years of HashiConf: A bold leap into AI-powered infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10158/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10158/</guid>
      <description>🚀 HashiConf 2025 marked a decade of innovation in cloud automation, emphasizing the future of infrastructure as automated and secure. This year, HashiCorp, now part of IBM, highlighted The Infrastructure Cloud, designed for comprehensive management of infrastructure and security. Attendees shared valuable insights, including customer success stories and strategies for implementing AI-ready automation across operations. Catch up on key sessions and announcements on our YouTube channel! 📹&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuing Positive Impact: This Year’s AI4SE Interns in their New Roles at JetBrains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10082/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10082/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news from JetBrains! This year’s AI4SE interns from TU Delft have transitioned to full-time roles on our tech team. During their internships, they worked on innovative projects, enhancing their technical skills and driving impactful changes in software development. Their contributions have already improved team performance and sparked collaboration across product teams. One intern even developed an AI tool that&amp;rsquo;s still in use today! We look forward to their continued growth and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brickster Voices: Meet Cindy Nicola, VP Global Talent Acquisition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10097/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 07:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10097/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Cindy Nicola, VP of Global Talent Acquisition at Databricks! In the latest Brickster Voices feature, Cindy shares her insights on career growth, collaboration, and leadership. Her journey highlights the importance of fostering a strong company culture and guiding talent development. Discover how Cindy&amp;rsquo;s experiences shape the future of talent acquisition at Databricks! #Leadership #TalentAcquisition #CareerGrowth #Databricks #BricksterVoices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Register now for the 2025 Epic MegaJam</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10107/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10107/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Exciting news for game developers! The 2025 Epic MegaJam is set to take place, marking 10 years of innovation in the industry. Gather your team and prepare for a week filled with creativity and game development. Participants will have the chance to win fantastic prizes from our sponsors. Don’t miss out on this opportunity to showcase your skills! #EpicMegaJam #GameDev #Innovation #Creativity #JoinUs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brickster Voices: Meet Chao Cai, Sr. Director, Engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10043/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10043/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Chao Cai, Sr. Director of Engineering at Brickster! In the latest installment of Brickster Voices, Chao shares insights into his career journey and the role of AI in today&amp;rsquo;s tech landscape. Discover how he leads at the intersection of innovation and engineering, shaping the future of the industry. #BricksterVoices #Leadership #AI #Engineering #CareerJourney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the builder: Tanise Love, Senior Employee Impact Manager</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10117/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10117/</guid>
      <description>Meet Tanise Love, Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Senior Employee Impact Manager! 🌟 In her role, Tanise emphasizes the importance of values that shape Twilio’s giving culture. She actively works to bring this culture to life, demonstrating how corporate responsibility can impact communities and employees alike. Discover more about her insights and contributions in the full article. #Twilio #EmployeeSpotlight #CorporateResponsibility #GivingCulture #Leadership</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Human Network – My Journey with Cisco</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9910/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9910/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Shweta Takate reflects on her journey with Cisco, highlighting her transformation since joining in 2007. She describes the supportive culture that felt like family in Bangalore, which fueled her passion and growth. After a brief hiatus for further education in New York, Shweta returned to Cisco, where she found the same welcoming atmosphere. Her story emphasizes the importance of human connection in the workplace. #Cisco #CareerJourney #HumanConnection #WorkCulture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From hackathon nerves to internship wins: Kavya’s journey at 1Password</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9915/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9915/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting journey alert! Meet Kavya, a UBC student who transitioned from a business major to a passionate Computer Science learner. She participated in cmd-f, a hackathon for underrepresented genders in tech, where her team created REALM, a wellness app that integrates personalized health insights and security through Passage by 1Password. 🛡️ After winning the hackathon, Kavya secured an internship at 1Password, where she thrives in a supportive remote culture while contributing to developer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future-proofing Singapore as an AI-first nation with Search AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9937/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9937/</guid>
      <description>During the 2025 National Day Rally, Singapore’s PM Lawrence Wong highlighted the commitment to integrating AI into business processes, aiming to empower local workers. He showcased an AI-powered orthopantomogram (OPG) scanner that cuts dental assessment time significantly. This is part of AI Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 100 Experiments program, which has over 200 AI projects since 2018. Elastic recently partnered with AI Singapore to host a workshop focused on developing AI skills, featuring insights on large&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Q Developer, AWS Step Functions, AWS Cloud Club Captain deadline, and more (September 22, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9886/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 16:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9886/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This week&amp;rsquo;s AWS Roundup highlights key developments from a recent trip to New Zealand, where several events showcased local tech talent. 🌍 A new feature in Amazon Q CLI, called tangent mode, allows users to maintain focus while exploring side topics. It&amp;rsquo;s currently in experimental mode. 📈 Notable launches include: - New models in Amazon Bedrock for enhanced text and image tasks. - Expansion of VPC Reachability Analyzer to seven new regions for better network diagnostics. - Remote MCP server&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lookback at Workers Launchpad and a Warm Welcome to Cohort #6</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9874/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9874/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Workers Launchpad program supports founders on the Cloudflare network with essential resources and mentorship. Since its inception, 145 startups from 23 countries have joined, tackling issues in AI, cloud infrastructure, and more. Notably, Cohort #5 showcased strong female founder representation. Participants benefit from hands-on support, bootcamps, and VC introductions, leading to funding and successful acquisitions. 🌍💡 Learn more about the program and its impact on innovation!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Come build with us: Cloudflare&#39;s new hubs for startups</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9870/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9870/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloudflare is set to open its San Francisco, Austin, London, and Lisbon offices to startups in 2026! These spaces will be available for collaboration, networking, and focused work, enhancing innovation within the tech community. The initiative aims to support early-stage startups by fostering connections in-person, building on Cloudflare’s long history of hosting community events. 🌍 Join us in creating a better digital environment! #Cloudflare #Startups #Innovation #TechCommunity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help build the future: announcing Cloudflare’s goal to hire 1,111 interns in 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9875/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9875/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Cloudflare is set to hire 1,111 interns in 2026! This ambitious program aims to tap into new ideas and energy as the company focuses on AI and innovation. The initiative reflects Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s commitment to building a better Internet and investing in future talent. It also aims to challenge traditional methods and explore novel applications of AI. As many firms reduce intern hiring, Cloudflare is taking a different approach, viewing AI as a tool to enhance new hires&amp;rsquo; contributions&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Bets on Austin: Celebrating Our New Downtown Office</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9862/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9862/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Cisco! Today, they opened their new downtown office in Austin, showcasing advanced workplace technologies. Nearly 30 years in Austin, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s commitment to the city continues to grow. The new office symbolizes their belief in Austin&amp;rsquo;s potential and innovation. With over 1,400 employees in the area, Cisco is focused on driving innovation and shaping the future of work. #Cisco #Austin #Innovation #FutureOfWork #TechCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktoberfest 2025: Celebrate All Things Open Source!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9828/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9828/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Hacktoberfest 2025 is coming soon! Starting October 1, join a global celebration of open-source contributions. Register now and help support various projects by completing 6 pull requests this month. The first 10,000 contributors will receive a t-shirt and a tree planted in their name! 🌳 Get ready for fun activities, including partnering with Major League Hacking for events worldwide. Visit Hacktoberfest.com for details and mark your calendars! 🗓️ #Hacktoberfest #OpenSource #CodingCommunity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating a decade of Connected Conservation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9811/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9811/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating a decade of impactful partnership! 🌍 For ten years, Cisco and the Connected Conservation Foundation (CCF) have worked together to enhance wildlife conservation. Their efforts have provided essential technology to monitor and protect species like rhinos and elephants across 46 protected areas in Africa. This World Rhino Day, we reflect on the progress made and the ongoing commitment to safeguarding these animals and their habitats. 🦏✨ #ConnectedConservation #WildlifeProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing: JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9796/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9796/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited to announce JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025! Join us on October 8-9 for a free, online event featuring practical talks, live demos, and expert tips from community speakers and the JetBrains .NET team. 🔗 Register here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://lp.jetbrains.com/dotnet-days-2025&#34;&gt;https://lp.jetbrains.com/dotnet-days-2025&lt;/a&gt; Don’t miss sessions on topics like Clean Architecture, Test Driven Development, and more! #DotNetDays #JetBrains #Programming #TechEvents #CommunityEngagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB.local NYC 2025: Defining the Ideal Database for the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9771/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9771/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from MongoDB.local NYC! Thousands of developers gathered to explore MongoDB&amp;rsquo;s new capabilities, including the release of MongoDB 8.2 and the Voyage AI embedding models. 🛠️ The MongoDB Application Modernization Platform (AMP) aims to help enterprises transition from costly legacy systems to more efficient solutions, showing impressive early results. 🌍 With nearly 60,000 organizations now using MongoDB, the focus remains on providing a flexible and powerful database that&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Excellence: MongoDB Global Partner Awards 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9761/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9761/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Celebrating innovation in tech, the MongoDB Global Partner Awards 2025 recognize partners driving success in AI and modernization. 🏆 Microsoft has been named Global Cloud Partner of the Year for its growth and collaboration with MongoDB across various industries. 🔗 AWS is honored as Global AI Cloud Partner of the Year, showcasing impactful AI solutions, while Google Cloud excels in joint go-to-market initiatives. ✨ Accenture earns recognition for its commitment to customer success in the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oktane Online 2025: The AI Security Event You Can’t Miss</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9833/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9833/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Join us for Oktane Online, streaming live on September 25-26, 2025! With over 40 sessions on AI, identity, and security, this free event is designed for IT leaders, security professionals, and anyone interested in the future of technology. Expect keynotes from industry leaders, real-time Q&amp;amp;As, and even entertainment from guests like Jeremy Renner! Plus, earn up to 13.5 CPE credits. Don’t miss out—secure your spot today! #OktaneOnline #AISecurity #TechEvent #CPEcredits #IdentityInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Databricks at Sibos in Frankfurt!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9714/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9714/</guid>
      <description>Join Databricks at Sibos in Frankfurt! 🌍 Sibos is a key event where leaders in banking and payments come together to connect and innovate. This year, the focus is on transforming finance through data and AI. Engage in insightful sessions, dynamic conversations, and enjoy a lively rooftop happy hour. Don’t miss out! 🍹💡 #Sibos2025 #Databricks #FinanceInnovation #Banking #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlock Unified Network and Security Analytics with Cisco and Splunk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9708/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 21:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9708/</guid>
      <description>Unlock unified network and security analytics with Cisco and Splunk! 🌐🔍 Join the livestream on September 17 at 9 a.m. PT, hosted by Adrian Illiesiu. Learn from Technical Marketing Engineer Taylor Cook as he demonstrates the Cisco Enterprise Networking app for Splunk. Discover how it integrates data from various Cisco platforms for enhanced network visibility and security management. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on the chance to ask your questions live! #Cisco #Splunk #NetworkSecurity #DevNet #LiveDemo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Profitable Partners Do Differently</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9701/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 19:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9701/</guid>
      <description>Join us at the Cisco Partner Summit 2025 in San Diego from November 3-5 to explore how profitable partnerships can enhance your business growth. The summit will focus on key questions guiding collaboration and the framework of &amp;ldquo;durable growth&amp;rdquo; to drive success. Gain insights from industry leaders and learn effective strategies for partnership profitability. 🌟🤝 #CiscoPartnerSummit #BusinessGrowth #Partnerships #Innovation #Cisco</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Splunk to Cisco: A Seamless Transition in Career and Family</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9680/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9680/</guid>
      <description>Excited to share insights from Vikram U.&amp;rsquo;s journey transitioning from Splunk to Cisco. He highlights the strong bond formed between both teams during the acquisition. Vikram also emphasizes the importance of Cisco&amp;rsquo;s generous parental leave, which allowed him and his wife to welcome their baby girl and navigate parenthood seamlessly. This supportive culture has made a significant impact on their family life. 👶❤️ #CareerTransition #ParentalLeave #Cisco #FamilySupport #WorkLifeBalance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the 2025 Webflow Awards winners</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9655/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9655/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Announcing the 2025 Webflow Awards winners! This annual event celebrates the creativity and innovation within the Webflow community. The awards highlight individuals and organizations making significant contributions to web experiences. 🏆 Community Educator of the Year: Timothy Ricks, known for his impactful educational resources. 🏆 Community Creator of the Year: Ilja van Eck, recognized for his award-winning projects and contributions to the design community. Explore the full list of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GameDev Day 2025 Is Back in October!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9646/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9646/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Exciting news for game developers! JetBrains GameDev Day returns on October 21, 2025! This free, one-day online event focuses on creativity, storytelling, and community in game development. Join industry professionals as they share valuable insights on various topics, from improving workflows to designing accessible games. New this year: local watch parties! Connect with fellow developers in your city while participating in this global event. All sessions will be streamed live on YouTube&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Voice Belongs Here: Creating Compelling KotlinConf Proposals [Livestream]</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9621/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9621/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Ready to elevate your speaking skills? Join the webinar &amp;ldquo;Your Voice Belongs Here&amp;rdquo; on October 14! This session is tailored for individuals from underrepresented groups in tech who have some speaking experience and want to present at KotlinConf. Learn what makes a compelling CFP, how to craft your proposal, and what reviewers seek. Connect, build confidence, and prepare to share your Kotlin journey! #KotlinConf #PublicSpeaking #TechInclusion #CFP #DiversityInTech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Fellowship: Games—explore the making of six awesome games in three weeks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9613/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9613/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Unreal Fellowship: Games 2025 featured an immersive bootcamp for game developers, focusing on skill enhancement and collaboration. 🌟 Participants created six unique games in just three weeks, showcasing their creativity and technical abilities. Discover the inspiring stories behind these innovative projects! #UnrealFellowship #GameDevelopment #IndieGames #GamingCommunity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains at the ICPC World Finals 2025 Baku</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9554/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9554/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The ICPC World Finals 2025 in Baku was a significant event, showcasing top student talent from around the globe. JetBrains was proud to support the competition and the community it fosters. 🎓 The Neapolis University Pafos team, Sigma++, participated and earned an Honors distinction. Andrey Ivanov from JetBrains emphasized the camaraderie and appreciation for those who organized the event. 🛠️ Attendees enjoyed activities at the JetBrains booth, including the Kotlin Challenge and interactions&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cisco Supports Work-Life Balance: My 21-Day Motorcycle Dream Trip</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9463/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9463/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Namita J., a Meraki Technical Leader at Cisco, shares her inspiring journey of a 21-day motorcycle trip across Europe. Cisco’s culture of trust and flexibility allowed her to take 30 days off without concerns about work. Her manager and team fully supported her adventure, ensuring a seamless workflow in her absence. This experience highlights how Cisco promotes work-life balance, empowering employees to pursue their dreams. 🏍️✨ #WorkLifeBalance #Cisco #EmployeeWellbeing #DreamBig&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Heartfelt Thanks to Our Community of Builders</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9496/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9496/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to announce that Twilio has been named one of Fast Company&amp;rsquo;s 2025 Best Workplaces for Innovators! 🎉 This recognition highlights our commitment to fostering a creative culture and empowering innovation within our community of builders. Thank you to everyone who contributes to this vibrant environment! 🙌 #Twilio #Innovation #BestWorkplaces #Community #Gratitude</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine data: The next frontier in AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9441/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9441/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At #SplunkConf25, Cisco and Splunk introduced new innovations to harness the potential of machine-generated data. 🔍 Machine data is crucial for AI, yet it remains underutilized due to challenges like data silos and the complexity of integration. 💡 Cisco aims to address these obstacles, providing the infrastructure needed for AI success. #AI #DataInnovation #Splunk #Cisco #MachineData</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash takes part in the 2025 Disability:IN Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9452/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9452/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This summer, DoorDash participated in the Disability:IN Conference for the first time, joining advocates and leaders focused on disability inclusion in the workplace. Our Able@ DoorDash group led the effort, with speakers Kinzie Keller and Lyndsey Leask sharing valuable insights on neurodiversity and creating accessible environments. We are committed to building inclusive products and practices, and this event provided us with new ideas to enhance our accessibility journey. Learn more about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Transform, Amazon Neptune, and more (September 8, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9440/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9440/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting updates in the AWS community! AWS Community Day 2025 is set for September 24 in Utrecht, bringing together over 500 cloud practitioners. The event will feature 25 breakout sessions focused on serverless architectures and container optimization. 📈 Recent AWS announcements include enhancements to AWS Transform, which now analyzes detached storage infrastructure for migration cost comparisons. Additionally, Amazon Bedrock introduces Global Cross-Region inference for Claude Sonnet 4,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Unscripted: Your Front-Row Seat for Honest Talk Between CIOs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9425/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover Tech Unscripted, a new video series featuring candid conversations with IT leaders tackling today&amp;rsquo;s challenges. Gain insights on managing ISP outages, securing remote work, and addressing AI demands. Each episode offers actionable tips for strategists, engineers, and security professionals. Tune in for valuable lessons straight from the experts. 📈💡 #TechUnscripted #CIOInsights #ITLeadership #Cybersecurity #DigitalTransformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan-Made PREDATOR Cinematic: IT ALL ENDS | Unreal Engine 5.6 | MetaHuman</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9537/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9537/</guid>
      <description>🎬 Exciting news for fans of the Predator franchise! A talented group has released a fan-made cinematic titled &amp;ldquo;PREDATOR: IT ALL ENDS,&amp;rdquo; crafted entirely using Unreal Engine 5.6. This project showcases impressive visuals and storytelling. The creators shared insights about the production process, revealing they completed a total of 108 shots. Check it out and immerse yourself in this indie creation! #Predator #FanFilm #UnrealEngine #Cinematic #IndieFilm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launching the 2nd Edition of the Cisco Cybersecurity Academy in Portugal</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9426/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9426/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for cybersecurity enthusiasts in Portugal! Cisco is launching the 2nd Edition of the Cybersecurity Academy, expanding on the success of the first edition. This six-month program aims to equip high-potential talent with hands-on training and industry-recognized certifications. Yves Mertens emphasizes that this initiative strengthens relationships among Cisco, customers, and partners, addressing the growing cybersecurity skills gap. Special thanks to the project team and Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Register for the Global Webinar: How to Prepare for NVIDIA Generative AI Certification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-07-8227/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-07-8227/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Join the global webinar on October 7 to learn how to prepare for the NVIDIA Generative AI Certification exams. Get insights into the new professional level certification and tips for success. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to enhance your skills! #NVIDIA #GenerativeAI #Webinar #Certification #ProfessionalDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7762/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 08:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7762/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited for September&amp;rsquo;s Java Annotated Monthly! This edition features updates on Java 25, set to release on September 16, 2025. Key enhancements include Compact Source Files, Flexible Constructor Bodies, and Scoped Values for better thread management. Additionally, IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2 supports these updates, including new debugging tools. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on the upcoming events and insights from Marit van Dijk! #Java25 #IntelliJIDEA #TechNews #SoftwareDevelopment #JavaCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7894/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 08:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7894/</guid>
      <description>🚀 September brings exciting updates in the latest Java Annotated Monthly! This edition features the much-anticipated Java 25 release on September 16, 2025, highlighting new features like Compact Source Files and improvements in performance. Marit van Dijk shares insights on these updates and the support in IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2. Don’t miss this month’s tech news and upcoming events! #Java25 #IntelliJ #TechNews #Kotlin #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading design through disruption: A conversation with Sara Vienna, Chief Design Officer at Metalab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7793/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7793/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited to share insights from my conversation with Sara Vienna, Chief Design Officer at Metalab! Sara reflects on her journey from a cold email to leading a top design firm. She emphasizes flexibility and continuous improvement in a rapidly evolving tech landscape. AI is reshaping design, prompting a redefinition of craft that focuses on user needs over time spent. Client expectations have also shifted, with heightened pressure on businesses to adapt. #DesignLeadership #AIinDesign&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover How Heroku’s AI PaaS Delivers Real-World Results at Dreamforce</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7743/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7743/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Heroku has transformed at Dreamforce into an AI PaaS, designed to enhance the shift from experimentation to production. Key highlights include new features like AppLink, Managed Inference, and Agents, all aimed at speeding up the delivery of AI-powered applications. Discover how companies like Workday and AT&amp;amp;T; are achieving significant results with Heroku’s solutions. Explore more at Dreamforce! #Heroku #Dreamforce #AI #TechInnovation #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains JavaScript Day 2025 Registration Is Now Open</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7727/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7727/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for JavaScript enthusiasts! Registration is now open for the fifth edition of JetBrains JavaScript Day, a free online event set for October 2 at 9:00 am EDT / 3:00 pm CEST. Join us for insightful talks from industry leaders, covering topics from modern JavaScript tooling to open source project management. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on this opportunity to learn and engage! 📅 Register now and be part of the conversation! #JavaScriptDay #JetBrains #JavaScript #TechEvent #WebDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Week 2025: Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7680/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7680/</guid>
      <description>🌐 AI Week 2025 has concluded, focusing on how to harness AI&amp;rsquo;s power while maintaining control. Key announcements included new products and partnerships aimed at enhancing AI security and usability. 🔒 The event emphasized four main areas: securing AI environments, protecting original content, supporting developers, and improving Cloudflare with AI features. Stay tuned for updates on our Blog, AI Avenue, and CloudflareTV! 📅 #AIWeek2025 #Cloudflare #AISecurity #TechInnovation #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conference Hopping: Training Attendee Scanning Def Con</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7665/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7665/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The Black Hat NOC faces unique challenges, as it operates in a cybersecurity hub where scanning and ethical hacking are expected. Cisco is enhancing security with network-based telemetry to monitor diverse personal devices at the conference. An alert recently identified suspicious activity linked to a training session targeting an external IP associated with Def Con. #Cybersecurity #BlackHat2025 #Cisco #ThreatDetection #EthicalHacking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving Cisco XDR Integration With Third-Party Partners at Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7666/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7666/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is the Official Security Cloud provider at Black Hat USA 2025, showcasing its latest advancements in XDR integration. These integrations enhance the Security Operations Center&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, allowing analysts to quickly investigate Indicators of Compromise (IOC) with a single search. Special thanks to alphaMountain.ai and Pulsedive for their contributions to the event. #Cisco #CyberSecurity #BlackHat2025 #XDR #MalwareAnalysis 🚀🔍💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Secure Firewall: SnortML at Black Hat USA 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7667/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7667/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is the Security Cloud Provider for Black Hat USA 2025! Attendees can participate in hands-on training sessions, using cloud resources for real-time attack simulations. The Cisco team ensures stable connectivity and monitors traffic to protect against unauthorized attacks. SnortML, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s machine learning tool, demonstrated high accuracy, detecting over 100 attacks with only 21 false positives. Stay informed about cybersecurity innovations! 🔒💻 #Cisco #BlackHat2025 #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat Training Attendees Scan Aviation Organization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7670/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7670/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Black Hat conference highlights the unique challenges of cybersecurity, particularly within its Security and Network Operations Center (NOC). Attendees engage in ethical hacking, leading to expected scanning and exploitation activities. This dynamic environment differs from typical corporate settings where such actions are seen as malicious. With a Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) policy, comprehensive monitoring becomes challenging. The focus shifts to robust network-based telemetry for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat USA 2025: 10 Years Protecting Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7671/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7671/</guid>
      <description>Cisco celebrates a decade as the Official Security Cloud Provider for Black Hat USA! 🎉 Partnering with companies like Arista, Corelight, Lumen, and Palo Alto Networks, Cisco helps build and secure the Black Hat network. The NOC focuses on continuous network stability, delivering seamless security and visibility through an embedded SOC. 🔒🌐 #BlackHat2025 #CyberSecurity #Cisco #NetworkOperations #TechPartnerships</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refining SSO at Black Hat USA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7672/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7672/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Black Hat USA 2025! Cisco Duo has enhanced its role as the multifactor authentication (MFA) and single sign-on (SSO) provider for the Network Operations Center (NOC). The successful deployment of Duo Directory has expanded user access, supporting over 100 users at the event. This upgrade improves identity and access management for both users and admins. Key features include streamlined password management and a new Global Enrollment Policy to simplify onboarding. 🔐&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing DNS With Umbrella at Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7673/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7673/</guid>
      <description>Cisco continues to enhance security at Black Hat, focusing on DNS monitoring since 2017. 🌐 With Umbrella, they route DNS traffic through a centralized service, gaining insights into potential threats like malware and phishing. At Black Hat USA 2025, encrypted DNS requests were blocked to improve visibility into user traffic. 🔍 The team prioritized monitoring the ApateWeb PUP delivery and phishing campaign, noting specific domain patterns. #Cisco #BlackHat2025 #CyberSecurity #DNS #Umbrella</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebuilding homes and a resilient community in Western North Carolina</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7627/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7627/</guid>
      <description>In Western North Carolina, Cisco Crisis Response and 40 Communities are aiding in the recovery from Hurricane Helene. 🌪️ After the storm caused severe damage, affecting over 73,000 homes, a coalition was formed to support local leaders and nonprofits in the rebuilding efforts. 🏠 Nearly a year later, the focus remains on restoring homes, especially for low-income families, while ensuring vital services are accessible. 🤝 #CommunitySupport #HurricaneHelene #RebuildingTogether #CrisisResponse&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Velocity Reimagined Wins Triple Industry Recognition!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7611/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7611/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco’s Marketing Velocity Reimagined has achieved a remarkable feat by winning three industry awards in 2025! 🏆 The program received the 2025 Killer Content Award for Channel Partner Marketing, recognizing its innovative digital co-marketing experience that empowers partners with learning and customizable campaigns. 📈 It also earned the 2025 Sammy Award for Sales and Marketing, celebrating the team&amp;rsquo;s efforts to enhance connections with partners and drive growth through data-driven&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello Developer: September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7651/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7651/</guid>
      <description>Get ready for an exciting design update! 🎨 Whether you&amp;rsquo;re an experienced developer or just starting out, discover resources to enhance your apps and games. Explore videos, downloads, and documentation. Additionally, you can sign up for one-on-one sessions focusing on machine learning and AI. Plus, meet the team behind the popular game, Hello Kitty Island Adventure! 🌟 #HelloDeveloper #AppDevelopment #GameDesign #MachineLearning #HelloKittyAdventure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Our Newest Innovators: Welcoming AI4SE Interns as JetBrains Employees!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7592/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7592/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting times at JetBrains as we welcome our new AI4SE interns! These recent graduates from TU Delft have transitioned from academic projects to full-time roles, applying their MSc thesis work in real-world settings. Meet Milan, Nadine, Saga, and Sergey, who gained hands-on experience during their internships and contributed to significant research. Their work will soon lead to journal publications! 📚 The AI4SE program, launched in 2023, combines academic research with industry&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon EC2, Amazon Q Developer, IPv6 updates, and more (September 1, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7588/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7588/</guid>
      <description>📅 This week, the AWS Heroes Summit in Seattle highlighted the contributions of the AWS Heroes community. These exceptional individuals share their expertise through content creation, speaking, and open-source projects. 🤝 The summit provided a platform for networking and collaboration, with discussions on AWS roadmaps and direct feedback opportunities to AWS service teams. 🚀 Notable launches included IPv6 support for AWS App Runner, AWS Client VPN, and RDS Data API, enhancing connectivity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICPC World Finals Livestream: ecnerwala and SecondThread Speed-Solving Kotlin Challenge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7550/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7550/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Join us live from the ICPC World Finals in Baku, Azerbaijan, on September 2, 2025, at 9:30 am UTC! Watch top programmers Andrew ‘ecnerwala’ He and David ‘SecondThread’ Harmeyer compete in a real-time Kotlin speed-solving challenge. Hosted by Sebastian Aigner from JetBrains, this event showcases coding mastery under time pressure. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the chance to see Kotlin&amp;rsquo;s strengths and get inspired to join the upcoming Kotlin Heroes contest! #ICPC #KotlinHeroes #CompetitiveProgramming #LiveEvent&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack Week 2025: How these engineers liquid-cooled a GPU server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7290/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7290/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Hack Week 2025 at Dropbox focused on the theme “Keep It Simple,” encouraging innovation and collaboration. One highlight was the &amp;ldquo;Liquid Cooling CPU/GPU Hardware&amp;rdquo; project, which won the Learn Fast award. The team developed a custom liquid cooling system for GPU servers to address the thermal demands of AI workloads. This system demonstrated significant benefits, including lower operating temperatures and quieter performance. Future plans include expanding testing across multiple data&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready for the Best School Year Ever? Join Our STEM Clubs, Camps, and Competitions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7211/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 07:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7211/</guid>
      <description>🎉 A new school year is here, bringing fresh opportunities in STEM! Join our free online Youth Clubs to enhance your skills in math, coding, and AI. Weekly sessions with expert instructors and a global community await you. 🔍 Explore the Math Club, AI Club, and Coding Club for tailored learning experiences. 🌐 Engage in competitions and prepare for olympiads with peers worldwide! #STEMEducation #YouthClubs #Math #Coding #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awe dropping.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7257/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7257/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Mark your calendars! Join us for a special Apple Event on September 9 at 10 a.m. PT. Tune in to watch live on apple.com, Apple TV, or YouTube Live. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on the latest announcements! #AppleEvent #TechNews #LiveStream 📅🍏📺</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living My Childhood Dream — Thanks to Cisco’s Time2Give Benefit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7199/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7199/</guid>
      <description>Rana K., a Technical Consulting Engineer at Cisco, shares her inspiring journey of fulfilling a childhood dream through the company&amp;rsquo;s Time2Give benefit. 🌍✨ This initiative allows employees to dedicate 80 hours annually to volunteer for causes they care about. Rana, originally from Egypt and now living in Poland, has embraced this opportunity to teach and give back globally. She reflects on the connections she&amp;rsquo;s made, highlighting that cultural differences have not hindered her ability to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare Launching AI Miniseries for Developers (and Everyone Else They Know)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6346/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6346/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloudflare has launched &amp;ldquo;AI Avenue,&amp;rdquo; a miniseries designed to demystify AI for developers and the general public. Each episode explores AI&amp;rsquo;s growth, capabilities, and human augmentation stories, making the technology approachable and engaging. Viewers can interact with AI hands-on, breaking down fears and showcasing its potential. Join the journey to learn more at aiavenue.show! #AI #Cloudflare #Innovation #Technology #HumanAugmentation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch the premiere of the award-winning animated short NEW IDEA here!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6338/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6338/</guid>
      <description>🎥 Discover &amp;ldquo;NEW IDEA,&amp;rdquo; the award-winning animated short that has captured 26 accolades! This film showcases the inspiring journey of its creator, who faced challenges before finding success. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the chance to watch this imaginative piece and appreciate its unique story! #NewIdea #Animation #FilmAwards #ShortFilm #Inspiration ✨</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin on the Backend – What’s New From KotlinConf 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6303/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6303/</guid>
      <description>KotlinConf 2025 showcased significant advancements in server-side Kotlin. 🌐 Key highlights include a strategic partnership with Spring for enhanced null-safety and Kotlin-centric tutorials. 📚 Developers are increasingly adopting Kotlin for backend, with notable insights shared by leaders from major tech companies. Ktor continues to evolve, offering support for modern scalable applications, including new features for dependency injection and server-driven UI development. For in-depth insights,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do any CISOs feel lucky?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6317/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6317/</guid>
      <description>Cybersecurity events like the RSA Conference and &amp;ldquo;Hacker Summer Camp&amp;rdquo; in Vegas are crucial for industry leaders. This year, CISOs expressed heightened concerns over nation-state threats and the impact of AI on security. Key discussions included resilience and anti-fragility in cybersecurity, with panels addressing AI’s role in enterprise threats. Informal settings also allowed for deeper conversations among CISOs about the practical use of AI and data protection challenges. #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The power of ten — and the power of Purpose</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5283/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5283/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco empowers employees through the Time2Give program, offering ten days off to volunteer and $10,000 in matching donations. In FY25, 81% of employees participated, contributing over 566,000 volunteer hours. This initiative not only supports communities but also enhances employee retention and recognition. Learn more about our impact and future goals for FY26! 🌍🤝 #Cisco #CorporateResponsibility #Volunteerism #CommunityImpact #EmployeeEngagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supabase Launch Week 15 Hackathon Winner Announcement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5292/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5292/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Supabase Launch Week 15 has concluded, and we are excited to announce the winners of our Hackathon! The event showcased remarkable innovation from participants, demonstrating their technical skills. The standout project, &amp;ldquo;Figma AI Tickets&amp;rdquo; by vickywane, is a plugin that converts design tasks into actionable user stories using OpenAI’s GPT-4. Congratulations to all participants for their impressive submissions! 👏 #Supabase #Hackathon #Innovation #Figma #GPT4</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackathon: Winners Announced!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-6361/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-6361/</guid>
      <description>🚆 The winners of the first Railway User Hackathon have been announced! This event showcased innovative projects aimed at improving railway user experiences. Several projects received honorable mentions for their creativity and potential impact. Congratulations to all participants for their hard work and dedication! 🎉 #Hackathon #RailwayInnovation #UserExperience #Winners #TechForGood</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
