<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Event on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/categories/event/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Event on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:38:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[Live session] Agentic developer workflows powered by Rovo Dev</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11640/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11640/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join us for a webinar on November 13th, 2025, focused on agentic developer workflows using Jira, Bitbucket, and Rovo Dev. Discover how Rovo Dev—our AI agent—can enhance code generation, reviews, and overall production speed. The session will include demos, getting started tips, and a live Q&amp;amp;A with Atlassian experts. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to transform your workflows! 🔗 Sign up now! #Webinar #AI #DevTools #Atlassian #RovoDev</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join the Unreal Engine simulation team at I/ITSEC 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11653/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11653/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join us at I/ITSEC 2025 to explore the latest in XR-based flight and drone simulator demos. Discover new updates for Unreal Engine focused on AI and robotics workflows. Learn how Epic ecosystem tools like MetaHuman and RealityScan can enhance your simulation projects. 📅 Book your meeting with us today! #IITSEC2025 #UnrealEngine #Simulation #AIFuture #Robotics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Next.js Got Its Snappy Client Navs Back</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11532/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11532/</guid>
      <description>Frontend developer Sam Selikoff recently joined Vercel and questioned the Next.js team about achieving snappy client navigation with React Server Components (RSC). At the Next.js Conference, he highlighted the challenges of using RSCs while maintaining fast navigation, referencing past trends where frameworks moved rendering back to the server for improved performance. Selikoff discussed how companies like Twitter and Netflix have successfully enhanced load times and performance by&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating the magic cycle of research breakthroughs and real-world applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11558/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11558/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements were shared at the recent Research@ event by Google Research, showcasing breakthroughs in earth science, genomics, and quantum computing. These innovations are part of a “magic cycle” where research and real-world applications drive each other forward. Enhanced AI tools and open platforms are accelerating this process, leading to new opportunities in various fields. 🌍🔬 Stay tuned for more updates on how technology is shaping our future! #GoogleResearch #Innovation #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start Your Engines: Codegeist 2025 Hackathon Is Here</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11511/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11511/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Codegeist 2025 is now open! This annual hackathon invites developers to create apps that enhance teamwork and collaboration, inspired by the precision of racing crews. Participants can use Forge to build solutions for Jira and Confluence. With over $120,000 in prizes available, including $15,000 for grand prize winners, there’s plenty to gain. The submission window runs from October 27 to December 22. Join the community and showcase your talent! 💻🏆 #Codegeist2025 #Atlassian #Hackathon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live from the OpenAI forum: Learning to code in the age of AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11504/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11504/</guid>
      <description>Join us for a virtual fireside chat featuring our CEO, Prashanth Chandrasekar, at the OpenAI Forum! 🗣️ The discussion will focus on the evolving role of developers as AI technology advances. Many junior developers are understandably concerned about their future in the field. 🌐 Tune in on November 3 at 3 PM EDT to learn about insights from our 2025 Developer Survey and how we can support the next generation of engineers. 💻 #OpenAI #SoftwareDevelopment #FutureOfWork #AI #TechTalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy birthday, Repo! A look back on our mascot’s first year</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11489/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 12:46:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11489/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Happy 1st Birthday, Repo! 🎉 This year marked the debut of Repo, our helpful &amp;ldquo;reponaut,&amp;rdquo; who assists developers in managing complex coding challenges. Key events included advancements in Red Hat OpenShift AI and the successful growth of the Quarkus project, highlighting the focus on developer productivity. In 2025, major releases such as Red Hat Enterprise Linux 10 and the Red Hat OpenShift Lightspeed assistant enhanced the developer experience. The community continues to embrace AI and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating partner excellence: The 2025–2026 Elastic Partner Awards</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11421/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11421/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Celebrating excellence in innovation, the 2025–2026 Elastic Partner Awards are underway! These awards honor partners globally for their significant contributions to Elastic&amp;rsquo;s Search AI Platform. Events kicked off in Bengaluru on September 24 and will continue in cities like New York, Amsterdam, and more. Awards are given in seven categories, including Top GenAI Partner and Top Services Partner, with updates provided as winners are announced. 🏆 Stay tuned for more! #ElasticPartnerAwards&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Distributed Systems: Jason Taylor Shows How .NET Aspire Makes the Complex Feel Effortless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11455/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 14:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11455/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025, Jason Taylor showcased how .NET Aspire simplifies building distributed systems. He emphasized that &amp;ldquo;effortless&amp;rdquo; means reducing friction while focusing on delivering user-centric features. With just a few clicks, developers can enhance ASP.NET Core apps with automatic resilience and health checks. The local development experience is notably improved, allowing new team members to onboard quickly with one press of F5. Discover more in the full presentation!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Distributed Systems: Jason Taylor Shows How .NET Aspire Makes the Complex Feel Effortless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11628/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 14:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11628/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025, Jason Taylor, Microsoft MVP, introduced .NET Aspire, a tool aimed at simplifying distributed systems development. He emphasized that “effortless” means focusing effort where it counts, reducing unnecessary complexity. With just a few clicks, developers can enhance applications with features like automatic retry policies and service discovery. Taylor showcased how .NET Aspire improves local development, making onboarding new team members easier and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DroidKaigi 2025 – Koog で広がる Kotlin とAI の可能性</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11632/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 07:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11632/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Recently, I attended the DroidKaigi After Party hosted by KINTO Technologies and JetBrains. The focus was on the session “AI Utilization in Development with Kotlin,” particularly on the Koog framework. 📹 For those interested, you can watch the session video featuring Sebastian Aigner discussing Koog, an OSS Kotlin agent framework. 📚 I also shared insights on how to construct AI workflows using Koog and provided additional resources for further learning. For more details, check out the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of BPO in the Age of AI and Automation: A Conversational Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11474/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11474/</guid>
      <description>Discover insights from our recent webinar on the future of BPO in an era shaped by AI and automation. 🤖 Industry leaders discussed the impact of intelligent automation, the need for upskilling, and the role of hyper-personalization. They emphasized that human empathy and adaptability remain crucial for success. As BPOs face digital transformation, the conversation highlighted what’s next for the industry. 🌐 #BPO #AI #Automation #DigitalTransformation #FutureOfWork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreal Engine Student Showcase 2025 just dropped</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11443/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11443/</guid>
      <description>🎉 The 2025 Unreal Engine Student Showcase has been released! This year&amp;rsquo;s showcase features impressive projects from students in various fields, including games, film and TV, and animation. These creations highlight the talent and creativity of the next generation of developers and artists. Check out the inspiring work that is shaping the future! 🌟 #UnrealEngine #StudentShowcase #GameDevelopment #Animation #CreativeArts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brickster Voices: Meet Maggie Chu, Sr. Manager, Field Engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11461/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11461/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Maggie Chu, Sr. Manager of Field Engineering at Brickster! In the latest Brickster Voices feature, she shares her journey in building and scaling alongside customers. Her insights highlight the importance of collaboration and innovation in the engineering field. Discover more about the experiences that shape our team! #BricksterVoices #FieldEngineering #Leadership #CareerJourney #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Than a Warm-Up: Start KubeCon With a Colocated Event</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11337/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11337/</guid>
      <description>KubeCon + CloudNativeCon is evolving beyond keynotes and pavilions. Colocated events are becoming essential for attendees, offering targeted learning opportunities before the main conference. From newcomers to seasoned pros, there’s something for everyone. 🌟 One highlight is KyvernoCon, focusing on Policy as Code, which aids enterprises in managing Kubernetes efficiently. 🚀 GitOps is also gaining traction with the introduction of FluxCon, emphasizing the growing importance of these practices&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Bonds Beyond Business: How Human Connection Defines Cisco Culture</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11334/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 12:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11334/</guid>
      <description>Cole A. shares his experience in India, attending a teammate&amp;rsquo;s wedding, highlighting Cisco&amp;rsquo;s people-first culture. He reflects on the importance of human connections in achieving success, emphasizing that behind every project are dedicated individuals. His trip enriched his understanding of different cultures and reinforced his philosophy: people come first. 🤝🌍💼 #CiscoCulture #HumanConnection #PeopleFirst #Diversity #Teamwork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Customer Achievement Awards: APJC 2025 Finalists</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11310/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11310/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Cisco! The inaugural Cisco Customer Achievement Awards for the APJC region have been launched to honor organizations driving innovation and digital transformation. These awards expand on the previous CX Customer Hero Awards. Congratulations to the finalists in the AI Infrastructure Innovation Award and CX AI Trailblazer Award categories! 🎉 Stay tuned for the awards ceremony at Cisco Live Melbourne on November 10, 2025. #CiscoAwards #DigitalTransformation #Innovation #APJC&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Modern Enterprise Toolkit for Secure, High-Quality Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11311/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11311/</guid>
      <description>Join JetBrains Qodana on November 19, 2025, for a live session focused on embedding quality, security, and compliance into development workflows. Hosted by Kai Schmithuesen, learn about Qodana&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and how it integrates with DevOps. Key topics include secure code practices, enhanced access control, and insights for managing project health. Mark your calendars and register! 🗓️🔒 #JetBrains #DevOps #Qodana #SecureCoding #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ken Thompson Recalls Unix’s Rowdy, Lock-Picking Origins</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-26-11284/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 13:05:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-26-11284/</guid>
      <description>Ken Thompson reflects on the early days of the Unix operating system in a recent oral history at the Computer History Museum. 🎤 At 82, he shares memories of the collaborative environment at Bell Labs, where innovation thrived among a spirited group of tech enthusiasts. 💡 Thompson details his transition from the failed Multics project to the creation of Unix, emphasizing the importance of experimentation and community. He also shares a quirky anecdote about raising a baby alligator at the lab!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why PyTorch Won</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-25-11279/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 20:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-25-11279/</guid>
      <description>During the PyTorch Conference 2025 in San Francisco, I had the opportunity to interview Luca Antiga, a key figure in the PyTorch Foundation. Antiga shared insights on why PyTorch has thrived in the AI landscape. Its user-friendly, &amp;ldquo;pythonic&amp;rdquo; nature has made it a favorite among researchers, who have since transitioned to the tech industry. Moreover, PyTorch has maintained relevance through various AI advancements, including generative AI. It’s now vital for both model training and production,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the AIPCon 8 Demos Transforming Manufacturing, Insurance, and Construction</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11254/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11254/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AIPCon 8 showcased how AI is reshaping manufacturing, insurance, and construction. 🌟 Companies like Ursa Major are transforming traditional workflows into automated, intelligent systems that enhance efficiency and accuracy. 📈 From automated insurance underwriting to streamlined construction operations, these implementations highlight the power of enterprise AI in real-world applications. 🔍 Discover how organizations are building new operating models tailored to their specific needs! #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One night changed everything: Why I sleep out for Covenant House</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11227/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11227/</guid>
      <description>I participated in my sixth Sleep Out for Covenant House, an event raising funds for homeless youth. 🌙 Each year, I learn more about the challenges faced by the 4.2 million young people experiencing homelessness. My first Sleep Out opened my eyes to the urgency of their needs. 🚶‍♂️💧 Join me in supporting this cause and raising awareness. #CovenantHouse #EndYouthHomelessness #SleepOut #SupportYouth #Community</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Affordability, Familiarity, and Novelty: DoorDash’s LLM-assisted personalization framework</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11222/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11222/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DoorDash recently presented at KDD 2025&amp;rsquo;s PARIS Workshop, discussing their LLM-assisted personalization framework for multi-vertical retail. The framework focuses on three key dimensions: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Familiarity&lt;/strong&gt; - highlighting trusted favorites. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Affordability&lt;/strong&gt; - aligning with price preferences. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Novelty&lt;/strong&gt; - introducing new and exciting products. This approach aims to enhance customer discovery, ensuring shopping feels personalized and effortless. #DoorDash #Personalization&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powering Your AI-Ready Campus of the Future: Join us at EDUCAUSE 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11140/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11140/</guid>
      <description>Join Cisco at EDUCAUSE 2025 from October 28-31 in Nashville! Discover how Cisco’s AI-ready solutions empower higher education institutions to harness AI securely. Learn about intelligent assistants and operational insights designed to enhance productivity and campus experiences. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss our lunch and learn session featuring insights from leading universities. #EDUCAUSE2025 #AI #HigherEd #CiscoInnovation #CampusTransformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Builder: Cesar Hernandez, Manager, Personalized Support</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11242/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11242/</guid>
      <description>Meet Cesar Hernandez, Manager of Personalized Support at Twilio. His journey highlights the importance of timely referrals and leading with empathy. 🌍 Cesar is dedicated to personal growth and giving back to his community in Bogotá, showcasing how professional development can align with social responsibility. 🤝 Read more about his inspiring story! #Leadership #Community #Twilio #Empathy #ProfessionalGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic at Money20/20 USA 2025: Powering the next era of financial services</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11157/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11157/</guid>
      <description>Join Elastic at Money20/20 USA 2025 in Las Vegas to explore how cloud and AI are transforming financial services. Key topics include data management, fraud prevention, and compliance. Financial institutions must innovate while maintaining trust. Customers expect seamless digital experiences, while regulators emphasize transparency and security. Elastic Cloud on AWS supports these goals, enhancing efficiency and resilience in the industry. #Money2020 #Fintech #AI #DataManagement #ElasticCloud 🌐💼🔍</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic recognized as a finalist for Innovation in Customer Portals in 2025 TSIA STAR Awards</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11147/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11147/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news! Elastic has been named a finalist in the 2025 TSIA STAR Awards for Innovation in Customer Portals. This recognition highlights our commitment to enhancing digital customer experiences through AI technology. We proudly utilize our own Search AI Platform, demonstrating our dedication to delivering exceptional support. Thank you, TSIA, for acknowledging our efforts! 🙌 #Elastic #CustomerExperience #AIInnovation #TSIA #DigitalSupport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showcasing Innovation and Commitment at NetAcad’s European Partner Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11116/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11116/</guid>
      <description>🌍 At the recent Cisco NetAcad European Partner Conference in Thessaloniki, leaders gathered to discuss the future of workforce training. Cisco aims to equip 1.5 million Europeans with essential digital skills by 2030, focusing on AI readiness. With 3,841 academies supporting 5.1 million students, the commitment to education is strong. AI is reshaping job roles, with 78% of tech positions now needing AI skills. #CiscoNetAcad #AIFuture #DigitalSkills #WorkforceDevelopment #EducationInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Block Got 12,000 Employees Using AI Agents in Two Months</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11082/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11082/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Block has successfully deployed AI agents to its 12,000 employees in just eight weeks, a feat shared at the All Things Open 2025 conference. It began with a single engineer frustrated by limited AI capabilities. After experimenting with OpenAI’s function calling, Block adopted the Model Context Protocol to enhance automation. The team pivoted to focus on user-friendly design, ensuring even non-technical staff could easily access the tools. #AI #Innovation #TechNews #EmployeeEngagement #Block</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Kiro waitlist, EBS Volume Clones, EC2 Capacity Manager, and more (October 20, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11081/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11081/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from the tech world! The global tech community is wrapping up the year with events like the Amazon Q Developer coding challenges in South Africa. The first event in Johannesburg was a success, with more to come in Durban and Cape Town. Key launches include: - &lt;strong&gt;Kiro&lt;/strong&gt;: Open to all developers now, with over 100,000 on the waitlist. - &lt;strong&gt;EC2 Capacity Manager&lt;/strong&gt;: A centralized tool for managing capacity across multiple accounts and regions. - &lt;strong&gt;EBS Volume Clones&lt;/strong&gt;: Create&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering the Course of Wireless Transformation with Cisco and USGA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11026/</guid>
      <description>Cisco played a crucial role in powering the 125th U.S. Open with advanced technology. They deployed 550 access points and used Wi-Fi 7 to ensure seamless connectivity for over 225,000 attendees. This infrastructure supported various digital interactions, from ticketing to social media sharing, enhancing the fan experience. The setup faced challenges of high demand and an outdoor environment, yet Cisco successfully managed the complexities to deliver reliable connectivity. #USOpen #Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf 2025 Is Coming Up Soon!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11010/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news for plugin developers! The JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf is set for November 5. This event features a full day of talks, live Q&amp;amp;A, and in-depth sessions on plugin development. Key topics include creating your first plugin, language plugins, AI-powered testing, and more. Join us live on YouTube or catch up later! #JetBrains #PluginDevelopment #DevConference #SoftwareDevelopment #TechEvent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Igniting our future workforce: Shaping the future in Europe through Cisco Networking Academy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10985/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10985/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The Cisco Networking Academy Partner Conference in Thessaloniki recently gathered educators, government officials, and industry partners to celebrate the past year’s achievements and discuss future goals. 🤝 This event highlighted the importance of collaboration in shaping the future workforce in Europe. The spirit of community and support was evident, emphasizing the shared commitment to education and skill development. #CiscoNetworkingAcademy #FutureWorkforce #Collaboration #Education&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic AI Unleashed: Join the AWS &amp; NVIDIA Hackathon</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10964/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 19:39:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10964/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to innovate? Join the AWS &amp;amp; NVIDIA Hackathon and build the future of Agentic AI! Create an autonomous application using advanced AI models and scalable infrastructure. This event offers hands-on experience, networking opportunities, and the chance to win prizes. Teams can request $100 in promotional credits to support their projects. Be sure to monitor your usage to maximize your resources! #AI #Hackathon #AWS #NVIDIA #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Livestream] Maximizing TeamCity: New Features in Action and a Look Ahead</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10941/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10941/</guid>
      <description>📅 Join us on October 22, 2025, for a livestream on maximizing TeamCity! TeamCity Solutions Engineers Ricardo Leite and Daniel Gallo will showcase new features and provide a sneak peek at future updates. This session is designed for those looking to enhance their TeamCity experience. Expect hands-on demos, configuration walkthroughs, and insights into licensing changes. 🕓 Don&amp;rsquo;t miss it! #TeamCity #DevOps #Webinar #CI/CD #JetBrains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 years of Cisco Crisis Response: Reflecting on resilience from Hurricane Katrina to Helene</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10923/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 07:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10923/</guid>
      <description>🌍 As we celebrate 20 years of Cisco Crisis Response (CCR), we reflect on resilience from Hurricane Katrina to Hurricane Helene. In 2005, CCR began by restoring communications in disaster-struck areas. Over the years, it has evolved to meet the growing needs of communities affected by crises. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s partnership with BBC StoryWorks highlights CCR&amp;rsquo;s vital role in reconnecting people and rebuilding hope. 👉 Watch the video to learn more about CCR’s impactful work! #CiscoCrisisResponse #Resilience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Taste of P99 CONF: Low Latency With eBPF, Rust and More</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10898/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:30:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10898/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Get ready for P99 CONF 2025! This free, virtual event will take place on October 22-23, focusing on performance and low latency engineering. 🗣️ Expect insights from industry leaders like Clickhouse, Arm, NVIDIA, and Disney, among many others. 📚 Don’t miss the chance to watch over 200 on-demand tech talks from P99 CONF 2024, covering essential topics in low latency. 🔍 Stay tuned for detailed sessions on latency management strategies from experts like Pekka Enberg. #P99CONF #LowLatency&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Years Ago, I Took a Chance — Now I’m at Cisco Living the Dream</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10886/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10886/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Two years ago, Jordan B. took a leap from the FinTech industry to Cisco, inspired by its people-first culture. He reflects on his journey of growth and mentorship that led him to a fulfilling role as an Inside Account Executive. Jordan emphasizes the importance of connections and the value of a supportive network. #Cisco #CareerJourney #Mentorship #Growth #PeopleFirst</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OCP Summit 2025: The Open Future of Networking Hardware for AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10879/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10879/</guid>
      <description>🌐 At the OCP Summit 2025, Meta outlined advancements in network fabrics tailored for AI training clusters. 📈 The company expanded its hardware portfolio, introducing new disaggregated network platforms to enhance collaboration within the Open Compute Project. 🔧 Meta emphasized the importance of open hardware in driving innovation and improving data center efficiency. Key milestones include the evolution of Disaggregated Scheduled Fabric and the launch of the Ethernet for Scale-Up Networking&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Global Impact Week Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10973/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10973/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Twilio recently shared insights from their 2025 Global Impact Week. The recap highlights cloud communications trends, showcasing customer stories and providing tips for developing scalable voice and SMS applications using Twilio&amp;rsquo;s APIs. Stay updated on the latest in tech and communication! 📱💬 #CloudCommunications #Twilio #TechTrends #APIs #VoiceAndSMS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Builder’s Arcade at SIGNAL Sydney 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10974/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10974/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Discover the Builder’s Arcade at SIGNAL Sydney 2025! This interactive space showcases innovative experiences designed for developers. Attendees can engage with various activations highlighting the latest in technology and collaboration. Join us to explore and connect with industry leaders, enhancing your skills and insights! #SIGNALSydney2025 #Developers #TechEvent #Innovation #Networking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Quick Suite, Amazon EC2, Amazon EKS, and more (October 13, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10875/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10875/</guid>
      <description>This week marked the inaugural AWS AI in Practice meetup hosted by the AWS User Group UK, focusing on AI-assisted software development and agents. Next week, the excitement continues in Italy with sessions on AI agents and context engineering at Codemotion in Milan and an AWS User Group meetup in Rome. 🇮🇹 Notable recent launches include the Amazon Quick Suite for enhanced AI-driven insights, new EC2 instances powered by AMD and Intel processors, and updates to Amazon EKS supporting Kubernetes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILES AND FLOWERS | Award-Winning Animated Short</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10606/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10606/</guid>
      <description>🎬 Exciting news in the animation world! The award-winning short film &amp;ldquo;Miles and Flowers&amp;rdquo; blends drama with humor for an engaging viewing experience. Created entirely in Unreal Engine, the filmmaker worked on this project for two years, focusing on a captivating story. Check it out and experience the unique storytelling! 🌼✨ #Animation #ShortFilm #UnrealEngine #MilesAndFlowers #FilmMaking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything Big Starts Small: Building Open Social Web Apps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10598/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10598/</guid>
      <description>🚀 It&amp;rsquo;s been nearly three years since Elon Musk acquired Twitter, and the fediverse is steadily growing. 🌐 At the recent FediForum, Ben Werdmuller emphasized the importance of starting small for the Open Social Web. He noted that successful platforms often originate from specific community needs. 📢 New projects like AltStore were announced, highlighting the potential of decentralized applications. #Fediverse #OpenSocialWeb #FediForum #CommunityDriven #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Door to More: Unlocking Creativity with AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10605/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10605/</guid>
      <description>Join us on November 6th in San Francisco for an exclusive event with DoorDash marketing leaders! 🚀 Hear from Gina Igwe, Jennifer Richardi, and Shannon Duncan about how AI is transforming creative marketing. This is a great opportunity to learn, network, and enjoy dinner and drinks. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out! RSVP by 10/22. #DoorDash #MarketingInnovation #AI #Networking #CreativeLeadership</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Kotlin Multiplatform Project and Win a Trip to KotlinConf 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10587/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10587/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for students and recent grads! The Kotlin Multiplatform Contest is now open. Build a project using Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP) for a chance to win a trip to KotlinConf 2026 in Munich, Germany! 🏆 Join the dedicated Slack channel for support, share progress, and connect with other participants. Prizes include travel, accommodation, and community recognition. Contest details: - Opens: September 15, 2025 - Deadline: January 12, 2026 - Winners announced: January 22, 2026 For more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting Your KotlinConf Proposal: Expert Tips to  Help You Stand Out</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10557/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10557/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to share your Kotlin expertise at KotlinConf? Here are some expert tips to craft a standout proposal! 1️⃣ Start with a clear and compelling title. First impressions matter! Make sure your title conveys your topic and its benefits to the audience. 2️⃣ Use storytelling in your abstract. Engage your audience by promising a valuable learning experience through a narrative. These insights can boost your chances of acceptance and help you shine at the event! 🌟 #KotlinConf #Kotlin&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charting the Course: Resilience and Innovation at AFCEA TechNet Indo Pacific 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10540/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10540/</guid>
      <description>Join Cisco at AFCEA TechNet Indo Pacific 2025 from October 28-30 in Hawai’i! 🌺 This year&amp;rsquo;s theme, &amp;ldquo;Sword &amp;amp; Shield: Ensuring a Secure, Free, and Prosperous Indo-Pacific,&amp;rdquo; focuses on overcoming challenges in mission connectivity and security. Visit Booth #1222 for demos on digital resiliency and AI-driven NetOps. Discover how Cisco’s solutions help maintain operations in tough environments. 💻✨ #AFCEA2025 #Cisco #Cybersecurity #Innovation #TechEvent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Direct Line to Cisco Automation: Ask Ed Novak About Workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10541/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 13:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10541/</guid>
      <description>📅 Join us on October 8 for a live Q&amp;amp;A with Ed Novak, a Cisco Technical Marketing Engineer! This interactive session will focus on Cisco Workflows, allowing you to ask questions and explore real-world use cases. Prepare your queries and gain insights to enhance your network operations. 🕘 Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to engage directly with an expert! #Cisco #Automation #Workflows #Networking #LiveQandA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Non-Commercial JetBrains Rider Users: Tell Us Your Stories!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10533/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 12:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10533/</guid>
      <description>📣 Attention non-commercial JetBrains Rider users! It’s been nearly a year since Rider became free for non-commercial use. To celebrate, JetBrains is inviting users to share their stories about projects developed with Rider. They are seeking participants for interviews to discuss your experiences, whether it’s for side projects, open-source contributions, or educational endeavors. If interested, contact &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sasha.ivanova@jetbrains.com&#34;&gt;sasha.ivanova@jetbrains.com&lt;/a&gt; for more details. Participants will gain visibility for their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team ’25 Europe: AI that’s changing the game for teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10527/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10527/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Exciting developments at Team ‘25 Europe in Barcelona! AI is reshaping teamwork, with Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s Rovo leading the way. Over three million users benefit from its features, enhancing productivity and collaboration across organizations. Rovo integrates seamlessly with existing systems, transforming workflows and delivering quick answers to users. The rollout continues, with a mobile app on the horizon. Stay tuned for more updates! 🚀 #Team25Europe #AI #Atlassian #Rovo #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From contributor to Elastician: João Neto</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10572/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10572/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Discover the inspiring journey of João Neto, who transitioned from a passionate community contributor to an Elastic employee. His active involvement in the Elastic Contributor Program helped shape his career through knowledge sharing and meaningful connections. João highlights how community engagement and technical expertise paved the way for his dream role at Elastic. Learn more about his experiences and insights! #Elastic #Community #CareerGrowth #Inspiration #TechJourney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet JetBrains at Azure Dev Summit 2025 (Lisbon, Oct 13–16)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10513/</guid>
      <description>🌍 JetBrains is excited to attend the Azure Dev Summit 2025 in Lisbon from October 13–16! Join Max Solovyev, Head of Growth for .NET and GameDev Tools, at our booth to explore how Rider and the dotUltimate suite can enhance your .NET on Azure projects. We will showcase practical demos, discuss Azure App Service, and share insights on performance diagnostics and JetBrains AI features. 📅 Book a brief chat with Max to discuss your goals. #JetBrains #AzureDevSummit #DotNet #Lisbon2025&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Atlas Camp: Amsterdam Call for Speakers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10508/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10508/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The call for speakers is now open for Atlas Camp 2026 in Amsterdam. This flagship Atlassian conference focuses on sharing real stories about platform extensibility, software delivery, and AI-powered solutions. Join a global community and inspire others! Submit your proposal at events.atlassian.com/atlascamp-cfs. #AtlasCamp #Developers #Atlassian #TechCommunity #CallForSpeakers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tech Career That Makes Room for Life — and a Book</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10487/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10487/</guid>
      <description>Discover how Ana N., a Marketing Networking Manager at Cisco, found the balance between her career and personal life. After 20 years in public relations, she turned her dream of writing a book into reality with Cisco&amp;rsquo;s supportive culture. The flexibility allowed her to excel at work while being a mother and a wife. Her journey shows how a positive work environment can help achieve personal goals. 📚💼✨ #Cisco #CareerGrowth #WorkLifeBalance #AuthorJourney #SupportiveCulture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker at AI Engineer Paris: Build and Secure AI Agents with Docker</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10446/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10446/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Last week, Docker participated in the inaugural AI Engineer Paris conference, highlighting the evolution of AI application development. Key discussions emphasized that true innovation requires rigorous engineering, not just &amp;ldquo;AI dust.&amp;rdquo; The focus is on creating robust AI agents through standardized practices. Docker&amp;rsquo;s Tushar Jain led a keynote on making AI agent development accessible to all developers. A hands-on workshop followed, teaching attendees how to build collaborative multi-agent&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the AIPCon 8 Demos Redefining the Future of Enterprise AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10393/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 21:37:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10393/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AIPCon 8 showcased transformative AI applications across various industries, highlighting real-world solutions at Palantir&amp;rsquo;s recent conference. From healthcare to motorsport, demos featured innovations like Andretti&amp;rsquo;s RaceOS for rapid data-driven decisions and Nebraska Medicine&amp;rsquo;s automated documentation for efficient revenue cycle management. These advancements illustrate how AI can solve operational challenges and enhance efficiency. #EnterpriseAI #AIPCon8 #Innovation #Healthcare #Motorsport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-World IT Sustainability: 3 Case Studies From Green IO London</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10350/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10350/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The recent Green IO conference in London showcased how organizations like HSBC, OVO Energy, and the British government are implementing sustainable tech practices. HSBC shared their open-source tool for measuring software carbon footprints and their commitment to achieving net-zero emissions by 2050. OVO Energy highlighted innovative uses of home boilers for distributed computing. These case studies illustrate the tangible benefits of aligning environmental responsibility with business&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Awareness Month: Become a Champion of Digital Resilience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10355/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10355/</guid>
      <description>🌐 October marks Cybersecurity Awareness Month! This year, Cisco is offering training and certification giveaways to help you enhance your skills in cybersecurity. You can enter the sweepstakes for a chance to win valuable e-learning bundles. 🎓 Additionally, enjoy a 25% discount on cybersecurity learning products from October 13–20, 2025. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to boost your professional journey! 🚀 #CybersecurityAwareness #Cisco #DigitalResilience #CybersecurityTraining #CareerGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the scenes: Supporting engineers and designers during Tech Week 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10347/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10347/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Tech Week 2025 brought together over 1,500 participants for a unique celebration of innovation at LINE Yahoo. Held from June 30 to July 4, the event featured Tech-Verse, a tech conference showcasing nearly 130 sessions, and Hack Day, an internal hackathon for creative projects. Support for presenters included comprehensive guides, expert reviews, and practice sessions, fostering a collaborative environment. Tech Week emphasizes teamwork and encourages sharing ideas, contributing to a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highlights from the Unreal Fest Stockholm opening session</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10372/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10372/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Unreal Fest Stockholm kicked off with an exciting look at Unreal Engine 5.7, showcasing its latest features. 🔧 Developers working on Fortnite can expect new tools designed to enhance their creative process. 🤖 Additionally, the Epic Developer Assistant has expanded, providing even more support for developers. #UnrealFest #UnrealEngine #GameDevelopment #Fortnite #EpicGames</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Maxims for Great Developer Platform Design</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10319/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10319/</guid>
      <description>Russell Miles shared insights on developer platform design at the Devmio International JavaScript Conference. 🎸 He outlined three maxims, starting with the idea that platforms require commitment and resources. If a company isn’t ready to invest, they may not need a platform. He emphasized that every organization already has a platform when they ship code. Understanding internal customers and viewing the platform as a product is crucial for success. #DeveloperPlatforms #JavaScript #Devmio&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Miss Out: Attend the 2025 OCP Global Summit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10322/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10322/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The 2025 OCP Global Summit is just around the corner! Cisco will showcase innovations in AI networking, security, and open networking. Key topics include AI infrastructure, P4 programmability, and SONiC, all aimed at supporting organizations in the AI era. Don’t miss this opportunity to see how Cisco is helping to shape the future of data centers. 🚀 #OCPSummit2025 #Cisco #AINetworking #DataCenter #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside LY Corporation&#39;s &#34;Tech-Verse 2025&#34; conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10303/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10303/</guid>
      <description>🌟 LY Corporation recently held its &amp;ldquo;Tech-Verse 2025&amp;rdquo; conference, focusing on artificial intelligence. The two-day event attracted over 1,200 attendees and featured 131 sessions across 12 categories. Key topics included platform integration post-merger and LY&amp;rsquo;s ambitious AI strategy. CTO Euivin Park outlined the goal of implementing AI across 44 services to enhance user experience. For more insights, check out the presentation slides or archived videos on YouTube! 📊💻 #TechVerse2025&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebexOne 2025: Unlocking the Power of Connected Intelligence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10260/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10260/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Today at WebexOne in San Diego, Cisco unveiled its vision for the future of work, emphasizing the importance of AI in the workplace. 🔑 Key challenges like infrastructure constraints, security threats, and data gaps are being addressed with innovative solutions. Webex is central to this strategy, enhancing communication and collaboration. 🤖 The concept of &amp;ldquo;Connected Intelligence&amp;rdquo; will redefine how we interact—blending human and AI communication seamlessly. #WebexOne #Cisco #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Can Help IT Teams Find the Signals in Alert Noise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10231/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 23:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10231/</guid>
      <description>🚨 IT teams face a challenge with alert fatigue as 95-98% of alerts are often noncritical. This overwhelming noise can lead to burnout and decreased productivity. Mandi Walls from PagerDuty emphasized the need for better frameworks using SLOs, automation, and machine learning to improve alert management. Effective solutions can reduce stress and enhance the work environment for developers. #AlertFatigue #DevOps #MachineLearning #ITManagement #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Modern IT Operations Are Becoming More Like Space Travel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10222/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 19:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10222/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The ManageEngine user conference in Las Vegas explored the link between IT operations and space travel. Former astronaut Mike Massimino shared insights on teamwork and problem-solving, drawing parallels between astronaut training and IT practices. He highlighted how both fields require trust in tools and collaboration among team members. Massimino&amp;rsquo;s experiences offered a fresh perspective on navigating challenges in IT, especially with the rise of AI. #ITOperations #SpaceTravel #Teamwork&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applications closing for the Airtable AI Incubator</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10225/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10225/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Applications are now open for the Airtable AI Incubator! This program offers builders a chance to transform their ideas into practical solutions with structured mentorship and support. Interested participants must submit their applications by 12pm ET on September 30. Answer key questions to clarify your vision and readiness. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to innovate! #AirtableAI #AIIncubator #Innovation #TechForGood #ApplyNow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 years of helping build a better Internet: a look back at Birthday Week 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10204/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10204/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Celebrating 15 years of Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s mission to build a better Internet! This year&amp;rsquo;s Birthday Week highlighted key themes: promoting new monetization models and enhancing community engagement. Major announcements included plans to hire 1,111 interns in 2026 and support for open-source projects like Ladybird and Omarchy. Cloudflare also opened collaboration hubs in major cities and extended free access to developer tools for non-profits. For more details, check out the blog! #Cloudflare&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience the Power of Connection and AI at Cisco Connect Cancun</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10200/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Cisco Connect is back at the Moon Palace Hotel in Cancun! This event unites 3,000 attendees to explore the latest Cisco innovations and reconnect with peers. The focus is on the “One Cisco” strategy, emphasizing integration across networking, security, and services to create value for customers. AI takes center stage, with discussions on its impact on customer experience. Insights reveal that 93% of global respondents see agentic AI enhancing personalized services by 2028. #CiscoConnect #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktoberfest 2025: How to Participate</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10194/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 07:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10194/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Hacktoberfest 2025 registrations are now open! Join the global celebration of open source this October. To participate, register before October 31 and contribute to projects on GitHub or GitLab with the hacktoberfest topic. Aim for at least 6 accepted pull/merge requests to earn rewards, including digital badges and a limited edition t-shirt for the first 10,000 participants. 👕 Ways to contribute include coding, maintaining projects, or even supporting with documentation and user experience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Digital Event: Open Accelerated Computing Summit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-28-10190/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-28-10190/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Join the Open Accelerated Computing Summit on October 7-8! This digital event will explore new research at the intersection of AI and High-Performance Computing (HPC). Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to gain insights and connect with experts in the field! 🔗 Sign up now: &lt;a href=&#34;https://zoom.us/signup&#34;&gt;Zoom Signup&lt;/a&gt; #OACSummit #AI #HPC #DigitalEvent #Research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networking at the Heart of AI — @Scale: Networking 2025 Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10161/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10161/</guid>
      <description>🌐 AI is transforming networking, and this year&amp;rsquo;s @Scale:Networking event highlighted its critical role. Engineers from major tech companies gathered to discuss the infrastructure needed for AI advancements. 🔍 Key topics included significant investments in AI infrastructure, with companies planning extensive builds and renewable energy initiatives. 📈 Additionally, the evolution of AI models and workloads was a focus, showcasing rapid growth and increasing demands on network performance&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 years of HashiConf: A bold leap into AI-powered infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10158/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10158/</guid>
      <description>🚀 HashiConf 2025 marked a decade of innovation in cloud automation, emphasizing the future of infrastructure as automated and secure. This year, HashiCorp, now part of IBM, highlighted The Infrastructure Cloud, designed for comprehensive management of infrastructure and security. Attendees shared valuable insights, including customer success stories and strategies for implementing AI-ready automation across operations. Catch up on key sessions and announcements on our YouTube channel! 📹&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuing Positive Impact: This Year’s AI4SE Interns in their New Roles at JetBrains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10082/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10082/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news from JetBrains! This year’s AI4SE interns from TU Delft have transitioned to full-time roles on our tech team. During their internships, they worked on innovative projects, enhancing their technical skills and driving impactful changes in software development. Their contributions have already improved team performance and sparked collaboration across product teams. One intern even developed an AI tool that&amp;rsquo;s still in use today! We look forward to their continued growth and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brickster Voices: Meet Cindy Nicola, VP Global Talent Acquisition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10097/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 07:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10097/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Cindy Nicola, VP of Global Talent Acquisition at Databricks! In the latest Brickster Voices feature, Cindy shares her insights on career growth, collaboration, and leadership. Her journey highlights the importance of fostering a strong company culture and guiding talent development. Discover how Cindy&amp;rsquo;s experiences shape the future of talent acquisition at Databricks! #Leadership #TalentAcquisition #CareerGrowth #Databricks #BricksterVoices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Register now for the 2025 Epic MegaJam</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10107/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10107/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Exciting news for game developers! The 2025 Epic MegaJam is set to take place, marking 10 years of innovation in the industry. Gather your team and prepare for a week filled with creativity and game development. Participants will have the chance to win fantastic prizes from our sponsors. Don’t miss out on this opportunity to showcase your skills! #EpicMegaJam #GameDev #Innovation #Creativity #JoinUs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brickster Voices: Meet Chao Cai, Sr. Director, Engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10043/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10043/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Chao Cai, Sr. Director of Engineering at Brickster! In the latest installment of Brickster Voices, Chao shares insights into his career journey and the role of AI in today&amp;rsquo;s tech landscape. Discover how he leads at the intersection of innovation and engineering, shaping the future of the industry. #BricksterVoices #Leadership #AI #Engineering #CareerJourney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the builder: Tanise Love, Senior Employee Impact Manager</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10117/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10117/</guid>
      <description>Meet Tanise Love, Twilio&amp;rsquo;s Senior Employee Impact Manager! 🌟 In her role, Tanise emphasizes the importance of values that shape Twilio’s giving culture. She actively works to bring this culture to life, demonstrating how corporate responsibility can impact communities and employees alike. Discover more about her insights and contributions in the full article. #Twilio #EmployeeSpotlight #CorporateResponsibility #GivingCulture #Leadership</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Human Network – My Journey with Cisco</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9910/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9910/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Shweta Takate reflects on her journey with Cisco, highlighting her transformation since joining in 2007. She describes the supportive culture that felt like family in Bangalore, which fueled her passion and growth. After a brief hiatus for further education in New York, Shweta returned to Cisco, where she found the same welcoming atmosphere. Her story emphasizes the importance of human connection in the workplace. #Cisco #CareerJourney #HumanConnection #WorkCulture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From hackathon nerves to internship wins: Kavya’s journey at 1Password</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9915/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9915/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting journey alert! Meet Kavya, a UBC student who transitioned from a business major to a passionate Computer Science learner. She participated in cmd-f, a hackathon for underrepresented genders in tech, where her team created REALM, a wellness app that integrates personalized health insights and security through Passage by 1Password. 🛡️ After winning the hackathon, Kavya secured an internship at 1Password, where she thrives in a supportive remote culture while contributing to developer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future-proofing Singapore as an AI-first nation with Search AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9937/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9937/</guid>
      <description>During the 2025 National Day Rally, Singapore’s PM Lawrence Wong highlighted the commitment to integrating AI into business processes, aiming to empower local workers. He showcased an AI-powered orthopantomogram (OPG) scanner that cuts dental assessment time significantly. This is part of AI Singapore&amp;rsquo;s 100 Experiments program, which has over 200 AI projects since 2018. Elastic recently partnered with AI Singapore to host a workshop focused on developing AI skills, featuring insights on large&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Q Developer, AWS Step Functions, AWS Cloud Club Captain deadline, and more (September 22, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9886/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 16:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9886/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This week&amp;rsquo;s AWS Roundup highlights key developments from a recent trip to New Zealand, where several events showcased local tech talent. 🌍 A new feature in Amazon Q CLI, called tangent mode, allows users to maintain focus while exploring side topics. It&amp;rsquo;s currently in experimental mode. 📈 Notable launches include: - New models in Amazon Bedrock for enhanced text and image tasks. - Expansion of VPC Reachability Analyzer to seven new regions for better network diagnostics. - Remote MCP server&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Lookback at Workers Launchpad and a Warm Welcome to Cohort #6</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9874/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9874/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Workers Launchpad program supports founders on the Cloudflare network with essential resources and mentorship. Since its inception, 145 startups from 23 countries have joined, tackling issues in AI, cloud infrastructure, and more. Notably, Cohort #5 showcased strong female founder representation. Participants benefit from hands-on support, bootcamps, and VC introductions, leading to funding and successful acquisitions. 🌍💡 Learn more about the program and its impact on innovation!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Come build with us: Cloudflare&#39;s new hubs for startups</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9870/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9870/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloudflare is set to open its San Francisco, Austin, London, and Lisbon offices to startups in 2026! These spaces will be available for collaboration, networking, and focused work, enhancing innovation within the tech community. The initiative aims to support early-stage startups by fostering connections in-person, building on Cloudflare’s long history of hosting community events. 🌍 Join us in creating a better digital environment! #Cloudflare #Startups #Innovation #TechCommunity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Help build the future: announcing Cloudflare’s goal to hire 1,111 interns in 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9875/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9875/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Cloudflare is set to hire 1,111 interns in 2026! This ambitious program aims to tap into new ideas and energy as the company focuses on AI and innovation. The initiative reflects Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s commitment to building a better Internet and investing in future talent. It also aims to challenge traditional methods and explore novel applications of AI. As many firms reduce intern hiring, Cloudflare is taking a different approach, viewing AI as a tool to enhance new hires&amp;rsquo; contributions&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Bets on Austin: Celebrating Our New Downtown Office</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9862/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9862/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Cisco! Today, they opened their new downtown office in Austin, showcasing advanced workplace technologies. Nearly 30 years in Austin, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s commitment to the city continues to grow. The new office symbolizes their belief in Austin&amp;rsquo;s potential and innovation. With over 1,400 employees in the area, Cisco is focused on driving innovation and shaping the future of work. #Cisco #Austin #Innovation #FutureOfWork #TechCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktoberfest 2025: Celebrate All Things Open Source!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9828/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9828/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Hacktoberfest 2025 is coming soon! Starting October 1, join a global celebration of open-source contributions. Register now and help support various projects by completing 6 pull requests this month. The first 10,000 contributors will receive a t-shirt and a tree planted in their name! 🌳 Get ready for fun activities, including partnering with Major League Hacking for events worldwide. Visit Hacktoberfest.com for details and mark your calendars! 🗓️ #Hacktoberfest #OpenSource #CodingCommunity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating a decade of Connected Conservation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9811/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9811/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating a decade of impactful partnership! 🌍 For ten years, Cisco and the Connected Conservation Foundation (CCF) have worked together to enhance wildlife conservation. Their efforts have provided essential technology to monitor and protect species like rhinos and elephants across 46 protected areas in Africa. This World Rhino Day, we reflect on the progress made and the ongoing commitment to safeguarding these animals and their habitats. 🦏✨ #ConnectedConservation #WildlifeProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing: JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9796/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9796/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited to announce JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025! Join us on October 8-9 for a free, online event featuring practical talks, live demos, and expert tips from community speakers and the JetBrains .NET team. 🔗 Register here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://lp.jetbrains.com/dotnet-days-2025&#34;&gt;https://lp.jetbrains.com/dotnet-days-2025&lt;/a&gt; Don’t miss sessions on topics like Clean Architecture, Test Driven Development, and more! #DotNetDays #JetBrains #Programming #TechEvents #CommunityEngagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB.local NYC 2025: Defining the Ideal Database for the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9771/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9771/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from MongoDB.local NYC! Thousands of developers gathered to explore MongoDB&amp;rsquo;s new capabilities, including the release of MongoDB 8.2 and the Voyage AI embedding models. 🛠️ The MongoDB Application Modernization Platform (AMP) aims to help enterprises transition from costly legacy systems to more efficient solutions, showing impressive early results. 🌍 With nearly 60,000 organizations now using MongoDB, the focus remains on providing a flexible and powerful database that&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating Excellence: MongoDB Global Partner Awards 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9761/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9761/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Celebrating innovation in tech, the MongoDB Global Partner Awards 2025 recognize partners driving success in AI and modernization. 🏆 Microsoft has been named Global Cloud Partner of the Year for its growth and collaboration with MongoDB across various industries. 🔗 AWS is honored as Global AI Cloud Partner of the Year, showcasing impactful AI solutions, while Google Cloud excels in joint go-to-market initiatives. ✨ Accenture earns recognition for its commitment to customer success in the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oktane Online 2025: The AI Security Event You Can’t Miss</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9833/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9833/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Join us for Oktane Online, streaming live on September 25-26, 2025! With over 40 sessions on AI, identity, and security, this free event is designed for IT leaders, security professionals, and anyone interested in the future of technology. Expect keynotes from industry leaders, real-time Q&amp;amp;As, and even entertainment from guests like Jeremy Renner! Plus, earn up to 13.5 CPE credits. Don’t miss out—secure your spot today! #OktaneOnline #AISecurity #TechEvent #CPEcredits #IdentityInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Databricks at Sibos in Frankfurt!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9714/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9714/</guid>
      <description>Join Databricks at Sibos in Frankfurt! 🌍 Sibos is a key event where leaders in banking and payments come together to connect and innovate. This year, the focus is on transforming finance through data and AI. Engage in insightful sessions, dynamic conversations, and enjoy a lively rooftop happy hour. Don’t miss out! 🍹💡 #Sibos2025 #Databricks #FinanceInnovation #Banking #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlock Unified Network and Security Analytics with Cisco and Splunk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9708/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 21:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9708/</guid>
      <description>Unlock unified network and security analytics with Cisco and Splunk! 🌐🔍 Join the livestream on September 17 at 9 a.m. PT, hosted by Adrian Illiesiu. Learn from Technical Marketing Engineer Taylor Cook as he demonstrates the Cisco Enterprise Networking app for Splunk. Discover how it integrates data from various Cisco platforms for enhanced network visibility and security management. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on the chance to ask your questions live! #Cisco #Splunk #NetworkSecurity #DevNet #LiveDemo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Profitable Partners Do Differently</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9701/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 19:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9701/</guid>
      <description>Join us at the Cisco Partner Summit 2025 in San Diego from November 3-5 to explore how profitable partnerships can enhance your business growth. The summit will focus on key questions guiding collaboration and the framework of &amp;ldquo;durable growth&amp;rdquo; to drive success. Gain insights from industry leaders and learn effective strategies for partnership profitability. 🌟🤝 #CiscoPartnerSummit #BusinessGrowth #Partnerships #Innovation #Cisco</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Splunk to Cisco: A Seamless Transition in Career and Family</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9680/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9680/</guid>
      <description>Excited to share insights from Vikram U.&amp;rsquo;s journey transitioning from Splunk to Cisco. He highlights the strong bond formed between both teams during the acquisition. Vikram also emphasizes the importance of Cisco&amp;rsquo;s generous parental leave, which allowed him and his wife to welcome their baby girl and navigate parenthood seamlessly. This supportive culture has made a significant impact on their family life. 👶❤️ #CareerTransition #ParentalLeave #Cisco #FamilySupport #WorkLifeBalance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the 2025 Webflow Awards winners</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9655/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9655/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Announcing the 2025 Webflow Awards winners! This annual event celebrates the creativity and innovation within the Webflow community. The awards highlight individuals and organizations making significant contributions to web experiences. 🏆 Community Educator of the Year: Timothy Ricks, known for his impactful educational resources. 🏆 Community Creator of the Year: Ilja van Eck, recognized for his award-winning projects and contributions to the design community. Explore the full list of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GameDev Day 2025 Is Back in October!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9646/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9646/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Exciting news for game developers! JetBrains GameDev Day returns on October 21, 2025! This free, one-day online event focuses on creativity, storytelling, and community in game development. Join industry professionals as they share valuable insights on various topics, from improving workflows to designing accessible games. New this year: local watch parties! Connect with fellow developers in your city while participating in this global event. All sessions will be streamed live on YouTube&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Voice Belongs Here: Creating Compelling KotlinConf Proposals [Livestream]</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9621/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9621/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Ready to elevate your speaking skills? Join the webinar &amp;ldquo;Your Voice Belongs Here&amp;rdquo; on October 14! This session is tailored for individuals from underrepresented groups in tech who have some speaking experience and want to present at KotlinConf. Learn what makes a compelling CFP, how to craft your proposal, and what reviewers seek. Connect, build confidence, and prepare to share your Kotlin journey! #KotlinConf #PublicSpeaking #TechInclusion #CFP #DiversityInTech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Fellowship: Games—explore the making of six awesome games in three weeks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9613/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9613/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Unreal Fellowship: Games 2025 featured an immersive bootcamp for game developers, focusing on skill enhancement and collaboration. 🌟 Participants created six unique games in just three weeks, showcasing their creativity and technical abilities. Discover the inspiring stories behind these innovative projects! #UnrealFellowship #GameDevelopment #IndieGames #GamingCommunity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains at the ICPC World Finals 2025 Baku</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9554/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9554/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The ICPC World Finals 2025 in Baku was a significant event, showcasing top student talent from around the globe. JetBrains was proud to support the competition and the community it fosters. 🎓 The Neapolis University Pafos team, Sigma++, participated and earned an Honors distinction. Andrey Ivanov from JetBrains emphasized the camaraderie and appreciation for those who organized the event. 🛠️ Attendees enjoyed activities at the JetBrains booth, including the Kotlin Challenge and interactions&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cisco Supports Work-Life Balance: My 21-Day Motorcycle Dream Trip</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9463/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9463/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Namita J., a Meraki Technical Leader at Cisco, shares her inspiring journey of a 21-day motorcycle trip across Europe. Cisco’s culture of trust and flexibility allowed her to take 30 days off without concerns about work. Her manager and team fully supported her adventure, ensuring a seamless workflow in her absence. This experience highlights how Cisco promotes work-life balance, empowering employees to pursue their dreams. 🏍️✨ #WorkLifeBalance #Cisco #EmployeeWellbeing #DreamBig&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Heartfelt Thanks to Our Community of Builders</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9496/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9496/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to announce that Twilio has been named one of Fast Company&amp;rsquo;s 2025 Best Workplaces for Innovators! 🎉 This recognition highlights our commitment to fostering a creative culture and empowering innovation within our community of builders. Thank you to everyone who contributes to this vibrant environment! 🙌 #Twilio #Innovation #BestWorkplaces #Community #Gratitude</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine data: The next frontier in AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9441/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9441/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At #SplunkConf25, Cisco and Splunk introduced new innovations to harness the potential of machine-generated data. 🔍 Machine data is crucial for AI, yet it remains underutilized due to challenges like data silos and the complexity of integration. 💡 Cisco aims to address these obstacles, providing the infrastructure needed for AI success. #AI #DataInnovation #Splunk #Cisco #MachineData</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash takes part in the 2025 Disability:IN Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9452/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9452/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This summer, DoorDash participated in the Disability:IN Conference for the first time, joining advocates and leaders focused on disability inclusion in the workplace. Our Able@ DoorDash group led the effort, with speakers Kinzie Keller and Lyndsey Leask sharing valuable insights on neurodiversity and creating accessible environments. We are committed to building inclusive products and practices, and this event provided us with new ideas to enhance our accessibility journey. Learn more about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Transform, Amazon Neptune, and more (September 8, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9440/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9440/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting updates in the AWS community! AWS Community Day 2025 is set for September 24 in Utrecht, bringing together over 500 cloud practitioners. The event will feature 25 breakout sessions focused on serverless architectures and container optimization. 📈 Recent AWS announcements include enhancements to AWS Transform, which now analyzes detached storage infrastructure for migration cost comparisons. Additionally, Amazon Bedrock introduces Global Cross-Region inference for Claude Sonnet 4,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Unscripted: Your Front-Row Seat for Honest Talk Between CIOs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9425/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover Tech Unscripted, a new video series featuring candid conversations with IT leaders tackling today&amp;rsquo;s challenges. Gain insights on managing ISP outages, securing remote work, and addressing AI demands. Each episode offers actionable tips for strategists, engineers, and security professionals. Tune in for valuable lessons straight from the experts. 📈💡 #TechUnscripted #CIOInsights #ITLeadership #Cybersecurity #DigitalTransformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan-Made PREDATOR Cinematic: IT ALL ENDS | Unreal Engine 5.6 | MetaHuman</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9537/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9537/</guid>
      <description>🎬 Exciting news for fans of the Predator franchise! A talented group has released a fan-made cinematic titled &amp;ldquo;PREDATOR: IT ALL ENDS,&amp;rdquo; crafted entirely using Unreal Engine 5.6. This project showcases impressive visuals and storytelling. The creators shared insights about the production process, revealing they completed a total of 108 shots. Check it out and immerse yourself in this indie creation! #Predator #FanFilm #UnrealEngine #Cinematic #IndieFilm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launching the 2nd Edition of the Cisco Cybersecurity Academy in Portugal</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9426/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9426/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for cybersecurity enthusiasts in Portugal! Cisco is launching the 2nd Edition of the Cybersecurity Academy, expanding on the success of the first edition. This six-month program aims to equip high-potential talent with hands-on training and industry-recognized certifications. Yves Mertens emphasizes that this initiative strengthens relationships among Cisco, customers, and partners, addressing the growing cybersecurity skills gap. Special thanks to the project team and Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Register for the Global Webinar: How to Prepare for NVIDIA Generative AI Certification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-07-8227/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-07-8227/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Join the global webinar on October 7 to learn how to prepare for the NVIDIA Generative AI Certification exams. Get insights into the new professional level certification and tips for success. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to enhance your skills! #NVIDIA #GenerativeAI #Webinar #Certification #ProfessionalDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7762/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 08:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7762/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited for September&amp;rsquo;s Java Annotated Monthly! This edition features updates on Java 25, set to release on September 16, 2025. Key enhancements include Compact Source Files, Flexible Constructor Bodies, and Scoped Values for better thread management. Additionally, IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2 supports these updates, including new debugging tools. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on the upcoming events and insights from Marit van Dijk! #Java25 #IntelliJIDEA #TechNews #SoftwareDevelopment #JavaCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7894/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 08:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7894/</guid>
      <description>🚀 September brings exciting updates in the latest Java Annotated Monthly! This edition features the much-anticipated Java 25 release on September 16, 2025, highlighting new features like Compact Source Files and improvements in performance. Marit van Dijk shares insights on these updates and the support in IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2. Don’t miss this month’s tech news and upcoming events! #Java25 #IntelliJ #TechNews #Kotlin #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading design through disruption: A conversation with Sara Vienna, Chief Design Officer at Metalab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7793/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7793/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited to share insights from my conversation with Sara Vienna, Chief Design Officer at Metalab! Sara reflects on her journey from a cold email to leading a top design firm. She emphasizes flexibility and continuous improvement in a rapidly evolving tech landscape. AI is reshaping design, prompting a redefinition of craft that focuses on user needs over time spent. Client expectations have also shifted, with heightened pressure on businesses to adapt. #DesignLeadership #AIinDesign&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover How Heroku’s AI PaaS Delivers Real-World Results at Dreamforce</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7743/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7743/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Heroku has transformed at Dreamforce into an AI PaaS, designed to enhance the shift from experimentation to production. Key highlights include new features like AppLink, Managed Inference, and Agents, all aimed at speeding up the delivery of AI-powered applications. Discover how companies like Workday and AT&amp;amp;T; are achieving significant results with Heroku’s solutions. Explore more at Dreamforce! #Heroku #Dreamforce #AI #TechInnovation #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains JavaScript Day 2025 Registration Is Now Open</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7727/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7727/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for JavaScript enthusiasts! Registration is now open for the fifth edition of JetBrains JavaScript Day, a free online event set for October 2 at 9:00 am EDT / 3:00 pm CEST. Join us for insightful talks from industry leaders, covering topics from modern JavaScript tooling to open source project management. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on this opportunity to learn and engage! 📅 Register now and be part of the conversation! #JavaScriptDay #JetBrains #JavaScript #TechEvent #WebDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Week 2025: Recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7680/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7680/</guid>
      <description>🌐 AI Week 2025 has concluded, focusing on how to harness AI&amp;rsquo;s power while maintaining control. Key announcements included new products and partnerships aimed at enhancing AI security and usability. 🔒 The event emphasized four main areas: securing AI environments, protecting original content, supporting developers, and improving Cloudflare with AI features. Stay tuned for updates on our Blog, AI Avenue, and CloudflareTV! 📅 #AIWeek2025 #Cloudflare #AISecurity #TechInnovation #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conference Hopping: Training Attendee Scanning Def Con</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7665/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7665/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The Black Hat NOC faces unique challenges, as it operates in a cybersecurity hub where scanning and ethical hacking are expected. Cisco is enhancing security with network-based telemetry to monitor diverse personal devices at the conference. An alert recently identified suspicious activity linked to a training session targeting an external IP associated with Def Con. #Cybersecurity #BlackHat2025 #Cisco #ThreatDetection #EthicalHacking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving Cisco XDR Integration With Third-Party Partners at Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7666/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7666/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is the Official Security Cloud provider at Black Hat USA 2025, showcasing its latest advancements in XDR integration. These integrations enhance the Security Operations Center&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, allowing analysts to quickly investigate Indicators of Compromise (IOC) with a single search. Special thanks to alphaMountain.ai and Pulsedive for their contributions to the event. #Cisco #CyberSecurity #BlackHat2025 #XDR #MalwareAnalysis 🚀🔍💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Secure Firewall: SnortML at Black Hat USA 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7667/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7667/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is the Security Cloud Provider for Black Hat USA 2025! Attendees can participate in hands-on training sessions, using cloud resources for real-time attack simulations. The Cisco team ensures stable connectivity and monitors traffic to protect against unauthorized attacks. SnortML, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s machine learning tool, demonstrated high accuracy, detecting over 100 attacks with only 21 false positives. Stay informed about cybersecurity innovations! 🔒💻 #Cisco #BlackHat2025 #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat Training Attendees Scan Aviation Organization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7670/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7670/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Black Hat conference highlights the unique challenges of cybersecurity, particularly within its Security and Network Operations Center (NOC). Attendees engage in ethical hacking, leading to expected scanning and exploitation activities. This dynamic environment differs from typical corporate settings where such actions are seen as malicious. With a Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) policy, comprehensive monitoring becomes challenging. The focus shifts to robust network-based telemetry for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat USA 2025: 10 Years Protecting Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7671/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7671/</guid>
      <description>Cisco celebrates a decade as the Official Security Cloud Provider for Black Hat USA! 🎉 Partnering with companies like Arista, Corelight, Lumen, and Palo Alto Networks, Cisco helps build and secure the Black Hat network. The NOC focuses on continuous network stability, delivering seamless security and visibility through an embedded SOC. 🔒🌐 #BlackHat2025 #CyberSecurity #Cisco #NetworkOperations #TechPartnerships</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refining SSO at Black Hat USA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7672/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7672/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Black Hat USA 2025! Cisco Duo has enhanced its role as the multifactor authentication (MFA) and single sign-on (SSO) provider for the Network Operations Center (NOC). The successful deployment of Duo Directory has expanded user access, supporting over 100 users at the event. This upgrade improves identity and access management for both users and admins. Key features include streamlined password management and a new Global Enrollment Policy to simplify onboarding. 🔐&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing DNS With Umbrella at Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7673/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7673/</guid>
      <description>Cisco continues to enhance security at Black Hat, focusing on DNS monitoring since 2017. 🌐 With Umbrella, they route DNS traffic through a centralized service, gaining insights into potential threats like malware and phishing. At Black Hat USA 2025, encrypted DNS requests were blocked to improve visibility into user traffic. 🔍 The team prioritized monitoring the ApateWeb PUP delivery and phishing campaign, noting specific domain patterns. #Cisco #BlackHat2025 #CyberSecurity #DNS #Umbrella</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebuilding homes and a resilient community in Western North Carolina</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7627/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7627/</guid>
      <description>In Western North Carolina, Cisco Crisis Response and 40 Communities are aiding in the recovery from Hurricane Helene. 🌪️ After the storm caused severe damage, affecting over 73,000 homes, a coalition was formed to support local leaders and nonprofits in the rebuilding efforts. 🏠 Nearly a year later, the focus remains on restoring homes, especially for low-income families, while ensuring vital services are accessible. 🤝 #CommunitySupport #HurricaneHelene #RebuildingTogether #CrisisResponse&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Velocity Reimagined Wins Triple Industry Recognition!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7611/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7611/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco’s Marketing Velocity Reimagined has achieved a remarkable feat by winning three industry awards in 2025! 🏆 The program received the 2025 Killer Content Award for Channel Partner Marketing, recognizing its innovative digital co-marketing experience that empowers partners with learning and customizable campaigns. 📈 It also earned the 2025 Sammy Award for Sales and Marketing, celebrating the team&amp;rsquo;s efforts to enhance connections with partners and drive growth through data-driven&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello Developer: September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7651/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7651/</guid>
      <description>Get ready for an exciting design update! 🎨 Whether you&amp;rsquo;re an experienced developer or just starting out, discover resources to enhance your apps and games. Explore videos, downloads, and documentation. Additionally, you can sign up for one-on-one sessions focusing on machine learning and AI. Plus, meet the team behind the popular game, Hello Kitty Island Adventure! 🌟 #HelloDeveloper #AppDevelopment #GameDesign #MachineLearning #HelloKittyAdventure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Our Newest Innovators: Welcoming AI4SE Interns as JetBrains Employees!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7592/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7592/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting times at JetBrains as we welcome our new AI4SE interns! These recent graduates from TU Delft have transitioned from academic projects to full-time roles, applying their MSc thesis work in real-world settings. Meet Milan, Nadine, Saga, and Sergey, who gained hands-on experience during their internships and contributed to significant research. Their work will soon lead to journal publications! 📚 The AI4SE program, launched in 2023, combines academic research with industry&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon EC2, Amazon Q Developer, IPv6 updates, and more (September 1, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7588/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7588/</guid>
      <description>📅 This week, the AWS Heroes Summit in Seattle highlighted the contributions of the AWS Heroes community. These exceptional individuals share their expertise through content creation, speaking, and open-source projects. 🤝 The summit provided a platform for networking and collaboration, with discussions on AWS roadmaps and direct feedback opportunities to AWS service teams. 🚀 Notable launches included IPv6 support for AWS App Runner, AWS Client VPN, and RDS Data API, enhancing connectivity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICPC World Finals Livestream: ecnerwala and SecondThread Speed-Solving Kotlin Challenge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7550/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7550/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Join us live from the ICPC World Finals in Baku, Azerbaijan, on September 2, 2025, at 9:30 am UTC! Watch top programmers Andrew ‘ecnerwala’ He and David ‘SecondThread’ Harmeyer compete in a real-time Kotlin speed-solving challenge. Hosted by Sebastian Aigner from JetBrains, this event showcases coding mastery under time pressure. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the chance to see Kotlin&amp;rsquo;s strengths and get inspired to join the upcoming Kotlin Heroes contest! #ICPC #KotlinHeroes #CompetitiveProgramming #LiveEvent&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack Week 2025: How these engineers liquid-cooled a GPU server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7290/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7290/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Hack Week 2025 at Dropbox focused on the theme “Keep It Simple,” encouraging innovation and collaboration. One highlight was the &amp;ldquo;Liquid Cooling CPU/GPU Hardware&amp;rdquo; project, which won the Learn Fast award. The team developed a custom liquid cooling system for GPU servers to address the thermal demands of AI workloads. This system demonstrated significant benefits, including lower operating temperatures and quieter performance. Future plans include expanding testing across multiple data&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready for the Best School Year Ever? Join Our STEM Clubs, Camps, and Competitions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7211/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 07:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7211/</guid>
      <description>🎉 A new school year is here, bringing fresh opportunities in STEM! Join our free online Youth Clubs to enhance your skills in math, coding, and AI. Weekly sessions with expert instructors and a global community await you. 🔍 Explore the Math Club, AI Club, and Coding Club for tailored learning experiences. 🌐 Engage in competitions and prepare for olympiads with peers worldwide! #STEMEducation #YouthClubs #Math #Coding #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awe dropping.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7257/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7257/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Mark your calendars! Join us for a special Apple Event on September 9 at 10 a.m. PT. Tune in to watch live on apple.com, Apple TV, or YouTube Live. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on the latest announcements! #AppleEvent #TechNews #LiveStream 📅🍏📺</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living My Childhood Dream — Thanks to Cisco’s Time2Give Benefit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7199/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7199/</guid>
      <description>Rana K., a Technical Consulting Engineer at Cisco, shares her inspiring journey of fulfilling a childhood dream through the company&amp;rsquo;s Time2Give benefit. 🌍✨ This initiative allows employees to dedicate 80 hours annually to volunteer for causes they care about. Rana, originally from Egypt and now living in Poland, has embraced this opportunity to teach and give back globally. She reflects on the connections she&amp;rsquo;s made, highlighting that cultural differences have not hindered her ability to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare Launching AI Miniseries for Developers (and Everyone Else They Know)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6346/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6346/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloudflare has launched &amp;ldquo;AI Avenue,&amp;rdquo; a miniseries designed to demystify AI for developers and the general public. Each episode explores AI&amp;rsquo;s growth, capabilities, and human augmentation stories, making the technology approachable and engaging. Viewers can interact with AI hands-on, breaking down fears and showcasing its potential. Join the journey to learn more at aiavenue.show! #AI #Cloudflare #Innovation #Technology #HumanAugmentation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch the premiere of the award-winning animated short NEW IDEA here!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6338/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6338/</guid>
      <description>🎥 Discover &amp;ldquo;NEW IDEA,&amp;rdquo; the award-winning animated short that has captured 26 accolades! This film showcases the inspiring journey of its creator, who faced challenges before finding success. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the chance to watch this imaginative piece and appreciate its unique story! #NewIdea #Animation #FilmAwards #ShortFilm #Inspiration ✨</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin on the Backend – What’s New From KotlinConf 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6303/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6303/</guid>
      <description>KotlinConf 2025 showcased significant advancements in server-side Kotlin. 🌐 Key highlights include a strategic partnership with Spring for enhanced null-safety and Kotlin-centric tutorials. 📚 Developers are increasingly adopting Kotlin for backend, with notable insights shared by leaders from major tech companies. Ktor continues to evolve, offering support for modern scalable applications, including new features for dependency injection and server-driven UI development. For in-depth insights,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do any CISOs feel lucky?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6317/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6317/</guid>
      <description>Cybersecurity events like the RSA Conference and &amp;ldquo;Hacker Summer Camp&amp;rdquo; in Vegas are crucial for industry leaders. This year, CISOs expressed heightened concerns over nation-state threats and the impact of AI on security. Key discussions included resilience and anti-fragility in cybersecurity, with panels addressing AI’s role in enterprise threats. Informal settings also allowed for deeper conversations among CISOs about the practical use of AI and data protection challenges. #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The power of ten — and the power of Purpose</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5283/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5283/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco empowers employees through the Time2Give program, offering ten days off to volunteer and $10,000 in matching donations. In FY25, 81% of employees participated, contributing over 566,000 volunteer hours. This initiative not only supports communities but also enhances employee retention and recognition. Learn more about our impact and future goals for FY26! 🌍🤝 #Cisco #CorporateResponsibility #Volunteerism #CommunityImpact #EmployeeEngagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supabase Launch Week 15 Hackathon Winner Announcement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5292/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5292/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Supabase Launch Week 15 has concluded, and we are excited to announce the winners of our Hackathon! The event showcased remarkable innovation from participants, demonstrating their technical skills. The standout project, &amp;ldquo;Figma AI Tickets&amp;rdquo; by vickywane, is a plugin that converts design tasks into actionable user stories using OpenAI’s GPT-4. Congratulations to all participants for their impressive submissions! 👏 #Supabase #Hackathon #Innovation #Figma #GPT4</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackathon: Winners Announced!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-6361/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-6361/</guid>
      <description>🚆 The winners of the first Railway User Hackathon have been announced! This event showcased innovative projects aimed at improving railway user experiences. Several projects received honorable mentions for their creativity and potential impact. Congratulations to all participants for their hard work and dedication! 🎉 #Hackathon #RailwayInnovation #UserExperience #Winners #TechForGood</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
