<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CircleCI-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/circleci-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CircleCI-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/circleci-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automated RAG pipeline evaluation and benchmarking with RAGAS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10477/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10477/</guid>
      <description>Explore the latest tutorial on automating RAG pipeline evaluation with RAGAS! 🚀 The article outlines key steps, including setting up the evaluation dataset, orchestrating your pipeline, and automating performance checks with CircleCI. With RAGAS, you can measure crucial aspects like faithfulness and context relevance, ensuring reliable RAG applications. Learn how to maintain quality as your system evolves! 🔧📈 #RAG #Automation #DataScience #MachineLearning #CircleCI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 ways AI agents are transforming software delivery</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10384/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10384/</guid>
      <description>AI agents are changing the software delivery landscape by addressing common bottlenecks that slow down teams. 1. &lt;strong&gt;Test Failure Triage&lt;/strong&gt;: Agents analyze logs to identify errors quickly. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Flaky Test Detection&lt;/strong&gt;: They track inconsistent tests, improving reliability. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Dependency Management&lt;/strong&gt;: Agents monitor updates, ensuring security and stability. 4. &lt;strong&gt;Incident Support&lt;/strong&gt;: They automate context gathering during production issues. 5. &lt;strong&gt;Auto-Generated Tests&lt;/strong&gt;: Agents help fill testing gaps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code coverage standards for a Next.js project using CircleCI and Coveralls</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10339/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10339/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how to implement code coverage standards in your Next.js project! This tutorial guides you through the essentials, including prerequisites, setting up Jest, and integrating Coveralls for code coverage reporting. Learn how to automate testing with CircleCI and simulate coverage failures for better code quality. #NextJS #CircleCI #Coveralls #CodeCoverage #SoftwareTesting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-powered email automation with CI/CD pipelines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10340/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10340/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into AI-powered email automation! This tutorial guides you through setting up a system that sends automated emails using Next.js, Nodemailer, and MongoDB. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn to connect OpenAI for generating content and use CircleCI for seamless deployment. Key steps include: - Project setup - Email service integration - CI/CD automation Get ready to streamline your communication! 📧💻 #EmailAutomation #AI #TechTutorial #CircleCI #NextJS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a multimodal RAG application with Gemma 3 and CircleCI on GKE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10341/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10341/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into the world of multimodal RAG applications with our latest tutorial! This guide walks you through the entire process, from setting up your development environment to deploying your application on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) using CircleCI. Key topics include: - Understanding the architecture - Installing Ollama - Creating a user-friendly UI with Streamlit By the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll build a scalable application that processes both text and images from PDFs. 📄✨ #TechTutorial #RAG #GKE&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an automated ETL pipeline for cryptocurrency data with CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10177/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10177/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Want to stay updated on cryptocurrency trends? This tutorial guides you through building an automated ETL pipeline using CircleCI and the CoinGecko API. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn to set up your project, configure workflows, and push your code to GitHub. Key steps include: - Prerequisites like GitHub and AWS accounts - Project structure overview - Creating ETL code and automation Get started and simplify your crypto data processing! 🌐📊 #Crypto #ETL #CircleCI #DataPipeline #CoinGecko</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audit log streaming for real-time security visibility in your CI/CD pipeline</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10116/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10116/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Security and compliance teams often face challenges in detecting suspicious activities in their CI/CD pipelines. Delays in incident response and gaps in visibility can leave organizations vulnerable. The article discusses automated audit log streaming as a solution. This method provides real-time access to audit events, enabling immediate threat detection and faster incident response. By integrating audit logs into security tools, teams can ensure continuous compliance and streamline their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a versatile query agent with RAG, LlamaIndex, and Google Gemini</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10178/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10178/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Looking to enhance your application with smart data retrieval? This tutorial guides you in building a versatile query routing agent. It helps direct questions to the right data sources, whether from a SQL database or document repository. Users can easily ask about U.S. states and receive accurate answers in a user-friendly Streamlit chat interface. #DataRetrieval #QueryAgent #Streamlit #AppDevelopment #TechTutorial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Chunk™: The agent that validates code at AI speed</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9948/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9948/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Chunk™: an autonomous agent designed to validate code at AI speed. As AI transforms software development, teams face new complexities that challenge traditional CI/CD methods. Chunk addresses this by providing smarter validation, allowing developers to focus on critical tasks while it handles time-consuming processes. With 24/7 optimization, Chunk fixes issues proactively, ensuring healthier code and streamlined workflows. #SoftwareDevelopment #AI #DevOps #Automation #CI_CD</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The real reason your AI initiatives are failing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9839/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9839/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming code generation, but it&amp;rsquo;s not solving the real challenges in software delivery. 🚀 Many organizations find that while AI speeds up coding, it leads to bottlenecks in getting that code into production. 📉 Studies show enterprise AI implementations often fail to yield significant returns, with delivery throughput stagnating in 2024. The focus on faster coding overlooks critical issues in integration and review processes. As AI-generated code floods systems, teams face delays&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build and deploy a Pinecone question answering RAG application</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7643/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7643/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to build a Pinecone question-answering RAG application? This tutorial walks you through the key steps: 1. Set up your Python environment and create necessary accounts (Pinecone, CircleCI, Heroku, OpenAI). 2. Create a Pinecone index for data management. 3. Define ingestion and query scripts, and set up environment variables. 4. Implement unit tests and define the Flask server. 5. Automate deployment with CircleCI. Learn how to enhance language model responses using Pinecone&amp;rsquo;s vector&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating GDPR compliance for web applications with CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7644/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7644/</guid>
      <description>🌐 This tutorial guides developers on automating GDPR compliance for web applications using CircleCI. It covers prerequisites, setting up a CI/CD pipeline, and integrating GitHub. Key topics include user consent, data security, and audit logging. By following this guide, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn to configure a CircleCI pipeline for GDPR tasks like privacy audits and compliance reporting. #GDPR #CircleCI #WebDevelopment #PrivacyCompliance #DataProtection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Streamlit app deployment with AWS Cognito, Streamlit, and CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7445/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7445/</guid>
      <description>🔒 This tutorial guides you on deploying a secure Streamlit app using AWS Cognito and CircleCI. It covers prerequisites, setting up AWS Cognito for user authentication, building the Streamlit application, and automating testing and deployment with CircleCI. By the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll be equipped to create a secure, scalable deployment pipeline for your applications. #AWS #Streamlit #CircleCI #WebDevelopment #Authentication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-downtime deployment with Flagsmith and CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5106/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5106/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn how to achieve zero-downtime deployment with Flagsmith and CircleCI! This tutorial covers the essentials, including setting up feature flags, project configuration, and automating deployments. Feature flags enable developers to control feature visibility without redeploying, minimizing risks associated with buggy releases. Get started with a GitHub, Flagsmith, CircleCI, and Vercel account to enhance your deployment process! #Deployment #FeatureFlags #CircleCI #Flagsmith&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
