<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CircleCI-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/circleci-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CircleCI-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/circleci-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Boost your test coverage with CircleCI Chunk AI agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-28-15038/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-28-15038/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Enhance your test coverage with CircleCI&amp;rsquo;s Chunk AI agent! This article outlines how to set up Chunk for automatic test coverage extension. It emphasizes the importance of maintaining quality in fast-paced AI development. Learn about reviewing results, using targeted prompts, and advanced configuration to improve your codebase. Explore how Chunk integrates into the AI development ecosystem and addresses common challenges in testing. #CircleCI #TestCoverage #AIDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fix bugs faster with CircleCI’s Chunk AI agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-28-15037/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-28-15037/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CircleCI introduces Chunk, an AI agent designed to streamline bug fixing in your CI/CD pipeline. Setting up Chunk is straightforward. Users need a CircleCI account and can connect their GitHub repository for access. Once set up, Chunk analyzes your project’s build history and failure patterns to identify and fix bugs automatically. The article also covers how to leverage targeted prompts and advanced configurations for optimal results. This tool enhances the AI development ecosystem by&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improve your documentation with the Chunk AI agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-28-15036/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-28-15036/</guid>
      <description>Improve your documentation with Chunk, CircleCI&amp;rsquo;s AI-powered agent! This article details how to set up Chunk, generate documentation, and review results. It emphasizes the need for accurate documentation, especially as AI-assisted coding evolves. Learn how Chunk analyzes your entire codebase for comprehensive documentation that keeps pace with your development. #Documentation #AIAssistance #DevOps #CircleCI 📄🤖✨</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimize your CI/CD pipeline with CircleCI Chunk AI agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-27-15040/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-27-15040/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Optimize your CI/CD pipeline with CircleCI&amp;rsquo;s Chunk AI agent! This tutorial guides you through: - Setting up Chunk - Asking Chunk for pipeline optimizations - Reviewing results - Advanced configurations Chunk analyzes your pipeline&amp;rsquo;s history to provide targeted optimizations, helping reduce build times and costs. For a seamless start, ensure you have a CircleCI account and follow the setup steps. #CICD #CircleCI #AI #DevOps #Optimization</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refactor your codebase with CircleCI Chunk AI agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-27-15039/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-27-15039/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Refactor your codebase efficiently with CircleCI&amp;rsquo;s Chunk AI agent! This article explores how to set up Chunk to enhance your CI/CD pipeline. Learn to ask Chunk for code refactoring, review results, and use targeted prompts for optimal outcomes. Discover advanced configurations and Chunk&amp;rsquo;s role in the AI development ecosystem. #CodeRefactoring #CircleCI #AIDevelopment #TechTools #ContinuousIntegration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Perk cut recovery time to 31 minutes with centralized rollbacks in CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-26-14889/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-26-14889/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Perk&amp;rsquo;s DevOps team has successfully reduced incident recovery time to just 31 minutes using CircleCI&amp;rsquo;s centralized rollback feature. By leveraging the Platform Team Toolkit, they&amp;rsquo;ve scaled these benefits across multiple services. This partnership is crucial for maintaining CI/CD pipelines for the Builders department. Perk utilizes a cloud-native architecture, ensuring scalability and reliability. Their modern services also embrace serverless solutions to enhance efficiency. Curious how this&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering waits and timeouts in Playwright</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-21-14790/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-21-14790/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Mastering waits and timeouts in Playwright is essential for reliable end-to-end testing. This tutorial covers prerequisites, understanding waits, built-in waits, best practices, and integrating CircleCI for seamless testing. Proper handling of waits can significantly reduce test flakiness, ensuring your CI/CD pipelines run smoothly. #Playwright #EndToEndTesting #CICD #SoftwareTesting #TestAutomation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign OCI containers &amp; other artifacts using Sigstore Cosign &amp; CircleCI OIDC tokens</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14116/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14116/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for CircleCI users! Sigstore’s Fulcio now recognizes CircleCI’s OIDC tokens, allowing you to sign container images and artifacts directly in your pipelines—no long-lived signing keys needed. This keyless signing approach simplifies the process, enhancing security while proving artifact provenance. Get started with our sample repository: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/CircleCI-Public/sign-and-publish-examples&#34;&gt;github.com/CircleCI-Public/sign-and-publish-examples&lt;/a&gt; #CircleCI #Sigstore&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ROI of autonomous validation: How to unlock $1.8M in engineering value</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13910/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 11:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13910/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking engineering value through autonomous validation is a game-changer for CI/CD processes. This innovative approach addresses the challenges of traditional pipelines by understanding code changes in context, leading to reduced delivery friction. An ROI calculator is introduced to measure the financial impact of these shifts. Key areas of improvement include shorter feedback cycles, better recovery insights, and enhanced review processes. For teams, this means significant time and budget&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get 97% faster feedback with Smarter Testing by CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13176/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13176/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Fast feedback is essential for efficient software delivery. Long build and test cycles disrupt developers, causing significant productivity loss. CircleCI addresses this with Smarter Testing, reducing feedback time by up to 97%. This innovative approach runs only the necessary tests based on code changes, enhancing efficiency without compromising quality. Stay productive with faster validation! 🔧💻 #SoftwareDevelopment #CircleCI #SmarterTesting #Productivity #DevOps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a multi-agent AI system using CrewAI, Gemini, and CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12875/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12875/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into the world of multi-agent AI systems with our latest tutorial! This guide walks you through the essentials: from prerequisites and project setup to building a system that gathers and summarizes trending news articles. You&amp;rsquo;ll utilize CrewAI for coordination, Google Gemini for intelligent processing, and CircleCI for automating tests. By the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a collaborative AI system ready for deployment! #AI #MachineLearning #SoftwareDevelopment #CrewAI #CircleCI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate CircleCI with Railway for automated deployments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11385/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11385/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how to integrate CircleCI with Railway for automated deployments! This tutorial guides you through the prerequisites, setting up a Node.js app, and configuring CircleCI for seamless deployments. Learn about the benefits of using CircleCI with Railway, including reduced manual errors and streamlined workflows. Get started now! 🌐💻 #CircleCI #Railway #DevOps #Automation #NodeJS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Validate CDC data in your CI/CD pipeline using CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11386/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11386/</guid>
      <description>Learn how to validate CDC data in your CI/CD pipeline using CircleCI! 🚀 This tutorial covers essential steps including setting up the CDC pipeline, running baseline validations, and verifying changes in your data lake. Automated validation is crucial to avoid issues like missing records and corrupted data. By following this guide, you&amp;rsquo;ll build a reliable framework to ensure data integrity with every code change. #DataValidation #CircleCI #CDCPipeline #DataIntegrity #DevOps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fix flaky tests in your sleep with Chunk by CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11240/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11240/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Tired of flaky tests slowing down your CI process? CircleCI introduces Chunk, an autonomous validation agent that analyzes test failures and identifies their root causes. It opens PRs with verified fixes automatically, allowing you to focus on coding or take a break. 💤 The setup is straightforward: enable Chunk, verify the GitHub App, select your AI provider, and enter your API key. Say goodbye to tedious debugging and hello to a more reliable pipeline! #CircleCI #FlakyTests #Automation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DORA is right: AI is an amplifier, for better or worse</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11172/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11172/</guid>
      <description>📊 The 2025 DORA report reveals that AI amplifies existing organizational strengths and weaknesses. It emphasizes that the best returns on AI investment come from improving internal processes, clarity of workflows, and team alignment. 🚀 With 90% of organizations now using AI in software development, the focus should be on enhancing delivery systems to manage the increased code production effectively. 🔎 Despite initial boosts in productivity, many teams face challenges in deployment frequency&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set up a live code editor in Next.js with CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11173/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11173/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn how to set up a live code editor in Next.js with CircleCI! This tutorial guides you through prerequisites, project setup, and embedding the editor. It emphasizes the importance of maintaining code quality through CI/CD practices using CircleCI. Key highlights include: - Project setup using create-next-app - Ensuring code quality with linting - Automating deployments with CircleCI #NextJS #CircleCI #CodeEditor #DevTools #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is autonomous validation? The future of CI/CD in the AI era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11046/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11046/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving landscape of software development, &lt;strong&gt;autonomous validation&lt;/strong&gt; is emerging as a key solution for CI/CD challenges. 🌐 This approach continuously assesses and improves the delivery process by utilizing intelligent automation, contextual learning, and agentic capabilities. It aims to streamline the development cycle, addressing inefficiencies created by rapid AI advancements. ⚙️ Key features include: - &lt;strong&gt;Contextual awareness&lt;/strong&gt; for data-driven decisions - &lt;strong&gt;Autonomous fixes&lt;/strong&gt; to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building LLM agents to validate LangGraph tool use and structured API responses</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10971/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10971/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how to build reliable LLM agents with rigorous testing! This tutorial guides you through setting up a Python project and the importance of validating tool use and structured API responses. Key points include automating regression tests with CircleCI and ensuring accurate tool invocation and output parsing for production-grade reliability. #LLMAgents #CircleCI #Python #API #TechTutorial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementing image recognition with React and continuous deployment</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10918/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10918/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into the world of AI with React! This tutorial guides you through building an image recognition app using TensorFlow.js. You will learn to set up your project, configure Jest for testing, and integrate CircleCI for CI/CD. By the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a reliable app that processes user-uploaded images! #ReactJS #AI #ImageRecognition #CircleCI #WebDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The new AI-driven SDLC</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10636/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10636/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The software development life cycle (SDLC) has evolved over the years, traditionally guiding teams through phases like planning, design, and testing. 🤖 With the introduction of AI, the landscape is changing. AI tools now actively participate in software delivery, enabling simultaneous activities and enhancing feedback flows. This shift is reshaping how teams work and adapt to a faster pace of development. Explore the implications of AI on the SDLC and how teams can evolve their practices&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Expo app build delivery to QA with CircleCI and EAS webhooks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10612/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10612/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Automate your Expo app build delivery with this tutorial! It explores the setup of an Expo project, AWS S3, and Slack integration. By utilizing CircleCI and a webhook server, developers can streamline the process of sharing builds with QA teams. No more manual uploads or miscommunication! This guide covers all prerequisites and steps for effective automation. #Expo #CircleCI #Automation #DevOps #QA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building and deploying a Python MCP server with FastMCP and CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10516/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10516/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Building a Python MCP Server is now easier than ever! This tutorial guides you through setting up your development environment, creating an MCP server with FastMCP, and automating package publishing to PyPI using CircleCI. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn to build a document parsing server that enhances LLMs by extracting text from various formats. Get ready to extend your AI capabilities! 📦📄 #Python #MCP #FastMCP #AI #CircleCI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automated RAG pipeline evaluation and benchmarking with RAGAS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10477/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10477/</guid>
      <description>Explore the latest tutorial on automating RAG pipeline evaluation with RAGAS! 🚀 The article outlines key steps, including setting up the evaluation dataset, orchestrating your pipeline, and automating performance checks with CircleCI. With RAGAS, you can measure crucial aspects like faithfulness and context relevance, ensuring reliable RAG applications. Learn how to maintain quality as your system evolves! 🔧📈 #RAG #Automation #DataScience #MachineLearning #CircleCI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 ways AI agents are transforming software delivery</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10384/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10384/</guid>
      <description>AI agents are changing the software delivery landscape by addressing common bottlenecks that slow down teams. 1. &lt;strong&gt;Test Failure Triage&lt;/strong&gt;: Agents analyze logs to identify errors quickly. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Flaky Test Detection&lt;/strong&gt;: They track inconsistent tests, improving reliability. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Dependency Management&lt;/strong&gt;: Agents monitor updates, ensuring security and stability. 4. &lt;strong&gt;Incident Support&lt;/strong&gt;: They automate context gathering during production issues. 5. &lt;strong&gt;Auto-Generated Tests&lt;/strong&gt;: Agents help fill testing gaps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Code coverage standards for a Next.js project using CircleCI and Coveralls</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10339/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10339/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how to implement code coverage standards in your Next.js project! This tutorial guides you through the essentials, including prerequisites, setting up Jest, and integrating Coveralls for code coverage reporting. Learn how to automate testing with CircleCI and simulate coverage failures for better code quality. #NextJS #CircleCI #Coveralls #CodeCoverage #SoftwareTesting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-powered email automation with CI/CD pipelines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10340/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10340/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into AI-powered email automation! This tutorial guides you through setting up a system that sends automated emails using Next.js, Nodemailer, and MongoDB. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn to connect OpenAI for generating content and use CircleCI for seamless deployment. Key steps include: - Project setup - Email service integration - CI/CD automation Get ready to streamline your communication! 📧💻 #EmailAutomation #AI #TechTutorial #CircleCI #NextJS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a multimodal RAG application with Gemma 3 and CircleCI on GKE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10341/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10341/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into the world of multimodal RAG applications with our latest tutorial! This guide walks you through the entire process, from setting up your development environment to deploying your application on Google Kubernetes Engine (GKE) using CircleCI. Key topics include: - Understanding the architecture - Installing Ollama - Creating a user-friendly UI with Streamlit By the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll build a scalable application that processes both text and images from PDFs. 📄✨ #TechTutorial #RAG #GKE&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an automated ETL pipeline for cryptocurrency data with CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10177/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10177/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Want to stay updated on cryptocurrency trends? This tutorial guides you through building an automated ETL pipeline using CircleCI and the CoinGecko API. You&amp;rsquo;ll learn to set up your project, configure workflows, and push your code to GitHub. Key steps include: - Prerequisites like GitHub and AWS accounts - Project structure overview - Creating ETL code and automation Get started and simplify your crypto data processing! 🌐📊 #Crypto #ETL #CircleCI #DataPipeline #CoinGecko</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audit log streaming for real-time security visibility in your CI/CD pipeline</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10116/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10116/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Security and compliance teams often face challenges in detecting suspicious activities in their CI/CD pipelines. Delays in incident response and gaps in visibility can leave organizations vulnerable. The article discusses automated audit log streaming as a solution. This method provides real-time access to audit events, enabling immediate threat detection and faster incident response. By integrating audit logs into security tools, teams can ensure continuous compliance and streamline their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a versatile query agent with RAG, LlamaIndex, and Google Gemini</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10178/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10178/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Looking to enhance your application with smart data retrieval? This tutorial guides you in building a versatile query routing agent. It helps direct questions to the right data sources, whether from a SQL database or document repository. Users can easily ask about U.S. states and receive accurate answers in a user-friendly Streamlit chat interface. #DataRetrieval #QueryAgent #Streamlit #AppDevelopment #TechTutorial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Chunk™: The agent that validates code at AI speed</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9948/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9948/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Chunk™: an autonomous agent designed to validate code at AI speed. As AI transforms software development, teams face new complexities that challenge traditional CI/CD methods. Chunk addresses this by providing smarter validation, allowing developers to focus on critical tasks while it handles time-consuming processes. With 24/7 optimization, Chunk fixes issues proactively, ensuring healthier code and streamlined workflows. #SoftwareDevelopment #AI #DevOps #Automation #CI_CD</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The real reason your AI initiatives are failing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9839/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9839/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming code generation, but it&amp;rsquo;s not solving the real challenges in software delivery. 🚀 Many organizations find that while AI speeds up coding, it leads to bottlenecks in getting that code into production. 📉 Studies show enterprise AI implementations often fail to yield significant returns, with delivery throughput stagnating in 2024. The focus on faster coding overlooks critical issues in integration and review processes. As AI-generated code floods systems, teams face delays&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build and deploy a Pinecone question answering RAG application</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7643/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7643/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to build a Pinecone question-answering RAG application? This tutorial walks you through the key steps: 1. Set up your Python environment and create necessary accounts (Pinecone, CircleCI, Heroku, OpenAI). 2. Create a Pinecone index for data management. 3. Define ingestion and query scripts, and set up environment variables. 4. Implement unit tests and define the Flask server. 5. Automate deployment with CircleCI. Learn how to enhance language model responses using Pinecone&amp;rsquo;s vector&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating GDPR compliance for web applications with CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7644/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7644/</guid>
      <description>🌐 This tutorial guides developers on automating GDPR compliance for web applications using CircleCI. It covers prerequisites, setting up a CI/CD pipeline, and integrating GitHub. Key topics include user consent, data security, and audit logging. By following this guide, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn to configure a CircleCI pipeline for GDPR tasks like privacy audits and compliance reporting. #GDPR #CircleCI #WebDevelopment #PrivacyCompliance #DataProtection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Streamlit app deployment with AWS Cognito, Streamlit, and CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7445/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7445/</guid>
      <description>🔒 This tutorial guides you on deploying a secure Streamlit app using AWS Cognito and CircleCI. It covers prerequisites, setting up AWS Cognito for user authentication, building the Streamlit application, and automating testing and deployment with CircleCI. By the end, you&amp;rsquo;ll be equipped to create a secure, scalable deployment pipeline for your applications. #AWS #Streamlit #CircleCI #WebDevelopment #Authentication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-downtime deployment with Flagsmith and CircleCI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5106/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5106/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn how to achieve zero-downtime deployment with Flagsmith and CircleCI! This tutorial covers the essentials, including setting up feature flags, project configuration, and automating deployments. Feature flags enable developers to control feature visibility without redeploying, minimizing risks associated with buggy releases. Get started with a GitHub, Flagsmith, CircleCI, and Vercel account to enhance your deployment process! #Deployment #FeatureFlags #CircleCI #Flagsmith&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
