<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Netflix-Technology-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/netflix-technology-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Netflix-Technology-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:53:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/netflix-technology-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Streams: Real-Time Recommendations for Live Events Part 3</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11092/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11092/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting insights from Netflix&amp;rsquo;s latest article on enhancing live event experiences! As live events attract millions of viewers, Netflix has engineered a system for real-time recommendations. This ensures fans receive timely updates without overwhelming cloud services. Key strategies include prefetching data and adaptive broadcasting, effectively synchronizing devices and managing traffic spikes. Stay tuned for more on Netflix&amp;rsquo;s innovative solutions! 🎥📡 #Netflix #LiveEvents #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How and Why Netflix Built a Real-Time Distributed Graph: Part 1 — Ingesting and Processing Data…</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11044/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:42:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11044/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Netflix has developed a Real-Time Distributed Graph (RDG) to analyze member interactions across various services effectively. In Part 1 of their blog series, they outline the motivation behind the RDG and its data processing architecture. The transition from a single streaming service to multi-faceted offerings like live events and games necessitated a new approach to data analysis. By leveraging a graph system, Netflix can connect user activities across devices rapidly, enhancing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100X Faster: How We Supercharged Netflix Maestro’s Workflow Engine</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10221/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:10:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10221/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting improvements to Netflix&amp;rsquo;s Maestro engine! The recent upgrade boosts performance by 100X, reducing workflow overhead from seconds to milliseconds. This redesign enhances scalability and meets evolving business needs, supporting more complex workflows. Explore the updated Maestro on GitHub and enhance your workflow orchestration today! 🌐 #Netflix #Maestro #DataEngineering #WorkflowOptimization #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Resilient Data Platform with Write-Ahead Log at Netflix</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10173/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:57:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10173/</guid>
      <description>📊 Netflix faces unique challenges in data management at scale, including data loss, corruption, and system entropy. To tackle these issues, they developed the Write-Ahead Log (WAL), a system that enhances data consistency and reliability. WAL ensures durable data changes and efficient message retries, crucial for Netflix’s real-time data pipelines. The simplified API allows teams to easily integrate different storage solutions while maintaining high performance. Learn more about how WAL is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Muse: How Netflix Powers Data-Driven Creative Insights at Trillion-Row Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9898/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 21:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9898/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At Netflix, our Muse application plays a vital role in delivering data-driven insights to enhance content discovery for members. Muse helps creative teams identify effective promotional media by analyzing audience engagement with various assets. As user demands evolved, we upgraded Muse&amp;rsquo;s architecture to support advanced features while ensuring high performance. We implemented techniques like HyperLogLog sketches for efficient data processing and utilized the Hollow library for faster&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Netflix Engineers with Incident Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9830/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9830/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Netflix is transforming its incident management approach to enhance reliability for users worldwide. The company has shifted from a centralized model to empowering engineering teams to manage incidents independently, promoting a culture of ownership and learning. This change involved selecting a user-friendly tool, Incident.io, to simplify the process and encourage participation. Key aspects include intuitive design, internal integrations, and a balance between customization and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Facts &amp; Metrics to Media Machine Learning: Evolving the Data Engineering Function at Netflix</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5177/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5177/</guid>
      <description>At Netflix, we are evolving our data engineering function with the introduction of Media ML Data Engineering. 🎥📊 This new specialization focuses on managing complex media data, allowing for centralized access to various media assets like video, audio, and text. The initiative aims to enhance machine learning capabilities and improve analytics through the Media Data Lake, which supports advanced technologies. Key responsibilities include standardizing media assets and enriching metadata to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ML Observability: Bringing Transparency to Payments and Beyond</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5178/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5178/</guid>
      <description>At Netflix, ML observability is crucial for monitoring and understanding machine learning models in production. It allows teams to track performance, detect anomalies, and ensure reliability. This is particularly important in payment processing, where optimizing transactions helps reduce friction for users. By utilizing ML observability tools, we can enhance model performance and maintain stakeholder trust through clear insights into model behavior. Examples include logging, monitoring, and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Video Quality Control at Netflix with Pixel Error Detection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4969/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4969/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Netflix has developed an automated method for video quality control that detects pixel-level artifacts, reducing manual reviews. This new system identifies hot pixels that can distract viewers, ensuring a seamless viewing experience. By using a specialized neural network, Netflix speeds up the QC process from hours to minutes. This innovation allows creative teams to focus more on storytelling rather than technical issues. 🎥✨ #Netflix #VideoQuality #Innovation #TechForGood #Filmmaking</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
