<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Netflix-Technology-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/sources/netflix-technology-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Netflix-Technology-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:39:40 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/sources/netflix-technology-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From Facts &amp; Metrics to Media Machine Learning: Evolving the Data Engineering Function at Netflix</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-5177/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-5177/</guid>
      <description>At Netflix, we are evolving our data engineering function with the introduction of Media ML Data Engineering. 🎥📊 This new specialization focuses on managing complex media data, allowing for centralized access to various media assets like video, audio, and text. The initiative aims to enhance machine learning capabilities and improve analytics through the Media Data Lake, which supports advanced technologies. Key responsibilities include standardizing media assets and enriching metadata to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ML Observability: Bringing Transparency to Payments and Beyond</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-5178/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-5178/</guid>
      <description>At Netflix, ML observability is crucial for monitoring and understanding machine learning models in production. It allows teams to track performance, detect anomalies, and ensure reliability. This is particularly important in payment processing, where optimizing transactions helps reduce friction for users. By utilizing ML observability tools, we can enhance model performance and maintain stakeholder trust through clear insights into model behavior. Examples include logging, monitoring, and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Video Quality Control at Netflix with Pixel Error Detection</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-4969/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 21:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-4969/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Netflix has developed an automated method for video quality control that detects pixel-level artifacts, reducing manual reviews. This new system identifies hot pixels that can distract viewers, ensuring a seamless viewing experience. By using a specialized neural network, Netflix speeds up the QC process from hours to minutes. This innovation allows creative teams to focus more on storytelling rather than technical issues. 🎥✨ #Netflix #VideoQuality #Innovation #TechForGood #Filmmaking</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
