<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Atlassian-Developer-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/atlassian-developer-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Atlassian-Developer-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:28:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/atlassian-developer-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Reimagining software delivery with AI-powered workflows in Jira &amp; Bitbucket</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12185/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 20:28:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12185/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in software delivery are here! The article discusses Rovo Dev, an AI agent that integrates with Jira and Bitbucket to enhance the software development lifecycle. It addresses common complexities developers face, such as managing vulnerabilities and tech debt. With Rovo Dev, routine tasks like code generation and pull requests become streamlined, allowing teams to focus on building quality software. The integration helps reduce friction and improves team efficiency&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 ways to prevent AI fatigue</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12177/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12177/</guid>
      <description>AI is revolutionizing our work, but it can also lead to AI fatigue. This occurs when we feel overwhelmed by the rapid changes and demands of using various AI tools. Instead of avoiding AI, we should focus on intentional collaboration with it. By questioning how we use AI, we can prevent it from dictating our priorities. Atlassian shares six dos and don’ts to reset our relationship with AI, helping us turn fatigue into creativity. For example, treat AI as a sparring partner rather than a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrades to Pipelines Artifacts: New Artifact Types &amp; Selective Download</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12152/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 20:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12152/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting enhancements to Bitbucket Pipelines artifacts are here! New artifact types include &lt;strong&gt;shared&lt;/strong&gt; (accessible across steps) and &lt;strong&gt;scoped&lt;/strong&gt; (specific to each step). This allows for better organization and management of your pipeline artifacts. Additionally, the &lt;strong&gt;selective download&lt;/strong&gt; feature lets you specify which artifacts to download, saving time and build minutes. Explore these new functionalities for improved workflow efficiency! #Bitbucket #Pipelines #DevOps #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An “unreasonable” era: Mike Cannon-Brookes on leading, creating, and staying ambitious in the age of AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12117/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12117/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In a recent interview on the 20VC podcast, Mike Cannon-Brookes shared insights on leading in the age of AI. He advocates for a mindset of “constructive unreasonableness,” challenging the status quo to simplify complex systems. 💡 He emphasizes the importance of psychological safety within teams, allowing for bold experimentation and quick pivots based on customer feedback. Atlassian focuses on integrating the best AI models to enhance customer value rather than creating their own. 🔍 This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building with Forge: Recap from the Atlassian Builders’ Summit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12118/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12118/</guid>
      <description>📅 Last month, around 150 Atlassian practitioners gathered at the Atlassian Builders’ Summit to explore Forge. The event featured presentations, hands-on workshops, and expert sessions aimed at empowering both admins and non-developers to build impactful apps and enhance security. Key sessions included a keynote by Matt Doar on the relevance of Forge, and practical workshops led by Liz Tanner and Darryl Lee, focusing on app development for non-developers. Tanya Botta concluded with insights on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reimagining how you structure workflows in Bitbucket Pipelines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12119/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 06:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12119/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in Bitbucket Pipelines! Managing CI/CD workflows is now streamlined with the introduction of &lt;strong&gt;triggers&lt;/strong&gt;. These allow teams to automate builds, tests, and deployments based on specific events and conditions. With the new &lt;strong&gt;top-level triggers property&lt;/strong&gt;, users can define event-driven rules that separate pipeline definitions from their executions. 🔍 You can now use logical expressions and glob patterns for precise control over conditions. Plus, all matching pipelines will&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why AI feels hard: We may need a new lens</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12120/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:40:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12120/</guid>
      <description>Developers are navigating challenges with AI as they often view it merely as an advanced autocomplete tool. 🤖 The real issue lies in the need for individual contributors (ICs) to adopt tech lead skills earlier in their careers. This shift requires them to think beyond just coding and focus on problem-solving and effective communication. 🔄 By understanding AI as a team member that requires clear direction, ICs can achieve better results and enhance their technical management skills. #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Rovo Dev Research: What Types of Code Review Comments Do Developers Most Frequently Resolve?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12121/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12121/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s Rovo Dev research highlights how LLM-powered code reviews can enhance software quality. Rovo Dev identifies 2.8× more bugs and 1.4× more maintainability issues than human reviewers. It focuses on actionable comments to improve readability, bugs, and maintainability, making the review process faster. The study categorizes review comments into four main types: readability, bugs, maintainability, and design, alongside general discussions. This research was presented at ASE 2025 and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>17 scripts for difficult conversations at work</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11951/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 20:47:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11951/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.atlassian.com/blog/rss&#34;&gt;Atlassian Developer Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.atlassian.com/blog/communication/scripts-for-difficult-conversations-at-work&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partner with Atlassian and unlock your next wave of growth</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11952/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11952/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.atlassian.com/blog/rss&#34;&gt;Atlassian Developer Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.atlassian.com/blog/enterprise/partner-with-atlassian-and-unlock-your-next-wave-of-growth&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laura Burkhauser on helping teams rewire for AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11821/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11821/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Laura Burkhauser shares insights on AI adoption from her experience leading the product team at Descript. She describes a tech acceptance scale that moves from hostile to rewired. 🔍 Teams often have mixed reactions to AI, from skepticism to full integration. Laura emphasizes the importance of guiding teams through these stages. 🌊 She advocates for focusing on excitement rather than fear in AI adoption. Finding your &amp;ldquo;beach moment&amp;rdquo; can inspire teams to embrace change. #AIAdoption&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating the Jira and Confluence applications to AWS Graviton</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11822/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 17:24:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11822/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Atlassian successfully migrated over 3,000 Jira and Confluence instances to AWS Graviton, enhancing performance and efficiency. The transition aimed to leverage both speed and cost-effectiveness, addressing challenges encountered during previous attempts. The move involved strategic planning to ensure minimal user impact while tackling complexities on a large scale. #AWSGraviton #Atlassian #CloudMigration #Jira #Confluence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extended Timelines for Marketplace Revenue Share Changes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11658/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11658/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Atlassian is extending the timeline for Marketplace revenue share rate increases to April 1, 2026. This change affects both Forge and Connect apps, allowing partners more time to adapt to evolving business models. The adjustments will support their transition from Data Center to cloud. Notably, Atlassian is also accelerating revenue share benefits, including a 100% revenue share discount for qualifying Forge apps starting January 1, 2026. This initiative aims to enhance partner support and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Live session] Agentic developer workflows powered by Rovo Dev</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11640/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:38:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11640/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join us for a webinar on November 13th, 2025, focused on agentic developer workflows using Jira, Bitbucket, and Rovo Dev. Discover how Rovo Dev—our AI agent—can enhance code generation, reviews, and overall production speed. The session will include demos, getting started tips, and a live Q&amp;amp;A with Atlassian experts. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to transform your workflows! 🔗 Sign up now! #Webinar #AI #DevTools #Atlassian #RovoDev</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Never heard of restorative conflict resolution? Catch up quick</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11557/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11557/</guid>
      <description>🛠️ Restorative conflict resolution is gaining popularity in schools and workplaces. It focuses on repairing relationships rather than imposing punishments after conflicts. 🗣️ This approach encourages open dialogue, allowing parties to understand each other’s perspectives and collaboratively find solutions. 🔍 It’s important to note that participation is voluntary, and accountability is emphasized through acknowledgment and responsibility for actions. #ConflictResolution #RestorativePractices&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Q1 FY26 letter to shareholders</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11549/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11549/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Atlassian reports a strong Q1 FY26 with total revenue reaching $1.4 billion, marking a 21% increase YoY. Cloud revenue surged to $998 million, a 26% rise YoY. AI adoption is growing rapidly, with over 3.5 million monthly active users. This is driving demand for our cloud services and strong migrations from Data Center to Cloud. We also announced the end of life for our Data Center offering, introducing ‘Atlassian Ascend’ to support customer upgrades. #Atlassian #Q1FY26 #CloudComputing #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian named a Leader in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Collaborative Work Management Platforms</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11539/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:02:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11539/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Atlassian has been named a Leader in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant for Collaborative Work Management Platforms. For nearly two decades, Atlassian has focused on enhancing teamwork across various sectors. Their Teamwork Collection, which includes Jira, Confluence, Loom, and Rovo, unifies work processes and improves collaboration. The report details how modern work management solutions can boost agility and productivity. Check it out to learn more! 📊 #Atlassian&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage your Pipelines usage with the new billing panel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11525/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11525/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates to the Pipelines Billing Panel! Users can now view pipeline minute usage by repository, not just the total for the workspace. This enhancement allows for better management of high-usage repositories across current and previous billing periods. To access, navigate to the Pipelines usage tab in workspace settings. Note: This feature is available only for monthly plan customers. #Atlassian #Pipelines #BillingPanel #WorkspaceManagement #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start Your Engines: Codegeist 2025 Hackathon Is Here</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11511/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11511/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Codegeist 2025 is now open! This annual hackathon invites developers to create apps that enhance teamwork and collaboration, inspired by the precision of racing crews. Participants can use Forge to build solutions for Jira and Confluence. With over $120,000 in prizes available, including $15,000 for grand prize winners, there’s plenty to gain. The submission window runs from October 27 to December 22. Join the community and showcase your talent! 💻🏆 #Codegeist2025 #Atlassian #Hackathon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make your Atlassian account safer (and easier to use!) with two-step verification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11512/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11512/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Have you noticed an increase in email one-time passcodes (OTPs) when logging into your Atlassian account? This is part of Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s enhanced security measures to protect your account. Two-step verification (2SV) offers a more efficient way to secure your login. With 2SV, you’ll use your password along with a second factor, like your phone, making it significantly harder for unauthorized access. 📱 Setting up 2SV takes just a few minutes and reduces the need for email codes, allowing for a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rovo for Everyone, Everywhere with CEO Mike Cannon-Brookes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11387/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11387/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Atlassian is enhancing teamwork with the latest Rovo innovations, as shared by CEO Mike Cannon-Brookes. Rovo is designed to empower teams everywhere by providing tailored support and insights. Catch Mike&amp;rsquo;s vision for the future of collaboration in the exclusive video from Team Europe 2025. Explore the new features and the future of AI at Atlassian! #Atlassian #AI #Teamwork #Rovo #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From tradition to transformation: how Ford continuously evolves as an enterprise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11388/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 21:35:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11388/</guid>
      <description>Ford Motor Company is evolving by harnessing the power of Atlassian Cloud Enterprise. 🌐 With a legacy of over 120 years, Ford is embracing data-driven insights and automation to enhance its operations. They are transforming their culture by fostering connected teams and actionable analytics. 🏭 Brandon Devito, Transformations Director, emphasizes the importance of continuous improvement and innovation in today’s technology-driven environment. 💡 Learn more about Ford&amp;rsquo;s journey from tradition to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoiding the broadcast trap: A simple ritual for effective adoption</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11351/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:57:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11351/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Effective AI adoption goes beyond just informing teams. Design company BUCK emphasizes the importance of hands-on experimentation over traditional training methods. Their findings reveal that active practice leads to better outcomes than passive learning. Creating “practice blocks” can foster this experimentation, allowing teams to test new workflows in low-stakes environments. Let’s rethink our approach to adopting new tools! #AIAdoption #TeamWork #Experimentation #Productivity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking workflow flexibility with variable-sharing between parent and child pipelines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11326/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 22:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11326/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Bitbucket Pipelines has introduced enhancements for the Parent/Child Pipelines feature! Users can now share variables from parent steps to child pipelines, improving workflow flexibility. This allows for efficient variable management within your YAML file. However, be cautious: this feature is not for sharing sensitive information due to security risks. For more details, check out the article! #Bitbucket #Pipelines #DevOps #Workflow #Atlassian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building on top of Rovo Dev Serve mode: Rovo Dev in the IDE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11317/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11317/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Explore the integration of Rovo Dev with IDEs! Rovo Dev is Atlassian’s AI coding agent designed to enhance your development workflow, achieving a 41.98% resolve rate on SWE-bench. Key features include code understanding, AI-assisted development, and robust security. The IDE integration allows developers to stay in their workflow, access context easily, and view changes seamlessly. Currently supported in Visual Studio Code and its forks. Learn more about Rovo Dev and how to get started!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Table Enhancer’s Evolution: Elevating User Experience from Data Center to Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11292/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11292/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in Confluence! The article discusses the evolution of the Table Enhancer plugin, designed to improve user experience from Data Center to Cloud. Key features include sorting, total lines, and sticky rows/columns. As Atlassian shifted to Cloud, the plugin faced challenges, leading to a temporary solution that impacted user experience. An automation assistant has been developed to simplify migration for existing users, streamlining the process. With new bodied macro&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 skills teams need to thrive in the age of AI (and how to build them)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11223/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:26:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11223/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming our work landscape rapidly. By 2030, it’s expected that only a third of tasks will be completed by humans. To adapt, teams need to develop key skills. 🔑 Here are the top 5 skills to invest in: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Critical Thinking&lt;/strong&gt;: Analyze and verify AI outputs to reduce risks. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Creativity&lt;/strong&gt;: Generate new ideas and connect concepts. These skills can help future-proof your work. 💡 For practical tips on building these competencies, check out the full article. #FutureOfWork #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ramping Up US Government Missions with Atlassian’s FedRAMP® Moderate Authorized Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11133/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 22:06:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11133/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of your agency with Atlassian Government Cloud! 🚀 With FedRAMP Moderate authorization achieved, agencies can enhance collaboration and protect data effectively. Atlassian tools are already trusted by all US cabinet agencies, proving their commitment to modernizing public sector services. Gain valuable insights and streamline workflows with advanced analytics, helping you make informed decisions. Explore how Atlassian can support your mission today! 💻🔍 #Atlassian #GovCloud&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The consulting industry’s human-powered renaissance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11014/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:57:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11014/</guid>
      <description>The consulting industry is undergoing significant changes due to AI integration. Traditional pyramid structures are being replaced by an &amp;ldquo;obelisk&amp;rdquo; model, emphasizing fewer layers and more efficient teamwork. Key roles now include AI facilitators, engagement architects, and client leaders, focusing on human skills like judgment and relationship-building. Firms are encouraged to adapt hiring practices for future-ready talent. Investing in hybrid training and encouraging collaboration around AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing social enterprise discounts: Atlassian tools for social impact teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10907/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10907/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian has announced new discounts aimed at social enterprises, expanding its support beyond nonprofits. 🌍 Eligible teams can access Atlassian tools at 50-75% off, along with free support programs. These offerings aim to enhance teamwork and efficiency in achieving positive social impacts. Social enterprises can also benefit from consultancy grants and a dedicated community forum to connect with peers. Learn more about how Atlassian is empowering social impact teams! 💪✨ #SocialImpact&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great managers meet uncertainty with curiosity and confidence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10908/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10908/</guid>
      <description>Great managers embrace uncertainty with curiosity and confidence, according to Mark C. Crowley. In his book, &lt;em&gt;The Power of Employee Well-Being&lt;/em&gt;, he emphasizes that focusing on team emotions boosts productivity. Crowley notes that 70% of employee feelings relate to their managers. By navigating uncertain situations with curiosity, leaders can reduce stress for their teams. Curiosity is a key leadership skill; asking questions and seeking diverse perspectives leads to better decision-making and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Databricks Query Runner: Transforming data into insight</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10537/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10537/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Introducing the Databricks Query Runner, now integrated with Atlassian Rovo. This new tool allows teams to access AI-powered insights directly within their workflow. By asking questions in natural language, users can receive immediate data-driven answers without needing SQL knowledge. Key features include: - Instant insights from your data - Seamless integration within your existing tools - Empowering all team members to uncover valuable information - Strong security measures&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team ’25 Europe: AI that’s changing the game for teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10527/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10527/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Exciting developments at Team ‘25 Europe in Barcelona! AI is reshaping teamwork, with Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s Rovo leading the way. Over three million users benefit from its features, enhancing productivity and collaboration across organizations. Rovo integrates seamlessly with existing systems, transforming workflows and delivering quick answers to users. The rollout continues, with a mobile app on the horizon. Stay tuned for more updates! 🚀 #Team25Europe #AI #Atlassian #Rovo #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Rovo everywhere: AI that connects every app, every team, every workflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10518/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10518/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Meet Rovo, the AI that connects every app, team, and workflow! Over the past year, Rovo has evolved with new AI-powered skills designed to enhance your workday. It integrates seamlessly into your organization, overcoming data silos and fragmentation. Key features include: - &lt;strong&gt;Enterprise Search&lt;/strong&gt;: Quickly find answers across all apps. - &lt;strong&gt;Chat&lt;/strong&gt;: AI chat powered by your company’s knowledge. - &lt;strong&gt;Studio&lt;/strong&gt;: Build automations and apps using natural language. - &lt;strong&gt;Agents&lt;/strong&gt;: Automate tasks and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Atlassian Software Collection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10519/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10519/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Atlassian! They&amp;rsquo;ve launched the &lt;strong&gt;Atlassian Software Collection&lt;/strong&gt;, an AI-Native solution designed to enhance productivity and satisfaction for developers. Over three years, developer satisfaction soared from 49% to 83%, with a notable 89% increase in pull requests. This collection includes tools like &lt;strong&gt;Rovo Dev&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Bitbucket&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Compass&lt;/strong&gt;, aimed at streamlining the software development lifecycle (SDLC) and ensuring effective AI integration. Developers can now&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Move Faster and Work Smarter with Atlassian’s AI-Powered Teamwork Collection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10520/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10520/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s Teamwork Collection is transforming collaboration! Since its launch, teams are leveraging Jira, Confluence, Loom, and Rovo to enhance productivity. This collection serves as a core collaboration stack, providing a unified language for teams. Key updates include: - &lt;strong&gt;Create with Rovo&lt;/strong&gt;: Turn notes into drafts quickly. - &lt;strong&gt;New Rovo skills in Jira&lt;/strong&gt;: Streamline project management. - &lt;strong&gt;Loom features&lt;/strong&gt;: Share knowledge easily with a new desktop app. Discover how these tools can help&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Atlassian Service Collection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10521/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Atlassian Service Collection! This new solution aims to modernize service management for all teams. It combines Jira Service Management, Customer Service Management, and Assets for a streamlined experience. Service Collection enhances internal and external support, making it faster and more intuitive with AI integration. Say goodbye to siloed teams and clunky tools! #Atlassian #ServiceManagement #AI #Teamwork #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategy Collection Delivers New Ways to Connect Priorities to Work, Goals, People, and Investments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10522/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 06:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10522/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s Strategy Collection! The collection now includes Rovo for AI-driven insights, Funds to track investments, and Strategic Events for efficient planning. These tools empower leaders to connect company priorities to work, goals, and people effectively. Organizations like Accenture and Lloyds Banking Group report improved strategic alignment and significant time savings. Explore how these innovations can transform your approach to strategy! #Atlassian&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Atlas Camp: Amsterdam Call for Speakers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10508/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 17:16:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10508/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The call for speakers is now open for Atlas Camp 2026 in Amsterdam. This flagship Atlassian conference focuses on sharing real stories about platform extensibility, software delivery, and AI-powered solutions. Join a global community and inspire others! Submit your proposal at events.atlassian.com/atlascamp-cfs. #AtlasCamp #Developers #Atlassian #TechCommunity #CallForSpeakers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runs on Atlassian Apps Can Now Take Home 100% of Marketplace Revenue</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10434/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 03:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10434/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Atlassian has announced that partners with Runs on Atlassian apps can now retain 100% of their Marketplace revenue until they reach $1 million in lifetime Forge revenue. This incentive is effective immediately for qualifying apps, allowing for greater financial growth. For apps launched after this announcement, they can also qualify for this revenue share benefit. This initiative aims to support partners in delivering secure solutions and fostering innovation&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the new ‘Get the most out of Forge’ learning path</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10419/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 16:05:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10419/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Atlassian has launched the &lt;strong&gt;Get the most out of Forge&lt;/strong&gt; learning path, a free curriculum aimed at helping users master Forge, their cloud app development platform. This structured program includes step-by-step modules, hands-on labs, and quizzes to track progress. It&amp;rsquo;s perfect for new developers and those looking to enhance their skills. Get started today on Atlassian Learning! #Atlassian #Forge #AppDevelopment #LearningPath #Developers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From embedded to everywhere: The new era of apps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10401/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 23:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10401/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian is evolving the way we view its offerings. The term &amp;ldquo;products&amp;rdquo; like Jira and Confluence is changing to &amp;ldquo;Atlassian apps,&amp;rdquo; reflecting a new approach. These apps run on the Atlassian platform, which provides a robust infrastructure for all. This shift allows users to assemble a unique system of work, combining Atlassian-built apps, Marketplace apps, and custom solutions seamlessly. Developers can now create apps that connect across the platform, enhancing integration and user&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Jenkins might cost you 10x more than Bitbucket Pipelines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10348/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:48:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10348/</guid>
      <description>Running your own CI/CD with Jenkins can lead to significant costs. Many teams overlook the true expenses associated with under-provisioning resources or hiring a platform-engineering team. While Jenkins may seem cheaper, the total cost of ownership can be up to 10x higher than using services like Bitbucket Pipelines. CI/CD workloads vary throughout the day, creating challenges in scaling efficiently. Consider the implications of your CI/CD choice carefully. 💻⚙️ #CICD #DevOps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less noise, more signal: Atlassian’s responsible AI journey continues</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10335/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:28:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10335/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian is committed to responsible AI, ensuring that its tools align with customer needs and community values. They&amp;rsquo;ve launched updated resources, including the No BS Guide to Responsible AI Governance and a streamlined Responsible Technology Review Template. These tools aim to help teams implement responsible AI practices effectively. This update reflects months of feedback and collaboration, focusing on key AI use cases and partnerships. Discover how your team can benefit from these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevMate: Accelerating React Native Development at Atlassian</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10328/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:18:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10328/</guid>
      <description>At Atlassian, we understand that a seamless developer experience is crucial for productivity and team satisfaction. Our Mobile Platform team faced challenges during the migration of the Confluence Mobile app to React Native, including lengthy build times and complex environment setups. To address these issues, we developed DevMate, an in-house CLI tool that streamlines environment setup and significantly reduces build times. With DevMate, developers can set up their environments in minutes,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Open beta] Introducing Packages: native container registry in Bitbucket Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10305/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 23:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10305/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Bitbucket Packages is now in open beta for Standard and Premium workspaces! This feature offers a built-in container registry, allowing teams to manage artifacts seamlessly within Bitbucket Cloud. It supports container images and carries over user permissions for security. 🔍 The beta is free for now, but will transition to a paid model in December 2025. Monitor your usage to avoid unexpected costs later. Get ready for a unified code and artifact management experience! #Bitbucket #DevOps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Nonprofit AI Collaboration Index 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10287/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:38:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10287/</guid>
      <description>AI is increasingly becoming essential for nonprofit professionals. According to Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s 2025 Nonprofit AI Collaboration Index, while 99% believe in AI&amp;rsquo;s workplace potential, only 31% view it as a strategic partner. Those who do report a 29% boost in productivity. The report highlights the importance of advancing AI collaboration to enhance work quality and creativity. 📊🤖✨ #Nonprofits #AI #Productivity #Collaboration #WorkplaceInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Good people management begins with self-understanding</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10270/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:41:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10270/</guid>
      <description>Understanding yourself is key to effective people management. 🧠 Margaret Andrews emphasizes that strong managers must reflect on their own values, emotions, and influences. Her book, &amp;ldquo;Manage Yourself to Lead Others,&amp;rdquo; provides tools for self-assessment at any career stage. Start your journey with six key questions to enhance self-awareness. Check out the worksheet to begin! 📊 #Leadership #SelfUnderstanding #ManagerTips #PersonalGrowth #WorkLife</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s your AI collaboration style? Take the quiz to find out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10236/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 21:33:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10236/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Discover your AI collaboration style with a quick quiz! Find out if you&amp;rsquo;re an AI Trailblazer, Champion, Personal Productivity Pro, Tinkerer, or Wallflower. Each result includes actionable, research-backed tips to enhance your work with AI. Despite increased AI usage, many teams struggle to achieve desired outcomes. This quiz aims to help you and your colleagues work smarter together. Take the quiz and share your results! #AI #Collaboration #WorkSmarter #Atlassian #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From pledges to practice: Atlassian’s commitments to the EU AI Pact and responsible AI governance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10160/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10160/</guid>
      <description>In September 2024, Atlassian participated in the launch of the EU AI Pact in Brussels, joining over 100 leaders in committing to responsible AI practices. 🤝 Our report, &amp;ldquo;From Pledges to Practice,&amp;rdquo; details our five key commitments aimed at ensuring compliance with the EU AI Act. These include strategies for AI governance, addressing high-risk use cases, team education, transparency, and user recognition of AI. 📊 We also updated our resources on responsible AI governance to reflect our&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian named a Leader in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for DevOps Platforms for the 3rd Year</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10111/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10111/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian has been recognized as a Leader in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for DevOps Platforms for the third consecutive year. 🏆 This year, Atlassian is proud to be rated highest in Ability to Execute and Completeness of Vision. Their focus is on AI-assisted DevOps, enhancing productivity and team collaboration. Key tools like Rovo are transforming the software development lifecycle, streamlining workflows, and reducing silos. With the Teamwork Graph, teams gain shared context, making&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>95 AI prompts for better teamwork</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10099/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:09:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10099/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of AI for teamwork! 🤝 Discover how collaboration enhances productivity and outcomes. The article highlights the need for AI to be integrated into team dynamics rather than just individual tasks. It shares insights from Atlassian on using AI tools to foster coordination and unity among team members. The right prompts can guide AI to support your team effectively. Explore 95 AI prompts designed to boost teamwork and achieve success together! 🚀 #Teamwork #AI #Collaboration&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Rovo Chat in Bitbucket: your AI-powered teammate</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9950/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 15:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9950/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Meet Rovo Chat in Bitbucket! Rovo Chat integrates AI insights directly into Bitbucket, enhancing code reviews and onboarding processes. It connects with Jira, Confluence, and over 50 other apps, ensuring you stay within your workflow. This beta release aims to reduce the time developers spend searching for information, allowing for more focus on coding. Check for Rovo Chat in your Bitbucket account and share your feedback! #Bitbucket #AI #RovoChat #DeveloperExperience #Atlassian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to minimize the impact of manager changes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9829/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:55:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9829/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Manager changes can be challenging, but how they are handled makes a difference. Research shows that frequent changes can impact employee retention, especially with external hires. However, the focus should be on effective transition strategies rather than just frequency. Atlassian’s People Insights team found that clear communication and empathy can ease disruptions. Managers can take proactive steps to support their teams during these times. #Leadership #ManagerChange #TeamSupport&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advice for first-time managers, from leaders who’ve been there</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9835/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9835/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stepping into a management role? Here are 29 valuable tips from experienced leaders to ease your transition. Key points include: - Embrace humility; it&amp;rsquo;s okay not to have all the answers. - Learn from mistakes; perfection isn&amp;rsquo;t the goal. - Avoid being a hero; empower your team to solve problems. Setting boundaries and prioritizing self-care are also essential for effective leadership. 🌱 #FirstTimeManager #LeadershipTips #CareerGrowth #ManagementAdvice #SelfCare</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian &#43; DX: Engineering Intelligence for the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9775/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9775/</guid>
      <description>📣 Exciting news from Atlassian! They&amp;rsquo;ve announced the acquisition of DX, a leader in engineering intelligence, aimed at helping over 300,000 customers optimize their AI investments in software development. With DX, organizations can measure developer productivity, assess AI impact, and gain valuable insights into the software development lifecycle. This partnership promises to enhance collaboration between business and technology teams. Developers will experience smoother workflows, while&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking UX: how Opus Guard built AI-assisted Data Governance with Rovo and Forge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9594/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:38:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9594/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Opus Guard explores AI-assisted data governance in their latest article, focusing on the integration of Rovo and Forge. AI, especially large language models (LLMs), enhances content analysis, making it easier to manage vast amounts of information. This is vital for organizations needing efficient content management. The Content Retention Manager for Confluence helps users classify and retain necessary content while maintaining compliance. With Rovo, classification becomes faster and more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitbucket Packages is coming soon: one important step you need to take</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9563/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:48:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9563/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Bitbucket Packages is launching soon! This feature will centralize the publishing and management of artifacts, starting with Docker images. 🔗 To access it, link your Bitbucket workspace to your Atlassian organization. This step is crucial for a smooth transition to the new billing experience. 💡 Packages will enhance productivity by reducing context switching and streamlining permission management. Stay tuned for more details on availability and pricing! #Bitbucket #Atlassian&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI is changing the way leaders lead and companies create</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9559/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:27:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9559/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming leadership and company operations. 📈 Recent insights show that many CEOs are leveraging AI to enhance their productivity. A survey revealed that 61% of executives have integrated AI tools into their workflows to improve efficiency and communication. As AI takes on tasks like data analysis and strategy, leaders must focus more on big-picture thinking and innovation. 🤖 For effective implementation, start with one AI tool and run short-term tests to streamline processes&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking insights: Introducing Step Metrics for Bitbucket Pipelines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9541/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 01:11:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9541/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Bitbucket Pipelines users! Introducing &lt;strong&gt;Step Metrics&lt;/strong&gt;, a new feature designed to enhance your CI/CD workflow management. These metrics allow you to monitor CPU and memory usage for each build and service container. You can view detailed graphs and filter data to optimize performance. 🔍 Key features include: - Identification of bottlenecks - Optimized resource allocation - Data-driven troubleshooting Access metrics easily through the dedicated Metrics tab and customize&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitbucket Cloud enters phase two of app password deprecation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9505/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9505/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Bitbucket Cloud is moving to Phase 2 of app password deprecation! Starting September 9, 2025, new app passwords will no longer be created. Existing passwords will remain valid until June 9, 2026. New integrations must use API tokens for enhanced security and control. Admins should start migrating their teams now to avoid disruptions. 🔗 Learn more about this transition! #Bitbucket #APITokens #Security #DeveloperTools #Atlassian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the screens: Building Atlassian’s new icon system</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9495/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:57:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9495/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Atlassian is evolving its icon system to enhance user experience! After six years, the team recognized inconsistencies in size, style, and clarity across over 350 icons. This led to a redesign aimed at creating a cohesive, modern look that aligns with current UI standards. The new icons feature refined stroke widths and improved alignment, ensuring better visual harmony with the overall design. Stay tuned for more updates on this exciting transformation! #Atlassian #Design #UserExperience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ascend to the cloud: The next chapter for Atlassian and our customers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9454/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9454/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Atlassian is embracing a cloud-first future! With 99% of its 300,000+ customers already on the cloud, the company is sunsetting Data Center products over the next three years. This transition, part of the Atlassian Ascend initiative, aims to enhance teamwork and innovation. 🌟 Customers will gain access to AI tools, improved data connectivity, and robust analytics. Many organizations report faster results and reduced costs through the cloud. Atlassian is committed to supporting all customers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Data Center to Cloud: The Next Chapter for Marketplace Apps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9455/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9455/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian announces the end of life for Data Center products, shifting to a cloud-first approach over the next three years. This transition aims to enhance innovation and agility for customers. Marketplace apps will also gradually be phased out, with key dates set for app submissions and renewals. A new license option for Bitbucket Data Center apps will allow more flexibility during this change. Atlassian is committed to supporting customers and partners throughout this journey. #Atlassian&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcoming The Browser Company to Atlassian</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7733/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7733/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Atlassian! We are welcoming The Browser Company, creators of the Dia and Arc browsers, into the Atlassian family. This acquisition aims to develop a browser tailored for knowledge workers, enhancing productivity in the AI era. The new browser, Dia, will prioritize work-related tasks, integrating seamlessly with SaaS applications and leveraging AI for improved workflow. With an emphasis on security and usability, it aims to redefine how we work online. Looking forward to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Research: What Do Developers Think About Code Readability in the Age of LLMs?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7695/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7695/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s research explores the importance of code readability in the era of Large Language Models (LLMs) like RovoDev. Key findings show that 81% of developers still view code readability as essential, primarily for reducing maintenance costs. Despite LLMs writing more code, many practitioners are open to using these tools to enhance readability. The study emphasizes that readable code remains crucial for effective collaboration. #CodeReadability #LLMs #SoftwareDevelopment #Atlassian&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State of Product in 2026: Navigating Change, Challenge, and Opportunity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7659/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7659/</guid>
      <description>Product work is evolving, becoming more complex and crucial. A recent article reveals insights from product teams in the U.S., France, and Germany. Most professionals feel empowered, with 85% having a strategic role. However, they face pressure to deliver results, with 84% fearing product failure. Challenges include limited time for planning and data analysis, leading to uninformed decisions. Collaboration often suffers as 80% of teams don’t involve engineers early on. AI tools are used&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cycle is joining Atlassian</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7660/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7660/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Cycle is joining Atlassian to enhance Jira Product Discovery with AI-powered feedback capabilities. This integration will help product managers capture and process customer insights directly within Jira, streamlining decision-making and improving alignment across teams. Cycle will simplify feedback management by automatically gathering insights and highlighting key information, enabling more confident product development. Stay tuned for smarter features that elevate your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1 Billion Build Minutes Later: How we reinvented CI/CD at Atlassian</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7560/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 17:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7560/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In 2022, Atlassian recognized the need to streamline its CI/CD process due to fragmentation and inefficiencies. 🛠️ The solution? Consolidating efforts on Bitbucket Pipelines to support over 9,000 users, enhancing reliability and flexibility while maintaining team autonomy. Key focus areas included enterprise-grade scale, centralized standards, and preparing for AI advancements. Discover how Atlassian is transforming its development landscape! 🌐 #Atlassian #CICD #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Assessing your Enterprise Strategy and Planning maturity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7449/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:58:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7449/</guid>
      <description>Assessing your enterprise strategy and planning maturity is key for continuous improvement. 📈 Organizations must understand their position on the maturity spectrum to enhance alignment and execution. This can lead to better revenue generation, cost savings, and risk mitigation. Atlassian emphasizes the importance of setting and operationalizing strategy through six facets: Goals, Funds, Work, Systems, Talent, and Updates. Utilize this assessment as a benchmark and revisit it regularly. 🗓️&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From contextual understanding to execution: AI that truly works as part of your team</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7247/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7247/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in Rovo Chat enhance team collaboration! New features allow teams to tackle complex tasks with ease. Rovo can now autonomously break down requests and gather insights from various Atlassian tools. Additionally, Rovo&amp;rsquo;s improved memory understands your organization&amp;rsquo;s context, making interactions more efficient. Explore how Rovo Chat can work as a true team member today! #AI #Teamwork #RovoChat #Atlassian #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Coding Agent Experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7191/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7191/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian is enhancing the coding agent experience through machine learning. This aims to identify well-scoped Jira work items and provide relevant code context, leading to more efficient AI-powered development for software teams. Key indicators of effective task descriptions include detailed descriptions, presence of file paths, code snippets, and technical terms. These elements help coding agents understand and act on tasks more effectively. For implementation, Atlassian is considering both&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comment ranker – An ML-based classifier to improve LLM code review quality using Atlassian’s proprietary data</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7192/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:22:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7192/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian has introduced an ML-based comment ranker to enhance code review quality using proprietary data. This tool, part of the Rovo Dev agents, helps developers by filtering comments generated by LLMs, significantly improving efficiency. In its open beta, it has already supported over 43K PRs monthly and reduced PR cycle time by 30%. The comment ranker optimizes comment selection based on success metrics, ensuring only valuable feedback is highlighted for developers. #Atlassian #CodeReview&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian’s AI Gateway: Best in Class Model Garden</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6538/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6538/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Atlassian has launched its AI Gateway, a solution designed to streamline access to various LLMs from top providers like OpenAI and Google. This platform supports developers by offering a curated model garden with over 20 LLMs and integrates seamlessly with existing tools. It features a unified API for easy model switching and automated fallback options for reliability. All models maintain zero data retention, ensuring user privacy and security. #Atlassian #AI #MachineLearning #LLM&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Bitbucket from Jenkins: Enhancing Developer Experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-6539/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:53:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-6539/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s latest article discusses the advantages of transitioning from Jenkins to Bitbucket Cloud with Bitbucket Pipelines for CI/CD. The 2025 State of DevEx report reveals that 50% of developers lose over 10 hours weekly due to inefficiencies, and only 16% of their time is spent on coding. This highlights the need for better tools to enhance developer experience. The article also outlines the setup process for Jenkins, emphasizing the complexities involved. #DevExperience #Bitbucket&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How TitanApps Migrated Smart Checklist to Forge (and Got It to Run on Atlassian)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-6540/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 23:44:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-6540/</guid>
      <description>🚀 TitanApps shares the journey of migrating Smart Checklist to Forge, ensuring it meets security standards and runs smoothly on Atlassian. The team tackled challenges like data migration without downtime, all while retaining the app&amp;rsquo;s reliability for thousands of users. This migration highlights the importance of planning and adapting to new technologies. For those considering a similar move, this post offers valuable insights. #Atlassian #SmartChecklist #ForgeMigration #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI needs human partners to elevate its work – and keep it in check</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-6541/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-6541/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming industries, especially in pharmaceutical innovation. 🧬 Researchers at MIT are using generative AI to design new antibiotics, potentially speeding up drug development and addressing antibiotic resistance. However, AI tools in hiring reveal concerning biases. A recent study found that AI often suggests lower salaries for women and non-white candidates, highlighting the need for human oversight. Understanding these dynamics is crucial for effective human-AI collaboration. 🤖&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From insights to impact: Content design research at Atlassian</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-6542/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-6542/</guid>
      <description>At Atlassian, effective content design is rooted in research. This guide outlines a structured approach to planning and executing content design research. Start by defining your research goals with a concise plan that aligns your team. Key components include understanding user needs, research questions, and methods. Choose appropriate research methods to gather insights, combining qualitative and quantitative approaches for comprehensive results. Techniques like unmoderated surveys can&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
