<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Okta-Developer-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/okta-developer-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Okta-Developer-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/okta-developer-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the Secrets of a Custom Sign-In Page with Tailwind and JavaScript</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13016/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to enhance your app&amp;rsquo;s sign-in experience? This article discusses customizing the Okta-hosted sign-in page using Tailwind CSS and JavaScript. It highlights the advantages of redirecting users to the secure Okta Identity Engine for authentication. Key elements include: - Creating a responsive layout with Tailwind CSS. - Adding a footer for brand links. - Implementing a terms and conditions modal with Alpine.js. Explore your creativity and improve your user interface! 🎨 #Okta&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Authentication with a Push Notification in Your iOS Device</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12778/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12778/</guid>
      <description>Unlock secure sign-ins in your iOS apps with Okta&amp;rsquo;s DirectAuth and push notifications! 📱✨ This guide covers everything from setting up your Okta account to building a SwiftUI demo. Learn to implement native, phishing-resistant multi-factor authentication (MFA) without leaving your app. Key steps include: - Configuring Okta for DirectAuth - Enabling push notifications - Creating an AuthService - Displaying user information For developers ready to enhance app security, this tutorial is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stretch Your Imagination and Build a Delightful Sign-In Experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12084/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12084/</guid>
      <description>Transform your sign-in experience with Okta&amp;rsquo;s customizable Sign-In Widget (SIW)! 🎨 This JavaScript component allows you to tailor your login interface while ensuring top-notch identity security. With SIW, you can implement various authentication methods, including multi-factor authentication and social login, without complex backend management. In a recent tutorial, steps are provided to customize the SIW for a to-do app, including changing fonts, colors, and layout elements. Using design&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Okta MCP Server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9944/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9944/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI and identity management! The Okta MCP Server now bridges LLMs with backend systems, translating natural language into structured API calls. This integration allows for user management, group control, and report generation while maintaining security. Key features include: - Flexible authentication methods - Secure credential handling - Seamless integration with Okta APIs Get started with easy setup in VS Code and automate your workflows! #Okta #IdentityManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Secure Agent-to-App Connections with Cross App Access (XAA)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7711/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7711/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover Cross App Access (XAA), a protocol designed to enhance secure communication between applications in an enterprise environment. XAA enables centralized control for IT admins, allowing them to manage connections and enforce security policies across various applications. This is crucial as AI agents increasingly interact across systems. Learn how to set up secure agent-to-app connections, utilizing Okta and sample apps like Todo0 and Agent0. For detailed guidance, check out the full&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Secure iOS App with MFA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5101/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5101/</guid>
      <description>Secure your iOS app with multi-factor authentication (MFA) using Okta’s Swift SDK! 🔐✨ This guide walks you through: - Setting up your Okta developer account - Configuring your app for OAuth 2.0 and OpenID Connect - Customizing MFA policies - Creating a testable AuthService protocol Follow best practices to protect sensitive user data while enhancing your app&amp;rsquo;s login experience. #iOSDevelopment #Okta #MobileSecurity #MFA #SwiftUI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find the intersection of security, AI, IAM, and fun at Oktane</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4948/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4948/</guid>
      <description>Join us at Oktane 2025 in Las Vegas, NV, from September 24-26! 🎉 This year’s focus is on AI, security, and identity management. Explore the Oktane Developer Lounge for insights into creating secure applications and connecting with identity experts. 🤖 Don’t miss our hands-on labs, covering topics like OAuth and Terraform. Network with peers and enjoy engaging events! For more info, feel free to reach out. We look forward to seeing you! #Oktane2025 #AI #Security #IdentityManagement #Networking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Time to Evolve Authentication Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4146/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4146/</guid>
      <description>Identity-based attacks are on the rise, making strong authentication security necessary. Okta emphasizes the need to enhance identity security through initiatives like the Secure Identity Commitment. Key steps include adopting phishing-resistant methods, avoiding weak authentication, and implementing Multi-factor Authentication (MFA). Tailoring authentication requirements dynamically is crucial for balancing security and user experience. For developers, leveraging Identity Providers and using&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing CIBA for Secure Transaction Verification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4073/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4073/</guid>
      <description>🔐 &lt;strong&gt;Introducing CIBA for Secure Transaction Verification&lt;/strong&gt; 🔐 Digital applications require identity verification beyond just login interfaces. CIBA (Client-Initiated Backchannel Authentication) enhances security by decoupling authentication from applications, allowing users to verify their identity securely on different devices. This method is particularly useful in scenarios like updating bank email addresses or making payments at retail POS systems without sharing credentials on public&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
