<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stripe-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/stripe-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stripe-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/stripe-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>All our product updates from Stripe Tour New York</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10273/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10273/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Stripe Tour New York! We announced over 40 new products and features aimed at enhancing global commerce. Key highlights include new agentic commerce capabilities and a modular infrastructure for the crypto stack. Businesses can now easily collect subscription payments using stablecoins, aligning with our focus on AI and innovation. Stay updated with the latest from Stripe! #StripeTour #ProductUpdates #CryptoCommerce #Innovation #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Open Issuance from Bridge: A new platform to launch your own stablecoin</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10272/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10272/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Open Issuance from Bridge! This new platform empowers businesses to launch and manage their own stablecoins. By having their own stablecoin, companies can control their product experience, mint and burn freely, and earn rewards from reserves. Open Issuance connects businesses to a shared liquidity network, enabling quicker market entry and reduced costs. Businesses across various sectors can now take control of their stablecoin strategies! #Stablecoins #Blockchain #Fintech&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing an open standard for agentic commerce</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10219/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10219/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news in commerce! Stripe is now powering OpenAI’s Instant Checkout in ChatGPT. This feature allows users in the US to shop directly from Etsy and soon from over a million Shopify sellers. The Instant Checkout is driven by the Agentic Commerce Protocol (ACP), a new open standard co-developed by Stripe and OpenAI. This protocol enables smoother transactions between AI agents and businesses, ensuring secure purchases. Businesses can implement the ACP to make their checkouts agent-&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High-growth companies stand out with flexible pricing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10038/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10038/</guid>
      <description>High-growth companies are adapting their pricing strategies to thrive in a changing economic landscape. 🌍 A recent Stripe report reveals that 65% of business leaders are concerned their current pricing models may be outdated. The fastest-growing firms are leading the way by frequently updating their pricing models, incorporating usage-based fees, and exploring diverse pricing options. 📊 These strategies are crucial for maintaining growth in a rapidly evolving market. #PricingStrategy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we built it: Real-time analytics for Stripe Billing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9741/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9741/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A recent Stripe survey found that 84% of global business leaders believe quick pricing adaptation is crucial for competitive advantage. To support this need, Stripe has launched a real-time analytics system for Billing. This allows businesses to track subscription metrics like MRR growth and churn rates with minimal latency—up to 15 minutes. The upgrade replaces traditional batch processing, enhancing data visibility and accuracy for fast-moving trends. #RealTimeAnalytics #StripeBilling&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A framework for pricing AI products</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9560/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9560/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the monetization of AI products can be complex. A recent article outlines a framework that addresses key pricing strategies for businesses. With accelerating AI adoption, many companies are developing AI products. However, defining value and managing costs remains a challenge. Key considerations include understanding customer value, choosing effective charge metrics, and aligning pricing models with growth goals. The article emphasizes the importance of managing risks associated&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Tempo, the payments-first blockchain</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7751/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7751/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Tempo, a new Layer 1 blockchain focused on payments! Incubated by Stripe and Paradigm, Tempo is designed for scalable and low-cost stablecoin transactions. This initiative aims to enhance the efficiency of payments in the crypto space. Stay tuned for more updates on this innovative project! #Blockchain #Crypto #Stablecoins #Payments #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The conversion paradox: 3DS trends in regulated markets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7248/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7248/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover the latest insights on 3D Secure (3DS) trends in regulated markets! Our analysis reveals that despite high two-factor authentication rates, countries like France, the UK, and Japan still enjoy strong conversion rates. This challenges the belief that authentication negatively impacts sales. Interestingly, the quality of the authentication process plays a crucial role in driving these results. Explore how these findings can enhance your authentication strategy. #3DS #Ecommerce&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The top industries and business models using AI for fraud prevention</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4962/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4962/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A recent survey reveals that 47% of businesses globally are now using AI tools to detect and prevent fraud, making it the leading application of AI in payments. 📊 Adoption varies by industry, with insurance, SaaS, and travel companies leading the way. These sectors face unique risks and handle high-value transactions, making AI essential for their fraud prevention strategies. 🔍 Insurance firms utilize AI for identity verification, SaaS companies target fraudulent sign-ups, and travel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
