<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stripe-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/stripe-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stripe-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/stripe-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A framework for pricing AI products</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9560/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9560/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the monetization of AI products can be complex. A recent article outlines a framework that addresses key pricing strategies for businesses. With accelerating AI adoption, many companies are developing AI products. However, defining value and managing costs remains a challenge. Key considerations include understanding customer value, choosing effective charge metrics, and aligning pricing models with growth goals. The article emphasizes the importance of managing risks associated&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Tempo, the payments-first blockchain</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7751/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7751/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Tempo, a new Layer 1 blockchain focused on payments! Incubated by Stripe and Paradigm, Tempo is designed for scalable and low-cost stablecoin transactions. This initiative aims to enhance the efficiency of payments in the crypto space. Stay tuned for more updates on this innovative project! #Blockchain #Crypto #Stablecoins #Payments #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The conversion paradox: 3DS trends in regulated markets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7248/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7248/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover the latest insights on 3D Secure (3DS) trends in regulated markets! Our analysis reveals that despite high two-factor authentication rates, countries like France, the UK, and Japan still enjoy strong conversion rates. This challenges the belief that authentication negatively impacts sales. Interestingly, the quality of the authentication process plays a crucial role in driving these results. Explore how these findings can enhance your authentication strategy. #3DS #Ecommerce&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The top industries and business models using AI for fraud prevention</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4962/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4962/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A recent survey reveals that 47% of businesses globally are now using AI tools to detect and prevent fraud, making it the leading application of AI in payments. 📊 Adoption varies by industry, with insurance, SaaS, and travel companies leading the way. These sectors face unique risks and handle high-value transactions, making AI essential for their fraud prevention strategies. 🔍 Insurance firms utilize AI for identity verification, SaaS companies target fraudulent sign-ups, and travel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
