<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stack-Overflow-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/stack-overflow-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stack-Overflow-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:00:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/stack-overflow-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Secure coding in JavaScript</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10948/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10948/</guid>
      <description>🔒 JavaScript is essential for web development, but it also attracts attackers. This article highlights ten tips for writing secure JavaScript, focusing on preventing cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. XSS allows attackers to execute malicious code directly in users&amp;rsquo; browsers, which can compromise security. Key recommendations include input validation, output encoding, and using Content Security Policy (CSP) headers. Implementing these measures can significantly reduce the risk of XSS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI agents for your digital chores</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10883/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10883/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Discover the future of AI agents with Dhruv Batra, co-founder of Yutori. In a recent podcast, he discusses how proactive AI can transform digital tasks and interactions with advertisements. 💻 Yutori is focused on creating AI agents that manage everyday online chores, streamlining user experience. 🔍 Explore the challenges of integrating these proactive agents into our daily workflows. #ArtificialIntelligence #DigitalInnovation #AIagents #TechTalk #Yutori</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vite is like the United Nations of JavaScript</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10615/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10615/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vite is reshaping web development as a powerful frontend build tool. Evan You, the creator of Vite and Vue.js, discusses its evolution, unique features like plugins and hot module capabilities, and its future integration with Rust. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss Vite&amp;rsquo;s new documentary for deeper insights! 🎥 #WebDevelopment #Vite #OpenSource #JavaScript #TechTalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who watches the watchers? LLM on LLM evaluations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10594/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10594/</guid>
      <description>As generative AI gains traction, developers are focused on ensuring the reliability of AI applications. Trust in AI appears to be declining, prompting engineers to seek methods for building trustworthy systems. Human moderation is often impractical at scale, leading to the use of LLMs to evaluate other LLM outputs. This approach, while seemingly risky, has shown promise in scaling evaluations effectively. Research indicates that LLM judges can align with human assessments, although they come&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new look for comments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10546/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10546/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates on Stack Overflow! A new comments user interface is now available, allowing all registered users to comment on questions and answers. This change removes the previous 50 reputation requirement, enhancing community engagement. The updated UI features threaded comments and a voting system for better interaction and value recognition. Users can now follow discussions more easily, improving the overall experience. Learn more about the new commenting features in the Help Center!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context is king for secure, AI-generated code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10484/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10484/</guid>
      <description>In a recent discussion, Dimitri Stiliadis, CTO of Endor Labs, emphasized the evolving role of AppSec in the era of AI-generated code. Key points include the need for human oversight in managing vulnerabilities and the balance between security and efficiency when integrating AI into development practices. Endor Labs aims to help organizations identify critical risks in both human and AI-written code. 🔒🤖💻 #AppSec #AIGeneratedCode #Cybersecurity #SoftwareDevelopment #EndorLabs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond code generation: How AI is changing tech teams&#39; dynamics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10437/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10437/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming tech team dynamics by automating non-coding tasks, boosting productivity, and enabling agile workflows. Developers can now focus on complex challenges instead of repetitive tasks. Tools like coding assistants streamline processes, enhance collaboration, and improve documentation. This shift allows teams to deliver software faster and tackle strategic issues effectively. 📈🤖 #TechInnovation #AI #SoftwareDevelopment #AgileTeams #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One is not the loneliest number for API calls</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10426/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10426/</guid>
      <description>🎧 In the latest Stack Overflow Podcast, Gil Feig, co-founder and CTO at Merge, shares insights on simplifying third-party API integrations. Merge aims to reduce multiple API calls to a single connection, addressing the complexities of data normalization. The discussion also touches on the role of AI and MCP in enhancing API functionality. For more details, listen to the episode! #APIs #DataIntegration #TechTalk #Merge #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI-ready teams: Why documentation and culture matter more than tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10349/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10349/</guid>
      <description>In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, Peter O&amp;rsquo;Connor and Ryan J. Salva discuss key strategies for AI adoption in engineering teams. 💡 They emphasize the importance of high-quality documentation to avoid errors in AI systems. 📄 Consistent tools and processes are crucial as teams learn and adapt to AI technology. Leaders are encouraged to foster a culture that prioritizes learning and experimentation with AI tools, rather than just focusing on productivity metrics. #AI #Engineering&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning investments into impact: Stack Overflow for Teams 2025.7</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10256/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10256/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stack Overflow for Teams is evolving with the 2025.7 release! Key updates include a new Teams SDK, enabling developers to create tailored tools, integrate with existing systems, and manage knowledge effectively. Enhanced commenting features, like threaded replies and intuitive interfaces, improve collaboration. All updates go live on October 1, 2025. For more details, visit the release notes or connect with your Customer Success partner. Join us at Microsoft Ignite for future insights!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As your AI gets smarter, so must your API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10239/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10239/</guid>
      <description>In a recent podcast, Ryan Donovan speaks with Marco Palladino, CTO of Kong, about the growth of AI agents and their influence on API usage. 📈 Palladino highlights that the rise of AI has significantly increased API traffic, surpassing previous trends driven by mobile and cloud-native technologies. They also discuss the new MCP protocol, designed to enhance the interaction between AI agents and APIs, making it easier to access various tools and services. Observability and security in AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making your code base better will make your code coverage worse</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10205/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10205/</guid>
      <description>Maintaining an 80% code coverage can influence coding decisions, sometimes negatively. 📉 The article highlights that code coverage, often seen as a quality metric, may not accurately reflect software quality. Key points include: - Code coverage treats all files equally, which isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case. - The 80% minimum is arbitrary. - Improving code structure may lower coverage metrics. While useful, high coverage alone doesn’t guarantee code quality. #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment #Testing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Backstage in front of a shifting dev experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10159/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10159/</guid>
      <description>🎙️ In a recent Stack Overflow Podcast, Ryan Donovan interviews Pia Nilsson, GM for Backstage at Spotify. They discuss the evolution of Backstage, an open-source platform designed to enhance developer experience by reducing friction and operational challenges. Pia shares insights on how Spotify utilizes AI in development and the importance of platform engineering for meeting team needs. For those interested in software development, this episode sheds light on significant industry shifts&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The history and future of software development (part 1)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9982/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9982/</guid>
      <description>The evolution of software development is fascinating. Just 20 years ago, our tools were far less advanced. Today, we enjoy environments with AI support, syntax highlighting, and version control. However, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t always this way. In the 1960s, developers used punch cards to code. Each card held just 80 characters, leading to stacks of cards for larger programs. Debugging was a tedious process, often done on paper. This article explores the rich history and future of software development&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratizing your data access with AI agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9902/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9902/</guid>
      <description>🤖 Exciting insights from Jeff Hollan of Snowflake on the role of data in enhancing AI capabilities! He explains how Snowflake&amp;rsquo;s managed data platform supports AI app development. The newly launched data marketplace includes Stack Exchange data, broadening access for developers. Learn how data influences AI agents and empowers innovation. #DataAccess #AI #Snowflake #TechInnovation #DataMarketplace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off with your CMS’s head! Composability and security in headless CMS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9810/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9810/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In a recent episode, Ryan speaks with Sebastian Gierlinger from Storyblok about headless content management systems (CMS) and their role in a modular software environment. They explore the key differences between headless and traditional CMS, focusing on prototyping and security concerns. Learn how decoupling content from rendering can enhance development speed. 🌐 For more insights on CMS design, check out our previous discussions with Drupal and Builder.io! #HeadlessCMS #ContentManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stack Overflow is helping you learn to code with new resources</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9774/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9774/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stack Overflow is enhancing resources for students this school year! They&amp;rsquo;ve introduced an AI Assist tool for quick answers and a new Lobby chat room for beginners to connect. Additionally, the updated comments interface allows for better community engagement through organized conversations. Explore these tools to boost your coding skills! 💻🤝 #StackOverflow #LearnToCode #TechEducation #CodingCommunity #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What an MCP implementation looks like at a CRM company</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9673/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9673/</guid>
      <description>Ryan discusses Model Context Protocol (MCP) with Karen Ng, EVP of Product at HubSpot. They delve into its role as a standard for agentic interactions and the challenges faced in integrating MCP within HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s ecosystem. MCP, developed by Anthropic, aims to enhance connections between AI agents and external systems. 🔗💡🤖 #AI #CRM #HubSpot #MCP #Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning to Arm mobile devices with chips that handle AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9616/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9616/</guid>
      <description>Exciting discussion on the future of mobile devices with AI chips! 🤖 Ryan hosts Geraint North from Arm, focusing on how GenAI influences chip design. They explore Arm&amp;rsquo;s flexible CPU architectures and the challenges in optimizing language models for edge devices. Arm&amp;rsquo;s new Lumex CSS Platform aims to enhance AI workloads on mobile and desktop. #AI #ChipDesign #TechInnovation #EdgeComputing #Arm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI is reshaping developer teams and the future of software development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9542/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9542/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI is transforming the landscape of software development. In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, Peter O’Connor and Ryan J. Salva discuss how AI tools enhance developer experiences beyond just coding. They highlight how AI tackles deployment bottlenecks and streamlines team collaboration. Furthermore, AI is reshaping team structures, allowing small engineering teams to operate efficiently. Learn about the future of platform engineering, where AI will help standardize and manage&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI vs Gen Z: How AI has changed the career pathway for junior developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9517/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9517/</guid>
      <description>The article discusses how AI is reshaping career prospects for Gen Z software developers. Once seen as a secure path, the tech job market has become increasingly volatile, with a notable 25% drop in entry-level tech positions in 2024. Concerns about layoffs are high, with 64% of Gen Z fearing job loss, particularly in a post-pandemic economy. AI&amp;rsquo;s ability to automate roles has significantly impacted opportunities for junior developers. #GenZ #AI #CareerDevelopment #JobMarket #TechJobs 🤖💼📉</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We built stackoverflow.ai with the community and for the community</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9453/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9453/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news from Stack Overflow! The team has launched stackoverflow.ai, designed to improve your experience by merging human-validated answers with AI. This innovation aims to provide quick and accurate technical solutions, leveraging 16 years of community knowledge. Future plans include enhanced personalization and deeper community integration. 👏 Congratulations to Ketan Ramani for earning a Populist badge for their excellent answer on formatting in Android Studio! #StackOverflow #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin is more than just the Android house language</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7769/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7769/</guid>
      <description>💡 Kotlin is evolving beyond its role as the Android house language. In a recent discussion, Jeffrey van Gogh from Google highlighted its journey from JVM to multiplatform capabilities. The Kotlin Foundation aims to support and enhance the language&amp;rsquo;s development while collaborating with the community to minimize breaking changes. This year, over half of developers expressed interest in adopting Kotlin. #Kotlin #Programming #DeveloperCommunity #Multiplatform #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to school? Developers at Stack Overflow have some advice for you</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7622/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7622/</guid>
      <description>Heading back to school means new challenges in coding and projects. Developers from Stack Overflow share valuable advice for students. They emphasize the importance of asking for help and normalizing feelings of imposter syndrome. Curiosity is key; understand the &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; behind coding concepts instead of just copying answers. Collaborating with peers can enhance learning experiences. Stack Overflow is a great resource for support and community among budding developers. Remember, you&amp;rsquo;re not&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting started on Stack Overflow: a step-by-step guide for students</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7623/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7623/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Getting started on Stack Overflow? Here’s what you need to know! 1️⃣ Create an account at stackoverflow.com to ask questions, save answers, and engage with the community. 2️⃣ Explore the platform’s vast knowledge base with over 60 million questions and answers. 3️⃣ Utilize the new AI Assist tool for instant answers while also learning from real developer experiences. Stack Overflow is a valuable resource for students and coders alike! #StackOverflow #CodingCommunity #StudentResources&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing your newest study buddy: stackoverflow.ai</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7625/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7625/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing stackoverflow.ai, your new study buddy for coding! This AI tool offers instant answers and guides you through learning, making it easier for developers at any level to find solutions. It prioritizes community-verified knowledge, ensuring reliable information. Plus, you can connect with the Stack Overflow community for deeper discussions. Try it out this school year and share your feedback! 👩‍💻👨‍💻 #Coding #AI #StackOverflow #Learning #DeveloperCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kickstart your career by building your Stack Overflow presence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7626/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7626/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Are you a student or early in your career? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone! Recent research shows that 11% of Stack Overflow users are students and 25% have under 5 years of experience. Instead of lurking, consider sharing your voice and building your presence in the community. Engaging with seasoned developers and peers can help you form valuable connections. Start by commenting on questions or answers that interest you. Building your Stack Overflow profile can enhance your personal brand, which hiring&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stack Overflow is helping you learn to code with new resources</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7624/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7624/</guid>
      <description>📚 Stack Overflow is enhancing learning for students this year! We&amp;rsquo;ve introduced new resources to support your coding journey. The AI Assist tool provides instant answers to your coding questions, making problem-solving quicker. Join the Stack Overflow Lobby for beginner-friendly chat and connect with experienced developers for real-time advice. We&amp;rsquo;ve also revamped the comments section for better organization and interaction. Explore our Coding Challenges to practice your skills effectively!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI for consumer applications isn’t all fun and games</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7600/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7600/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kylan Gibbs, CEO of Inworld, shares insights on the technical challenges of developing interactive AI for virtual worlds and games. He highlights the importance of user experience, accessibility, and cost-efficiency in AI deployment. Inworld aims to streamline workload management and enhance iteration speed for teams. 👏 Congratulations to MrWhite for earning an Illuminator badge by answering 500 questions in just 12 hours! #AI #VirtualWorlds #UserExperience #Inworld #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-source is for the people, by the people</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7521/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7521/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in the world of Python! Travis Oliphant, the creator of NumPy and SciPy, discusses the growth of Python as a data science tool and the significance of community in open-source projects. He highlights recent releases of NumPy 2.3.0 and SciPy 1.16.0, and introduces the OpenTeams Incubator, aimed at supporting sustainable open-source communities. 📊 Connect with Travis for insights on open-source growth! #OpenSource #DataScience #Python #Community #Collaboration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving the public Stack Overflow sites to the cloud: Part 1</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7471/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7471/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stack Overflow is transitioning from physical servers to the cloud! This move marks a significant shift from their traditional data center model, primarily based in the US. The journey began with Stack Overflow for Teams successfully migrating to Azure, but challenges remain for the public site. 🌐 Key project deadlines are set for July 31, 2025, coinciding with the data center&amp;rsquo;s closure. The team is focused on setting milestones to ensure a smooth transition while maintaining flexibility&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From punch cards to prompts: a history of how software got better</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7242/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7242/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Dive into the history of software development with Ryan and Darko Mesaroš from AWS! They explore key technologies and breakthroughs that have enhanced productivity for developers, moving from punch cards to modern prompts. For those interested in learning more, check out the AWS Builder Center for resources and community connection. #SoftwareDevelopment #AWS #TechHistory #DeveloperProductivity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Svelte was built on “slinging code for the sheer love of it”</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7189/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7189/</guid>
      <description>🎙️ In a recent discussion, Rich Harris, creator of Svelte, explored the evolution of web frameworks with Ryan. He highlighted Svelte&amp;rsquo;s development during the mobile boom and the complexities of building efficient web applications. They also touched on the importance of supporting open-source projects and the nuances of asynchronous operations in component frameworks. Stay connected with the Svelte community! #Svelte #WebDevelopment #OpenSource #TechTalk #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making continuous learning work at work</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6343/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6343/</guid>
      <description>Continuous learning is vital for success in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced work environment. 🛠️ The most effective learning occurs in real work situations—during code reviews, problem-solving, and retrospectives. Leaders can embed learning into daily routines using the Learn → Question → Answer → Apply cycle. To ensure skills remain relevant, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to be intentional, lead by example, and offer diverse learning methods. Capturing these learning moments helps prevent knowledge decay and retains&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots in the skies (and they use Transformer models)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6313/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6313/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how AI is transforming defense technology! In a recent discussion, Nathan Michael, CTO of Shield AI, shared insights on the Hivemind platform. This technology enables drones to make autonomous decisions while ensuring human oversight. The conversation also touched on software security and the ethical implications of using AI in defense. #AI #DefenseTechnology #Drones #Innovation #Ethics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research roadmap update, August 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5123/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 14:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5123/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stack Overflow is evolving to better serve developers! The platform is preparing for a redesign aimed at enhancing user experience with a modern UI and features that foster collaboration and skill development. New content types and sub-communities are being explored to address the needs of users. Feedback indicates strong interest in Challenges, with many users eager to engage in coding puzzles and skill growth. As Stack Overflow looks to create focused communities, the goal is to replicate&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning in the flow: Unlocking employee potential through continuous learning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5124/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5124/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking employee potential through continuous learning is vital in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced work environment. In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, Stack Overflow CEO Prashanth Chandrasekar and Christina Dacauaziliqua from Morgan Stanley discuss the benefits of experiential learning. They highlight the need for intentional learning environments that combine innovative tools and collaborative communities. The conversation covers the importance of leaders modeling continuous learning, three key&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documents: The architect’s programming language</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5125/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5125/</guid>
      <description>Architects in tech play a vital role in bridging ideas and people. While senior developers focus on coding, architects leverage their experience to deploy concepts effectively within teams. This involves collaboration, communication, and consensus-building across various stakeholders. Tools like Confluence and Notion aid architects in organizing and sharing ideas, ensuring projects move forward smoothly. #TechLeadership #SoftwareArchitecture #Collaboration #CareerPaths #EngineeringManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening the core: Stack Overflow for Teams 2025.6</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5126/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5126/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are here with Stack Overflow for Teams 2025.6! This release focuses on back-end improvements enhancing stability, data integrity, and identity management. Key upgrades include better SAML and SCIM integrations for smoother onboarding. Email address changes now sync automatically for improved reporting accuracy. Look forward to upcoming features like nested comments for richer discussions and an ingestion engine to convert content from various platforms into reusable&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The server-side rendering equivalent for LLM inference workloads</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-6344/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-6344/</guid>
      <description>Join Ryan and Tuhin Srivastava, CEO of Baseten, as they discuss the changing AI infrastructure landscape. They highlight how the shift to large-scale neural networks is impacting GPU usage and the future of hardware optimizations in AI. Baseten offers the tools and expertise needed to accelerate AI product development. 📈🤖💡 #AI #MachineLearning #NeuralNetworks #Baseten #TechTalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of Vue is you (and You)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5127/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting insights from Evan You, the creator of Vue.js! In a recent discussion, Evan highlighted the origins of Vue.js and the challenges faced over the past decade. The framework has grown significantly, now ranking as the eighth most popular in the 2025 Developer Survey. They also explored future developments, AI integrations, and the sustainability of open-source projects. Learn more about what’s next for Vue.js and the team at Void Zero. #VueJS #WebDevelopment #OpenSource #JavaScript&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI isn’t stealing your job, it’s helping you find it</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4958/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4958/</guid>
      <description>🔍 AI is reshaping the way we search for jobs on LinkedIn! Wenjing Zhang and Caleb Johnson discuss how LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s job search feature has evolved from keyword-based to semantic search, enhancing the experience for job seekers and employers alike. With over one billion members, LinkedIn continues to leverage AI for better connections. Explore Caleb&amp;rsquo;s blog for more insights! #LinkedIn #JobSearch #AI #SemanticSearch #CareerAdvice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renewing Chat on Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4853/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4853/</guid>
      <description>🔄 Stack Overflow is focusing on enhancing its chat features to foster better conversations among developers. 💬 The goal is to create a more collaborative environment where users can engage in meaningful discussions. 👥 These improvements aim to make the platform a valuable space for sharing knowledge and support. #StackOverflow #DeveloperCommunity #Collaboration #TechTalk #ChatImprovements</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python: Come for the language, stay for the community</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4765/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4765/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In a recent discussion, Ryan welcomed Paul Everitt from JetBrains to delve into Python&amp;rsquo;s journey. They highlighted key moments in its history and growth, particularly its transition from Python 2 to 3. 📊 Python&amp;rsquo;s relevance is growing, especially in academia and data science, making it the fourth most popular language according to the 2025 Developer Survey. 🔧 JetBrains continues to enhance the developer experience with its tools. #Python #JetBrains #ProgrammingCommunity #DataScience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new worst coder has entered the chat: vibe coding without code knowledge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4766/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4766/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving tech landscape, a new trend called &amp;ldquo;vibe coding&amp;rdquo; has emerged, allowing those without coding skills to create applications. This concept, popularized in early 2025, raises questions about its effectiveness and impact on junior developers. The author shares their experience building an app using the vibe coding tool, Bolt, during a Hackathon. While it was easy to start, the lack of technical knowledge revealed flaws in the final product. This highlights the potential limitations&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being unambiguous in what you want: the software engineer in a vibe coding world</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2095/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2095/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Quinn Slack, CEO of Sourcegraph, discusses the impact of AI coding tools on software engineering. He highlights the shift from syntax tasks to higher-level design and management roles for developers. AI&amp;rsquo;s integration into enterprises is set to enhance software development processes. Connect with Quinn on LinkedIn and X for more insights! #SoftwareEngineering #AI #Sourcegraph #TechTalks #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-pollination as a strategic advantage for forward-thinking organizations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2096/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2096/</guid>
      <description>Innovation is key for growing organizations, and fostering a culture of cross-pollination can enhance this. 🌱 By sharing knowledge across teams, companies can combat stagnation and encourage fresh ideas. Leaders play a vital role in creating an environment where employees feel safe to share and explore new concepts. 🤝 This approach not only boosts engagement but also helps teams understand how their work contributes to broader goals. #CrossPollination #Innovation #Teamwork #Leadership&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving into the results of the 2025 Developer Survey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2097/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2097/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting insights from the 2025 Developer Survey are here! Ryan and Eira speak with Erin Yepis from Stack Overflow about key findings. Notably, there is a decline in trust in AI tools among developers. The survey also highlights shifts in popular programming technologies and trends in salary growth for tech professionals. #DeveloperSurvey #TechTrends #AI #SalaryGrowth #ProgrammingInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do AI coding tools help with imposter syndrome or make it worse?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2098/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2098/</guid>
      <description>AI coding tools can influence imposter syndrome in developers in complex ways. While tools like Copilot and Codex may ease self-doubt by accelerating learning, they can also lead to overreliance, affecting code quality and understanding. The pressure to continually upskill with these tools can intensify anxiety for some developers. #ImposterSyndrome #AICoding #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTrends #ContinuousLearning 🤖📈🖥️</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The innovation, leadership, and team agility inside U.S. Bank’s cloud journey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2099/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2099/</guid>
      <description>🌐 In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, industry experts discuss U.S. Bank&amp;rsquo;s transition from traditional banking to a multi-cloud strategy. 💡 The bank is focused on innovation while maintaining compliance in a regulated environment. Key topics include team empowerment, collaboration, and cloud migration strategies. 🤝 Leaders highlight the significance of transparency and continuous communication in driving successful change. #CloudComputing #DigitalTransformation #BankingInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
