<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stack-Overflow-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/stack-overflow-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stack-Overflow-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:40:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/stack-overflow-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Transforming enterprise workflows: How IBM is unlocking AI&#39;s potential</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14555/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14555/</guid>
      <description>IBM is making strides in integrating AI into enterprise workflows. In a recent episode of Leaders of Code, Jody Bailey interviews Matt Lyteson, IBM&amp;rsquo;s CIO of Technology Platform Transformation. They discuss the strategic adoption of AI, emphasizing the importance of employee engagement with automation. Key challenges highlighted include data privacy, security, and the need for workforce reskilling. For more insights, connect with Matt Lyteson on LinkedIn! 🤖💼 #AI #EnterpriseSolutions&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 lessons from tech leadership on scaling teams and AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14522/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14522/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In its first year, Leaders of Code shared valuable lessons from tech leaders on scaling teams and AI. Key insights highlight the critical role of high-quality training data in successful AI initiatives. Poor data quality can undermine even the best AI models, emphasizing the need for robust data strategies. Conversations from leaders at companies like Google and JPMorgan Chase shed light on overcoming common challenges in AI adoption. #TechLeadership #AI #DataQuality #Innovation #LeadersOfCode</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you&#39;re a Zoomer, this one&#39;s for you: Everything Gen Z needs to know about the 2025 tech landscape</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14521/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14521/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Gen Z, here&amp;rsquo;s what you need to know about the 2025 tech landscape! The article dives into key trends, including the ongoing discussion about whether AI is a bubble and its potential to burst. It also highlights the rise of vibe coding and shifts in the job market. For those who prefer quick insights, a TLDR and helpful links are provided at the end of each section. Stay informed and keep up with the tech world! 🌐💻 #GenZ #TechTrends #AI #VibeCoding #JobMarket</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe code anything in a Hanselminute</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14436/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14436/</guid>
      <description>🎙️ Exciting crossover alert! Ryan welcomes Scott Hanselman, VP of Developer Community at Microsoft, for a discussion on vibe coding. They explore how vibe coding enhances the software development lifecycle and the role of human judgment in understanding code. AI is highlighted as a valuable learning tool, demonstrated by Scott&amp;rsquo;s vibe-coded app created over lunch. Check out Scott&amp;rsquo;s insights through his podcasts and his vibe-coded app on GitHub! #VibeCoding #SoftwareDevelopment #Microsoft #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now everyone can chat on Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-12-14424/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-12-14424/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Great news for Stack Overflow users! Registered users can now join public chat rooms from day one. This change makes it easier to connect and learn within the community. Previously, chat access was limited to users with 20 reputation points. By opening it up to all, Stack Overflow aims to enhance engagement for newcomers. Chat Room Owners can also create onboarding cards to guide new users. This initiative supports users in finding their voice and participating effectively. #StackOverflow&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Every ecommerce hero needs a Sidekick</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-09-14364/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-09-14364/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in ecommerce! Ryan interviews Vanessa Lee, VP of Product at Shopify, about the impact of AI on the industry. They introduce Sidekick, Shopify’s new AI assistant designed to improve user experiences. The discussion highlights the challenges of building AI tools, the need for human oversight, and future possibilities in personalized ecommerce. Learn more about these innovations! #Ecommerce #AI #Shopify #TechInnovation #Personalization</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now everyone can chat on Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14306/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14306/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stack Overflow has made a significant update! Registered users can now join public chat rooms from day one. This change fosters easier connections and learning opportunities within the community. Previously, chat access was limited to users with 20 reputation points, but this new approach lowers barriers for newcomers. The Stack Overflow Lobbies, introduced in May 2025, have shown great engagement from novice users. Now, all public chat rooms will welcome new participants to enhance their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You need quality engineers to turn AI into ROI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14295/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 05:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14295/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Pete Johnson, Field CTO at MongoDB, discusses AI&amp;rsquo;s role in the workforce on a recent podcast. He argues that viewing AI as a job killer is a misconception. Instead, AI should be seen as a collaborator that enhances human productivity. Johnson emphasizes the importance of having quality engineers to effectively leverage AI for business ROI. #AI #Productivity #MongoDB #TechInsights #Collaboration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search engine bots crawled so AI bots could run</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14251/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14251/</guid>
      <description>In a recent episode, Ryan interviews Akamai data scientist Robert Lester about the impact of AI bots on internet traffic. They explore how these AI bots differ from traditional search engine optimization bots. Interestingly, Lester suggests that mitigating AI bots on websites may not be necessary for all. For more insights, connect with Robert on LinkedIn and check out his AI Pulse blogs. #AIBots #InternetTraffic #SEO #TechTalk #Akamai</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s new at Stack Overflow: January 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14227/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14227/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Stack Overflow for January 2026! This month focuses on key features introduced over the past year. Notably, AI Assist launched in December 2025, providing instant access to community-verified answers and support for coding challenges. Additionally, testing for open-ended questions began in October 2025, promoting inclusivity while maintaining quality standards. A Beta release is expected soon! #StackOverflow #TechUpdates #AI #CodingCommunity #2026Trends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new worst coder has entered the chat: vibe coding without code knowledge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-02-14207/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 14:43:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-02-14207/</guid>
      <description>In the era of AI, creating applications has become more accessible through &amp;ldquo;vibe coding.&amp;rdquo; This approach allows individuals without technical skills to develop apps using user-friendly platforms like Bolt. However, the effectiveness of vibe coding is questioned. While it simplifies app creation, experts may find significant flaws in the output. This raises concerns about its impact on junior developers and the tech industry as a whole. #VibeCoding #TechTrends #AI #AppDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The most dangerous shortcuts in software</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-02-14203/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-02-14203/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In a recent discussion, Ryan and Tom Totenberg from LaunchDarkly explored the risks of shortcuts in software development. They highlighted how business pressures and AI tools can lead to unsafe practices. Balancing speed with sustainable methods is crucial for maintaining system integrity. Connect with Tom on LinkedIn for more insights! #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTalk #Sustainability #AI #LaunchDarkly</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documents: The architect’s programming language</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-01-14200/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-01-14200/</guid>
      <description>Senior developers excel at coding, while architects focus on deploying ideas within teams. Career paths diverge at the senior level—many choose management, trading coding for meetings and team dynamics. Others pursue the architect track, allowing them to stay involved in coding and enhancing their influence. The architect role, though similar to senior development, requires a different approach to impact and output. Understanding these distinctions is key for those aspiring to transition into&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A look under the hood: How (and why) we built Question Assistant</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-31-14193/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 15:07:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-31-14193/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The article explores the development of Question Assistant, a tool designed to enhance question quality on Stack Overflow. It highlights the use of machine learning and AI to streamline feedback processes, allowing human reviewers to focus on complex inquiries. The partnership with Google and the application of classic ML techniques alongside generative AI have proven effective in this initiative. Learn more about the journey and results! 🤖💡 #MachineLearning #AI #StackOverflow&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new era of Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-30-14185/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-30-14185/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Stack Overflow! At WeAreDevelopers, the team introduced a new vision and mission for the platform, emphasizing their commitment to serving the tech community. This year marks significant changes, including the launch of OverflowAI and new user engagement features. With a focus on the evolving tech landscape, Stack Overflow aims to adapt to the AI era. Stay tuned for more developments! #StackOverflow #WeAreDevelopers #TechCommunity #AI #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI is helping us build better communities</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-30-14181/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-30-14181/</guid>
      <description>🌐 AI is reshaping how we build communities! In a recent discussion, MIT and Stanford professor Alex “Sandy” Pentland highlights the role of shared knowledge in community growth. His new book, &amp;ldquo;Shared Wisdom: Cultural Evolution in the Age of AI,&amp;rdquo; examines how technology can support dialogue and decision-making. He emphasizes designing tech that aligns with human nature rather than letting it dictate our society. Explore more about Sandy&amp;rsquo;s insights and work at deliberation.io. #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers remain willing but reluctant to use AI: The 2025 Developer Survey results are here</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-29-14174/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 15:04:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-29-14174/</guid>
      <description>Developers are increasingly using AI tools, yet their trust in these technologies is declining. 🤖 According to the 2025 Developer Survey, 80% of developers incorporate AI in their workflows, but trust has dropped to 29%. Key frustrations include dealing with nearly accurate AI outputs, leading to longer debugging times. Despite this, many continue to learn new coding techniques, with 44% using AI tools for guidance. #DeveloperSurvey #AITools #Programming #TechTrends #CodingCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI vs Gen Z: How AI has changed the career pathway for junior developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-26-14159/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-26-14159/</guid>
      <description>The article explores how AI has altered career prospects for Gen Z software developers. Once viewed as a stable career choice, software development now faces challenges due to advancements in AI. Many Gen Z students, who once felt assured about their future in this field, are now reassessing their paths. The shift raises questions about the evolving landscape of tech careers. 🔍💻📉 #GenZ #SoftwareDevelopment #AI #CareerPaths #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Containers are easy—moving your legacy system off your VM is not</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-26-14155/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-26-14155/</guid>
      <description>In a recent podcast, Ryan Donovan discusses cloud-native environments with Dan Ciruli of Nutanix. They explore the integration of virtual machines (VMs) and Kubernetes, emphasizing the ongoing importance of VMs in enterprise applications. Dan also highlights how AI can aid in modernizing legacy systems, making the transition smoother. For more insights, tune in to the full episode! 🎧💻 #CloudComputing #VirtualMachines #AI #Kubernetes #Nutanix</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whether AI is a bubble or revolution, how does software survive?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-25-14153/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:42:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-25-14153/</guid>
      <description>The AI industry continues to see significant investment, surpassing $100 billion since the launch of ChatGPT in November 2022. 💰 Tech companies are exploring various applications of generative AI, from security testing to healthcare improvements. The HumanX conference highlighted these advancements and shared insights on funding trends. As AI evolves, predictions suggest increased funding and potential acquisitions in the near future. 📈🤖 #AI #TechInvestment #Innovation #GenerativeAI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Great Unracking: Saying goodbye to the servers at our physical datacenter</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-24-14147/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 14:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-24-14147/</guid>
      <description>📅 On July 2, 2025, Stack Exchange bid farewell to its physical datacenter in New Jersey. For 16 years, the SRE team managed the servers, but now all operations have transitioned to the cloud. This shift means no more physical visits for maintenance. Kudos to the SRE team for their hard work in making this change possible! More insights on the migration will be shared soon. #CloudComputing #DataCenter #TechTransition #StackExchange #SRE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Xerox and Stack Overflow partnered to preserve knowledge and power innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14130/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14130/</guid>
      <description>Xerox has teamed up with Stack Overflow to tackle the challenge of preserving collective knowledge in a hybrid work environment. 🌍🤝 To improve collaboration among its global engineering network, Xerox implemented Stack Internal as a centralized knowledge hub. This platform helps capture expertise and fosters innovation across teams. The initiative aligns with Xerox&amp;rsquo;s goal to enhance scalability and support continuous learning. 📈💡 #Xerox #StackOverflow #Innovation #Collaboration&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI ick</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14134/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:41:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14134/</guid>
      <description>The article &amp;ldquo;The AI ick&amp;rdquo; explores the mixed feelings surrounding AI-generated content. It highlights a conversation between colleagues where one expresses concern over the perception of writing as AI-produced. This raises questions about how we define creativity and art. The piece delves into the differences in how we experience AI art versus human-created works. #AI #Creativity #ContentCreation #Art #HumanTouch 🎨🤖✍️💭</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Settle down, nerds. AI is a normal technology</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14123/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14123/</guid>
      <description>In a recent episode of the Stack Overflow podcast, Anil Dash discusses AI as a normal technology, not a magical one. He emphasizes the importance of democratizing access to technology and addresses the challenges posed by non-deterministic LLMs. Developers are encouraged to maintain the community ethos of Stack Overflow while adapting to AI advancements. 💻🤖 #AI #TechCommunity #StackOverflow #SoftwareDevelopment #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making your code base better will make your code coverage worse</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14101/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14101/</guid>
      <description>Maintaining a minimum of 80% code coverage may not always lead to better code quality. The article discusses how this requirement can influence coding decisions negatively. It highlights that not all files or features hold equal value in testing, and automated testing isn’t always the most cost-effective solution. Additionally, making code DRYer could actually reduce coverage metrics, which raises questions about the reliance on code coverage as the primary measure of quality. #CodeCoverage&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last week in AWS re:Invent with Corey Quinn</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14040/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14040/</guid>
      <description>Last week at AWS re:Invent, Ryan Donovan spoke with Corey Quinn, Chief Cloud Economist at Duckbill. They explored the impact of AI agents and the focus on large enterprises by AWS. Corey highlighted the challenges faced by startups and independent developers in this landscape, noting a shift towards more inclusive technology offerings. For more insights, check Ryan’s recap on our blog! #AWS #CloudComputing #AI #TechTrends #StartupInsights 🚀💻📊</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2025 Stack Overflow and Stack Exchange wrap—our top ten questions of the year!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13943/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13943/</guid>
      <description>🚀 As 2025 ends, Stack Overflow and Stack Exchange highlight their top questions of the year! From tech fixes to historical insights, users engaged with diverse topics. Notable questions include Docker’s update troubleshooting and a unique visualization of the Pythagorean proof. Curiosity drives our communities, keeping knowledge alive. 💡 #StackOverflow #StackExchange #CommunityKnowledge #TechQuestions #LearningTogether</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your 2025 Stacked: A year of knowledge, community, and impact</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13864/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13864/</guid>
      <description>🚀 2025 was a significant year for Stack Internal! Your 2025 Stacked is now available, showcasing the collective achievements of your community. This summary highlights key contributions, including top contributors and popular posts that shaped your year. From engaging questions to impactful articles, see how knowledge sharing drove your organization forward. Explore this year&amp;rsquo;s highlights and celebrate your team&amp;rsquo;s efforts! 🌟📈 #StackInternal #KnowledgeSharing #CommunityImpact #YearInReview&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live from re:Invent…it’s Stack Overflow!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13865/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13865/</guid>
      <description>📢 Live from AWS re:Invent! Ryan Donovan hosts Stack Overflow&amp;rsquo;s CEO Prashanth Chandrasekar and Director of Data Science Michael Foree. They discuss key themes from the event, including AI agents and the enterprise&amp;rsquo;s trust issues regarding AI. Prashanth highlights the growing interest in AI, emphasizing the need for trust in its adoption. For more insights, check out the full recap on our blog! #AWS #AI #TechTrends #StackOverflow #reInvent2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>At AWS re:Invent, the news was agents, but the focus was developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13866/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:53:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13866/</guid>
      <description>AWS re:Invent brought together around 60,000 developers in Las Vegas for four days of innovation and networking. Key announcements focused on AI agents, including Kiro developer, security, and DevOps agents. These autonomous agents aim to enhance application efficiency and security. AWS also introduced AWS Transform, aimed at reducing tech debt, and discussed the importance of policy guardrails for agent collaboration. Additionally, AI Factories were announced to cater to entities needing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The shift in enterprise AI—what we learned on the floor at Microsoft Ignite</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13554/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13554/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At Microsoft Ignite, a shift in enterprise AI strategies was evident. Companies are moving from flashy innovations to steady, focused approaches that emphasize market fit and real proof of effectiveness. Many enterprises showcased AI solutions that enhance existing offerings rather than introducing entirely new concepts. Examples included Docusign’s AI-powered forms, designed to tackle user challenges efficiently. Companies are now prioritizing tangible results and use cases over just&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Treating your agents like microservices</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13519/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13519/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the future of multi-agent architectures, Ryan talks with Guillaume De Saint Marc from Outshift by Cisco. They discuss how treating agents as microservices can enhance scalability and decentralization. Key points include the challenges of current infrastructure and the need for effective communication protocols. Discover more about these emerging technologies and connect with the AGNTCY community. 🚀🔗 #MultiAgentArchitecture #Microservices #Cisco #EmergingTech #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postman’s journey and unlocking the power of APIs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13417/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13417/</guid>
      <description>In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, Abhinav Asthana, co-founder and CEO of Postman, shares the platform&amp;rsquo;s evolution from a side project to a vital tool for developers. He discusses scaling Postman&amp;rsquo;s engineering team from three founders to over 400, and highlights how AI agents enhance developer feedback clarity. Asthana emphasizes the importance of APIs in connecting AI to live data, enabling actionable outcomes beyond mere conversation. 🔗💻📈 #APIs #TechLeadership #AI #Postman&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disrupting yourself in the age of AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13234/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13234/</guid>
      <description>The internet is undergoing a significant transformation due to AI. Traditional metrics like traffic are becoming outdated. In this new era, success is measured by reach, trust, attribution, and influence. Businesses must evolve to provide structured knowledge, engage users, and form API partnerships to thrive. The focus is now on delivering verified, human-contributed content that AI can utilize effectively. #AI #DigitalTransformation #KnowledgeAsAService #ContentStrategy #Innovation 🌐🤖📊</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Stack Overflow AI Assist—a tool for the modern developer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13233/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13233/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing AI Assist at Stack Overflow! This innovative tool transforms how developers access knowledge. By combining human-verified answers with generative AI, users can find solutions faster and with less hassle. Our team engaged with users to create an experience that eases barriers and enhances learning, ensuring everyone feels at home in our community. #StackOverflow #AI #DeveloperTools #KnowledgeSharing #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Abstraction, but for robots</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13211/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13211/</guid>
      <description>🤖 Exciting insights from Ryan&amp;rsquo;s discussion with Simone Kalmakis, VP of Engineering at Viam! They explore how Viam is bridging the gap between software and robotics through abstraction layers. This makes robotics more accessible for various applications, including lobster traps and industrial sanding robots. Connect with Simone on LinkedIn to learn more! #Robotics #SoftwareDevelopment #Innovation #Technology #Engineering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s new at Stack Overflow: December 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13179/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 15:18:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13179/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Stack Overflow this December! The new MCP server is now in beta, allowing developers to integrate the site’s knowledge into AI applications. It supports 100 requests per day for prototyping and projects. A new question type is expanding access to developer preferences and subjective topics, maintaining quality standards. Users can now easily copy code blocks with a new button, including attribution. Plus, chat room owners can add onboarding cards for new members&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightning-as-a-service for agriculture</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13118/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13118/</guid>
      <description>🌾 Exciting developments in AgTech! Darryl Lyons, co-founder of Rainstick, shares how they are using bioelectricity to boost agricultural productivity. Rainstick mimics thunderstorms to create electric fields that promote plant growth. They also address challenges and breakthroughs in their research and their involvement in the AWS Compute for Climate Fellowship. 🌩️ Learn more about these innovations in agriculture! #AgTech #SustainableFarming #Bioelectricity #Innovation #ClimateTech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essential ingredients for enterprise AI success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13043/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13043/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The 2025 Stack Overflow Developer Survey reveals insights into AI adoption among developers. 🔍 Trust in AI tools is declining, with over 75% of developers seeking human validation. Many express frustration over AI-generated code being &amp;ldquo;almost right&amp;rdquo; but needing more context for debugging. 🧠 Complex reasoning remains a challenge for current AI models, indicating a need for improvement. 📊 While more than half prefer simpler AI tools, 70% of those using advanced tools report saved time on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You’re probably underutilizing your GPUs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13029/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13029/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Discover the insights on GPU utilization with Ryan Donovan and Jared Quincy Davis, CEO of Mithril, in a recent podcast episode. They discuss the significance of effective resource allocation in AI, debunking myths around GPU shortages. The conversation highlights how new scheduling strategies can reshape GPU economics. Mithril’s platform enables seamless access to multi-cloud resources for enhanced efficiency. Tune in for key takeaways! 🎧💻 #GPU #AI #TechTalk #ResourceManagement #Mithril</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Only you can stop AI database drops</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12931/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12931/</guid>
      <description>AI is reshaping the software landscape! 🤖 In a recent podcast, David Hsu, CEO of Retool, discussed how AI is evolving the role of software developers into architects. He highlighted the growing accessibility of coding for non-engineers and stressed the need for guardrails in AI coding assistants. Retool offers an AI AppGen platform for internal software development, enabling app creation with various data sources and APIs. Tune in for insights! 🎧 #AI #SoftwareDevelopment #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community Products roadmap update, November 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12901/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12901/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Stack Overflow! As we approach the year&amp;rsquo;s end, the Community Products team is enhancing user experiences. Recent focus areas include AI-powered solutions, community growth, and a rebranding effort. Key highlights include the AI Assist beta, Stack Overflow MCP Server, and new Coding Challenges. Efforts to lower barriers for commenting and voting aim to foster inclusivity. Stay tuned for more updates! 💡✨ #StackOverflow #CommunityGrowth #AIEvolution #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Stack Internal: Powering the human intelligence layer of enterprise AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12767/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12767/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Microsoft Ignite! Stack Overflow for Teams is now Stack Internal, a secure knowledge platform designed for the AI era. Stack Internal centralizes verified expertise, helping enterprises streamline development and reduce the workload on subject matter experts. By combining human expertise with AI, it automates knowledge curation. This partnership with Microsoft aims to empower developers by enhancing productivity and fostering innovation. With seamless integration into&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to create agents that people actually want to use</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12742/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12742/</guid>
      <description>💡 Ryan welcomes Assaf Elovic, head of AI at monday.com, to discuss user-friendly AI tools. They share insights on developing the Monday Sidekick agent, focusing on user experience to boost adoption. monday.com aims to enhance productivity and efficiency through its AI-first product suite. #AI #Productivity #UserExperience #MondayDotCom #WorkManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The fastest agent in the race has the best evals</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12161/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12161/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ryan interviews Benjamin Klieger, lead engineer at Groq, about the infrastructure behind AI agents. They discuss how to enhance agent efficiency, turning a one-minute process into just ten seconds. Groq’s custom-designed LPU enables fast, low-cost inference, powering their Compound agent that can search and run code. Connect with Benjamin on LinkedIn and X! #AI #Inference #Groq #TechTalk #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One thing enterprise AI projects need to succeed? Community.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12111/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12111/</guid>
      <description>🌟 In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, Stack Overflow&amp;rsquo;s CEO Prashanth Chandrasekar and JPMorgan Chase&amp;rsquo;s VP Ramprasad Rai discuss the importance of community in enterprise AI projects. They highlight how a community-driven knowledge layer can enhance AI reliability, prevent hallucinations, and ensure quality code validation. The conversation also touches on the challenges of AI implementation amid compliance and security needs. 🔗 Connect with Ramprasad Rai on LinkedIn for more insights!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025.8 release introduces Stack Overflow Internal: The next generation of enterprise knowledge intelligence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12112/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12112/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Stack Overflow! Introducing Stack Overflow Internal, the next evolution in enterprise knowledge intelligence. This platform enhances the way teams access and manage trusted information across their tools and workflows. With features like the Model Context Protocol Server, AI agents can deliver accurate responses based on verified knowledge, ensuring privacy and control. Knowledge Ingestion transforms existing content into structured, reliable information, helping teams&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI code means more critical thinking, not less</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12113/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12113/</guid>
      <description>AI is reshaping the coding landscape, emphasizing the need for critical thinking among developers. In a recent discussion, Matias Madou from Secure Code Warrior highlighted the variability of LLMs and their impact on code security. As AI coding assistants grow in popularity, the focus on training developers, especially juniors, becomes crucial. Secure Code Warrior aims to enhance the skills of development teams to mitigate cybersecurity risks. 🔒💻 #AICoding #CyberSecurity #DeveloperTraining&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revealing the unknown unknowns in your software</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11949/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11949/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://stackoverflow.blog/feed/&#34;&gt;Stack Overflow Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://stackoverflow.blog/2025/11/07/revealing-the-unknown-unknowns-in-your-software/&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To write secure code, be less gullible than your AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11682/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11682/</guid>
      <description>Exploring AI in coding, Greg Foster, CTO of Graphite, highlights the importance of not fully trusting AI-generated code. 💻 He emphasizes the need for proper tooling to enhance code security and the significance of human readability in AI-generated code. 🛠️ Graphite aims to provide context on code changes and improve PR processes. Stay informed about the evolving landscape of coding! 🔍 #AICoding #CodeSecurity #Graphite #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s new at Stack Overflow: November 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11657/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11657/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting updates from Stack Overflow! This month marks the launch of a new blog series keeping you informed on the latest features. Key highlights include: - Introduction of &amp;ldquo;free votes&amp;rdquo; for new users to enhance engagement. - Exploration of hosting more open-ended questions while maintaining quality. - Sneak peek at the upcoming redesign with focus areas shared on Meta Stack Exchange. - Launch of a new anti-spam tool to improve community safety. Stay informed and engage with these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe coding needs a spec, too</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11528/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11528/</guid>
      <description>In a recent discussion, Deepak Singh from AWS highlights the shift towards spec-driven development in AI coding. The Kiro AI IDE introduces structure by allowing developers to create software using specifications rather than just code. This evolution reflects how AI tools have advanced significantly, moving from simple autocompletion to sophisticated coding agents. For deeper insights, join Deepak on the Kiro Discord and catch the upcoming virtual OpenAI Forum with CEO Prashanth Chandrasekar&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Live from the OpenAI forum: Learning to code in the age of AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11504/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 14:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11504/</guid>
      <description>Join us for a virtual fireside chat featuring our CEO, Prashanth Chandrasekar, at the OpenAI Forum! 🗣️ The discussion will focus on the evolving role of developers as AI technology advances. Many junior developers are understandably concerned about their future in the field. 🌐 Tune in on November 3 at 3 PM EDT to learn about insights from our 2025 Developer Survey and how we can support the next generation of engineers. 💻 #OpenAI #SoftwareDevelopment #FutureOfWork #AI #TechTalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craft and quality beat speed and scale, with or without agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11329/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11329/</guid>
      <description>In the latest Stack Overflow Podcast, Ryan Donovan speaks with Tom Moor from Linear about AI agents and their impact on productivity. They discuss the mixed results of AI agents in development and the importance of context for their effectiveness. Junior developers also play a crucial role in adapting to an AI-driven landscape. Listen to the full episode for insights! 🎧💻 #AI #SoftwareDevelopment #TechPodcast #Productivity #JuniorDevelopers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI agents will succeed because one tool is better than ten</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11306/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11306/</guid>
      <description>AI agents are transforming the tech landscape by offering a single interface for chatting, tool use, and coding. This simplifies workflow and reduces context switching for developers. As companies shift focus from chatbots to AI agents, the emphasis is on enhancing productivity with natural language as an interface. This evolution aims to streamline the multitude of tools developers juggle. Surveys show developers often use multiple tools, leading to wasted time. AI agents could be the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your runbooks are obsolete in the age of agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11245/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11245/</guid>
      <description>In a recent podcast episode, Ryan Donovan speaks with Spiros Xanthos, CEO of Resolve AI, about the evolving role of AI in incident management and software troubleshooting. They discuss the limitations of traditional runbooks and the need for AI agents to assist developers. Spiros shares insights from his experience at Splunk, highlighting that a significant amount of time in software engineering is spent on maintenance rather than development. Resolve AI aims to address this by creating&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What leaders need to know from the 2025 Stack Overflow Developer Survey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11183/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11183/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, insights from the 2025 Stack Overflow Developer Survey are discussed to help leaders navigate the AI landscape. Key points include a decline in developer trust in AI due to frustrations with inaccurate solutions and debugging challenges. Despite AI&amp;rsquo;s rise, 80% of developers still rely on Stack Overflow for community support, highlighting the importance of human connection. Tool sprawl remains a significant issue, with most developers using 6–10&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open source is giving you choices with your agent systems</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11094/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11094/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Open source is shaping the future of AI agents! In a recent podcast, John Dickerson, CEO of Mozilla.ai, discussed the importance of open-source technology in maintaining a healthy tech ecosystem. He addressed the challenges faced by open-source communities amid the rise of AI and the significance of data privacy and user choice. Mozilla.ai is focused on creating platforms that enable organizations to safely automate tasks using AI agents. For further insights, connect with John on LinkedIn&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From multilingual semantic search to virtual assistants at Bosch Digital</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11070/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11070/</guid>
      <description>Bosch Digital is transforming the way riders and mechanics access information with its multilingual SmartSearch system. 🌍🚴‍♂️ The new system allows for instant answers to queries, like &amp;ldquo;reset Kiox 300 display,&amp;rdquo; rather than sifting through lengthy manuals. This shift enhances customer experience by understanding user intent across languages. SmartSearch employs a three-step process: crawling vast documentation, chunking content for clarity, and ranking results efficiently. This ensures quick&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why rent a cloud when you can build one?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11018/</guid>
      <description>🌥️ Andrei Kvapil, founder of Ænix and core developer of Cozystack, discusses building a private cloud from scratch. He explains the role of Kubernetes and open-source technology in achieving digital sovereignty. Cozystack offers a platform for managed services, moving beyond traditional virtual machines. Learn more about the future of cloud technology! #CloudComputing #Kubernetes #OpenSource #TechTalk #DigitalSovereignty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure coding in JavaScript</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10948/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10948/</guid>
      <description>🔒 JavaScript is essential for web development, but it also attracts attackers. This article highlights ten tips for writing secure JavaScript, focusing on preventing cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. XSS allows attackers to execute malicious code directly in users&amp;rsquo; browsers, which can compromise security. Key recommendations include input validation, output encoding, and using Content Security Policy (CSP) headers. Implementing these measures can significantly reduce the risk of XSS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI agents for your digital chores</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10883/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10883/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Discover the future of AI agents with Dhruv Batra, co-founder of Yutori. In a recent podcast, he discusses how proactive AI can transform digital tasks and interactions with advertisements. 💻 Yutori is focused on creating AI agents that manage everyday online chores, streamlining user experience. 🔍 Explore the challenges of integrating these proactive agents into our daily workflows. #ArtificialIntelligence #DigitalInnovation #AIagents #TechTalk #Yutori</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vite is like the United Nations of JavaScript</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10615/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10615/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vite is reshaping web development as a powerful frontend build tool. Evan You, the creator of Vite and Vue.js, discusses its evolution, unique features like plugins and hot module capabilities, and its future integration with Rust. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss Vite&amp;rsquo;s new documentary for deeper insights! 🎥 #WebDevelopment #Vite #OpenSource #JavaScript #TechTalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who watches the watchers? LLM on LLM evaluations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10594/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10594/</guid>
      <description>As generative AI gains traction, developers are focused on ensuring the reliability of AI applications. Trust in AI appears to be declining, prompting engineers to seek methods for building trustworthy systems. Human moderation is often impractical at scale, leading to the use of LLMs to evaluate other LLM outputs. This approach, while seemingly risky, has shown promise in scaling evaluations effectively. Research indicates that LLM judges can align with human assessments, although they come&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new look for comments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10546/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10546/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates on Stack Overflow! A new comments user interface is now available, allowing all registered users to comment on questions and answers. This change removes the previous 50 reputation requirement, enhancing community engagement. The updated UI features threaded comments and a voting system for better interaction and value recognition. Users can now follow discussions more easily, improving the overall experience. Learn more about the new commenting features in the Help Center!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context is king for secure, AI-generated code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10484/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10484/</guid>
      <description>In a recent discussion, Dimitri Stiliadis, CTO of Endor Labs, emphasized the evolving role of AppSec in the era of AI-generated code. Key points include the need for human oversight in managing vulnerabilities and the balance between security and efficiency when integrating AI into development practices. Endor Labs aims to help organizations identify critical risks in both human and AI-written code. 🔒🤖💻 #AppSec #AIGeneratedCode #Cybersecurity #SoftwareDevelopment #EndorLabs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond code generation: How AI is changing tech teams&#39; dynamics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10437/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10437/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming tech team dynamics by automating non-coding tasks, boosting productivity, and enabling agile workflows. Developers can now focus on complex challenges instead of repetitive tasks. Tools like coding assistants streamline processes, enhance collaboration, and improve documentation. This shift allows teams to deliver software faster and tackle strategic issues effectively. 📈🤖 #TechInnovation #AI #SoftwareDevelopment #AgileTeams #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One is not the loneliest number for API calls</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10426/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10426/</guid>
      <description>🎧 In the latest Stack Overflow Podcast, Gil Feig, co-founder and CTO at Merge, shares insights on simplifying third-party API integrations. Merge aims to reduce multiple API calls to a single connection, addressing the complexities of data normalization. The discussion also touches on the role of AI and MCP in enhancing API functionality. For more details, listen to the episode! #APIs #DataIntegration #TechTalk #Merge #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI-ready teams: Why documentation and culture matter more than tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10349/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10349/</guid>
      <description>In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, Peter O&amp;rsquo;Connor and Ryan J. Salva discuss key strategies for AI adoption in engineering teams. 💡 They emphasize the importance of high-quality documentation to avoid errors in AI systems. 📄 Consistent tools and processes are crucial as teams learn and adapt to AI technology. Leaders are encouraged to foster a culture that prioritizes learning and experimentation with AI tools, rather than just focusing on productivity metrics. #AI #Engineering&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Turning investments into impact: Stack Overflow for Teams 2025.7</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10256/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10256/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stack Overflow for Teams is evolving with the 2025.7 release! Key updates include a new Teams SDK, enabling developers to create tailored tools, integrate with existing systems, and manage knowledge effectively. Enhanced commenting features, like threaded replies and intuitive interfaces, improve collaboration. All updates go live on October 1, 2025. For more details, visit the release notes or connect with your Customer Success partner. Join us at Microsoft Ignite for future insights!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As your AI gets smarter, so must your API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10239/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10239/</guid>
      <description>In a recent podcast, Ryan Donovan speaks with Marco Palladino, CTO of Kong, about the growth of AI agents and their influence on API usage. 📈 Palladino highlights that the rise of AI has significantly increased API traffic, surpassing previous trends driven by mobile and cloud-native technologies. They also discuss the new MCP protocol, designed to enhance the interaction between AI agents and APIs, making it easier to access various tools and services. Observability and security in AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making your code base better will make your code coverage worse</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10205/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10205/</guid>
      <description>Maintaining an 80% code coverage can influence coding decisions, sometimes negatively. 📉 The article highlights that code coverage, often seen as a quality metric, may not accurately reflect software quality. Key points include: - Code coverage treats all files equally, which isn&amp;rsquo;t always the case. - The 80% minimum is arbitrary. - Improving code structure may lower coverage metrics. While useful, high coverage alone doesn’t guarantee code quality. #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment #Testing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Backstage in front of a shifting dev experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10159/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10159/</guid>
      <description>🎙️ In a recent Stack Overflow Podcast, Ryan Donovan interviews Pia Nilsson, GM for Backstage at Spotify. They discuss the evolution of Backstage, an open-source platform designed to enhance developer experience by reducing friction and operational challenges. Pia shares insights on how Spotify utilizes AI in development and the importance of platform engineering for meeting team needs. For those interested in software development, this episode sheds light on significant industry shifts&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The history and future of software development (part 1)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9982/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9982/</guid>
      <description>The evolution of software development is fascinating. Just 20 years ago, our tools were far less advanced. Today, we enjoy environments with AI support, syntax highlighting, and version control. However, it wasn&amp;rsquo;t always this way. In the 1960s, developers used punch cards to code. Each card held just 80 characters, leading to stacks of cards for larger programs. Debugging was a tedious process, often done on paper. This article explores the rich history and future of software development&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratizing your data access with AI agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9902/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9902/</guid>
      <description>🤖 Exciting insights from Jeff Hollan of Snowflake on the role of data in enhancing AI capabilities! He explains how Snowflake&amp;rsquo;s managed data platform supports AI app development. The newly launched data marketplace includes Stack Exchange data, broadening access for developers. Learn how data influences AI agents and empowers innovation. #DataAccess #AI #Snowflake #TechInnovation #DataMarketplace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Off with your CMS’s head! Composability and security in headless CMS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9810/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9810/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In a recent episode, Ryan speaks with Sebastian Gierlinger from Storyblok about headless content management systems (CMS) and their role in a modular software environment. They explore the key differences between headless and traditional CMS, focusing on prototyping and security concerns. Learn how decoupling content from rendering can enhance development speed. 🌐 For more insights on CMS design, check out our previous discussions with Drupal and Builder.io! #HeadlessCMS #ContentManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stack Overflow is helping you learn to code with new resources</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9774/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:36:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9774/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stack Overflow is enhancing resources for students this school year! They&amp;rsquo;ve introduced an AI Assist tool for quick answers and a new Lobby chat room for beginners to connect. Additionally, the updated comments interface allows for better community engagement through organized conversations. Explore these tools to boost your coding skills! 💻🤝 #StackOverflow #LearnToCode #TechEducation #CodingCommunity #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What an MCP implementation looks like at a CRM company</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9673/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 19:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9673/</guid>
      <description>Ryan discusses Model Context Protocol (MCP) with Karen Ng, EVP of Product at HubSpot. They delve into its role as a standard for agentic interactions and the challenges faced in integrating MCP within HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s ecosystem. MCP, developed by Anthropic, aims to enhance connections between AI agents and external systems. 🔗💡🤖 #AI #CRM #HubSpot #MCP #Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Planning to Arm mobile devices with chips that handle AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9616/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9616/</guid>
      <description>Exciting discussion on the future of mobile devices with AI chips! 🤖 Ryan hosts Geraint North from Arm, focusing on how GenAI influences chip design. They explore Arm&amp;rsquo;s flexible CPU architectures and the challenges in optimizing language models for edge devices. Arm&amp;rsquo;s new Lumex CSS Platform aims to enhance AI workloads on mobile and desktop. #AI #ChipDesign #TechInnovation #EdgeComputing #Arm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI is reshaping developer teams and the future of software development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9542/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9542/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI is transforming the landscape of software development. In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, Peter O’Connor and Ryan J. Salva discuss how AI tools enhance developer experiences beyond just coding. They highlight how AI tackles deployment bottlenecks and streamlines team collaboration. Furthermore, AI is reshaping team structures, allowing small engineering teams to operate efficiently. Learn about the future of platform engineering, where AI will help standardize and manage&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI vs Gen Z: How AI has changed the career pathway for junior developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9517/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9517/</guid>
      <description>The article discusses how AI is reshaping career prospects for Gen Z software developers. Once seen as a secure path, the tech job market has become increasingly volatile, with a notable 25% drop in entry-level tech positions in 2024. Concerns about layoffs are high, with 64% of Gen Z fearing job loss, particularly in a post-pandemic economy. AI&amp;rsquo;s ability to automate roles has significantly impacted opportunities for junior developers. #GenZ #AI #CareerDevelopment #JobMarket #TechJobs 🤖💼📉</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We built stackoverflow.ai with the community and for the community</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9453/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9453/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news from Stack Overflow! The team has launched stackoverflow.ai, designed to improve your experience by merging human-validated answers with AI. This innovation aims to provide quick and accurate technical solutions, leveraging 16 years of community knowledge. Future plans include enhanced personalization and deeper community integration. 👏 Congratulations to Ketan Ramani for earning a Populist badge for their excellent answer on formatting in Android Studio! #StackOverflow #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin is more than just the Android house language</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7769/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7769/</guid>
      <description>💡 Kotlin is evolving beyond its role as the Android house language. In a recent discussion, Jeffrey van Gogh from Google highlighted its journey from JVM to multiplatform capabilities. The Kotlin Foundation aims to support and enhance the language&amp;rsquo;s development while collaborating with the community to minimize breaking changes. This year, over half of developers expressed interest in adopting Kotlin. #Kotlin #Programming #DeveloperCommunity #Multiplatform #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Back to school? Developers at Stack Overflow have some advice for you</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7622/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7622/</guid>
      <description>Heading back to school means new challenges in coding and projects. Developers from Stack Overflow share valuable advice for students. They emphasize the importance of asking for help and normalizing feelings of imposter syndrome. Curiosity is key; understand the &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; behind coding concepts instead of just copying answers. Collaborating with peers can enhance learning experiences. Stack Overflow is a great resource for support and community among budding developers. Remember, you&amp;rsquo;re not&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting started on Stack Overflow: a step-by-step guide for students</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7623/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7623/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Getting started on Stack Overflow? Here’s what you need to know! 1️⃣ Create an account at stackoverflow.com to ask questions, save answers, and engage with the community. 2️⃣ Explore the platform’s vast knowledge base with over 60 million questions and answers. 3️⃣ Utilize the new AI Assist tool for instant answers while also learning from real developer experiences. Stack Overflow is a valuable resource for students and coders alike! #StackOverflow #CodingCommunity #StudentResources&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing your newest study buddy: stackoverflow.ai</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7625/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7625/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing stackoverflow.ai, your new study buddy for coding! This AI tool offers instant answers and guides you through learning, making it easier for developers at any level to find solutions. It prioritizes community-verified knowledge, ensuring reliable information. Plus, you can connect with the Stack Overflow community for deeper discussions. Try it out this school year and share your feedback! 👩‍💻👨‍💻 #Coding #AI #StackOverflow #Learning #DeveloperCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kickstart your career by building your Stack Overflow presence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7626/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7626/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Are you a student or early in your career? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone! Recent research shows that 11% of Stack Overflow users are students and 25% have under 5 years of experience. Instead of lurking, consider sharing your voice and building your presence in the community. Engaging with seasoned developers and peers can help you form valuable connections. Start by commenting on questions or answers that interest you. Building your Stack Overflow profile can enhance your personal brand, which hiring&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stack Overflow is helping you learn to code with new resources</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7624/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7624/</guid>
      <description>📚 Stack Overflow is enhancing learning for students this year! We&amp;rsquo;ve introduced new resources to support your coding journey. The AI Assist tool provides instant answers to your coding questions, making problem-solving quicker. Join the Stack Overflow Lobby for beginner-friendly chat and connect with experienced developers for real-time advice. We&amp;rsquo;ve also revamped the comments section for better organization and interaction. Explore our Coding Challenges to practice your skills effectively!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI for consumer applications isn’t all fun and games</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7600/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7600/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kylan Gibbs, CEO of Inworld, shares insights on the technical challenges of developing interactive AI for virtual worlds and games. He highlights the importance of user experience, accessibility, and cost-efficiency in AI deployment. Inworld aims to streamline workload management and enhance iteration speed for teams. 👏 Congratulations to MrWhite for earning an Illuminator badge by answering 500 questions in just 12 hours! #AI #VirtualWorlds #UserExperience #Inworld #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-source is for the people, by the people</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7521/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7521/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in the world of Python! Travis Oliphant, the creator of NumPy and SciPy, discusses the growth of Python as a data science tool and the significance of community in open-source projects. He highlights recent releases of NumPy 2.3.0 and SciPy 1.16.0, and introduces the OpenTeams Incubator, aimed at supporting sustainable open-source communities. 📊 Connect with Travis for insights on open-source growth! #OpenSource #DataScience #Python #Community #Collaboration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving the public Stack Overflow sites to the cloud: Part 1</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7471/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7471/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stack Overflow is transitioning from physical servers to the cloud! This move marks a significant shift from their traditional data center model, primarily based in the US. The journey began with Stack Overflow for Teams successfully migrating to Azure, but challenges remain for the public site. 🌐 Key project deadlines are set for July 31, 2025, coinciding with the data center&amp;rsquo;s closure. The team is focused on setting milestones to ensure a smooth transition while maintaining flexibility&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From punch cards to prompts: a history of how software got better</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7242/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 04:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7242/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Dive into the history of software development with Ryan and Darko Mesaroš from AWS! They explore key technologies and breakthroughs that have enhanced productivity for developers, moving from punch cards to modern prompts. For those interested in learning more, check out the AWS Builder Center for resources and community connection. #SoftwareDevelopment #AWS #TechHistory #DeveloperProductivity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Svelte was built on “slinging code for the sheer love of it”</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7189/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7189/</guid>
      <description>🎙️ In a recent discussion, Rich Harris, creator of Svelte, explored the evolution of web frameworks with Ryan. He highlighted Svelte&amp;rsquo;s development during the mobile boom and the complexities of building efficient web applications. They also touched on the importance of supporting open-source projects and the nuances of asynchronous operations in component frameworks. Stay connected with the Svelte community! #Svelte #WebDevelopment #OpenSource #TechTalk #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making continuous learning work at work</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6343/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6343/</guid>
      <description>Continuous learning is vital for success in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced work environment. 🛠️ The most effective learning occurs in real work situations—during code reviews, problem-solving, and retrospectives. Leaders can embed learning into daily routines using the Learn → Question → Answer → Apply cycle. To ensure skills remain relevant, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to be intentional, lead by example, and offer diverse learning methods. Capturing these learning moments helps prevent knowledge decay and retains&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots in the skies (and they use Transformer models)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6313/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6313/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how AI is transforming defense technology! In a recent discussion, Nathan Michael, CTO of Shield AI, shared insights on the Hivemind platform. This technology enables drones to make autonomous decisions while ensuring human oversight. The conversation also touched on software security and the ethical implications of using AI in defense. #AI #DefenseTechnology #Drones #Innovation #Ethics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research roadmap update, August 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5123/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 14:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5123/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stack Overflow is evolving to better serve developers! The platform is preparing for a redesign aimed at enhancing user experience with a modern UI and features that foster collaboration and skill development. New content types and sub-communities are being explored to address the needs of users. Feedback indicates strong interest in Challenges, with many users eager to engage in coding puzzles and skill growth. As Stack Overflow looks to create focused communities, the goal is to replicate&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning in the flow: Unlocking employee potential through continuous learning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5124/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5124/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking employee potential through continuous learning is vital in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced work environment. In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, Stack Overflow CEO Prashanth Chandrasekar and Christina Dacauaziliqua from Morgan Stanley discuss the benefits of experiential learning. They highlight the need for intentional learning environments that combine innovative tools and collaborative communities. The conversation covers the importance of leaders modeling continuous learning, three key&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Documents: The architect’s programming language</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5125/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5125/</guid>
      <description>Architects in tech play a vital role in bridging ideas and people. While senior developers focus on coding, architects leverage their experience to deploy concepts effectively within teams. This involves collaboration, communication, and consensus-building across various stakeholders. Tools like Confluence and Notion aid architects in organizing and sharing ideas, ensuring projects move forward smoothly. #TechLeadership #SoftwareArchitecture #Collaboration #CareerPaths #EngineeringManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening the core: Stack Overflow for Teams 2025.6</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5126/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5126/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are here with Stack Overflow for Teams 2025.6! This release focuses on back-end improvements enhancing stability, data integrity, and identity management. Key upgrades include better SAML and SCIM integrations for smoother onboarding. Email address changes now sync automatically for improved reporting accuracy. Look forward to upcoming features like nested comments for richer discussions and an ingestion engine to convert content from various platforms into reusable&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The server-side rendering equivalent for LLM inference workloads</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-6344/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-6344/</guid>
      <description>Join Ryan and Tuhin Srivastava, CEO of Baseten, as they discuss the changing AI infrastructure landscape. They highlight how the shift to large-scale neural networks is impacting GPU usage and the future of hardware optimizations in AI. Baseten offers the tools and expertise needed to accelerate AI product development. 📈🤖💡 #AI #MachineLearning #NeuralNetworks #Baseten #TechTalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of Vue is you (and You)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5127/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting insights from Evan You, the creator of Vue.js! In a recent discussion, Evan highlighted the origins of Vue.js and the challenges faced over the past decade. The framework has grown significantly, now ranking as the eighth most popular in the 2025 Developer Survey. They also explored future developments, AI integrations, and the sustainability of open-source projects. Learn more about what’s next for Vue.js and the team at Void Zero. #VueJS #WebDevelopment #OpenSource #JavaScript&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI isn’t stealing your job, it’s helping you find it</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4958/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4958/</guid>
      <description>🔍 AI is reshaping the way we search for jobs on LinkedIn! Wenjing Zhang and Caleb Johnson discuss how LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s job search feature has evolved from keyword-based to semantic search, enhancing the experience for job seekers and employers alike. With over one billion members, LinkedIn continues to leverage AI for better connections. Explore Caleb&amp;rsquo;s blog for more insights! #LinkedIn #JobSearch #AI #SemanticSearch #CareerAdvice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renewing Chat on Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4853/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4853/</guid>
      <description>🔄 Stack Overflow is focusing on enhancing its chat features to foster better conversations among developers. 💬 The goal is to create a more collaborative environment where users can engage in meaningful discussions. 👥 These improvements aim to make the platform a valuable space for sharing knowledge and support. #StackOverflow #DeveloperCommunity #Collaboration #TechTalk #ChatImprovements</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python: Come for the language, stay for the community</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4765/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4765/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In a recent discussion, Ryan welcomed Paul Everitt from JetBrains to delve into Python&amp;rsquo;s journey. They highlighted key moments in its history and growth, particularly its transition from Python 2 to 3. 📊 Python&amp;rsquo;s relevance is growing, especially in academia and data science, making it the fourth most popular language according to the 2025 Developer Survey. 🔧 JetBrains continues to enhance the developer experience with its tools. #Python #JetBrains #ProgrammingCommunity #DataScience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new worst coder has entered the chat: vibe coding without code knowledge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4766/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4766/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving tech landscape, a new trend called &amp;ldquo;vibe coding&amp;rdquo; has emerged, allowing those without coding skills to create applications. This concept, popularized in early 2025, raises questions about its effectiveness and impact on junior developers. The author shares their experience building an app using the vibe coding tool, Bolt, during a Hackathon. While it was easy to start, the lack of technical knowledge revealed flaws in the final product. This highlights the potential limitations&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being unambiguous in what you want: the software engineer in a vibe coding world</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2095/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2095/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Quinn Slack, CEO of Sourcegraph, discusses the impact of AI coding tools on software engineering. He highlights the shift from syntax tasks to higher-level design and management roles for developers. AI&amp;rsquo;s integration into enterprises is set to enhance software development processes. Connect with Quinn on LinkedIn and X for more insights! #SoftwareEngineering #AI #Sourcegraph #TechTalks #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-pollination as a strategic advantage for forward-thinking organizations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2096/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2096/</guid>
      <description>Innovation is key for growing organizations, and fostering a culture of cross-pollination can enhance this. 🌱 By sharing knowledge across teams, companies can combat stagnation and encourage fresh ideas. Leaders play a vital role in creating an environment where employees feel safe to share and explore new concepts. 🤝 This approach not only boosts engagement but also helps teams understand how their work contributes to broader goals. #CrossPollination #Innovation #Teamwork #Leadership&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving into the results of the 2025 Developer Survey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2097/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2097/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting insights from the 2025 Developer Survey are here! Ryan and Eira speak with Erin Yepis from Stack Overflow about key findings. Notably, there is a decline in trust in AI tools among developers. The survey also highlights shifts in popular programming technologies and trends in salary growth for tech professionals. #DeveloperSurvey #TechTrends #AI #SalaryGrowth #ProgrammingInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do AI coding tools help with imposter syndrome or make it worse?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2098/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2098/</guid>
      <description>AI coding tools can influence imposter syndrome in developers in complex ways. While tools like Copilot and Codex may ease self-doubt by accelerating learning, they can also lead to overreliance, affecting code quality and understanding. The pressure to continually upskill with these tools can intensify anxiety for some developers. #ImposterSyndrome #AICoding #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTrends #ContinuousLearning 🤖📈🖥️</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The innovation, leadership, and team agility inside U.S. Bank’s cloud journey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2099/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2099/</guid>
      <description>🌐 In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, industry experts discuss U.S. Bank&amp;rsquo;s transition from traditional banking to a multi-cloud strategy. 💡 The bank is focused on innovation while maintaining compliance in a regulated environment. Key topics include team empowerment, collaboration, and cloud migration strategies. 🤝 Leaders highlight the significance of transparency and continuous communication in driving successful change. #CloudComputing #DigitalTransformation #BankingInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
