<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Webflow-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/webflow-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Webflow-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/webflow-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SoDA: The end of extraction: Building agencies for the age of intelligence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-21-14719/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-21-14719/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://webflow.com/blog/rss.xml&#34;&gt;Webflow Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://webflowmarketingmain.com/blog/soda-2026-end-of-extraction-building-agencies-for-the-age-of-intelligence&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an event registration system with Webflow and Mailchimp</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14629/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14629/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Looking to streamline your event registration process? This article details how to connect Webflow forms to Mailchimp. You can efficiently manage event sign-ups with tag segmentation and automated confirmation emails. Learn how to enhance your registration system for a smoother experience! #Webflow #Mailchimp #EventRegistration #Automation #TechTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build custom feedback portals with UserVoice API and Webflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14631/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14631/</guid>
      <description>🔧 Discover how to integrate UserVoice with Webflow to build custom feedback portals! The article outlines the use of a secure API proxy, OAuth 2.0, webhooks, and CMS syncing to enhance user engagement and feedback collection. This integration can streamline your feedback process effectively. #UserVoice #Webflow #FeedbackPortals #Integration #WebDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build scalable client campaign workflows in Webflow with HubSpot integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14628/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14628/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how to enhance your client campaign workflows! This article explains how to connect Webflow forms to HubSpot CRM, enabling you to build scalable and efficient processes. Learn the steps to streamline your marketing efforts and improve client management. #Webflow #HubSpot #MarketingAutomation #ClientManagement #WorkflowOptimization</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embed UserVoice feedback widgets in Webflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14630/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14630/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how to enhance your Webflow projects by embedding UserVoice feedback widgets! This guide explains the process of using JavaScript for seamless client-side feedback and idea voting. It&amp;rsquo;s a practical way to engage your users and gather valuable insights. Learn the steps and elevate user interaction! 🗳️💻 #Webflow #UserFeedback #JavaScript #WebDevelopment #UserVoice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to implement Hotjar analytics on Webflow e-commerce sites</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14638/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14638/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of your Webflow e-commerce site by implementing Hotjar analytics. 📊 This article guides you through using session recordings, heatmaps, and conversion funnels to understand user behavior and improve site performance. Discover how these tools can enhance your customer experience and drive sales. #Webflow #Hotjar #Ecommerce #Analytics #UserExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How developers are building in Webflow with code components</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14575/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14575/</guid>
      <description>Discover how developers are leveraging code components in Webflow to create unique custom React experiences. From integrating 3D effects to designing audio players, the possibilities are expanding. These tools enable more dynamic web applications and enhance user interaction. Explore the innovative ways developers are pushing boundaries! 🌐💻✨ #Webflow #React #WebDevelopment #CodeComponents #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Es oficial: Webflow llega a la Argentina</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14511/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14511/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Webflow has officially launched in Argentina! 🇦🇷 This platform aims to empower users to build and design websites with ease. The launch signals exciting opportunities for creativity and innovation within the region. Stay tuned for more updates as Webflow looks forward to collaborating with the local community! #Webflow #Argentina #WebDesign #Innovation #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s official: Webflow is opening an office in Argentina</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14512/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14512/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news from Webflow! We are pleased to share that Webflow is opening a new office in Buenos Aires, Argentina. This location will serve as a hub for engineers, designers, and the wider community. Stay tuned for more updates on how we aim to foster collaboration and innovation in this vibrant city! 🌍✨ #Webflow #BuenosAires #OfficeOpening #Community #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the prompt: Why successful AI localization requires a strategy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14454/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14454/</guid>
      <description>Successful AI localization goes beyond simply using tools as they come. To achieve accurate and scalable multilingual content, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to develop a strategic approach. This ensures that your AI solutions effectively meet specific localization needs. Explore how to enhance your Webflow content with tailored AI strategies. 🌍🤖 #AILocalization #Webflow #ContentStrategy #MultilingualContent #DigitalMarketing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the team: How curiosity and community brought Jon Saxton to Webflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-09-14389/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-09-14389/</guid>
      <description>Meet Jon Saxton, a Senior Solutions Architect at Webflow. His journey from a dedicated Webflow builder to a key team member highlights the importance of curiosity and community. In his story, Jon emphasizes how these values shaped his professional path and led him to join the Webflow team. 🌟 Discover more about his experiences and insights in the full article! #Webflow #TeamSpotlight #Curiosity #Community #CareerJourney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building brand-aware global websites: LILT’s enterprise AI strategy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14273/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14273/</guid>
      <description>LILT is revolutionizing how Webflow marketers approach global revenue. 🌍 By combining custom AI with expert verification, they ensure that brand integrity is maintained while expanding reach. This approach empowers marketers to effectively build brand-aware global websites. Learn more about LILT&amp;rsquo;s enterprise AI strategy! 🤖💼 #GlobalMarketing #AI #BrandIntegrity #Webflow #DigitalStrategy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expose your Webflow CMS with a simple API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14304/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14304/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of your Webflow projects! The article discusses how the integration of Webflow Cloud with the CMS API allows developers to share Webflow content through a tailored API. This combination enhances flexibility and accessibility for developers looking to customize their content sharing. Explore new possibilities for your projects! 🌐✨ #Webflow #CMS #APIDevelopment #WebDevelopment #TechTutorial</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 web design trends to watch in 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14138/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14138/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting changes are on the horizon for web design in 2026! Key trends include innovative text effects and a vibrant use of color. The influence of AI is reshaping design capabilities, leading to heightened audience expectations. Stay ahead of the curve and explore these emerging trends! 🎨✨ #WebDesign #DesignTrends #AI #2026Trends #DigitalInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AEO voices to watch in 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13972/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13972/</guid>
      <description>Discover the AEO&amp;rsquo;s influential voices to watch in 2026! 📢 This article highlights key figures shaping the marketing landscape. These voices offer valuable insights and trends that every marketer should consider. Stay informed and connected with these leaders as they guide the industry forward. #MarketingTrends #AEO #InfluentialVoices #2026Insights #MarketingLeadership</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the 2025 Webflow Awards winners</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9655/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9655/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Announcing the 2025 Webflow Awards winners! This annual event celebrates the creativity and innovation within the Webflow community. The awards highlight individuals and organizations making significant contributions to web experiences. 🏆 Community Educator of the Year: Timothy Ricks, known for his impactful educational resources. 🏆 Community Creator of the Year: Ilja van Eck, recognized for his award-winning projects and contributions to the design community. Explore the full list of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How leading agencies are navigating the new era of brand storytelling</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9557/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9557/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Modern businesses face a challenge: delivering content across diverse platforms. A recent panel with industry leaders explored this evolving landscape of brand storytelling. Key insights included the necessity of creating modular content systems and mapping content types to audience preferences. Agencies must shift to treat content as integral to brand identity. Collaboration is also changing, with agencies becoming creative partners to clients, ensuring mutual respect and clear roles for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Motion design isn’t just eye candy; it’s UX infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9527/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9527/</guid>
      <description>Motion design is transforming user experience (UX) by enhancing both function and feel. Today’s web users expect dynamic, responsive interfaces. Motion design helps communicate messages quickly, making interactions clearer and more engaging. For instance, using scroll-triggered animations can effectively highlight key features. Recent studies emphasize that smooth animations enhance user satisfaction and decision-making. Tools like LottieFiles for Webflow simplify the integration of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Form follows function: Building resilient form submissions at scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9476/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9476/</guid>
      <description>Webflow is enhancing its system resiliency to ensure reliable form submissions, crucial for businesses. Key features include: - &lt;strong&gt;Durability&lt;/strong&gt;: Submissions are preserved even during database failures. - &lt;strong&gt;Non-blocking&lt;/strong&gt;: Recovery mechanisms do not slow down requests. - &lt;strong&gt;Idempotent&lt;/strong&gt;: Submissions can be safely replayed without duplicates. The process involves write-ahead backups stored in Amazon S3, allowing for both targeted and global replay of submissions during outages. #Webflow&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing trust, access, and control on Webflow Enterprise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9433/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9433/</guid>
      <description>Webflow Enterprise addresses the challenges of managing access in a world of numerous applications. With enterprises handling over 300 apps, effective Identity and Access Management (IAM) is crucial to prevent security risks. Webflow integrates IAM into its platform, ensuring secure user onboarding, authentication, and access monitoring. This holistic approach allows teams to collaborate freely while maintaining IT oversight and compliance. Automated provisioning and deprovisioning support&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading design through disruption: A conversation with Sara Vienna, Chief Design Officer at Metalab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7793/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7793/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited to share insights from my conversation with Sara Vienna, Chief Design Officer at Metalab! Sara reflects on her journey from a cold email to leading a top design firm. She emphasizes flexibility and continuous improvement in a rapidly evolving tech landscape. AI is reshaping design, prompting a redefinition of craft that focuses on user needs over time spent. Client expectations have also shifted, with heightened pressure on businesses to adapt. #DesignLeadership #AIinDesign&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to win AEO with content</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7744/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7744/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The landscape of brand discovery is changing with AI-driven search. A recent Webflow study reveals only 25% of marketing professionals understand Answer Engine Optimization (AEO), despite 93% of CMOs recognizing its future importance. Focusing on four key pillars—content, technical, authority, and measurement—can help brands thrive. AEO emphasizes moving from keyword-centric content to personalized answers that meet buyer needs. This evolution is crucial for long-term visibility and growth&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing The Webflow Way: Best practices to help you build with confidence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7689/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7689/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing The Webflow Way! This new resource offers best practices to help teams maximize their use of the Webflow platform. It focuses on six key areas: Design Systems, CMS, SEO, Localization, Optimization, and Collaboration. These guidelines aim to enhance efficiency, improve site performance, and support global reach. Perfect for teams striving to achieve ambitious goals! 🔗 Explore the Webflow Way today! #Webflow #BestPractices #WebDevelopment #DigitalMarketing #Collaboration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing The Webflow Way: Best practices to help you build with confidence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7709/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7709/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing The Webflow Way! This new resource offers best practices to enhance your experience on the Webflow platform. It focuses on key areas: Design Systems, CMS, SEO, Localization, Optimization, and Collaboration. Learn how to build scalable, high-performing web experiences that drive results for your business. 🔗 Explore the Webflow Way today! #Webflow #BestPractices #WebDesign #Marketing #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROI of websites: Metrics that matter to the C-suite</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7403/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7403/</guid>
      <description>Understanding the ROI of websites is crucial for marketing leaders. While they focus on metrics like conversion and engagement, C-suite executives prioritize ROI and revenue impact. Traditional metrics often fall short, as they do not align with executive goals. For effective buy-in, it’s essential to connect website performance to business outcomes. Key metrics such as conversion rate, customer acquisition cost, and customer lifetime value resonate with executives, highlighting the real&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to choose between a blog, resource center, and content hub for maximum impact</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7216/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7216/</guid>
      <description>Choosing the right content structure is crucial for business success. 📊 Many companies lack a clear content strategy, leading to poor user experiences and lost sales. Research shows that 82% of consumers abandon purchases due to this issue. Understanding the differences between blogs, resource centers, and content hubs can enhance lead generation and SEO. A blog focuses on timely, engaging content, while a resource center offers actionable resources. Content hubs provide organized, evergreen&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Color and typography pairings: A designer’s cheatsheet</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5650/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5650/</guid>
      <description>Designing an effective website starts with two key elements: color and typography. 🎨✍️ These choices are interconnected and can significantly impact user perception and emotional response. Colors elicit feelings quickly, while typography conveys your brand&amp;rsquo;s personality. For instance, finance sites use deep blues and clean fonts to communicate trust, while creative agencies opt for bold colors and unique typefaces. Accessibility is crucial; poor contrast can hinder readability for users with&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A look at our roadmap: shipping for resiliency, security, and performance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5652/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5652/</guid>
      <description>🚀 We&amp;rsquo;re committed to enhancing Webflow&amp;rsquo;s platform for our users. Following a recent incident, we&amp;rsquo;ve taken steps to improve resiliency, security, and performance. Key investments are underway to strengthen our systems and ensure reliability. 🌐 Our hosting now leverages Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s global network, enhancing speed and protection against threats. 🔧 Additionally, we&amp;rsquo;re re-architecting our CMS to better meet the growing needs of our users. Stay tuned for more updates! #Webflow #TechUpdates #CMS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP servers worth knowing if you&#39;re building with AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5651/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5651/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exploring MCP servers is essential for AI development! These servers help integrate structured context into AI models, crucial for building advanced tools like agents and code assistants. The article highlights various MCP servers, especially Context7, which is optimized for codebases and offers access to numerous open-source libraries. Cursor IDE makes integration straightforward, enhancing workflow efficiency across platforms. For developers, understanding these tools can streamline&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A data-driven approach to building better user journeys with Webflow Analyze</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5653/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5653/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of your website with Webflow Analyze! 🌐 This tool empowers web teams to access user behavior data directly within their design workflow. Understanding user journeys—from first click to conversion—can lead to significant increases in demo requests and revenue. Learn how to analyze visitor touchpoints to enhance engagement and reduce bounce rates. Discover a three-step roadmap for optimizing user journeys and driving better results. 📈 #WebDesign #UserExperience #DataDriven&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The marketer’s guide to LLM search terms: From SEO to AEO</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5654/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5654/</guid>
      <description>SEO strategies are evolving due to the rise of AI in search. 🌐 Today, 55% of users rely on AI search for general research, often receiving direct answers on results pages without visiting websites. Marketers need to adapt by understanding new terms like AIO, GEO, and LLMs, which shape this AI-first search landscape. Learn how to optimize your content for a changing digital environment. 📊✨ #DigitalMarketing #SEO #AI #SearchTrends #MarketingStrategy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July 28 Incident report: Service availability disruption</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5655/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5655/</guid>
      <description>Webflow faced service disruptions from July 28-31, impacting the Designer, Dashboard, Marketplace, and user sign-ups. While hosted sites remained operational, core functionalities were affected. The incident involved multiple phases of malicious attacks leading to elevated latency and outages. Mitigation efforts included firewall protections and database optimizations. Full stability was restored through configuration changes and adopting a more efficient CPU architecture. For a deeper&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webflow’s availability incident: what we got wrong and what we’re changing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5656/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5656/</guid>
      <description>Webflow faced a significant service disruption on July 28, caused by a malicious attack that affected customer access. The team worked quickly to stabilize the platform. CEO&amp;rsquo;s reflections highlight shortcomings in communication and support during this incident. Immediate changes include enhanced monitoring, improved infrastructure, and proactive customer updates. Webflow is committed to making the platform more reliable and transparent moving forward. #Webflow #ServiceUpdate #CustomerSupport&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
