<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Vercel-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/vercel-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Vercel-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/vercel-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cline now runs on Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13694/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13694/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/atom&#34;&gt;Vercel Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/blog/cline-on-ai-gateway&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Export Observability query results to CSV or JSON</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13696/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13696/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/atom&#34;&gt;Vercel Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/changelog/export-observability-query-results-to-csv-or-json&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Knowledge Base</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13695/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13695/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/atom&#34;&gt;Vercel Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/changelog/vercel-knowledge-base&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build smarter workflows with Notion and v0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13698/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13698/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/atom&#34;&gt;Vercel Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/blog/build-smarter-workflows-with-notion-and-v0&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to prompt v0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13697/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13697/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/atom&#34;&gt;Vercel Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/blog/how-to-prompt-v0&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust runtime now in public beta for Vercel Functions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13561/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13561/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Vercel! The Rust runtime is now in public beta, enhancing Vercel Functions with native support. This update includes features like HTTP response streaming and an increased environment variable limit from 6KB to 64KB. Deployments seamlessly integrate with Vercel&amp;rsquo;s logging and monitoring systems. To get started, check out the Rust Hello World and Rust Axum starter templates! #Vercel #Rust #WebDevelopment #Serverless #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT 5.1 Codex Max now available on Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13508/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13508/</guid>
      <description>🚀 OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s GPT-5.1 Codex Max is now available through Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway! This latest model allows users to access advanced Codex capabilities without needing additional provider accounts. It&amp;rsquo;s designed for software engineering tasks, offering improved speed and efficiency. With features like multi-context operation and long-term reasoning, it&amp;rsquo;s optimized for sustained coding sessions. The AI Gateway also provides a unified API for model management and performance enhancements. Explore more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Platform Elements</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13506/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13506/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Vercel for Platforms! You can now enhance your application with prebuilt UI blocks and actions. This new library includes production-ready shadcn/ui components designed for quick launches and upgrades. Key features include domain configuration, deployment interfaces, and ownership verification. You can easily install these components using the Vercel Platforms CLI. Start building today with our Quickstart guide for Multi-Tenant or Multi-Project platforms! #Vercel #WebDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Vercel for Platforms</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13507/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13507/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Vercel! Introducing Vercel for Platforms, a new product that simplifies building and managing customer projects. Two modes are available: Multi-Tenant for a single codebase serving multiple customers, and Multi-Project for separate projects per customer. Key features include domain support, automatic routing, and easy project creation with the Vercel SDK. Start building today with the Quickstart guide! #Vercel #WebDevelopment #Platforms #TechNews #SoftwareEngineering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New deployments of vulnerable Next.js applications are now blocked by default</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13516/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important update for Next.js users! 🚨 New deployments with vulnerable versions of Next.js (CVE-2025-66478) will now be blocked by default on Vercel. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to upgrade to a patched version to ensure your application’s security. If needed, this automatic protection can be disabled by setting the environment variable DANGEROUSLY_DEPLOY_VULNERABLE_CVE_2025_66478=1. Stay safe and informed! 🔒✨ #NextJS #Vercel #CyberSecurity #WebDevelopment #Updates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources for protecting against &#39;React2Shell&#39;</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13514/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13514/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New security alert! As of December 4, proof-of-concept exploits for CVE-2025-55182 are now publicly available. This vulnerability affects all Next.js apps from versions 15.0.0 to 16.0.6. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial for developers to assess their applications and implement necessary protections. Stay informed and secure! 🔒💻 #Cybersecurity #NextJS #VulnerabilityAlert #CVE2025 #DevCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rewrites and redirects now available in runtime logs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13515/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13515/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has introduced a new feature for users! You can now access requests for rewrites and redirects directly in the Vercel dashboard&amp;rsquo;s runtime logs. By default, these requests are filtered out, but you can easily view them by using the Resource dropdown. - &lt;strong&gt;Rewrites&lt;/strong&gt;: Displays the destination of the rewrite. - &lt;strong&gt;Redirects&lt;/strong&gt;: Shows the redirect status code and location. This feature is available to all users. Explore it today! #Vercel #WebDevelopment #RuntimeLogs #TechUpdates&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Domains must now be managed at the team level</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13467/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13467/</guid>
      <description>🔄 Important Update for Domain Management! Domains must now be managed at the team level instead of the account level. This change aims to enhance access control and collaboration while simplifying billing processes. Existing account-level domains will continue to function normally. However, any modifications will require transferring the domain to a designated team. When managing your account-level domain, you will now be prompted to select a team for the transfer. All related project&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New npm package for automatic recovery of broken streaming markdown</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13399/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13399/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Remend, a new npm package for seamless Markdown recovery! This standalone library enhances any application by intelligently handling incomplete Markdown syntax. It detects and completes unterminated blocks, ensuring clean rendering during streaming. Remend works with any Markdown renderer and has proven effective in production AI applications. Get started with Remend today! #Markdown #WebDevelopment #AI #npm #Remend</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nova 2 Lite now available on Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13411/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13411/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news! Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Nova 2 Lite is now accessible through Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway without needing other provider accounts. This reasoning model can handle text, images, and videos to generate text outputs. To use it, simply set the model to amazon/nova-2-lite in the AI SDK. Note that reasoning is disabled by default but can be enabled with specific settings. The AI Gateway offers a unified API for model calls, usage tracking, and performance optimizations. Explore more in the model&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary of CVE-2025-55182</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13385/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13385/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A critical vulnerability, CVE-2025-55182, has been discovered in React Server Components affecting versions 19.0 to 19.2.0. This issue can lead to remote code execution through specially crafted requests. 🛡️ Projects hosted on Vercel have protections in place, but upgrading to patched versions is strongly recommended. 🔧 Users should update to React 19.0.1, 19.1.2, or 19.2.1, and Next.js versions 15.0.5 or later. #CyberSecurity #React #NextJS #Vulnerability #SoftwareUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Agent can now install Web Analytics and Speed insights for you</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13279/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13279/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel Agent now simplifies adding Web Analytics and Speed Insights to your projects using AI! To get started, navigate to your Vercel dashboard, enable the feature, and let the agent handle the installation. It analyzes your project, installs the necessary packages, and creates a pull request for your review. Once merged, tracking begins automatically. This feature is in Public Beta for all teams. 🌐✨ #WebAnalytics #SpeedInsights #Vercel #AI #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Billions of requests: Black Friday-Cyber Monday 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13283/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13283/</guid>
      <description>Black Friday and Cyber Monday 2025 saw over 115.8 billion requests, marking a 33.6% increase from last year. 📈 Vercel&amp;rsquo;s platform maintained performance during this busy weekend, adapting seamlessly to the high traffic without manual adjustments. Traffic patterns showed a dip on Thanksgiving, a surge on Black Friday, and sustained activity through Cyber Monday. 🌐 #BlackFriday #CyberMonday #Ecommerce #TrafficAnalytics #Vercel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy steps are now up to 21% faster</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13374/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13374/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Good news for developers! The deploy step is now, on average, 17% faster. This means a reduction of 1.67 seconds in total time to go live. Projects with many functions may experience even larger gains, saving up to 2.8 seconds. This improvement is due to reduced idle time and better concurrency during the deploy phase. For more details, check out the documentation! 📄✨ #FasterDeploys #Vercel #WebDevelopment #TechUpdates #Efficiency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investing in the Python ecosystem</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13268/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13268/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the tech world! The Gel Data team is joining Vercel to enhance the Python ecosystem. This collaboration will be led by notable Python core developer Yury Selivanov and contributor Elvis Pranskevichus. Their goal is to provide top-notch support for Python on the AI Cloud. Stay tuned for more updates! #Python #TechNews #Vercel #AI #Collaboration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mistral Large 3 now available on Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13280/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13280/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Mistral&amp;rsquo;s latest model, Mistral Large 3, is now available on Vercel AI Gateway. This model features a sparse mixture-of-experts architecture with 41B active parameters and is the first of its kind since the Mixtral series. Accessing it requires no additional provider accounts; simply set the model to mistral/mistral-large-3 in the AI SDK. Explore built-in observability and intelligent routing with the AI Gateway. Check out the docs and model playground for more details! 📊🔧&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Agent can now install Web Analytics and Speed insights for you</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13279/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13279/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel Agent now simplifies adding Web Analytics and Speed Insights to your projects using AI! To get started, navigate to your Vercel dashboard, enable the feature, and let the agent handle the installation. It analyzes your project, installs the necessary packages, and creates a pull request for your review. Once merged, tracking begins automatically. This feature is in Public Beta for all teams. 🌐✨ #WebAnalytics #SpeedInsights #Vercel #AI #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Databases coming to the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13187/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13187/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! AWS is expanding its partnership with Vercel. Starting December 15th, Aurora PostgreSQL, Amazon DynamoDB, and Aurora DSQL will be available as native integrations in the Vercel Marketplace. These integrations aim to streamline the development process, allowing developers to focus on building products without worrying about infrastructure setup. #AWS #Vercel #WebDevelopment #CloudComputing #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek V3.2 models now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13204/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13204/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI developers! DeepSeek&amp;rsquo;s latest models, V3.2 and V3.2 Speciale, are now available through Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway. No additional provider accounts are needed to access them. DeepSeek V3.2 supports combined thinking and tool use, while V3.2 Speciale is tailored for complex tasks but requires more tokens. Explore the unified API for model calls, usage tracking, and performance optimizations. Check the docs and start using the models in the playground! #AI #DeepSeek #Vercel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek V3.2 models now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13208/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13208/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! DeepSeek V3.2 models are now accessible through Vercel AI Gateway without additional provider accounts. DeepSeek V3.2 offers combined thinking and tool use for various operations, while DeepSeek V3.2 Speciale focuses on high reasoning performance for complex tasks. To utilize these models, set the AI SDK accordingly. The AI Gateway also provides a unified API for tracking usage and optimizing performance. Explore the documentation and model leaderboard today! 📊✨ #DeepSeek&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Runtime Logs now appear in the dashboard 6x faster</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13162/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13162/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Vercel users! Runtime Logs now load up to 6x faster in the dashboard. You can see 90% of log entries within just 5 seconds of execution. Filtering and querying are also enhanced, with 80% of filter counts resolving in under 1 second. This makes Live Mode a more efficient experience. #Vercel #RuntimeLogs #PerformanceUpgrade #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trinity Mini model now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13207/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13207/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Arcee AI&amp;rsquo;s Trinity Mini model is now accessible through Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway. This model features 26B parameters, with 3B active, and offers an open weight MoE reasoning capability. No additional provider accounts are needed to start using it! Simply set the model to arcee-ai/trinity-mini in the AI SDK. The AI Gateway also provides a unified API for usage tracking, cost management, and performance optimizations. Explore the documentation, check the AI Gateway model&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image-only models available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13132/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13132/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Vercel! You can now access image-only models through the AI Gateway without needing any additional provider accounts. These models are designed exclusively for image generation, including options like FLUX and Google’s Imagen. To utilize them, simply set the model to the specified slug in the AI SDK. The AI Gateway also offers a unified API for tracking usage, cost, and performance. Check out the documentation for more details or try the models in the playground! #Vercel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intellect-3 model from Prime Intellect AI available on the Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13086/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13086/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI enthusiasts! Prime Intellect AI&amp;rsquo;s latest model, Intellect-3, is now available on the Vercel AI Gateway. This open-source model features 106B parameters and excels in math, code, science, and reasoning benchmarks. Users can easily access it without needing additional provider accounts. For more details on using the model, visit the AI Gateway and explore its features. #AI #MachineLearning #OpenSource #Intellect3 #Vercel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sign in with Vercel now generally available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13070/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13070/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Sign in with Vercel is now available for all developers! You can easily integrate Vercel as a sign-in option for your apps right from the Vercel dashboard. This means no need to manage users or sign-in methods manually. 🔑 The feature supports OAuth and OpenID, allowing users to sign in with their existing Vercel accounts and access their info. Check out the example app to get started! #Vercel #WebDevelopment #OAuth #OpenID #DeveloperTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.fast, .you, .talk, and .to TLDs now available on Vercel Domains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13054/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13054/</guid>
      <description>Vercel Domains has expanded its offerings by adding new TLDs: .fast, .you, .talk, and .to. These domains are now available for purchase at vercel.com/domains. Users can also transfer existing domains with these TLDs to the Vercel platform for streamlined integration with their projects. Explore the new options today! 🌐✨ #Vercel #Domains #WebDevelopment #TLDs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLUX.2 Pro image model is now available on Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13037/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13037/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! The FLUX.2 Pro image model from Black Forest Labs is now available on Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway. No additional provider accounts are needed for access. This model delivers higher-resolution outputs (up to 4MP) and enhanced visual intelligence with features like multi-reference inputs and precise color matching. FLUX.2 Pro stands out as a pure image-focused model, differing from existing multimodal LLMs. To start using it, simply set the model to bfl/flux-2-pro in the AI SDK. For&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node.js 24 LTS is now generally available for builds and functions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13036/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13036/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Node.js version 24 is now available for builds and functions! To use it, navigate to Project Settings -&amp;gt; Build and Deployment -&amp;gt; Node.js Version and select 24.x. This is the default for new projects. Key updates include: - &lt;strong&gt;V8 Engine Upgrade&lt;/strong&gt;: Improved performance and new features like Float16Array. - &lt;strong&gt;URLPattern API&lt;/strong&gt;: Simplifies URL routing. - &lt;strong&gt;Undici v7&lt;/strong&gt;: Enhanced fetch API for better HTTP performance. - &lt;strong&gt;npm v11&lt;/strong&gt;: Updated for better compatibility with modern packages. For more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Opus 4.5 now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13000/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13000/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Anthropic&amp;rsquo;s Claude Opus 4.5 is now available through Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway without the need for additional provider accounts. This model enhances reasoning and problem-solving capabilities, excelling in coding tasks and agentic workflows. It effectively utilizes context and external memory files, making it ideal for frontend development. To get started, use the model identifier &amp;ldquo;anthropic/claude-opus-4.5&amp;rdquo; in the AI SDK. The new effort parameter allows for control over token&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Convex joins the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13013/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13013/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Convex is now part of the Vercel Marketplace. You can easily add a real-time backend to your Vercel projects directly from the dashboard. This integration allows you to provision a Convex project, manage accounts, and enjoy seamless data sync—all in one place. Start building with a fully connected backend in just a few clicks! #Convex #Vercel #WebDevelopment #RealTimeData #DevTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployments can now require cryptographically-verified commits</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13012/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Vercel introduces commit verification for deployments! Now, you can enhance your project security by requiring cryptographically-verified commits from GitHub before they are deployed. To enable this feature, simply adjust your project settings for GitHub-connected projects. Learn more about commit signing and verification in our documentation. #Vercel #WebDevelopment #GitHub #Security #DevOps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we built the v0 iOS app</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13020/</guid>
      <description>🚀 We are excited to announce the release of v0 for iOS, Vercel’s first mobile app! This project marked a new chapter for us as we ventured into native app development. Our aim was to create an app worthy of an Apple Design Award. Through numerous iterations and experiments with various tech stacks and UI patterns, we refined our approach before launching the public beta. #iOSApp #Vercel #AppDevelopment #TechInnovation #MobileApp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open your Vercel dashboard from the Vercel CLI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13002/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13002/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Vercel users! You can now open your current project directly from the Vercel CLI using the command &lt;code&gt;vercel open&lt;/code&gt;. This feature simplifies access to your project without navigating through your browser. To use this, make sure to update to version 48.10.0 or newer with &lt;code&gt;npm i -g vercel&lt;/code&gt;. For more details, check the documentation. #Vercel #WebDevelopment #CommandLine #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security through design: Creating the improved Firewall experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13011/</guid>
      <description>🔒 At Vercel, we prioritize intuitive security that enhances user experience. The redesigned Vercel Firewall aims to eliminate the tradeoff between security and shipping speed. A clear and useful interface encourages teams to actively use security tools instead of leaving them in passive modes. Explore how this new UI boosts confidence in app resilience against attacks. #CyberSecurity #UserExperience #Vercel #Firewall #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shai-Hulud 2.0 Supply Chain Compromise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13014/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A recent security breach involved multiple npm packages being compromised through account takeover. A malicious actor added a stealthy loader to these packages, targeting the Bun runtime. 🔍 Vercel has confirmed that their environment remains secure and no internal systems were affected. They are resetting the cache for projects using the vulnerable packages. 📞 Affected customers are being notified with specific mitigation steps. Updates will be provided as the investigation continues&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamdown 1.6 is now available to run faster and ship less code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13001/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13001/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel Streamdown 1.6 is here with key updates to enhance performance and reduce code size. Key improvements include memoization, LRU caching, and optimized string operations. Features like Code Blocks, Mermaid, and Math components are now lazy-loaded for efficiency. Static Mode allows markdown rendering without streaming, making it suitable for blogs. The code highlighting system has been revamped for better performance. Update now with &lt;code&gt;npm i streamdown@latest&lt;/code&gt;! #Vercel #Streamdown&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Workflow Builder: Build your own workflow automation platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13010/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Today marks the launch of Workflow Builder, an open-source visual automation platform. It includes a visual editor, an execution engine, and the necessary infrastructure to create custom workflow automation tools. You can deploy it to Vercel and tailor it to your specific needs. Explore the possibilities! #WorkflowAutomation #OpenSource #TechInnovation #AutomationTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now configure advanced sampling rules for Vercel Drains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13015/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Vercel users! You can now set advanced sampling rules when exporting data to third-party observability tools with Vercel Drains. This feature allows for specific sampling rates based on environments and path prefixes, enhancing cost management. Vercel Drains is available for Pro and Enterprise teams, enabling better control over logs and traces. #Vercel #DataManagement #Observability #TechUpdate #SoftwareTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-driving infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12939/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12939/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI is revolutionizing code management! Vercel is developing self-driving infrastructure that autonomously handles production operations. This innovation aims to enhance application code with real-world insights and adapt to the unpredictable nature of production environments. The goal is for developers to focus on intent rather than infrastructure, allowing ops teams to establish principles over configurations. #SelfDrivingTech #AI #Vercel #CloudComputing #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Agent investigations now included in Observability Plus</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12940/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12940/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has enhanced its Observability Plus service by including Vercel Agent investigations at no extra cost. This addition offers 10 investigations per billing cycle. 🔍 These investigations help teams quickly diagnose incidents by running automatically on error alerts. They identify root causes and suggest remediation steps. 💼 Currently in public beta for Pro and Enterprise teams, Vercel Agent aims to improve incident response. Learn more about this feature! #Vercel #Observability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Open Source Program: Fall 2025 cohort</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12953/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12953/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news from Vercel! The Fall 2025 cohort of the Open Source Program is here. This initiative supports open-source maintainers with resources, credits, and guidance to enhance their projects. The program showcases innovative work in AI-native applications, developer infrastructure, and more. Discover the talented creators and their amazing projects today! 🚀💻 #OpenSource #Vercel #Innovation #TechCommunity #Fall2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok 4.1 Fast models now available on Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12923/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12923/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! xAI’s Grok 4.1 Fast models are now available on Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway! You can access Grok 4.1 Fast Reasoning and Fast Non-Reasoning without needing additional provider accounts. These models feature a 2M context window, ideal for tool calling. Grok 4.1 Fast Reasoning focuses on structured reasoning, while Fast Non-Reasoning prioritizes speed. Explore the unified API for model calls, usage tracking, and performance optimizations. Check out the AI Gateway model leaderboard and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved analytics experience now available on the Vercel Firewall</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12906/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12906/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Exciting updates are here for the Vercel Firewall! The improved UI enhances application security monitoring and analysis. Key features include a consolidated Overview page for DDoS attacks and a new Traffic page for detailed traffic analysis. Users can now easily write custom rules and queries for streamlined actions and insights. Explore these updates in the Firewall tab on your project! #Vercel #CyberSecurity #AppSecurity #Firewall #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nano Banana Pro (Gemini 3 Pro Image) now available in the AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12898/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12898/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! The Nano Banana Pro (Gemini 3 Pro Image) is now available through Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway. This advanced image model offers enhanced features for professional and creative tasks, including diagram generation with accurate labeling and real-time web search integration. Users can access higher resolution images and manage multi-image inputs for effective compositing. To get started, set the model to google/gemini-3-pro-image in the AI SDK. Explore the AI Gateway docs for examples&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can now invalidate the CDN cache by providing a source image</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12919/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12919/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has introduced a new feature for CDN cache management! You can now invalidate the cache by providing a source image. This means all transformed images from that source will be marked stale, ensuring seamless updates without impacting user experience. Options for invalidation include Dashboard Settings, Vercel CLI, Function API, and REST API. Note: Deleting a source image may increase latency and could lead to downtime if the origin is unresponsive. This feature is available on all&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini 3 Pro now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12776/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12776/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Google’s Gemini 3 Pro is now accessible through Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway without needing additional provider accounts. This advanced model excels in reasoning and can handle complex tasks like multi-step function calling and instruction following. To use it, specify the model as google/gemini-3.0-pro-preview in the AI SDK. AI Gateway also offers a unified API for model management, usage tracking, and performance optimizations. Learn more about AI Gateway and its features! 🌐✨&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel collaborates with Google for Gemini 3 Pro Preview launch</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12764/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12764/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Vercel has launched the Gemini 3 Pro Preview in collaboration with Google. Now available through the Vercel AI Gateway and on v0.app, this model has been tested across various platforms. It demonstrates significant improvements in coding, multimodal reasoning, and instruction following. Gemini 3 Pro shows nearly a 17% increase in correctness compared to its predecessor, ranking it among the top models in performance. #Vercel #Google #Gemini3 #AI #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support for Elysia</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12218/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12218/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Elysia, the ergonomic TypeScript framework, is now instantly deployable on Vercel! When you deploy, Vercel automatically optimizes resources for Elysia. By default, it runs on Node, but you can choose the Bun runtime easily. Vercel’s Fluid compute ensures you only pay for active CPU time. Check out the documentation for more details! 📚💻 #Elysia #Vercel #TypeScript #WebDevelopment #Deployment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel now supports Build Commands for FastAPI and Flask</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12777/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12777/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has introduced Build Commands for FastAPI and Flask, enhancing deployment options for Python projects. Users can now define Build Commands in the project Settings dashboard or within the [tool.vercel.scripts] section of their pyproject.toml file. This script executes after dependency installation and before application deployment. Learn more about these updates and streamline your Python deployments! #Vercel #FastAPI #Flask #Python #WebDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk redirects are now generally available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12184/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12184/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has introduced bulk redirects, enabling up to one million static URL redirects per project. This feature supports CSV and JSON formats, simplifying large-scale migrations and fixing broken links. To implement, set the bulkRedirectsPath in your vercel.json for automatic imports at build time. Available for Pro and Enterprise users, with options for additional capacity. #Vercel #WebDevelopment #URLRedirects #TechUpdate #ProFeatures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT 5.1 Codex models now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12183/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12183/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s GPT-5.1 Codex models are now accessible via Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway. This includes both GPT-5.1 Codex and GPT-5.1 Codex mini, optimized for complex coding tasks. 🌐 The AI Gateway offers a streamlined API for model usage, tracking, and performance enhancements. It features built-in observability and supports custom key integration. 🔗 Explore the AI Gateway, view the model leaderboard, or test it out in the playground. #OpenAI #Vercel #AI #Coding #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT 5.1 models now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12149/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12149/</guid>
      <description>🚀 OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s latest models, GPT-5.1 Instant and GPT-5.1 Thinking, are now available via Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway. GPT-5.1 Instant enhances instruction following and provides conversational responses. Meanwhile, GPT-5.1 Thinking focuses on performance tuning for various task complexities. The AI Gateway simplifies model access with a unified API, tracking usage, and performance optimizations. Explore more about AI Gateway and try it out! 🌐✨ #OpenAI #AIModels #Vercel #GPT5 #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rollbar joins the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12072/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12072/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Rollbar is now integrated into the Vercel Marketplace! This new feature enables real-time error monitoring and code observability within your Vercel workflow. Developers can easily detect, track, and resolve issues linked to specific releases and commits, enhancing production confidence. In just a few clicks, you can manage accounts, connect projects, and align environments for clearer stack traces. Discover more about this integration today! 🔧💻 #Rollbar #Vercel #ErrorMonitoring #DevOps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Model fallbacks now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12075/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12075/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway now features model fallbacks! This enhancement provides a safety net when primary models fail or are unavailable. Fallbacks can handle errors and capability mismatches, ensuring requests are processed smoothly. Requests will be billed based on the model that succeeds, and users can specify their fallback options in provider settings. The AI Gateway also offers built-in observability and supports OpenAI-compatible APIs. #Vercel #AIGateway #ModelFallbacks #TechUpdates #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support for TanStack Start</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12074/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12074/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel now supports TanStack Start applications, enhancing deployment for full-stack projects with TanStack Router. To get started, create a new TanStack Start app or simply add nitro() to your vite.config.ts. Enjoy automatic scaling with Active CPU pricing, so you only pay for what you use. Learn more in the TanStack Start documentation! 📖💻 #TanStack #Vercel #WebDevelopment #React #SolidJS</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel: The anti-vendor-lock-in cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12073/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12073/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Vercel offers a solution to vendor lock-in in cloud platforms by allowing developers to focus on their framework rather than specific vendor tools. Unlike other platforms that require proprietary configurations, Vercel enables automatic infrastructure provisioning from your existing framework code. This approach promotes portability and empowers developers to choose their environment freely. Discover how Vercel is redefining cloud flexibility! #CloudComputing #DeveloperExperience #Vercel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI domain search now available via Vercel Domains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11914/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11914/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for domain seekers! Vercel has launched an AI-powered smart search for domain names. Simply press space in the search bar to enter this mode. You can click on a suggested domain to receive similar options and search across all supported TLDs. Try it out at vercel.com/domains! 🌐✨ #Vercel #DomainSearch #AIPowered #WebDevelopment #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Nous Research used BotID to block automated abuse at scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11912/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11912/</guid>
      <description>Nous Research recently offered their open-source language model, Hermes, for free, leading to a surge in automated abuse. 🤖 Within days, scripts created fake accounts to bypass rate limits, despite existing protections. This resulted in wasted resources and increased bills for identity verification. Moving forward, Nous plans to strengthen bot protection before offering free access again. #AI #Cybersecurity #NousResearch #BotProtection #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel now supports post-quantum cryptography</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11915/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11915/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Vercel enhances security with post-quantum cryptography for HTTPS connections. This update protects applications from future quantum computing threats. Current encryption methods may become vulnerable, but Vercel&amp;rsquo;s support ensures secure TLS handshakes without extra configuration or cost. Stay informed about encryption and secure deployments. #CyberSecurity #PostQuantum #Vercel #Encryption #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Sandbox CLI is now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11913/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11913/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel has launched the Sandbox CLI, enabling easy management of isolated compute environments. Key features include: - Support for Node.js and Python workloads - Command execution in existing sandboxes - File copying between local and remote setups - Sandbox management across projects - Workflow automation with authentication tokens Check the full reference in the Sandbox CLI docs! #Vercel #CLI #Developers #SoftwareDevelopment #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-48985: Input Validation Bypass on AI SDK</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11922/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11922/</guid>
      <description>🔒 A recent security vulnerability, CVE-2025-48985, was found in Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI SDK. This low-severity issue allowed possible bypass of filetype whitelists during file uploads. 🔧 The flaw stemmed from improper URL-to-data mapping in the SDK&amp;rsquo;s conversion pipeline. This could lead to attackers injecting arbitrary content. 📢 Vercel has addressed the issue in versions 5.0.52 and 6.0.0-beta.* Users are encouraged to upgrade to these versions for enhanced security. #Cybersecurity #Vercel #AI #TechNews&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-52662: XSS on Nuxt DevTools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11919/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11919/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A medium-severity security vulnerability, CVE-2025-52662, has been identified in Nuxt DevTools. This vulnerability allowed for potential remote code execution through XSS, leading to authentication token theft. The issue was fixed in version 2.6.4. Users are urged to upgrade to the latest version for security. For more details, check the official release. 🔒🛠️ #Nuxt #SecurityUpdate #XSS #CVE2025 #DevTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Edge Config reads and writes now billed per unit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11918/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11918/</guid>
      <description>📢 Important Update for Pro Plan Users! Edge Config Reads and Writes are transitioning to a per-unit billing system. This change means you&amp;rsquo;ll be billed based on your actual usage rather than a package. 🔹 New Rates: - Edge Config Reads: $0.000003 per read - Edge Config Writes: $0.01 per write This adjustment allows for smoother scaling across different team sizes and usage patterns. Learn more about how this impacts your billing and usage! #EdgeConfig #BillingUpdate #ProPlan #CloudServices&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Gateway runs on Fluid compute</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11917/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11917/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI Gateway is revolutionizing access to AI models! This Node.js service connects users to hundreds of AI models via one interface, processing billions of tokens daily. The key to its impressive scale lies in the innovative Fluid technology. Discover more about how AI Gateway works! #AIGateway #FluidCompute #NodeJS #AIModels #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonshot AI&#39;s Kimi K2 Thinking models are now available on Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11920/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11920/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Moonshot AI! The Kimi K2 Thinking models are now available through Vercel AI Gateway. Users can access Kimi K2 Thinking and Kimi K2 Thinking Turbo without needing additional provider accounts. Kimi K2 Thinking offers deep reasoning capabilities, while Kimi K2 Thinking Turbo is optimized for speed. Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway simplifies model access with a unified API, usage tracking, and performance optimizations. Explore more about the AI Gateway and its features today!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skew Protection max age now supports the full deployment lifetime</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11921/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11921/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! You can now set your project&amp;rsquo;s Skew Protection max age to last for the entire deployment lifetime. This update allows for more flexibility in managing your settings. The new max age can be configured to any duration that aligns with your Deployment Retention policy, removing previous limits of 12 hours for Pro and 7 days for Enterprise. Learn more about how to enable Skew Protection in your project! #SkewProtection #Deployment #TechUpdate #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What we learned building agents at Vercel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11916/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11916/</guid>
      <description>At Vercel, we&amp;rsquo;ve explored the potential of AI agents to boost productivity and improve outcomes in various business areas. 🤖 Companies are leveraging these agents for customer support, code reviews, and sales operations. The key is identifying the right problems AI can solve effectively and affordably. Through our journey, we developed a repeatable methodology to evaluate AI projects for substantial business impact. #AIAgents #Productivity #Vercel #Innovation #BusinessImpact</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build and deploy data applications on Snowflake with v0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11832/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11832/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! v0 now integrates with Snowflake, allowing you to connect and build data-driven Next.js applications seamlessly. You can ask questions about your data, while Vercel manages application and authentication securely. The compute runs on Snowflake’s platform, ensuring data stays protected. Join the waitlist for testing updates! #DataApplications #Snowflake #NextJS #Vercel #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Route build traffic through Static IPs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11841/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11841/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New feature alert! You can now route build traffic through Static IPs. To enable this, navigate to Project Settings → Connectivity and toggle &amp;ldquo;Use static IPs for builds.&amp;rdquo; By default, this setting is off. When activated, both build and function traffic will use Static IPs and contribute to Private Data Transfer usage. This feature is available to all teams using Static IPs. #StaticIPs #BuildTraffic #ProjectSettings #TechUpdate #API</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redirects and Rewrites now available in Observability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11679/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11679/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Improved observability features are now available for all Vercel customers! This update enhances visibility into redirects and external rewrites, allowing Vercel to act as a reverse proxy or standalone CDN. Key metrics include total external rewrites and rewrites by hostnames. Pro and Enterprise customers can upgrade to Observability Plus for additional insights like connection latency and rewrite paths. Learn more about these updates and how they can benefit your projects! 🌐📊 #Vercel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotID Deep Analysis catches a sophisticated bot network in real-time</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11556/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11556/</guid>
      <description>🚨 On October 29, BotID Deep Analysis identified a significant increase in traffic—500% above normal levels—on a customer&amp;rsquo;s project. 📈 This surge appeared to originate from legitimate human users, raising concerns about disguised bot activity. Our team promptly engaged with the customer to address the issue. Remarkably, before discussions concluded, Deep Analysis utilized Kasada’s machine learning to identify and adapt to the threat. #BotID #CyberSecurity #MachineLearning #ThreatDetection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Caching details now available in Runtime Logs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11531/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11531/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Vercel users! You can now access detailed caching information in the Runtime Logs. This includes: - &lt;strong&gt;Cache key&lt;/strong&gt;: Unique identifier for cached pages - &lt;strong&gt;Cache tags&lt;/strong&gt;: Tags linked to cached data - &lt;strong&gt;Revalidation reason&lt;/strong&gt;: Explanation for any content revalidation This feature is available for all users at no extra cost. Explore it today! #Vercel #CDN #RuntimeLogs #WebDevelopment #Caching</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microfrontends now generally available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11546/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11546/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Microfrontends are now generally available on Vercel! This feature allows teams to break down large applications into smaller, independently deployable units, improving user experience. Each team can choose their framework and deploy at their own pace. Notable improvements include enhanced domain routing and simplified onboarding. Over 250 teams are already utilizing this feature, including Cursor and A+E Networks. Pricing starts with 2 microfrontend projects, with additional projects&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Agent can now run AI investigations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11545/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11545/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel is enhancing incident response with the launch of Vercel Agent Investigations in Public Beta. This new feature automatically detects application issues, conducts root cause analysis, and offers actionable remediation plans. By integrating anomaly alerts, Vercel aims to streamline how development teams address production issues. #Vercel #IncidentResponse #AIAssistance #DevOps #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-configuration support for Fastify</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11560/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11560/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel now supports Fastify applications, streamlining the developer experience with zero-configuration deployment. Fastify&amp;rsquo;s plugin architecture allows for easy scaling, utilizing Fluid compute and Active CPU pricing. This means your app adjusts automatically based on traffic, ensuring cost efficiency. Discover more about deploying Fastify on Vercel today! #Fastify #Vercel #WebDevelopment #CloudComputing #DeveloperExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI&#39;s GPT-OSS-Safeguard-20B now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11472/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11472/</guid>
      <description>🚀 OpenAI has released GPT-OSS-Safeguard-20B, now accessible via Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway without needing other provider accounts. This model is fine-tuned for developers to implement custom content moderation. The AI Gateway offers a consistent API, usage tracking, and performance optimizations. To get started, use the model identifier openai/gpt-oss-safeguard-20b. Explore built-in observability and intelligent routing features. #OpenAI #Vercel #ContentModeration #AIGateway #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel achieves TISAX AL2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11459/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11459/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has achieved TISAX Assessment Level 2 (AL2), a key security standard in the automotive and manufacturing sectors. This certification evaluates information security and cloud service usage in supply chains. Customers can access Vercel’s TISAX results via the ENX portal. For more details, check out our blog post! #Vercel #TISAX #InformationSecurity #CloudServices #AutomotiveCompliance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel achieves TISAX AL2 compliance to serve automotive partners</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11458/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11458/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has achieved TISAX Level 2 (AL2) compliance, enhancing its ability to serve automotive partners. This milestone highlights Vercel&amp;rsquo;s focus on providing secure and reliable infrastructure, especially for industries with strict security needs. This achievement complements existing certifications such as ISO/IEC 27001:2022 and SOC 2 Type II. #Vercel #TISAX #CyberSecurity #Compliance #Automotive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bun runtime now in Public Beta for Vercel Functions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11363/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11363/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Bun runtime is now in Public Beta for Vercel Functions! Developers can choose between Node.js and Bun for their projects, optimizing performance based on workload. Benchmarks indicate a 28% reduction in average latency for CPU-bound Next.js rendering with Bun. Supported frameworks include Next.js, Hono, Express, and Nitro. Bun also seamlessly integrates with Vercel&amp;rsquo;s logging and monitoring systems. Check out the benchmarks and documentation for more details! 📊✨ #BunRuntime&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bun runtime on Vercel Functions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11362/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11362/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel Functions now supports Bun as a runtime option in Public Beta. You can choose between Node.js and Bun based on your project needs. This flexibility lets you optimize performance for different workloads. 🖥️ Internal tests show Bun reduces average latency by 28% for CPU-bound Next.js rendering compared to Node.js, thanks to its efficient architecture. #Vercel #Bun #WebDevelopment #NextJS #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MiniMax M2 now available for free in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11384/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11384/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI enthusiasts! The MiniMax M2 model is now available for free through Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway until November 7th, 2025. This open-source model is designed for efficient performance with only 10B active parameters. Users can easily access it via a unified API, allowing for tracking, optimizations, and robust uptime. To get started, set the model to minimax/minimax-m2. Explore the AI Gateway and try the model in the playground today! #AI #OpenSource #Vercel #MiniMaxM2 #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>David Totten Joins Vercel to Lead Global Field Engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11324/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11324/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Vercel! David Totten is joining as VP of Global Field Engineering. With 20 years of experience in building technical teams, he will oversee Sales Engineering, Developer Success, Professional Services, and Customer Support Engineering. This move aims to enhance how companies translate ideas into impactful outcomes. #Vercel #Leadership #FieldEngineering #TechNews #DavidTotten</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Ship AI 2025 recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11313/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11313/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Earlier this year, Vercel introduced the AI Cloud, a platform for creating intelligent systems. At the recent Ship AI event, they unveiled new SDKs, infrastructure, and open source templates. These tools simplify the creation of production-ready agents. Now, you can define, deploy, and manage intelligent workflows seamlessly alongside your apps, making AI development as straightforward as web development. #Vercel #AICloud #Technology #Innovation #Development</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Chat now available on Vercel docs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11269/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11269/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! AI Chat is now integrated into Vercel docs, making it easier to find information. You can ask questions directly on any docs page and receive instant responses. 🔍 To start, visit vercel.com/docs and click the &amp;ldquo;Ask AI&amp;rdquo; button. Use the feature to load specific pages for more tailored answers or copy conversations as Markdown. #Vercel #AIChat #Documentation #TechUpdates #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage Next.js Server Actions in the Vercel Firewall</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11266/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11266/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Vercel Firewall now offers enhanced support for Server Actions with Next.js 15.5. Users can set custom rules for specific actions, such as rate limiting requests to app/auth/actions.ts#getUser to 100 per minute per IP. This feature is available for all plans at no extra cost. Explore the documentation for more details! 📚 #Vercel #NextJS #WebDevelopment #ServerActions #RateLimiting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI agents and services on the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11212/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11212/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The Vercel Marketplace now features a new category for AI agents and services. This addition allows for seamless integration of AI-powered workflows into projects. No more juggling multiple dashboards or billing systems! Enjoy unified billing, observability, and easy installation directly within the platform. #AI #VercelMarketplace #DeveloperTools #TechUpdates #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Built-in durability: Introducing Workflow Development Kit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11213/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11213/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the Workflow Development Kit (WDK) - a new open source TypeScript framework designed to enhance software durability. It simplifies the process for developers creating AI agents or data pipelines, allowing functions to pause and resume seamlessly, even after long periods or during system crashes. WDK runs on any framework, platform, or runtime, making it easier to build reliable software without deep knowledge of distributed systems. #WorkflowDevelopmentKit #SoftwareDurability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AI agents &amp; services on the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11217/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11217/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Vercel Marketplace has launched a new category for AI Agents &amp;amp; Services, simplifying the integration of AI automation into projects. Developers can now access off-the-shelf agents like CodeRabbit for automated code reviews and Corridor for real-time security. This category also includes AI services for building custom agents, such as Braintrust for monitoring and Chatbase for conversational analytics. Explore the new offerings and enhance your projects with AI! #Vercel #AIAgents&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Vercel Agent: Your new Vercel teammate</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11214/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11214/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has launched Vercel Agent, an AI teammate designed to enhance your development workflow. This tool utilizes AI, deep platform knowledge, and application code to help teams ship faster and improve quality. Currently in Public Beta, Vercel Agent offers two main features: Code Review and Investigations. #Vercel #AI #Development #TechUpdates #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open source Workflow Development Kit is now in public beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11219/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11219/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Workflow Development Kit is now in public beta! This framework simplifies building durable, long-running processes in async JavaScript. Key features include: - &lt;strong&gt;Reliability&lt;/strong&gt;: Just add &amp;ldquo;use workflow&amp;rdquo; to make async functions durable. - &lt;strong&gt;Durability&lt;/strong&gt;: Use the sleep function to pause and resume without holding compute. - &lt;strong&gt;Observability&lt;/strong&gt;: Access traces, logs, and metrics for every run. No lock-in is required, allowing for local development and deployment to Vercel or other clouds&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Agent Investigations now in Public Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11216/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11216/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel Agent&amp;rsquo;s AI investigations are now in public beta! This feature helps teams respond to anomaly alerts by diagnosing issues quickly. It identifies root causes, analyzes impacts, and provides remediation steps, reducing alert fatigue and improving stability. Available for Pro and Enterprise teams with Observability Plus, teams can start with $100 in credits. Learn more about enhancing your incident response! #Vercel #AI #IncidentResponse #TechInnovation #Observability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Python SDK is now available in beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11218/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11218/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Python developers! The Vercel Python SDK is now in beta. This SDK supports key Vercel features including Vercel Sandbox, Blob storage, and the Runtime Cache API. To start, simply run &lt;code&gt;pip install vercel&lt;/code&gt; and explore how you can run untrusted code, manage blob storage, and store data across functions. 🔗 #Vercel #Python #SDK #WebDevelopment #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You can just ship agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11211/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11211/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Building AI agents should feel like shaping ideas, not battling complex code. Just as web development evolved with frameworks, AI is now following suit. The emergence of Vercel AI Cloud offers tools and infrastructure that simplify the development process, allowing developers to focus on creation rather than technical hurdles. Explore how this shift enhances productivity and quality in AI development! #AIDevelopment #Vercel #TechInnovation #DeveloperExperience #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-config backends on Vercel AI Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11215/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11215/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel AI Cloud now offers zero-config backends! Teams can build sophisticated AI applications that manage complex workflows and respond to real-time events. This new feature allows for easy deployment of popular Python and TypeScript frameworks without the need for manual configuration. Vercel automatically provisions the necessary infrastructure, streamlining the development process. #Vercel #AICLOUD #TechNews #BackendDevelopment #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster builds with Turbo build machines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11160/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11160/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Turbo build machines are now accessible for all paid plans! These machines feature 30 vCPUs and 60GB of memory, providing enhanced build performance. They are perfect for Turbopack builds and large monorepos, allowing parallel task execution for faster static generation and dependency resolution. Enable Turbo build machines per project with usage-based pricing. Learn more in the documentation! 📚 #TurboBuild #TechUpdate #SoftwareDevelopment #PerformanceBoost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamically extend timeout of an active Sandbox</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11121/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11121/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Vercel users! You can now extend the duration of an active Sandbox using the new extendTimeout method. This feature is designed to keep long-running sandboxes active beyond their initial timeout. It supports workflows that involve chained tasks or multi-step code generation. Users can extend the timeout multiple times until they reach their plan&amp;rsquo;s maximum runtime—up to 5 hours for Pro and Enterprise plans, and 45 minutes for Hobby plan. Learn more in the docs! 📚 #Vercel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preview links between microfrontends projects now serve all paths</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11097/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11097/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Teams utilizing microfrontends can now access all routes from any domain within their group. This improvement enhances the testing experience by eliminating broken links. Previously, only the root domain served paths from child microfrontends. Now, preview links route paths between all projects, reducing 404 errors. Deployments from the same commit or branch link automatically, simplifying testing in monorepos. Fallback routing also resolves requests for microfrontends on different&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update regarding Vercel service disruption on October 20, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11131/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11131/</guid>
      <description>On October 20, 2025, Vercel experienced a service disruption due to an unexpected outage in the AWS us-east-1 region. Vercel takes full responsibility for this incident, emphasizing their commitment to providing reliable services. Despite the challenges, they managed to serve significant traffic while minimizing risks for their customers. The company aims to enhance cloud simplicity, operating across 19 AWS regions to optimize performance. #Vercel #CloudServices #AWS #ServiceUpdate #TechNews 🌐🔧📉</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preview links between microfrontends projects now serve all paths</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11097/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11097/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Teams utilizing microfrontends can now access all routes from any domain within their group. This improvement enhances the testing experience by eliminating broken links. Previously, only the root domain served paths from child microfrontends. Now, preview links route paths between all projects, reducing 404 errors. Deployments from the same commit or branch link automatically, simplifying testing in monorepos. Fallback routing also resolves requests for microfrontends on different&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-configuration support for NestJS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11041/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11041/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel now offers zero-configuration support for NestJS, a leading framework for building Node.js applications. With this feature, your NestJS app will automatically scale based on traffic, utilizing Fluid compute with Active CPU pricing. This means you only pay for the resources you actually use. For more details on deploying NestJS on Vercel, check out the documentation. #NestJS #Vercel #NodeJS #WebDevelopment #Serverless</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Braintrust joins the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11000/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11000/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Braintrust is now part of the Vercel Marketplace. With this integration, developers can easily stream traces and evaluation data from Vercel to Braintrust. This allows for real-time visibility into model quality and user experience. Key features include: - Built-in evaluation and observability for AI features - Monitoring model quality in production - Performance benchmarking across LLMs Explore the template for easy setup and unified billing! #AI #Development #Vercel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents at work, a partnership with Salesforce and Slack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10978/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10978/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The future of software is here! Vercel and Salesforce are teaming up to integrate AI agents within the Salesforce ecosystem, starting with Slack. This partnership aims to enhance collaboration by enabling software to understand user intent and take action seamlessly. As the shift towards conversational interfaces continues, enterprises must consider where these AI agents will operate. Stay tuned for more updates! 🤖💼 #AI #Salesforce #Slack #Collaboration #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Haiku 4.5 now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10958/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10958/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Claude Haiku 4.5 is now available through Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway, making it easy to access without additional provider accounts. This model matches the performance of Sonnet 4 for coding and agent tasks, but at a lower cost and faster speeds. The AI Gateway provides a unified API for tracking usage, costs, and performance optimizations. With built-in observability and support for multiple providers, including Anthropic and Vertex AI, users can expect reliable service. Check out&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Trace Drains on the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-11001/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-11001/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel introduces Trace Drains on its Marketplace! Developers can now send traces and logs to their chosen observability providers, starting with Braintrust and Dash0. This integration supports real-time streaming of performance data for improved debugging and monitoring. The Trace Drain API enhances Vercel&amp;rsquo;s observability, allowing for seamless integration with logging and analytics tools. This update is available for Pro and ENT customers. #Vercel #Observability #DevelopmentTools&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just another (Black) Friday</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10943/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10943/</guid>
      <description>This Black Friday, Vercel ensures that teams experience seamless performance. Their platform is built to handle traffic spikes, with automatic caching and edge rendering. Teams focus on refining their setups, confirming observability, and tightening security. Last year, Vercel handled over 86 billion requests, peaking at nearly 2 million requests per second. Major brands like Helly Hansen benefited from this robust infrastructure. #BlackFriday #Vercel #Ecommerce #TechPerformance #CyberMonday 📈🛒🌐</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Running Next.js inside ChatGPT: A deep dive into native app integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10969/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10969/</guid>
      <description>OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s recent Apps SDK now supports embedding web applications in ChatGPT, enabling a new level of integration. This article explores how a Next.js app can operate within ChatGPT&amp;rsquo;s triple-iframe structure. It highlights features like client-side navigation and dynamic routing, showcasing the advancements in web app functionality. Discover how this integration works! 🌐🤖 #NextJS #ChatGPT #WebDevelopment #OpenAI #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talha Tariq joins Vercel as CTO (Security)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10968/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10968/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news at Vercel! Talha Tariq joins as CTO (Security) to address the growing security challenges in software development. With experience as CISO &amp;amp; CIO at HashiCorp and CTO (Security) at IBM, he brings valuable expertise to the team. His role will focus on enhancing security measures as AI continues to evolve. #Vercel #Cybersecurity #TechNews #Leadership #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly alerts now in public beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10894/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10894/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Anomaly alerts are now in public beta for Observability Plus users! Teams can monitor applications in real-time and receive alerts for unexpected behavior. This includes usage anomalies, like unusual patterns in metrics, and error anomalies, such as spikes in 5XX responses. Stay informed by viewing alerts on your dashboard or subscribing via email, Slack, or webhooks. Available for Pro and Enterprise customers. #Observability #AnomalyDetection #SoftwareMonitoring #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Commits to the same branch now build with no queues</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-11011/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-11011/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has introduced a new feature that allows multiple commits on the same branch to build simultaneously when On-Demand Concurrent Builds is enabled. 🛠️ This update removes the waiting period for new commits, enabling them to start building immediately upon arrival. For more details, visit the On-Demand Concurrent Builds documentation. #Vercel #WebDevelopment #ContinuousIntegration #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expanded Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) for Enterprise teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10627/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10627/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has enhanced its Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) system for Enterprise teams. Key updates include multi-role support, allowing users to have several roles, and a new security role focused on compliance settings. Extended permissions enable more precise control over actions like project creation, full production deployment, and environment management. For more details, check the RBAC documentation! 📄🔐 #RBAC #Vercel #EnterpriseSecurity #AccessControl #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-configuration Flask backends</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10630/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10630/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Great news for Flask developers! Flask applications can now be deployed instantly on Vercel without any configuration changes. This new feature simplifies the process, eliminating the need for redirects in vercel.json or using the /api folder. With Vercel’s Fluid compute and Active CPU pricing, your app will automatically adjust based on traffic. You only pay for the CPU time your code uses. Learn more about deploying Flask on Vercel in the documentation! 📚 #Flask #Vercel #WebDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Block Vercel deployment promotions with Github Actions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10600/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10600/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New feature alert! You can now block deployment promotions to production on Vercel until selected GitHub Actions are completed successfully. This ensures only verified builds that pass tests are released. Deployment Checks are available for all GitHub-connected projects. Configure them in your project settings or check the documentation for more info. #Vercel #GitHubActions #DevOps #Deployment #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT apps support on Vercel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10608/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10608/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! You can now build and deploy ChatGPT apps directly on Vercel. These apps allow integration of custom UI components within ChatGPT, utilizing modern web frameworks. Frameworks like Next.js can enhance these experiences using the Model Context Protocol (MCP). Take advantage of Next.js features and Vercel&amp;rsquo;s capabilities for seamless development. Get started today! 🌐✨ #ChatGPT #Vercel #WebDevelopment #NextJS #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Server rendering benchmarks: Fluid Compute and Cloudflare Workers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10607/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10607/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Independent developer Theo Browne has released benchmarks comparing server-side rendering performance of Fluid compute and Cloudflare Workers. The tests covered frameworks like Next.js, React, and SvelteKit, revealing that Fluid compute outperformed Cloudflare Workers by 1.2 to 5 times for compute-bound tasks. This study highlights the differences in response times, with Fluid compute showing more consistency. #ServerRendering #WebDevelopment #FluidCompute #Cloudflare #PerformanceTesting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Domains Registrar API for domain search, pricing, purchase, and management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10573/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10573/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has launched a new Domains Registrar API! This API allows users to programmatically search, price, purchase, renew, and transfer domains. Key features include: - &lt;strong&gt;Catalog &amp;amp; Pricing:&lt;/strong&gt; List TLDs and pricing. - &lt;strong&gt;Availability Checks:&lt;/strong&gt; Access single or bulk domain availability. - &lt;strong&gt;Orders &amp;amp; Purchases:&lt;/strong&gt; Buy and track domains. - &lt;strong&gt;Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Handle renewals, auto-renewal, and nameserver updates. Explore the API documentation for more details! 📄 #DomainsAPI #Vercel #WebDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly alerts now available via email</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10488/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10488/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New feature alert for Enterprise customers! Anomaly alerts are now available via email and in-app notifications for those using Observability Plus. This adds to existing options like webhooks, Slack, and alerts dashboard. Currently, two alert types are offered: - &lt;strong&gt;Usage anomalies&lt;/strong&gt;: Identifies unusual spikes in key metrics. - &lt;strong&gt;Error anomalies&lt;/strong&gt;: Detects sudden increases in 5XX responses. This feature is in limited beta. Check it out to enhance your monitoring! 📊💡 #Observability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Invalidate the CDN cache by tag</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-03-9849/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-03-9849/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for website managers! You can now invalidate CDN cache contents by tag. This marks all cached content with that tag as stale. The next request will serve stale content while revalidating in the background, ensuring users experience no latency. Three ways to revalidate content include the Dashboard, CLI, and Function API. For more details, check out the link: &lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/docs/functions/functions-api-reference/vercel-functions-package#invalidatebytag&#34;&gt;https://vercel.com/docs/functions/functions-api-reference/vercel-functions-package#invalidatebytag&lt;/a&gt; #CDN #WebDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python package manager uv is now available for builds with zero configuration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10424/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10424/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has introduced uv, a fast Python package manager written in Rust, as the default for Python builds. This update boosts build speeds by 30-65% and expands support for various dependency formats. Now, projects can use uv.lock or pyproject.toml alongside the traditional requirements.txt or Pipfile. Discover more about this enhancement for Python on Vercel! #Python #Vercel #PackageManager #Development #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment-level configuration for Fluid compute</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10375/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10375/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! You can now configure Fluid compute on a per-deployment basis. Simply set &amp;ldquo;fluid&amp;rdquo;: true in your vercel.json to activate it for that specific deployment. This feature allows teams to enable or disable Fluid compute without altering global project settings, making it easier to test and adopt. For more details, check out the documentation! 📚✨ #FluidCompute #WebDevelopment #Vercel #TechUpdates #Deployment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Faster time-to-start for v0 builds</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10374/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10374/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Publishing v0 apps is now, on average, 1.1 seconds faster. This improvement comes from reducing the time needed to send source files during deployment creation. The enhanced deployment pipeline shortens feedback loops, making your development process more efficient. Deploy your apps today at v0.app! #AppDevelopment #Deployment #DeveloperEfficiency #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Static IPs are now available for more secure connectivity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10397/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10397/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting update for Pro and Enterprise teams! Static IPs are now available for connecting to external services requiring IP allowlisting. This means your traffic from builds and functions will route through consistent, shared static IPs. To enable this feature, visit Connectivity &amp;gt; Static IPs in your project or team settings. Secure Compute remains available for those needing a fully dedicated VPC model and has also moved under Connectivity settings. For more details, check the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stripe is now available in beta on the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10264/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10264/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stripe is now in beta on the Vercel Marketplace! This new integration allows users to easily provision a fully functional Stripe sandbox directly from Vercel, simplifying the transition from prototype to production. Key use cases include ecommerce storefronts, SaaS billing, demos, and developer onboarding. Start building your online store today using Vercel and Stripe! #Stripe #Vercel #Ecommerce #SaaS #Development</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards the AI Cloud: Our Series F</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10279/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10279/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has reached a significant milestone with its Series F funding round, now valuing the company at $9.3 billion. This round raised $300M, co-led by Accel and GIC, along with other supporters. Additionally, Vercel is initiating a ~$300M tender offer for certain early investors and employees. A big thank you to all our customers, investors, and team members for your support! 🙏 #Vercel #Funding #TechNews #Investment #Growth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>View &amp; query bot verification data in Vercel Observability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10263/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10263/</guid>
      <description>📊 Vercel is enhancing bot traffic analysis with new features in Observability. Now, users can view detailed bot verification data through three new query dimensions: - &lt;strong&gt;Bot name&lt;/strong&gt;: Identify specific bots - &lt;strong&gt;Bot category&lt;/strong&gt;: Group by type - &lt;strong&gt;Bot verified&lt;/strong&gt;: Distinguish between verified, spoofed, and unverifiable bots Additionally, verification badges are now displayed next to bot names in the Edge Requests dashboard. All users can view these badges, while Observability Plus subscribers can&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Collaborating with Anthropic on Claude Sonnet 4.5 to power intelligent coding agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10224/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10224/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Claude Sonnet 4.5 is now available on the Vercel AI Gateway, enhancing the AI SDK&amp;rsquo;s capabilities. We&amp;rsquo;ve tested the model in our Next.js pipelines and the results are promising. It shows improved design sensibility and code quality, particularly in building and linting Next.js applications. This collaboration with Anthropic enables new developer workflows, allowing AI to plan, execute, and safely manage changes in repositories. #AI #Coding #DeveloperTools #Vercel #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node.js Vercel Functions now support per-path request cancellation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10154/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10154/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel Functions with Node.js now support request cancellation on a per-path basis. This feature allows functions to stop execution when a request is canceled, such as when a user navigates away or closes a tab. This change helps to reduce unnecessary compute and token generation. To enable cancellation, simply add &amp;ldquo;supportsCancellation&amp;rdquo;: true to your vercel.json file. Learn more about this update and its implementation! 🔗 #Vercel #NodeJS #WebDevelopment #TechUpdate #RequestCancellation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preventing the stampede: Request collapsing in the Vercel CDN</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10084/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10084/</guid>
      <description>🚀 When deploying Next.js apps with Incremental Static Regeneration (ISR), users may experience &amp;ldquo;cache stampedes.&amp;rdquo; This occurs when multiple requests for the same page trigger separate function invocations, leading to wasted resources and potential downtime. 🌍 Vercel&amp;rsquo;s CDN now tackles this issue with request collapsing. Only one request per region will invoke a function for uncached paths, while others wait for the cached response. 🔧 This feature requires no manual configuration, as Vercel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Request collapsing for ISR cache misses</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10085/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10085/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel CDN introduces request collapsing to manage cache misses for ISR pages. This feature prevents cache stampedes by consolidating simultaneous requests into a single regeneration per region. As a result, it enhances reliability and significantly reduces backend load. No extra configuration is needed, as cacheability is automatically detected. For more details, check out their blog post! #Vercel #CDN #WebDevelopment #ISR #Caching</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Domains overhauled with instant search and at-cost pricing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10108/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10108/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has revamped its Domains service, making it easier and more affordable to find and purchase domains for your projects. Now, you can search for domains without logging in, and enjoy at-cost pricing with savings of up to 50% on popular TLDs. Results are transparent and available instantly, providing real-time updates on availability and premium status. Plus, with expanded TLD coverage and bulk checkout options, managing multiple domains is streamlined. Discover the new features at&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-configuration FastAPI backends</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10109/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10109/</guid>
      <description>🚀 FastAPI just got easier! Vercel now supports FastAPI with zero-configuration, simplifying deployment. No more redirects or /api folder requirements are needed. With Fluid compute and Active CPU pricing, your app will scale based on traffic, ensuring you only pay for what you use. For more details, check out the FastAPI on Vercel documentation! 🌐💻 #FastAPI #Vercel #WebDevelopment #APIs #Python</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query data on external API requests in Vercel Observability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10034/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10034/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Vercel users! Observability Plus now enables the querying and visualizing of external API requests. This feature includes a query builder that helps explore Vercel data related to traffic and performance. You can create custom queries on request counts and time to first byte (TTFB) for API calls. TTFB queries provide detailed breakdowns and can be filtered by request hostname. This tool is available for Pro and Enterprise teams. #Vercel #Observability #APIs&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claimed deployments now include third-party resources</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9942/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9942/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has introduced a new feature allowing users to claim deployments that include third-party resources. AI platforms and coding tools can now create projects on Vercel, enabling instant deployment. When a user claims a deployment, any attached resources like databases are transferred automatically. Currently, Prisma is the first provider to support this feature, allowing users to bundle a database with their Vercel-hosted app seamlessly. More providers will follow soon. Explore the live&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly alerts now include error spikes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9889/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9889/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New feature alert for Enterprise customers! With Observability Plus, users can now receive alerts for error spikes that deviate from normal behavior. This helps teams identify issues early on. The system groups abnormal error patterns, such as sudden increases in 5XX responses on specific routes. Detailed alert pages include relevant log lines for easier investigation. This error anomaly detection is currently in limited beta. #Observability #ErrorDetection #EnterpriseSolutions #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotID uncovers hidden SEO poisoning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9884/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9884/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A recent case highlights the risks of hidden SEO poisoning. A major financial institution observed unexpected bot traffic and deployed BotID. Instead of detecting malicious scrapers, they found verified Google bots. However, the search queries were unrelated to their business, revealing a long-standing SEO attack that was distorting their traffic patterns. Stay vigilant! 🕵️‍♂️ #SEOSecurity #BotID #CyberThreats #DigitalSafety #TrafficMonitoring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filter deployments by author</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9885/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9885/</guid>
      <description>New feature alert! 🚀 You can now filter deployments in the dashboard by author. Use a username, email, or Git username for easy tracking. These filters will stay in the URL, making it simple to share specific views with your team. Check it out in your project&amp;rsquo;s deployments! #TechUpdate #SoftwareDevelopment #TeamCollaboration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we made global routing faster with Bloom filters</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9838/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9838/</guid>
      <description>🚀 We recently optimized our global routing service, achieving a 15% reduction in memory usage. This update improved time-to-first-byte (TTFB) by 10% for the 75th percentile and enhanced routing speeds for sites with numerous static paths. By implementing a Bloom filter instead of slow JSON parsing, we significantly decreased path lookup latency, benefiting all users. #TechUpdate #RoutingOptimization #PerformanceEnhancement #WebDevelopment #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Observability Plus replacing legacy Monitoring</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9820/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9820/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/atom&#34;&gt;Vercel Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://vercel.com/changelog/observability-plus-replacing-legacy-monitoring&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI code reviews by Vercel Agent now in Public Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9806/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9806/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Vercel! The Vercel Agent is now in public beta, offering AI-driven code reviews. It provides validated suggestions that focus on correctness, security, and performance. Key features include optimizations for popular frameworks like Next.js and React, along with support for multiple languages like TypeScript and Python. The reviews come with high-signal inline comments and in-dashboard observability for metrics. This tool is available for all Pro and Enterprise teams, with&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scale to one: How Fluid solves cold starts</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9787/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9787/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cold starts are a challenge for traditional serverless platforms, causing delays during crucial user interactions. Vercel&amp;rsquo;s Fluid compute technology addresses this issue by achieving zero cold starts for 99.37% of requests. This means faster response times and a better user experience. Say goodbye to the choice between cost and performance! #Serverless #TechInnovation #UserExperience #WebDevelopment #Vercel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What you need to know about vibe coding</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9786/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9786/</guid>
      <description>In February 2025, Andrej Karpathy coined the term &amp;ldquo;vibe coding,&amp;rdquo; highlighting a new approach to programming with AI. This method encourages developers to embrace creativity and focus on ideas rather than the technical details of code. Currently, over 90% of U.S. developers are using AI coding tools, and the trend is expanding to other professions. English is now recognized as the fastest growing programming language globally. Explore more insights in our State of Vibe Coding report! 🖥️✨🌍&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate static AI SDK tools from MCP servers with mcp-to-ai-sdk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9737/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9737/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Model Context Protocol (MCP) is becoming a key standard for federating tool calls between AI agents. However, using MCP tools in production can pose risks, such as unexpected changes in tool names and argument schemas, which may lead to security and quality issues. To address this, the mcp-to-ai-sdk CLI generates static AI SDK tools from MCP servers, ensuring stability in agent loops. #AI #MCP #TechInnovation #SDK #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI agents at scale: Rox’s Vercel-powered revenue operating system</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9738/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9738/</guid>
      <description>Rox is revolutionizing revenue management with its new operating system powered by AI agents. 🤖 These intelligent agents assist sellers by researching, prospecting, and engaging, helping businesses grow revenue effectively. Built on Vercel&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure, Rox ensures fast shipping and global scalability for a seamless customer experience. 🌍🚀 #RevenueGrowth #AIAgents #TechInnovation #Vercel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Builds now start up to 30% faster</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9676/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9676/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Builds now start up to 30% faster thanks to improvements in the build cache. The cache now downloads parts in parallel using a worker pool, reducing initialization time by 30% and cutting down build times by up to 7 seconds for all plans. This enhancement is automatically enabled for new builds, building on previous improvements. Learn more about this update on Vercel! #DevUpdates #BuildFaster #Vercel #TechNews #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shai-Halud Supply Chain Campaign — Expanded Impact &amp; Vercel Response</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9788/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9788/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The Shai-Halud supply chain campaign has escalated, impacting over 40 npm packages, including Tinycolor and CrowdStrike. Vercel identified 10 customer projects affected by compromised packages but confirmed that no builds were impacted in the DuckDB incident. Steps taken include blocking compromised versions and purging build caches. Vercel is enhancing supply chain defenses and monitoring for further threats. For Vercel users, audit dependencies and consider using pnpm&amp;rsquo;s new settings to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helly Hansen migrated to Vercel and drove 80% Black Friday growth</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9694/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9694/</guid>
      <description>Helly Hansen, a leader in technical apparel, faced challenges with its outdated digital experience. 🌐 By migrating to Next.js and Vercel, the company enhanced site performance, improving Core Web Vitals significantly. This transition not only boosted developer efficiency but also led to a record-breaking performance during Black Friday. 📈 This strategic move sets the stage for future innovations. #HellyHansen #DigitalTransformation #Ecommerce #Nextjs #Vercel</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Vercel Drains: Complete observability data, anywhere</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9647/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9647/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has rebranded Log Drains to Vercel Drains, expanding their functionality. Now, you can export not only logs but also OpenTelemetry traces, Web Analytics events, and Speed Insights metrics. This enhancement allows teams to stream observability data seamlessly into their existing systems. Learn more about these updates! #Vercel #Observability #WebAnalytics #OpenTelemetry #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updated defaults for deployment retention</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9648/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9648/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for Vercel Users! 🚨 Starting October 15, 2025, the default deployment retention policy will change for projects using the legacy “unlimited” setting. Here are the new guidelines: - Canceled Deployments: 30 days (max 1 year) - Errored Deployments: 3 months (max 1 year) - Pre-Production Deployments: 6 months (max 3 years) - Production Deployments: 1 year (max 3 years) Projects with custom settings remain unaffected. Team owners can set default policies for new projects under&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>402-mcp enables x402 payments in MCP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9615/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9615/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing x402-mcp! This new library integrates with the AI SDK, allowing for seamless x402 paywalls on Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers. It enables secure, account-less payments for MCP tools with confirmation times of just 100–200ms and low fees under $0.01. Getting started is simple with just one function needed for integration. Learn more about x402 and the AI Starter Kit today! #x402mcp #AI #Payments #MCP #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing x402-mcp: Open protocol payments for MCP tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9614/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9614/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing x402-mcp: a new solution for open protocol payments in MCP tools. AI agents face challenges when accessing paid external services due to complex workflows. The x402 protocol simplifies this by allowing payment requests directly within HTTP requests, using the 402 Payment Required status code. This integration enhances the Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers alongside the Vercel AI SDK. #AI #OpenProtocol #PaymentSolutions #TechInnovation #MCP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Vercel CLI login flow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9607/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9607/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for Vercel users! The new Vercel CLI login now employs the OAuth 2.0 Device Flow for enhanced security and ease of use. You can sign in from any browser-enabled device. Before approving a login, remember to check the location, IP, and request time. Note that email-based logins and several flags will be phased out by February 1, 2026. Upgrade today with &lt;code&gt;npm i vercel@latest&lt;/code&gt;! #Vercel #OAuth #SecurityUpdate #WebDevelopment #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen3-Next models are now supported in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9628/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9628/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Qwen3 Next models are now available through the Vercel AI Gateway. These two efficient models from QwenLM utilize only 3B parameters. You can access them without needing additional provider accounts. The AI Gateway offers a unified API, tracking usage, cost management, and performance optimizations. To get started, install the AI SDK v5 and set the model to alibaba/qwen3-next-80b-a3b-thinking. Learn more about the capabilities of the AI Gateway! #AI #Vercel #QwenLM #TechNews&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LongCat-Flash Chat model is now supported in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9605/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9605/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news for developers! LongCat Flash Chat, a new model from Meituan, is now available through Vercel AI Gateway. This model allows for agentic tool use and adapts based on contextual demands. Access it easily with a unified API, track usage, and optimize performance without needing other provider accounts. To get started, install the AI SDK v5 and set the model to meituan/longcat-flash-chat. Learn more about this integration! #Vercel #AI #Meituan #TechUpdates #Developers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT can now integrate with Vercel MCP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9540/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9540/</guid>
      <description>🚀 ChatGPT now integrates with Vercel MCP, enhancing its capabilities for Pro and Plus users. To set it up, enable developer mode in ChatGPT settings, add Vercel MCP, and authenticate via OAuth. This allows agents to access protected deployments and analyze build logs. Explore the new features and optimize your workflow! 🔧💻 #ChatGPT #VercelMCP #AIIntegration #TechUpdate #DeveloperTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB Atlas is now available on the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9524/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9524/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! MongoDB Atlas is now available on the Vercel Marketplace. You can easily set up a fully managed MongoDB database directly from the Vercel dashboard. This integration allows for quick provisioning and seamless connection to your Vercel projects, eliminating the need for separate sign-ups or complex configurations. #MongoDB #Vercel #Developers #TechNews #DatabaseIntegration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB Atlas joins the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9525/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9525/</guid>
      <description>🚀 MongoDB Atlas is now available on the Vercel Marketplace! You can easily provision a fully managed database directly from the Vercel dashboard. This integration allows developers to connect their MongoDB Atlas databases to Vercel projects seamlessly. Key features include a flexible document model, built-in search capabilities, and options for horizontal scaling. This simplifies the setup process, enabling faster development for web and AI applications. Explore the new integration on the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Sandbox maximum duration extended to 5 hours</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9526/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9526/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Vercel users! Pro and Enterprise teams can now utilize Vercel Sandboxes for up to 5 hours, an increase from the previous limit of 45 minutes. This extension allows for more extensive workloads, including large-scale data processing and end-to-end testing pipelines. To get started with Sandbox or learn more, check out the documentation! #Vercel #TechUpdate #SoftwareDevelopment #DataProcessing #WebDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A more flexible Pro plan for modern teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9480/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9480/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel is enhancing its Pro plan to better support modern team collaboration and evolving workloads, including those driven by AI. Key updates aim to align with how applications now consume infrastructure. Stay tuned for a more flexible approach to managing your projects! #Vercel #ProPlan #TeamCollaboration #AI #Infrastructure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Viewer seats now available on Pro</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9484/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9484/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Pro teams! You can now add unlimited Viewer seats at no extra cost. This allows team members to collaborate more flexibly without affecting your budget. Viewers can access project dashboards, deployments, and analytics but can&amp;rsquo;t change production settings or see sensitive data. Developer seats remain at $20, while Viewer seats are free. Team members can easily request upgrades from owners directly in the dashboard. #ProUpdates #TeamCollaboration #ViewerSeats #CostEfficient&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIPAA BAAs are now available to Pro teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9485/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9485/</guid>
      <description>Pro teams can now enter into a Business Associate Agreement (BAA) on Vercel, supporting HIPAA-compliant workloads without needing an Enterprise contract. Vercel ensures HIPAA compliance through technical safeguards, annual audits, and breach notifications. However, compliance is a shared responsibility; teams must manage security features and access. This update simplifies regulatory compliance for healthcare applications. #HIPAA #Vercel #HealthcareTech #DataSecurity #ProTeams 🏥🔒📊</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Included Pro usage is now credit-based</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9482/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9482/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Big news for Pro users! The Pro plan now features a $20 monthly usage credit, replacing fixed allocations with a flexible system that adjusts to your workload. This update enhances your experience by allowing better management of resources. Additional benefits include free viewer seats, self-serve enterprise features like SAML SSO and HIPAA BA, and improved spend management. #ProPlan #UsageCredit #TechUpdates #EnterpriseFeatures #FlexibleSystem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No build queues: On-demand concurrent builds now on by default</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9481/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9481/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for teams on the new Pro pricing model! On-demand concurrent builds are now enabled by default, allowing builds to start immediately across projects without queue delays. This applies unless multiple builds target the same Git branch. Teams can manage this setting anytime with the new bulk enable feature, even if not yet on the Pro model. Learn more about these updates and the Pro pricing switch in the documentation! #BuildAutomation #ProPricing #DevOps #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spend Management now enabled by default on Pro</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9483/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9483/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Spend Management is now the default for all Pro teams! New Pro teams will have a budget set based on previous usage, while existing teams will see no changes to their current budgets. You’ll receive email alerts when approaching your spend threshold, helping you manage costs effectively. Adjust settings anytime for flexibility. Stay informed and optimize your spending! #SpendManagement #ProTeams #CostControl #Budgeting #BusinessUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The second wave of MCP: Building for LLMs, not developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9556/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9556/</guid>
      <description>The second wave of the MCP standard emphasizes the need for building tools tailored for LLMs, rather than simply wrapping existing APIs. Initial implementations focused on quick solutions, resulting in repeated orchestration and inefficiencies. LLMs require a fresh understanding of tools for each interaction. To optimize performance, it is essential to create tools that manage complete user intentions rather than fragmenting processes. #MCP #LLMs #TechDevelopment #AI #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI SDK and AI Gateway now integrated in GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9448/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9448/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The new integration of the AI SDK and AI Gateway with GitHub Actions allows users to access the vercel/ai-action@v2. This feature enables the generation of text or structured JSON directly within workflows by specifying prompts, models, and API keys. This opens up various AI-powered use cases, such as summarizing release notes, conducting light PR code reviews, moderating comments, and identifying duplicate issues. Explore more in the GitHub Actions marketplace&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk enable on-demand concurrent builds across projects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9439/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9439/</guid>
      <description>Pro teams can now enhance efficiency by bulk enabling on-demand concurrent builds across all projects with a single click. 🔄 This feature allows builds to start immediately upon request, optimizing compute capacity, except when multiple builds target the same Git branch. To activate this, visit your Pro team&amp;rsquo;s billing settings to enable or disable it for existing projects or select specific projects. Learn more in the documentation! 📄💻 #BuildAutomation #DevOps #ProjectManagement #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical npm supply chain attack response - September 8, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9447/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9447/</guid>
      <description>On September 8, 2025, a supply chain attack impacted 18 popular npm packages, including chalk, debug, and ansi-styles. These packages had malicious code aimed at intercepting cryptocurrency transactions in browsers. 🚨 Our security and engineering teams responded by identifying the affected projects and purging build caches. Affected customers have been notified with specific guidance. 🔍🔒 #CyberSecurity #npm #SupplyChainAttack #Cryptocurrency #Malware</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Functions now support graceful shutdown</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9432/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9432/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel Functions now enhance Node.js and Python runtimes with graceful shutdown support! This feature allows up to 500 milliseconds for running cleanup tasks before termination. When a function is terminated, a SIGTERM signal can be used to manage essential tasks like closing database connections or flushing logs. Learn more about the benefits of this update! #Vercel #NodeJS #Python #WebDevelopment #Serverless</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Export traces, web analytics events, and speed insights datapoints to any destination</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7788/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7788/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Vercel users! You can now export OpenTelemetry traces, Web Analytics events, and Speed Insights data to any third-party tool. This enhancement allows streaming of more raw data through expanded Log Drains infrastructure. Pro and Enterprise teams can set custom HTTP endpoints and choose from various encodings like JSON, NDJSON, or Protobuf. Explore Vercel Drains today! #Vercel #DataExport #WebAnalytics #OpenTelemetry #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Export traces, web analytics events, and speed insights datapoints to any destination</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7809/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7809/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel now allows users to export OpenTelemetry traces, Web Analytics events, and Speed Insights data to any third-party tool. This enhancement expands the Log Drains infrastructure for seamless data streaming. Users can set up custom HTTP endpoints to receive data in various formats like JSON, NDJSON, or Protobuf. Pro and Enterprise teams can export data at a cost of $0.50 per GB. Learn more about Vercel Drains! #DataExport #WebAnalytics #Vercel #OpenTelemetry&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-configuration Express backends</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7787/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7787/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Express, the minimalist web framework for Node.js, now offers zero-configuration support on Vercel. This means you can deploy Express applications without the hassle of setting up redirects in vercel.json or using the /api folder. For a seamless experience, check out the Express on Vercel documentation. #NodeJS #Express #Vercel #WebDevelopment #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonshot AI&#39;s Kimi K2 0905 model is now supported in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7775/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7775/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Moonshot AI&amp;rsquo;s Kimi K2 0905 model is now accessible through Vercel AI Gateway. This model supports agentic coding with a 256K context window and requires no additional provider accounts. AI Gateway offers a unified API for tracking usage, costs, and optimizing performance. It includes built-in observability and intelligent routing for enhanced reliability. To get started, install the AI SDK v5 and set the model to moonshotai/kimi-k2-0905. #AI #MoonshotAI #Vercel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stress testing Biome&#39;s noFloatingPromises lint rule</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7748/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7748/</guid>
      <description>We recently collaborated with the Biome team to enhance their noFloatingPromises lint rule. This rule is crucial for identifying unhandled Promises that can lead to errors. To test its effectiveness, we organized a friendly competition to create challenging test cases that could still pass the updated lint rule. This initiative not only fostered creativity but also encouraged learning among our team. Stay tuned for more insights! 🚀💡 #SoftwareDevelopment #LintRules #Teamwork #Innovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open SDK strategy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7702/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7702/</guid>
      <description>At Vercel, open source is a core principle. They focus on developing high-quality software without the goal of profit. Their approach aims to enhance the overall software landscape for everyone, not just their customers. This philosophy reflects the belief that improving software benefits all users. Learn more about Vercel&amp;rsquo;s commitment to open source. 🌍💻 #OpenSource #SoftwareDevelopment #Vercel #TechCommunity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-55173</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7555/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7555/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A vulnerability (CVE-2025-55173) affecting Next.js Image Optimization has been identified. It impacts versions prior to v15.4.5 and v14.2.31, allowing attacker-controlled external image servers to trigger arbitrary file downloads. This could lead to phishing and social engineering attacks. A patch was released on July 29th, 2025, addressing this issue for Vercel customers. For more details, check the GitHub Advisory and Next.js Release Notes. #CyberSecurity #NextJS #Vulnerability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-57752</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7553/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7553/</guid>
      <description>A vulnerability, CVE-2025-57752, has been identified in Next.js Image Optimization affecting versions prior to v15.4.5 and v14.2.31. It involved cache poisoning, risking unauthorized access to sensitive images. The issue arose when API routes returned images based on headers, leading to potential disclosure of user-specific content. The vulnerability has been resolved in the latest versions, ensuring that request headers are not forwarded to image endpoints. For more details, refer to the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-57822</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7554/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7554/</guid>
      <description>A recent vulnerability, CVE-2025-57822, has been identified in Next.js Middleware, affecting versions before v14.2.32 and v15.4.7. This flaw allowed for Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) risks due to misconfigured NextResponse.next() usage. Applications that reflected user request headers could unintentionally allow servers to make requests to harmful destinations. A patch was released on August 25, 2025, to protect Vercel customers. For those unable to upgrade, it is vital to adhere to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for the worst: Our core database failover test</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7485/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7485/</guid>
      <description>On July 24, 2025, we conducted a successful failover test of our core control-plane database from Azure West US to East US 2. This exercise confirmed our disaster recovery plans in real-world conditions. All control-plane traffic was tested, ensuring stability without any customer impact. While preview and development traffic were affected, our production CDN traffic remained unaffected across 19 regions. The operation highlighted our commitment to resilience, achieving zero downtime and no&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly alerts now in limited beta for Enterprise customers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7270/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7270/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Enterprise customers can now access anomaly alerts in limited beta! These alerts help quickly identify unusual patterns in application metrics, allowing for prompt issue resolution. Users can integrate alerts via webhooks into existing monitoring systems and receive notifications directly in Slack channels. Explore this feature with Observability Plus and streamline your monitoring process! #AnomalyDetection #EnterpriseSolutions #MonitoringAlerts #TechUpdates #ObservabilityPlus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Slack&#39;s Bolt.js to Vercel with @vercel/slack-bolt</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7271/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7271/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! @vercel has released @vercel/slack-bolt, an adapter that allows you to deploy Slack&amp;rsquo;s Bolt for JavaScript on Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Cloud. This tool helps manage Slack webhook events efficiently. It addresses the challenge of responding within three seconds to avoid timeouts, using Fluid compute’s streaming feature. Compatible with any function or framework like Hono, Nitro, or Next.js, you can start with the Slack Agent Template or explore the library on npm. #Slack&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>s1ngularity: supply chain attack in Nx packages</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7486/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7486/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A supply chain attack has targeted the Nx package in the npm registry. Malicious versions were published using a stolen npm token, leading to potential exfiltration of developer credentials. 🔍 The Nx team quickly removed the compromised packages, but Vercel customers are generally safe unless specific conditions were met. 👉 For detailed information, visit the GitHub advisory from the Nx team. Stay vigilant! #SupplyChainAttack #CyberSecurity #NxPackages #Vercel #DeveloperSafety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30-day runtime log retention, now available in Observability Plus</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7230/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7230/</guid>
      <description>📊 Exciting news for Observability Plus users! Teams can now access 30 days of runtime log retention, which includes valuable details on requests, Vercel Functions, and cache activity. This feature allows you to view, query, and share up to 14 consecutive days of log data at once. Best of all, this extended retention comes at no extra cost for Pro and Enterprise plans! Learn more about Runtime Logs and how to utilize this feature. #ObservabilityPlus #LogRetention #DataInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devin, Raycast, Windsurf, and Goose now supported on Vercel MCP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6342/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6342/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! You can now integrate Devin, Raycast, Windsurf, and Goose with Vercel&amp;rsquo;s Model Context Protocol (MCP). This allows for secure access to AI clients approved by Vercel. To get started, follow the installation steps for each client. Discover how to enhance your projects with Vercel MCP! #Vercel #AIIntegration #WebDevelopment #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-powered prototyping with design systems</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6306/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6306/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking the potential of AI in prototyping means speeding up collaboration and maintaining brand consistency. While many AI tools excel in speed and teamwork, they often fall short in producing on-brand designs. This gap arises from a lack of context about design components. To bridge this gap, a design system tailored for AI can help create prototypes that are both brand-aware and production-ready. Discover how to enhance your prototyping process! #AIDesign #Prototyping #DesignSystems&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy xmcp servers with zero-configuration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6307/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6307/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel now supports xmcp, a framework for building MCP servers using TypeScript with zero configuration. 📁 It utilizes file-based routing, making it easy to develop tools for your MCP server. You can create tools simply by adding a file with a default export. 🛠️ Learn more about deploying xmcp to Vercel in the documentation. #Vercel #xmcp #TypeScript #WebDevelopment #MCPServers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Gateway is now generally available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5777/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5777/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI Gateway is now available! This new tool offers a unified API to access hundreds of AI models with features like transparent pricing and built-in observability. Key benefits include sub-20ms latency, automatic failover, and detailed usage analytics. You can use the AI SDK or an OpenAI-compatible endpoint to get started quickly. Discover more about AI Gateway today! #AIGateway #AIModels #TechNews #Innovation #APIs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Gateway: Production-ready reliability for your AI apps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5776/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5776/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Building AI apps just got easier! With tools like the AI SDK, developers can create both frontends and backends in minutes. However, moving to production poses challenges, especially with reliability. Connecting to a single LLM provider can create risks if that provider faces downtime or rate limits. Introducing AI Gateway: it ensures consistent availability and stability for AI workloads, having already supported millions of users. #AIGateway #AIApps #TechInnovation #Reliability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Streamdown: Open source Markdown for AI streaming</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5778/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5778/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Streamdown: a new open-source Markdown renderer tailored for AI streaming! Streamdown enhances the AI Elements Response component and can also function as a standalone option for developers. It effectively manages unterminated chunks, interactive code blocks, and math expressions. Key features include: - Tailwind typography styles - GitHub Flavored Markdown support - Interactive code blocks with Shiki highlighting - LaTeX math support - Enhanced security for untrusted content&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&lt;script type=&#34;text/llms.txt&#34;&gt;</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5082/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5082/</guid>
      <description>Discover a new approach for AI agents interacting with protected pages. The emerging standard, llms.txt, proposes including instructions directly in HTML responses using the &lt;script type=&#34;text/llms.txt&#34;&gt; tag. This could simplify how AIs access and consume documentation without relying on external sources. Learn more about this innovative concept! 💻📄 #AI #HTML #llms #Innovation #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking prototyping, requirements, and project delivery at Code and Theory</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5083/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5083/</guid>
      <description>Code and Theory is a digital agency that integrates strategy, design, and engineering. Their team consists of equal parts creatives and engineers, working on projects for major brands like Microsoft and Amazon. They focus on creating scalable digital experiences and utilize a method called v0 to streamline the process from concept to functioning software. Learn more about their innovative approach! 🌐💻 #DigitalAgency #Prototyping #Innovation #Tech #ProjectDelivery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents can now access protected deployments via Vercel’s MCP server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5084/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5084/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel has introduced two new tools in its MCP server. The &lt;strong&gt;get_access_to_vercel_url&lt;/strong&gt; feature allows agents to generate a temporary shareable URL, enabling access to Vercel Auth-protected deployments without login credentials. Additionally, the &lt;strong&gt;web_fetch_vercel_url&lt;/strong&gt; tool lets agents fetch content directly from protected deployments, even when access would normally be denied. Explore these features to streamline your development process! #Vercel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node.js Vercel Functions now support fetch web handlers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5086/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5086/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel Functions on the Node.js runtime now support fetch web handlers. This enhancement boosts interoperability across various JavaScript frameworks and runtimes. You can still choose to export individual HTTP methods if that suits your project better. For further details, check out the documentation! 📚 #NodeJS #Vercel #WebDevelopment #JavaScript #APIs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If agents are building your app, who gets the W-2?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5087/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5087/</guid>
      <description>Autonomous coding agents are changing the software development landscape. 🤖 These agents can now fully design, build, test, and deploy features without human intervention. However, current U.S. GAAP regulations have not fully adapted to this technology. While third-party software costs can be capitalized, developer tools are often classified as overhead. It&amp;rsquo;s essential to consider how to treat work done by these agents in a manner similar to salaried engineers. #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Native support for SvelteKit&#39;s new OpenTelemetry spans</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5089/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5089/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has added native support for SvelteKit&amp;rsquo;s new server-side OpenTelemetry spans. To begin, users can activate experimental tracing in SvelteKit and set up a tracing instrumentation file with the Vercel OpenTelemetry collector. Generated traces will now include built-in SvelteKit spans, and other collectors can also be configured. For further details, check the SvelteKit observability documentation. 📊 #SvelteKit #OpenTelemetry #Vercel #WebDevelopment #Observability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Sandbox increases concurrency and port limits</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5088/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5088/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has enhanced its Sandbox capabilities for Pro and Enterprise teams! Now, users can run up to 2,000 Sandboxes concurrently, a significant increase from the previous limit of 150. Each Sandbox can also expose up to 4 ports for external access. This improvement allows for better handling of traffic spikes, untrusted code execution, and more complex applications. For projects needing even higher limits, contacting the sales team is an option. Learn more in the Vercel Sandbox docs! 📊🔧&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved fake hardware detection with Vercel BotID</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5091/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5091/</guid>
      <description>Vercel has enhanced its BotID Deep Analysis with an updated detection model. This improvement expands fingerprinting coverage for headless browsers and simulated device hardware, allowing for better identification of advanced bots. The upgraded model works in real-time without disrupting genuine users. Current users can benefit from these updates immediately by upgrading to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:botid@1.5.2&#34;&gt;botid@1.5.2&lt;/a&gt;. 🔍🤖🚀 #BotID #CyberSecurity #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Coxwave delivers GenAI value faster with Vercel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4935/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4935/</guid>
      <description>Coxwave is revolutionizing the development of GenAI products for enterprises. 🚀 Their consulting arm, AX, and analytics platform, Align, serve leading companies like Anthropic, Meta, Microsoft, and PwC. Since 2021, Coxwave has focused on speed—not just in model performance, but in iteration and value delivery. To enhance their web app strategy, they utilized Next.js and Vercel, enabling quicker results for their clients. #GenAI #Coxwave #Nextjs #Vercel #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Runtime Cache API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4938/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4938/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel has launched the Runtime Cache API, allowing you to store and retrieve data seamlessly across Functions, Routing Middleware, and Builds within the same region. This ephemeral cache offers tag-based invalidation for better cache management. You can monitor performance metrics like hit rates and storage usage in the Observability dashboard. Keep in mind, reads and writes are billed regionally based on your runtime area. Learn more in the documentation! 📊&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The real serverless compute to database connection problem, solved</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4936/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4936/</guid>
      <description>The article addresses a common misconception about serverless compute and its connection to traditional databases. It highlights that the challenge lies not in the number of connections during normal operation but in potential connection leaks when serverless functions are suspended. The piece provides clarity on the actual cause and offers a simple solution to this issue. 🔍💻🔗 #Serverless #Database #TechSolutions #CloudComputing #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The three types of AI bot traffic and how to handle them</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4937/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4937/</guid>
      <description>AI bot traffic is on the rise, and recent data identifies three types of AI-driven crawlers. These bots can enhance discoverability but may disrupt teams if not managed properly. 🤖 Understanding the role of these crawlers is vital. While some bots are beneficial, blocking them could lead to missed opportunities, similar to restricting early search engines. 🌐 As user behavior shifts towards seeking direct answers, sites that strategically manage bot access will gain a competitive edge. #AIBots&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-recharge available in AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4940/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4940/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Great news for Vercel users! The AI Gateway now offers an auto-recharge feature. This allows for automatic credit top-ups, ensuring your apps run smoothly without interruptions. You can easily enable or adjust this feature in the AI Gateway dashboard. Set your preferred top-up amount, trigger balance, and even a monthly spend limit to manage your credits efficiently. Learn more about this update! #Vercel #AIGateway #AutoRecharge #WebDevelopment #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Sonnet 4 now supports 1M token context in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4941/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4941/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Claude Sonnet 4 now offers a 1 million-token context window through Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway. This enhancement allows for larger inputs, such as extensive codebases and document sets. With a unified API, users can easily manage performance optimizations and track usage. The AI Gateway also supports built-in observability and intelligent provider routing for reliability. For implementation, simply install the AI SDK v5 and set up the model. #AI #Vercel #ClaudeSonnet4&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cutting delivery times in half with v0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4939/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4939/</guid>
      <description>Ready.net is enhancing utility company operations with its new feature, v0. This platform streamlines the process for managing financing and compliance with state-level stakeholders. Faced with urgent and often unclear requirements, Ready.net needed a solution to accelerate ideation, validation, and delivery. v0 is designed to cut delivery times significantly, supporting three teams with limited design resources. Learn more about this innovative approach! 🚀⚡️ #UtilityManagement #Innovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel BotID now leverages Vercel&#39;s verified bot directory</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4942/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4942/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! With the release of BotID 1.5.0, you can now access Vercel&amp;rsquo;s verified bot directory for deeper insights. This update enhances real-time detection of verified bots, allowing for secure programmatic decisions. The Deep Analysis mode provides key information like source IP range and user-agent validation, helping teams manage bot interactions effectively. Discover how BotID can improve your workflow! #BotID #Vercel #WebDevelopment #TechUpdates #Bots 🤖</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel&#39;s bot verification now supports Web Bot Auth</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4943/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4943/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has enhanced its bot verification system by supporting Web Bot Auth, developed through collaboration with industry partners. This new protocol uses HTTP Message Signatures for verifying traffic from various automated sources. It helps maintain a curated directory of verified bots, ensuring legitimate ones access your site while blocking spoofed bots. Web Bot Auth uses public-key cryptography to authenticate bots, including popular tools like SEO crawlers and AI bots. Notably,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add context when using Instant Rollback</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4944/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4944/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New feature alert! You can now add context when performing an Instant Rollback. This allows you to include a reason visible to your team in the project overview. You can even incorporate links or notes for clarity. Plus, updates can be made at any time! Learn more about enhancing your rollback process. #InstantRollback #ProjectManagement #TeamCollaboration #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>v0.dev -&gt; v0.app</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4838/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4838/</guid>
      <description>Transform your ideas into deployed apps with ease using v0.app! 🚀 With just one prompt, v0 streamlines the process by providing UI, content, backend, and logic. It also offers support for research, debugging, and planning. From product managers to recruiters, v0 is revolutionizing team operations. #AppDevelopment #TechInnovation #Teamwork #Productivity #v0app</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cursor now supported on Vercel MCP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-09-4791/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-09-4791/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Great news for developers! Cursor is now compatible with Vercel&amp;rsquo;s Model Context Protocol (MCP). With this integration, you can easily explore projects, inspect deployments, and fetch logs directly from Cursor. 🔍 To get started, simply follow the one-click setup or update your .cursor/mcp.json file. A Vercel account login will be required. Learn more about using Cursor with Vercel MCP! #Vercel #Cursor #DevTools #MCP #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk upgrade deprecated Node.js versions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4733/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4733/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Upgrade your Node.js projects easily! Team owners can now update all projects using Node.js 18 or earlier to Node.js 22 with just one click in the Vercel Dashboard. Remember, if your project specifies a version in package.json, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to update it manually. Existing deployments remain unaffected. Check out your deprecated Node.js projects today! #Nodejs #Vercel #TechUpdate #WebDevelopment #SoftwareEngineering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Zapier scales product partnerships with v0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4730/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4730/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Zapier is enhancing product partnerships with its v0 tool, streamlining how SaaS and AI companies can integrate automation. This innovation allows partners to embed Zapier&amp;rsquo;s automation engine directly into their products without extensive in-house integration work. With v0, the Powered by Zapier team can now create high-fidelity demos in just hours, leading to quicker implementation and more integrations. #Automation #Partnerships #SaaS #Innovation #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved metrics search in Observability Plus</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4731/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4731/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in Vercel Observability! The metrics search and navigation experience has been enhanced. You can now quickly find metrics using partial names or abbreviations like TTFB (time to first byte). Additional features include a side-by-side view of all metrics for an event, keyboard shortcuts for faster navigation, and a mobile-optimized interface. These updates are available now for all teams using Observability Plus. #Vercel #Observability #TechUpdates #Metrics #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>vlt is now available in builds via zero configuration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4732/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4732/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel now supports the vlt package manager for builds without the need for configuration. 📂 Projects with a vlt-lock.json file will automatically execute vlt install as the default Install Command. 🔧 Note: vlt requires Node 20.x and is available only in the modern build image. Learn more about this new feature on Vercel! #Vercel #vlt #WebDevelopment #PackageManager #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-5, GPT-5-mini, and GPT-5-nano are now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4736/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4736/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s GPT-5, GPT-5-mini, and GPT-5-nano are now accessible via Vercel AI Gateway. This platform allows seamless model integration without needing multiple provider accounts. Users can easily track usage, costs, and optimize performance. To get started, install the AI SDK v5 and select your preferred model. Explore more about the AI Gateway and its features! 🌐✨ #OpenAI #Vercel #AIGateway #GPT5 #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel collaborates with OpenAI for GPT-5 launch</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4734/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4734/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has partnered with OpenAI to launch the GPT-5 family of models! These models are now available through AI Gateway and in production on v0.dev. Vercel has been testing GPT-5 in various environments, and the results indicate improved frontend design capabilities. GPT-5 generates clean, composable code and enhances workflows, particularly with long-context reasoning and tool handling. Vercel is already integrating GPT-5 into its dashboard and other applications. #Vercel #OpenAI #GPT5&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel is the only vendor to be recognized as a Visionary in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud-Native Application Platforms</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4735/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4735/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Vercel has been recognized as a Visionary in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud-Native Application Platforms. With over 4M weekly active domains and 115B requests served, Vercel’s AI Cloud empowers teams to create fast and secure applications effortlessly. This acknowledgment underscores Vercel&amp;rsquo;s role in shaping the future of web development. #CloudComputing #Gartner #WebDevelopment #Vercel #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AI Elements: build AI interfaces faster</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4693/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4693/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for frontend engineers! Vercel has launched AI Elements, a tool designed to simplify the process of building AI interfaces. With this new product, developers can create ChatGPT or v0-like interfaces in just minutes. This innovation aims to streamline the app-building process, allowing teams to focus on functionality over design complexity. #AIElements #Vercel #FrontendDevelopment #TechInnovation #AIInterfaces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AI Elements: Prebuilt, composable AI SDK components</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4171/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4171/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing AI Elements, a new open-source library designed for customizable React components! Built on shadcn/ui, it allows developers to create interfaces using the Vercel AI SDK. Key features include control over UI elements like message threads and input boxes. To get started, simply initialize with our CLI, choose your components, and begin building. For detailed guidance, check out the documentation. #AI #OpenSource #React #Vercel #Development</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Vercel MCP: Connect Vercel to your AI tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4161/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4161/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel has launched its MCP server, now in Public Beta. This secure interface allows AI tools to connect with your Vercel projects seamlessly. With Vercel MCP, tools like Cursor and Claude can access project logs, documents, and metadata directly, enhancing your workflow. Discover more about this innovative development! #Vercel #AIDevelopment #MCP #TechNews #DeveloperTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microfrontends support is now in Public Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4162/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4162/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Microfrontends support is now in Public Beta! This feature allows developers to split large applications into smaller, manageable parts, enabling faster development and independent testing. Vercel simplifies the assembly and routing of these microfrontends into a cohesive user experience. To get started, users can clone examples from the Vercel dashboard, create microfrontend groups, and configure their projects with ease. For more details, check the documentation or contact Vercel support&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Opus 4.1 is now supported in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4163/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4163/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Claude Opus 4.1 is now accessible via Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway without the need for additional provider accounts. This new model enhances task execution, coding, and reasoning compared to its predecessor. AI Gateway offers a unified API, usage tracking, and performance optimizations for improved reliability. Start using it with the AI SDK v5 by installing the package and setting the model to anthropic/claude-4.1-opus. Learn more about the AI Gateway and explore the new model&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gpt-oss-20b and gpt-oss-120b are now supported in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4164/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4164/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Vercel AI Gateway now supports OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s gpt-oss-20b and gpt-oss-120b models. These open-weight reasoning models enhance access with a unified API, simplifying usage tracking and performance optimizations. 💻 Developers can easily integrate them using AI SDK v5, with built-in observability and support for multiple model providers. Discover more about AI Gateway and check out the new model leaderboard! 📊 #Vercel #OpenAI #AIModels #TechNews #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New custom visualization in Vercel Observability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4167/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4167/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Observability Plus users! You can now customize your data visualizations with options like line charts, volume charts, tables, or big numbers. 📊 Both queries and visualization settings can be saved in shareable notebooks, enhancing teamwork. This update is available at no extra cost for Observability Plus teams. Explore the new features today! #DataVisualization #Observability #TechUpdate #Vercel #Collaboration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>v0: vibe coding, securely</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4165/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4165/</guid>
      <description>Vibe coding is transforming software development, allowing rapid prototyping with tools like v0. Anthropic&amp;rsquo;s CEO indicates that in just 3-6 months, 90% of code may be AI-generated. However, this speed can lead to significant risks. A recent incident involved a viral app that leaked 72,000 selfies and IDs due to misconfigured settings, emphasizing the need for security measures. #VibeCoding #SoftwareDevelopment #CyberSecurity #AI #TechNews 🚀🔒📱</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel MCP now in Public Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4166/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4166/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel&amp;rsquo;s Model Control Protocol (MCP) server is now in Public Beta! The server, accessible at mcp.vercel.com, offers a remote interface with OAuth-based authorization, allowing secure interactions with AI tools and Vercel projects. It supports AI assistants like Claude.ai and integrates with tools such as VS Code to help manage projects, analyze deployment logs, and navigate documentation. This update aims to enhance collaboration between AI workflows and the Vercel ecosystem. For more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new wave of software, shipped on Vercel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-4168/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-4168/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A new initiative, &amp;ldquo;Shipped on Vercel,&amp;rdquo; highlights innovative apps currently in production on the Vercel platform. This platform showcases teams that are reimagining web development, offering insights into their creative processes and technologies used. Discover how these real-world applications are shaping the future of the web! 🌐 #Vercel #WebDevelopment #Innovation #TechTrends #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Hono backends with zero configuration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-4169/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-4169/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel now offers native support for Hono, a lightweight backend framework, with zero configuration required. This integration allows Vercel to optimize Hono applications for builds and deployments, enhancing performance. New deployments benefit from features like Fluid compute, Active CPU pricing, and automatic cold start optimizations. For more details, check out Hono&amp;rsquo;s Vercel documentation. #Hono #Vercel #BackendDevelopment #WebStandards #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI SDK 5</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4170/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4170/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The AI SDK 5 is making waves with over 2 million weekly downloads! This open-source toolkit for TypeScript and JavaScript offers a unified provider API, allowing developers to utilize any language model easily. It also supports powerful integrations with popular web frameworks. Explore the potential of AI SDK 5 for your projects! #AISDK #OpenSource #WebDevelopment #JavaScript #TypeScript</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Open Source Program: Summer cohort</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4737/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4737/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Vercel! The Vercel Open Source Program has announced its summer 2025 cohort. This initiative supports developers by providing resources, credits, and assistance to enhance their projects. This season features 28 innovative projects, including AI-powered calendars and stylish React Native components. Learn more about these amazing contributions! #Vercel #OpenSource #DeveloperCommunity #Innovation #TechForGood</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
