<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Robinhood-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/robinhood-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Robinhood-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 12:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/robinhood-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood’s Money Drills Levels the Financial Playing Field: Expanding Financial Education to New Campuses and More Athletes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9816/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9816/</guid>
      <description>📚 Exciting news in financial education! Robinhood&amp;rsquo;s Money Drills program is expanding to four new campuses: University of Delaware, University of North Carolina Chapel Hill, Pennsylvania State University, and Stanford University. This initiative aims to provide students, especially athletes, with essential financial skills. The program focuses on budgeting, saving, investing, and managing NIL income, contributing to a financially literate generation. Since its launch, 96% of students have&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Robinhood Ventures</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9642/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 12:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9642/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Robinhood! Introducing Robinhood Ventures Fund I (RVI), a new initiative aimed at expanding retail access to private markets. This closed-end fund will allow everyday investors to invest in private companies, previously accessible only to elite investors. The SEC has received a registration statement for RVI, which will focus on a concentrated portfolio of innovative private firms. Retail investors can expect to trade shares under the symbol RVI on the NYSE. For more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood Unveils Powerful New Tools for Active Traders at HOOD Summit 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9503/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9503/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Robinhood has launched exciting new tools for active traders at the HOOD Summit 2025! Introducing &lt;strong&gt;Robinhood Social&lt;/strong&gt;, a community feature offering live, verified trades and discussions on strategies. Users can follow traders, track real performance, and connect with market insiders. 🔍 &lt;strong&gt;Robinhood Legend&lt;/strong&gt; also sees enhancements with AI-powered indicators, futures trading, and expanded asset options, all aimed at improving trading analysis. These features will roll out early next year to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood Launches Pro and College Football Prediction Markets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5033/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5033/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Robinhood has launched pro and college football prediction markets in its app! Since the introduction of prediction markets last year, over 2 billion contracts have been traded. Now, users can trade outcomes for popular football games, including all regular season pro matchups and college Power 4 schools. These markets will be available for eligible customers soon, with contracts for the first two weeks of the season. Unlike traditional sports betting, these contracts allow customers to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Digests by Robinhood Cortex for customers in the UK</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5036/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5036/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for UK investors! Robinhood has launched Digests powered by Robinhood Cortex, an AI-driven feature that explains stock movements in clear language. This tool reviews news, analyst reports, and proprietary data to help users make informed decisions. Available for free on stock detail pages, Digests aims to support investors of all experience levels. For more details, visit the Help Centre. #InvestSmart #StockMarket #AI #Robinhood #UKInvestors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood Presents: HOOD Summit ‘25 – Enter the Mainframe</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4710/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4710/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Robinhood! Join us for the second annual HOOD Summit in Las Vegas on September 9-10. This event will showcase new technology and trading tools for active traders. 📅 Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the keynote by CEO Vlad Tenev on September 9 at 5:30 PM PT, available via livestream. 📈 On September 10, industry leaders will share insights on active trading. Celebrate with HOOD Month starting August 19, featuring special promotions! For more details, visit events.robinhood.com/presents-&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
