<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google-Developers-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/google-developers-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google-Developers-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/google-developers-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Under the Hood: Universal Commerce Protocol (UCP)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-11-14407/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-11-14407/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing the Universal Commerce Protocol (UCP), a new open-source standard for agentic commerce co-developed by Google and industry leaders. UCP connects consumer surfaces like Gemini and AI Mode in Search with business backends, streamlining the shopping experience from product discovery to purchase. This protocol supports various payment providers and offers flexible integration options for businesses through APIs and other methods. With endorsements from over 20 global partners, UCP&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Developer&#39;s Guide to Debugging JAX on Cloud TPUs: Essential Tools and Techniques</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14242/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14242/</guid>
      <description>🔍 A new guide for debugging JAX on Cloud TPUs is here! This article discusses essential tools and techniques for effective debugging in distributed cloud environments. Key components include libtpu, JAX, and jaxlib, which help in accessing logs and hardware metrics. Highlighted tools include Verbose Logging, TPU Monitoring Library, tpu-info for utilization metrics, XLA HLO Dumps for compiler debugging, and the XProf suite for performance analysis. Explore how these tools can enhance your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-World Agent Examples with Gemini 3</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14070/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14070/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Gemini 3 is revolutionizing AI agents with advanced capabilities for real-world tasks. This article highlights six open-source frameworks, such as ADK and Agno, showcasing practical workflows for browser automation, deep search, and more. Developers can clone these examples to build their own agentic systems. Explore how Gemini 3 enhances reliability and state management in complex AI applications. #AIAgents #Gemini3 #OpenSource #Automation #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conductor: Introducing context-driven development for Gemini CLI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-14007/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-14007/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Conductor, the new Gemini CLI extension for context-driven development! This tool shifts project context from chat logs to persistent Markdown files, allowing teams to create formal specs and plans. Conductor ensures AI agents align with project goals and style while maintaining developer control. It’s ideal for both new and existing projects! #GeminiCLI #ContextDrivenDevelopment #AI #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini 3 Flash is now available in Gemini CLI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13946/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13946/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Gemini 3 Flash is now live in Gemini CLI! This new addition offers pro-grade coding performance with a SWE-bench Verified score of 78%. It excels in auto-routing and agentic coding, making it ideal for high-frequency development tasks. Access is available for most paid tier customers, with gradual rollout for free tier users. Upgrade your Gemini CLI to version 0.21.1 to get started! #Gemini3Flash #Coding #AI #GeminiCLI #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Agent Development Kit for TypeScript: Build AI Agents with the Power of a Code-First Approach</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13963/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13963/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The Agent Development Kit (ADK) for TypeScript is now available. This open-source framework allows for the creation of multi-agent AI systems using a code-first approach. With ADK, developers can apply best practices like version control and testing while building their AI agents. It simplifies the process with modular components, making it easy to define agent logic directly in TypeScript. Get started with ADK and enhance your AI projects! #AI #TypeScript&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer’s guide to multi-agent patterns in ADK</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13915/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13915/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of multi-agent systems with the latest guide on using the Agent Development Kit (ADK)! 🚀 This article discusses the importance of decentralization in AI, highlighting how multi-agent design patterns enhance modularity and reliability. It introduces 8 key patterns, including the Sequential Pipeline, which simplifies data processing by assigning specific roles to agents. With practical examples and pseudocode, developers can build efficient agent teams that minimize errors&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing A2UI: An open project for agent-driven interfaces</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13916/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13916/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing A2UI: an open-source project focused on agent-driven interfaces! A2UI allows agents to generate custom UIs for various platforms, enhancing interaction quality. This project aims to solve challenges in cross-platform, generative UI responses, enabling seamless updates and native styling. The initiative invites community collaboration to refine specifications and expand integrations across frameworks like Flutter and Angular. Explore the future of user interfaces! 🌐💡 #A2UI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MediaTek NPU and LiteRT: Powering the next generation of on-device AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13567/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13567/</guid>
      <description>🚀 MediaTek and LiteRT have introduced the LiteRT NeuroPilot Accelerator, designed to enhance on-device AI capabilities. This new solution enables seamless deployment and advanced performance for large language models across various devices, including smartphones and IoT products. The NPU technology drives significant improvements in processing power while minimizing energy consumption, making sophisticated AI models more accessible. #MediaTek #AI #NPU #TechInnovation #LiteRT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architecting efficient context-aware multi-agent framework for production</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13461/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13461/</guid>
      <description>🔍 The AI landscape is evolving, with organizations deploying multi-agent systems for complex tasks. However, managing context has become a significant challenge. 🔧 ADK introduces &lt;strong&gt;Context Engineering&lt;/strong&gt;, a new approach that treats context as a separate system. This architecture focuses on efficient processing, compaction, and caching to enhance AI performance. 💡 By enabling scoped context handoffs, this method aims to improve reliability and cost-effectiveness in production environments. #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Data Commons Gemini CLI extension</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13274/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13274/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! The new Data Commons extension for Gemini CLI simplifies access to public data. Users can now ask complex questions in natural language, querying a vast repository of datasets from trusted sources like the UN and World Bank. This helps ground LLM responses and minimize AI errors. The extension allows for quick data analysis and easy integration with other tools. Explore the world of public data effortlessly! 📊🔍 #DataCommons #GeminiCLI #PublicData #AI #DataAnalysis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Gemini API updates for Gemini 3</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13050/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13050/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are here for the Gemini API with the launch of Gemini 3! Developers can now leverage the new &lt;code&gt;thinking_level&lt;/code&gt; parameter to control the depth of reasoning, enhancing task complexity management. The &lt;code&gt;media_resolution&lt;/code&gt; setting allows customization of token usage for various media types, balancing quality and efficiency. Additionally, the introduction of &lt;code&gt;Thought Signatures&lt;/code&gt; improves function calling and image generation. Combined with Google Search/URL Grounding, these updates&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Peak Performance on Qualcomm NPU with LiteRT</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12991/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12991/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking on-device GenAI performance is now possible with LiteRT&amp;rsquo;s Qualcomm AI Engine Direct (QNN) Accelerator. 🚀 This innovation allows for up to 100x speedup over CPU, enabling real-time AI experiences on Android devices. FastVLM-0.5B achieves impressive rates of over 11,000 tokens/sec on Snapdragon 8 Elite Gen 5 NPU. The NPU, found in over 80% of recent Qualcomm SoCs, provides dedicated AI compute, enhancing mobile performance while conserving battery life. 🔋 #GenAI #Qualcomm #NPU #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build with Google Antigravity, our new agentic development platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12911/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12911/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Google Antigravity, a new development platform designed to enhance coding efficiency. This platform combines an AI-powered Editor View with a Manager Surface, allowing agents to autonomously plan, execute, and verify tasks across various environments. Antigravity is now available in public preview, enabling developers to streamline their workflow and delegate complex tasks easily. Learn more about the future of coding! #GoogleAntigravity #Development #AI #Coding #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI Agents with Google Gemini 3 and Open Source Frameworks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12861/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12861/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in AI with the introduction of Gemini 3 Pro Preview! This powerful model enhances (semi)-autonomous workflows through new features like &lt;code&gt;thinking_level&lt;/code&gt; for better reasoning control and Stateful Tool Use via Thought Signatures. It supports major open-source frameworks from Day 0. Key practices include simplifying prompts and maintaining a temperature setting of 1.0 for optimal performance. #AIAgents #Gemini3 #OpenSource #TechInnovation #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building production AI on Google Cloud TPUs with JAX</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12862/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12862/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover the JAX AI Stack, a modular platform designed for scalable machine learning on Google Cloud TPUs. Built on the JAX library, it includes essential tools like Flax, Optax, and Orbax, enabling efficient model development and production. Learn more about its architecture and benefits in the detailed technical report. #AI #MachineLearning #GoogleCloud #JAX #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jules &#43; Gemini 3</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12877/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12877/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for Jules users! Gemini 3 is now part of the software development agent, enhancing clarity and reliability. Key improvements include parallel CLI runs, a stable API, and safer Git handling. Upcoming features will allow directory attachments without GitHub and automatic PR creation, making development smoother. #SoftwareDevelopment #Jules #Gemini3 #TechUpdates #DeveloperTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 things to try with Gemini 3 Pro in Gemini CLI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12770/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12770/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Gemini 3 Pro is now integrated into Gemini CLI. This upgrade enhances terminal performance with smart reasoning and agentic coding, boosting productivity for complex engineering tasks. It&amp;rsquo;s currently available for Google AI Ultra subscribers and those with a paid Gemini API key. Upgrade your CLI to version 0.16.x to start using these new features today! #Gemini3Pro #GeminiCLI #DeveloperTools #AI #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 things to try with Gemini 3 Pro in Gemini CLI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12797/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12797/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Gemini 3 Pro is now integrated into Gemini CLI, enhancing developer productivity with advanced features! Users can generate 3D apps from visual sketches, run complex shell commands, and debug live Cloud Run services. It&amp;rsquo;s available for Google AI Ultra and paid Gemini API key subscribers. Upgrade your CLI to version 0.16.x to start using these capabilities today! #Gemini3Pro #DeveloperTools #AI #Productivity #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Colab is Coming to VS Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12140/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12140/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Google Colab has launched an official extension for Visual Studio Code. This integration allows users to connect local notebooks to Colab&amp;rsquo;s powerful runtimes, including GPUs and TPUs. It merges the popular features of VS Code with Colab&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, enhancing productivity for AI/ML projects. Now, developers can work seamlessly within their preferred environment! #GoogleColab #VSCODE #AI #ML #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Code Wiki: Accelerating your code understanding</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12141/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12141/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Code Wiki, a new platform designed to enhance code understanding! It provides a continuously updated wiki for code repositories, featuring hyper-linked documentation and a Gemini-powered chat agent tailored to your repo. A public preview is available for open-source projects, with a Gemini CLI extension for private repos coming soon. #CodeWiki #SoftwareDevelopment #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Metrax: performant, efficient, and robust model evaluation metrics in JAX</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12153/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12153/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Metrax: a new metrics library from Google designed for JAX. Metrax standardizes model evaluation with robust metrics for classification, NLP, and vision. It eliminates the need for manual re-implementation as teams migrate from TensorFlow. Key features include parallel computation of &amp;ldquo;at K&amp;rdquo; metrics and strong integration with the JAX AI Stack. Metrax is open-source and already in use by major Google teams. #MachineLearning #JAX #AI #OpenSource #Google</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making the terminal beautiful one pixel at a time</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12159/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12159/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Google has unveiled the redesigned &lt;strong&gt;Android AI Sample Catalog&lt;/strong&gt;, an open-source app for Android developers. It features examples using both on-device and cloud models, including image generation and chatbots. The code is easy to use, helping developers kickstart their projects. Additionally, the Gemini CLI has received a significant upgrade, enhancing user experience with smoother rendering and mouse navigation. #AndroidDevelopment #AI #GeminiCLI #OpenSource #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Request-Response: Architecting Real-time Bidirectional Streaming Multi-agent System</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11515/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11515/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the limitations of the traditional request-response model for AI agents, the article advocates for a real-time bidirectional streaming architecture. This approach, implemented by the Agent Development Kit (ADK), supports true concurrency and seamless multimodal processing. Key features include real-time I/O management and stateful sessions for efficient agent handoffs. The shift to this model aims to enhance interactivity and responsiveness in multi-agent systems. 🔗🤖💡 #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Jules extension for Gemini CLI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11465/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11465/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The Jules extension for Gemini CLI is now available. This autonomous sidekick helps streamline your coding workflow by handling tasks like asynchronous work, bug fixes, and branch changes while you focus on your main tasks in Gemini CLI. To get started, install the extension and use the /jules command to initiate tasks and check their status. Check it out on GitHub! #GeminiCLI #JulesExtension #CodingWorkflow #DevTools #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Veo 3.1 and new creative capabilities in the Gemini API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10963/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10963/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Google has launched Veo 3.1 and Veo 3.1 Fast in paid preview through the Gemini API. This updated video generation model enhances audio quality and narrative control, allowing for improved cinematic outputs. Notable features include guiding video creation with reference images and generating seamless transitions. Companies like Promise Studios and Latitude are already leveraging these capabilities for innovative applications. #GoogleAI #Veo31 #VideoGeneration #GeminiAPI #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Say hello to a new level of interactivity in Gemini CLI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10962/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10962/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The Gemini CLI has received an upgrade that enhances interactivity within the terminal. Now, you can run complex commands like vim, top, and git rebase directly in Gemini CLI, eliminating the need to switch terminals. This improvement utilizes pseudo-terminal (PTY) support, allowing commands to run within Gemini CLI&amp;rsquo;s context, making your workflow smoother and more efficient. Check out this new feature and elevate your command-line experience! #GeminiCLI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Coral NPU: A full-stack platform for Edge AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10930/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10930/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Coral NPU, a new full-stack platform tailored for Edge AI. It aims to tackle challenges in performance, fragmentation, and user trust in low-power devices. Designed for wearables and IoT, Coral NPU enables contextual awareness and audio/image processing while prioritizing user privacy. Synaptics is the first partner to implement this innovative technology. Explore the future of always-on AI! 🌐🤖🔋 #CoralNPU #EdgeAI #IoT #Privacy #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Genkit Extension for Gemini CLI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10548/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10548/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI developers! The new Genkit Extension for Gemini CLI is now available. This extension enhances command line capabilities with deep knowledge of Genkit&amp;rsquo;s architecture, allowing for easier building, debugging, and iteration of AI applications. With features like context-aware assistance and direct integration with Genkit’s tools, developers can streamline their workflow directly from the terminal. To install, use: `gemini extensions install &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/gemini-cli-&#34;&gt;https://github.com/gemini-cli-&lt;/a&gt;&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Own your AI: Learn how to fine-tune Gemma 3 270M and run it on-device</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10571/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10571/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news for developers! Learn how to fine-tune the Gemma 3 270M model for custom tasks, such as creating an emoji translator. This guide offers a step-by-step process to optimize and run the model on-device for a fast and private user experience. Key steps include fine-tuning, quantizing for efficiency, and deploying in a web app using MediaPipe or Transformers.js. Unlock the potential of AI with accessible technology! 🚀🤖 #AI #MachineLearning #Gemma3 #WebDevelopment #OnDeviceAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level Up Your Dev Game: The Jules API is Here!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10420/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10420/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The Jules API has launched to enhance your workflow. This new tool automates, integrates, and innovates throughout the software development lifecycle. Key features include: - &lt;strong&gt;Source&lt;/strong&gt;: Use your GitHub repository for input. - &lt;strong&gt;Session&lt;/strong&gt;: Start a project with your coding agent. - &lt;strong&gt;Activity&lt;/strong&gt;: Track individual steps within a session. With Jules API, you can create custom bots for tasks like fixing bugs directly from Slack or managing backlog items. Ready to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini 2.5 Flash Image now ready for production with new aspect ratios</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10392/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10392/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! The Gemini 2.5 Flash Image is now ready for production. This advanced image generation model introduces new features, including support for 10 different aspect ratios, enhancing creative flexibility for users. It allows for seamless blending of images and precise editing through natural language. Access Gemini 2.5 via the Gemini API on Google AI Studio and Vertex AI. #Gemini25 #ImageGeneration #AI #CreativeTools #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Jules Tools: A Command Line Companion for Google’s Async Coding Agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10391/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10391/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! You can now interact with Jules, Google’s asynchronous coding agent, directly through the command line. Jules Tools offers a lightweight interface that integrates with your repositories, allowing you to manage tasks like writing tests, fixing bugs, and more, all within your workflow. To get started, simply install via npm: &lt;code&gt;npm install -g jules-tools&lt;/code&gt; #Google #JulesTools #CodingAgent #DevTools #CommandLine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini for Home: Expanding the Platform for a New Era of Smart Home AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10309/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10309/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in smart home technology! Google has introduced Gemini for Home, replacing the Google Assistant on devices and enhancing AI capabilities for cameras. This change aims to improve device integration and user experience. Developers can now access Gemini-powered features for over 800M devices. Testing existing integrations is crucial for a seamless transition. Stay tuned for tools to monitor device performance! #SmartHome #AI #GoogleHome #Gemini #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Multi-Spectral Data with Gemini</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10346/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10346/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of multi-spectral imagery with Google&amp;rsquo;s Gemini models! 🌍✨ This technology allows developers to analyze invisible wavelengths without needing specialized training. By mapping these bands to RGB channels, applications can monitor vegetation health, water quality, and more. Explore how Gemini simplifies access to complex satellite data, enhancing environmental monitoring and agriculture. #GoogleGemini #MultiSpectral #TechInnovation #EnvironmentalMonitoring #DataScience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Tunix: A JAX-Native Library for LLM Post-Training</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10246/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10246/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for JAX developers! Introducing Tunix, an open-source library designed to simplify post-training for large language models (LLMs). This toolkit offers a comprehensive suite of algorithms for tasks like Supervised Fine-Tuning and preference tuning. Tunix features a &amp;ldquo;white-box&amp;rdquo; design for full control and seamless integration with JAX, enhancing the developer experience. Check out the modular APIs included in this initial release! #Tunix #JAX #MachineLearning #AI #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apigee Operator for Kubernetes and GKE Inference Gateway integration for  Auth and AI/LLM policies</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10123/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking the power of generative AI relies heavily on APIs. 🌐 The GKE Inference Gateway enhances AI workloads with features like optimized load balancing, dynamic model serving, and autoscaling. It also prioritizes latency-sensitive requests and integrates AI safety checks. Discover how these tools streamline AI model management! 🤖📈 #AI #Kubernetes #GKE #APIs #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delight users by combining ADK Agents with Fancy Frontends using AG-UI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10124/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10124/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in AI integration! The Agent Development Kit (ADK) now works with AG-UI, enhancing how developers connect backend AI agents to user-friendly frontends. ADK simplifies agent creation with features like multi-step planning and state management. AG-UI standardizes communication, making it easier to build interactive experiences. This combination streamlines the process of creating collaborative AI applications. #AI #Developers #AGUI #ADK #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your AI is now a local expert: Grounding with Google Maps is now GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10125/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10125/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting update! Grounding with Google Maps in Vertex AI is now Generally Available (GA). This feature allows developers to create AI applications that utilize real-world information from Google Maps. It enhances the accuracy of model outputs, ensuring users receive reliable data for decision-making. Key benefits include timely updates on local businesses, personalized insights based on user queries, and improved business discovery using geospatial context. Developers can now leverage&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building the Next Generation of Physical Agents with Gemini Robotics-ER 1.5</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10102/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10102/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Gemini Robotics-ER 1.5 is now available, marking a significant advancement in robotics. This embodied reasoning model excels in visual and spatial understanding, task planning, and progress estimation. It can even access tools like Google Search to enhance task execution. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s sorting objects or more complex tasks, this model is designed to tackle real-world challenges. Get started today via Google AI Studio and the Gemini API! #Robotics #AI #Innovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuing to bring you our latest models, with an improved Gemini 2.5 Flash and Flash-Lite release</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10101/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10101/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Google has unveiled updated Gemini 2.5 Flash and Flash-Lite models, now available on Google AI Studio and Vertex AI. These releases promise enhanced quality, speed, and efficiency. Notably, the Flash-Lite version sees a 50% reduction in output tokens, helping lower costs. Developers can access the &amp;ldquo;-latest&amp;rdquo; alias for testing and feedback to influence future stable versions. #GoogleAI #Gemini2_5 #Innovation #TechUpdate #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Data Commons Model Context Protocol (MCP) Server: Streamlining Public Data Access for AI Developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10029/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10029/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Data Commons has launched the Model Context Protocol (MCP) Server, enhancing access to public datasets for AI developers globally. This server allows developers to easily integrate vast data without needing to navigate complex APIs. It aims to reduce hallucinations in AI models by providing reliable information. The MCP Server supports a range of data-driven queries, from exploratory to generative reports. Explore the possibilities with Gemini CLI today! #DataCommons&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On-device GenAI in Chrome, Chromebook Plus, and Pixel Watch with LiteRT-LM</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10028/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10028/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Google AI has unveiled LiteRT-LM, a new runtime for on-device generative AI, enhancing user experiences across Chrome, Chromebook Plus, and Pixel Watch. 💻 This innovative framework supports large language models, ensuring efficient performance even on resource-constrained devices. With its modular architecture, it enables capabilities like smart replies and WebAI. 🔧 Developers now have access to high-level APIs and a C++ interface, allowing for custom AI solutions tailored to their needs&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini CLI 🤝 FastMCP: Simplifying MCP server development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9864/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9864/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news for developers! Gemini CLI now integrates with FastMCP, a top Python library for Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers. This collaboration simplifies the connection of custom MCP tools directly to Gemini CLI. With FastMCP v2.12.3, use the command &lt;code&gt;fastmcp install gemini-cli&lt;/code&gt; to set up your local MCP servers easily. This integration streamlines configuration and dependency management, making server development more efficient. #GeminiCLI #FastMCP #MCPDevelopment #OpenSource&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A2A Extensions: Empowering Custom Agent Functionality</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9500/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9500/</guid>
      <description>A2A Extensions enhance agent-to-agent communication by allowing developers to add custom functionalities beyond the core protocol. These extensions support specialized features tailored to specific needs, making it easier for agents to meet unique requirements. 📈 Getting started is user-friendly; developers can define and publish extensions through a simple &amp;ldquo;Agent Card.&amp;rdquo; This fosters an open, community-driven ecosystem. 🌐 Current use cases, like the Traceability Extension, highlight the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Genkit Go 1.0 and Enhanced AI-Assisted Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9510/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9510/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Go developers! We are thrilled to announce the stable release of &lt;strong&gt;Genkit Go 1.0&lt;/strong&gt;. This open-source framework enables the creation of production-ready AI applications seamlessly. Key features include: - Type-safe AI flows - Unified model interface - Support for multiple model providers Additionally, the new &lt;strong&gt;genkit init:ai-tools&lt;/strong&gt; command enhances your AI development experience. Check out the latest tools and get started today! #GenkitGo #AIDevelopment #OpenSource&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond backpropagation: JAX&#39;s symbolic power unlocks new frontiers in scientific computing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9501/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9501/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JAX is expanding its role beyond AI model development, now making strides in scientific computing. Researchers are utilizing JAX to tackle complex Partial Differential Equations (PDEs), achieving notable speed and memory efficiency. Its support for composable transformations simplifies the computation of high-order derivatives, essential for advanced research. This shift towards JAX is helping scientists overcome computational challenges in areas like physics-informed machine learning&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini Batch API now supports Embeddings and OpenAI Compatibility</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9518/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9518/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The Gemini Batch API now supports the new Gemini Embedding model and OpenAI SDK, allowing for efficient batch processing. This enhancement offers asynchronous processing at 50% lower rates, ideal for high-volume use cases. You can access the Gemini Embedding model at just $0.075 per 1M input tokens. Start integrating with just a few lines of code! #GeminiAPI #OpenAI #Developers #TechUpdates #Embeddings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veo 3 and Veo 3 Fast – new pricing, new configurations and better resolution</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9456/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9456/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for Veo users! Veo 3 and Veo 3 Fast now support vertical format outputs (9:16 aspect ratio) and 1080p HD resolution. This is ideal for mobile and social media content. Additionally, pricing has been reduced: - Veo 3: $0.40/second (was $0.75) - Veo 3 Fast: $0.15/second (was $0.40) These changes enhance accessibility and video quality. #VeoUpdates #VideoProduction #TechNews #ContentCreation #HDVideo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Fine-Tuning to Production: A Scalable Embedding Pipeline with Dataflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7794/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7794/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Unlock the power of AI with Google&amp;rsquo;s new EmbeddingGemma! This 308M parameter open embedding model is designed for efficient on-device applications and cloud customization. It works seamlessly with Google Cloud&amp;rsquo;s Dataflow and vector databases like AlloyDB to create scalable, real-time knowledge ingestion pipelines. Learn how embeddings can enhance applications like semantic search and Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) by capturing the relationships between concepts. #AI #MachineLearning&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing EmbeddingGemma: The Best-in-Class Open Model for On-Device Embeddings</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7752/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7752/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing EmbeddingGemma, Google&amp;rsquo;s new open embedding model tailored for on-device AI applications. With 308 million parameters, it ranks highest among multilingual text models under 500M on the MTEB benchmark. This model supports advanced features like Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) and semantic search without needing an internet connection. EmbeddingGemma is optimized for efficiency, running on devices like smartphones and laptops. It offers customizable output dimensions and a 2K&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to prompt Gemini 2.5 Flash Image Generation for the best results</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7498/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7498/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of Gemini 2.5 Flash Image! 🌟 This advanced model combines text and image processing for seamless image generation. Key features include: - &lt;strong&gt;Text-to-image&lt;/strong&gt;: Create images from descriptions. - &lt;strong&gt;Image editing&lt;/strong&gt;: Use text to modify existing images. - &lt;strong&gt;Multi-image composition&lt;/strong&gt;: Combine multiple images into one. Learn how to write effective prompts to enhance results. Descriptive narratives yield better images than simple keywords. Start creating in Google AI Studio today!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the terminal: Gemini CLI comes to Zed</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7253/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7253/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Gemini CLI is now integrated into the Zed code editor. This partnership brings AI capabilities directly into your coding environment. With this integration, developers can generate and refactor code in real-time, and get instant answers to coding queries. The seamless workflow enhances productivity and efficiency. Explore the power of AI in your coding tasks with Gemini CLI in Zed! 💻✨ #GeminiCLI #Zed #AIinCoding #DeveloperTools #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop “vibe testing” your LLMs. It&#39;s time for real evals.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7292/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7292/</guid>
      <description>Stop relying on &amp;ldquo;vibe testing&amp;rdquo; for LLMs! Stax, a new developer tool, aims to improve AI evaluations by streamlining the testing process. It allows users to conduct thorough assessments and make data-driven decisions using human labeling and LLM-as-a-judge auto-raters. General benchmarks may not fit your specific needs. With Stax, you can create tailored evaluations that offer clear metrics for performance. #AI #LLM #Stax #Evaluation #TechInnovation 🤖📈🔍</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Gemini 2.5 Flash Image, our state-of-the-art image model</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7255/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7255/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Gemini 2.5 Flash Image! This advanced image generation and editing model allows users to blend multiple images seamlessly. It maintains character consistency for storytelling and enables targeted transformations through natural language. Available via the Gemini API, Google AI Studio, and Vertex AI, it is priced at $30 per million output tokens. #Gemini2.5 #AI #ImageEditing #GoogleAI #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s new in Gemini Code Assist</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5172/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5172/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Gemini Code Assist! Agent Mode is now available in VS Code (Preview) and IntelliJ (Stable), enhancing your coding experience. It offers a collaborative approach to complex tasks by proposing detailed plans for user review and approval. Key features include inline diffs for visual code modifications and persistent chat history to streamline workflows. This aims to boost developer productivity and efficiency significantly. #GeminiCodeAssist #DeveloperTools #Programming&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>URL context tool for Gemini API now generally available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5173/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5173/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Gemini API&amp;rsquo;s URL Context tool is now generally available for developers! This tool allows users to enhance prompts using web content, making applications more contextually aware. Key features include support for PDFs and images, expanding the types of content that can be grounded. The tool is now ready for scaled production use, with updated limits based on the specific Gemini model. #GeminiAPI #AI #TechUpdate #Developers #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Imagen 4 Fast and the general availability of the Imagen 4 family in the Gemini API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5174/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5174/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Google! Imagen 4, the advanced text-to-image model, is now generally available in the Gemini API and Google AI Studio. This update brings substantial improvements in text rendering, enhancing image generation quality. Introducing Imagen 4 Fast, designed for speed and efficiency, alongside Imagen 4 and Imagen 4 Ultra, which now support up to 2K resolution for detailed visuals. Explore the capabilities of the Imagen 4 family for your creative needs! 🎨✨ #GoogleAI #Imagen4&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Gemma 3 270M: The compact model for hyper-efficient AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5175/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5175/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Google has unveiled the Gemma 3 270M, a compact AI model with 270 million parameters designed for efficiency and task-specific fine-tuning. This model excels in instruction-following and text structuring, making it ideal for on-device and research use. It sets a new performance standard for its size, enhancing accessibility to sophisticated AI capabilities. Explore the future of AI with Gemma! 🌟 #Gemma3 #AI #MachineLearning #Innovation #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini CLI &#43; VS Code: Native diffing and context-aware workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4967/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4967/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The latest update to Gemini CLI enhances its integration with VS Code. This update offers context-aware suggestions by accessing your workspace and selected text. This means targeted help right when you need it. Additionally, you can now use native in-editor diffing. Review and modify proposed changes directly in a full-screen diff view for better control over your code. 🔧 Ready to enhance your workflow? Check your Gemini CLI version and get started! #GeminiCLI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Jules’ sharpest critic and most valuable ally</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4968/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4968/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Jules&amp;rsquo; new critic functionality! 🛠️ This feature enhances AI-generated code by acting as a peer reviewer during the generation process. With &amp;ldquo;critic-augmented generation,&amp;rdquo; every code change undergoes adversarial review, aiming for higher quality output. It flags potential issues like subtle bugs and logic errors before you see the code. This integration helps ensure better code quality while you focus on other tasks. #AICoding #CodeQuality #Innovation #TechNews #GoogleLabs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train a GPT2 model with JAX on TPU for free</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5176/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5176/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Interested in building a GPT-2 model? Check out this guide on training a GPT-2 model with JAX using Google TPUs, completely for free! It includes a hands-on Python notebook suitable for Colab or Kaggle. Learn about defining a hardware mesh, partitioning model parameters, and optimizing training. For those new to JAX, a PyTorch developer’s guide is also available. #MachineLearning #GPT2 #JAX #AI #GoogleTPUs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Google Developer Program is evolving</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-20/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are here for the Google Developer Program! 🔹 A new flexible monthly subscription is now available for $24.99. This plan includes access to AI tools, Google Cloud credits, and more. 🔹 The launch of the Google Developer Program forums simplifies collaboration among developers, allowing for easy sharing of knowledge and support. Explore these enhancements to elevate your coding experience! #GoogleDeveloper #AI #TechUpdates #DeveloperCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veo 3 Fast and new image-to-video capabilities</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-21/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Google has launched Veo 3 Fast, a new model designed for speed and cost-effectiveness. It allows developers to create high-quality videos quickly, supporting both text-to-video and image-to-video capabilities. This functionality is available through the Gemini API. With prices starting at $0.40/second for videos with audio, Veo 3 Fast is ideal for programmatic advertising and content creation at scale. #Google #Veo3 #VideoContent #TechNews #Developers</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
