<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HubSpot-Developers on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/hubspot-developers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HubSpot-Developers on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:49:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/hubspot-developers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Automated Testing for UI Extensions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13831/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:49:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13831/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! HubSpot has launched new testing utilities for the UI Extensions SDK. This framework addresses the challenges of automated testing in a sandboxed environment, offering a custom test renderer that simplifies the process. 🌟 TypeScript users will enjoy full type safety, enhancing the development experience with quick error detection and autocomplete features. Get started by installing the @hubspot/ui-extensions package and consider using Vitest for optimal&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to CODE: Simplifying the Developer Experience with HubSpot</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12085/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12085/</guid>
      <description>🌟 HubSpot is transforming the developer experience with CODE: the Center of Developer Excellence. Instead of overwhelming developers with extensive documentation, we focus on guiding them through specific customer problems. By offering opinionated guidance, we help developers solve issues without the burden of architectural decisions. This approach allows them to concentrate on what they do best—creating effective applications. #DeveloperExperience #HubSpot #Coding #TechInnovation #APIs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the Power of Webhooks &amp; Custom Workflow Actions in HubSpot’s New Developer Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11162/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 17:14:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11162/</guid>
      <description>🚀 HubSpot introduces its new Developer Platform, designed for easy app building and customization. The platform features a structured file system for managing app logic, including dedicated folders for workflow actions and webhooks. This modular approach enhances flexibility and scalability. Developers can efficiently version and extend their apps, ensuring consistency across environments. For quick setups, the HubSpot CLI simplifies the process. #HubSpot #DeveloperPlatform #Webhooks&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Developer Docs in the Age of AI: Our Mintlify Migration Story</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10591/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10591/</guid>
      <description>🚀 We’ve migrated our developer docs to Mintlify, marking a significant shift in how we approach developer education in an AI-centric world. In 2025, we recognized the emergence of AI-native developers who prefer concise, structured documentation. Our goal is to cater to both fast-paced learners and those who prefer traditional methods. We faced challenges with context overload in our legacy documentation. By implementing the Model Context Protocol (MCP) server, we aim to provide precise,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Serverless Functions on HubSpot’s New Developer Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10381/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:38:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10381/</guid>
      <description>🚀 HubSpot has launched a major update to its developer platform, introducing new features like Custom Workflow Actions and revamped UI Extensions with dedicated App Home pages. Developers may have questions about existing apps, especially those using serverless functions. It&amp;rsquo;s essential to migrate to v2025.1 or v2025.2 before support for v2023.2 ends on October 1, 2025. For optimal performance, consider hosting serverless functions externally and connecting via hubspot.fetch(). #HubSpot&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Omnichannel Customer Connections at HubSpot: A Look Under the Hood</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10054/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10054/</guid>
      <description>🌟 HubSpot is addressing the challenge of meeting customer expectations for seamless communication across channels like chat, email, voice, and social media. With a focus on developers, HubSpot is making omnichannel experiences practical and scalable. They aim to unify customer data and streamline integrations, moving away from fragmented systems. Their Custom Channels API allows businesses to create tailored messaging experiences, syncing third-party apps with HubSpot’s Help Desk and CRM for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Legacy Apps to Platform Speed: Building with the New Developer Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9916/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9916/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At INBOUND 2025, HubSpot announced over 200 updates, enhancing CRM experiences and launching the Data Hub for AI-ready datasets. 📈 A key highlight was the overhaul of the HubSpot CLI. New commands like hs project migrate and hs mcp setup were introduced, streamlining developer workflows significantly. 🔧 SimpleEvents.io leveraged these updates to migrate their app quickly and create a centralized App Home experience. For developers, these changes promise faster and more efficient app&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Reimagined Marketplace for App Developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7690/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7690/</guid>
      <description>🌐 The marketplace for app developers is evolving. With customer purchasing behavior shifting to quicker decisions, traditional models are no longer sufficient. At HubSpot, we’re addressing the visibility challenge for partners and customers. Our reimagined marketplace helps customers discover solutions faster by focusing on the problems they need to solve. With a unified infrastructure, we&amp;rsquo;ve reduced dead-end searches by 56%, increasing opportunities for app partners. This ensures that your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall Spotlight 2025: A Look at Tools for Developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7640/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7640/</guid>
      <description>🚀 HubSpot is enhancing the developer experience by providing powerful tools and seamless integrations. With direct links to Sentry and Honeycomb, developers can now monitor app health in real-time, ensuring better visibility and faster troubleshooting. 🔍 The new MCP server allows integration of popular IDE tools, simplifying project management with chat-based prompts. Plus, the Figma Design Kit enables quick prototyping of app cards without coding. #DeveloperTools #HubSpot #AppDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Faster, Deliver Smarter: Introducing the HubSpot Developer Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7641/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7641/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from HubSpot! The new HubSpot Developer Platform is here, offering a unified framework for building apps. This platform enhances developer productivity with AI-native documentation and a streamlined CLI setup. Developers can now create deeper integrations and rich user experiences, with expanded UI flexibility. Customize app spaces and empower HubSpot admins to utilize unique functionalities. #HubSpot #DeveloperPlatform #Innovation #SoftwareDevelopment #AppIntegration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Developer&#39;s Guide to Building on the HubSpot Marketplace: The Swarm&#39;s Journey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7546/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7546/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the sales world, time is precious. The Swarm is addressing this challenge by creating an app card using HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s UI Extensions. Their platform maps relationships within a company&amp;rsquo;s network, helping sales teams identify trusted connections based on shared history and education. This integration allows for smoother workflows and credible conversations directly within HubSpot CRM. Explore their journey and insights on building in the HubSpot Marketplace! 🌐🤝 #SalesEfficiency #HubSpot&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Developer’s Guide to INBOUND25</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4757/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4757/</guid>
      <description>🚀 INBOUND 2025 is just around the corner, taking place in San Francisco from September 3rd-5th! This year&amp;rsquo;s event will focus on how HubSpot is evolving, bringing developers and builders closer together. AI will be a key topic, promising fresh insights and innovations. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss Partner Day on September 2nd for app and solutions partners, featuring valuable sessions and networking opportunities. #INBOUND25 #HubSpot #DeveloperCommunity #TechInnovation #Networking 🌟</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Intelligent Support Workflows with HubSpot and Postman</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-1975/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-1975/</guid>
      <description>Unlock efficient customer support with intelligent workflows! 🚀 This article explores how to enhance ticket escalation using HubSpot and Postman. It highlights the need for systems that not only respond quickly but also integrate human expertise. Key components include HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s Service Hub for ticket management and Postman Flows for automation. This blend improves response quality while managing rising ticket volumes. #CustomerSupport #HubSpot #Postman #AI #Workflows</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
