<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HubSpot-Developers on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/sources/hubspot-developers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HubSpot-Developers on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:02:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/sources/hubspot-developers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Developer&#39;s Guide to Building on the HubSpot Marketplace: The Swarm&#39;s Journey</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-7546/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-7546/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the sales world, time is precious. The Swarm is addressing this challenge by creating an app card using HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s UI Extensions. Their platform maps relationships within a company&amp;rsquo;s network, helping sales teams identify trusted connections based on shared history and education. This integration allows for smoother workflows and credible conversations directly within HubSpot CRM. Explore their journey and insights on building in the HubSpot Marketplace! 🌐🤝 #SalesEfficiency #HubSpot&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Developer’s Guide to INBOUND25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-4757/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-4757/</guid>
      <description>🚀 INBOUND 2025 is just around the corner, taking place in San Francisco from September 3rd-5th! This year&amp;rsquo;s event will focus on how HubSpot is evolving, bringing developers and builders closer together. AI will be a key topic, promising fresh insights and innovations. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss Partner Day on September 2nd for app and solutions partners, featuring valuable sessions and networking opportunities. #INBOUND25 #HubSpot #DeveloperCommunity #TechInnovation #Networking 🌟</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Intelligent Support Workflows with HubSpot and Postman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-1975/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-1975/</guid>
      <description>Unlock efficient customer support with intelligent workflows! 🚀 This article explores how to enhance ticket escalation using HubSpot and Postman. It highlights the need for systems that not only respond quickly but also integrate human expertise. Key components include HubSpot&amp;rsquo;s Service Hub for ticket management and Postman Flows for automation. This blend improves response quality while managing rising ticket volumes. #CustomerSupport #HubSpot #Postman #AI #Workflows</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
