<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugging-Face-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/hugging-face-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugging-Face-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:50:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/hugging-face-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Custom Policy Enforcement with Reasoning: Faster, Safer AI Applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13301/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13301/</guid>
      <description>Explore how custom policy enforcement enhances AI applications. The article discusses the integration of reasoning mechanisms that improve both speed and safety in AI systems. Key insights include the importance of tailored policies to meet specific needs and the role of reasoning in decision-making processes. Stay informed about the future of AI! 🤖🔍 #AI #PolicyEnforcement #TechInnovation #Safety #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SARLO-80: Worldwide Slant SAR Language Optic Dataset at 80 cm Resolution</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13302/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 10:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13302/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Introducing SARLO-80, a new global dataset focused on slant synthetic aperture radar (SAR) imagery at 80 cm resolution. This dataset is designed to enhance machine learning applications in remote sensing. It provides a comprehensive resource for researchers and developers in the field. 📊 Explore how SARLO-80 can advance your projects! #SARData #RemoteSensing #MachineLearning #DataScience #SARLO80</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transformers v5: Simple model definitions powering the AI ecosystem</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13188/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13188/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the AI world! The release of Transformers v5.0.0rc-0 marks a significant milestone, evolving from just 40 model architectures to over 400. In just five years, daily installations have soared from 20,000 to over 3 million! 📈 The community has also contributed more than 750,000 model checkpoints, enhancing collaboration within the ecosystem. Key focuses for v5 include simplicity, training, inference, and production efficiency. The library continues to adapt, ensuring its&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuous batching from first principles</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13039/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13039/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Continuous batching is a key method for improving AI chatbot performance. It enhances throughput by processing multiple conversations simultaneously, which is crucial for high-demand scenarios. Starting from attention mechanisms and KV caching, this optimization allows for faster token generation, making user interactions smoother. Learn more about how these techniques work together to optimize AI responses. #AI #Chatbots #ContinuousBatching #MachineLearning #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diffusers welcomes FLUX-2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13038/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13038/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news in the world of image generation! Black Forest Labs has introduced FLUX.2, a new series of image generation models that features a fresh architecture and has been pre-trained from scratch. This model is distinct from its predecessor, FLUX.1, and is not intended as a direct replacement. The article discusses key updates, how to perform inference with FLUX.2, and the process of LoRA fine-tuning. Stay tuned for more advancements! #ImageGeneration #AI #MachineLearning #FLUX2&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20x Faster TRL Fine-tuning with RapidFire AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12954/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12954/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for TRL users! Hugging Face TRL now integrates with RapidFire AI, allowing for 20x faster fine-tuning and post-training experiments. This integration helps streamline the process of comparing multiple configurations without extensive code changes or increased GPU demands. 🔍 With RapidFire AI, teams can run various TRL configurations concurrently, even on a single GPU. This adaptive scheduling enhances efficiency and can improve evaluation metrics significantly. #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open ASR Leaderboard: Trends and Insights with New Multilingual &amp; Long-Form Tracks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12941/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12941/</guid>
      <description>The Open ASR Leaderboard has recently updated to include new multilingual and long-form transcription tracks. 📊 Currently, there are 150 Audio-Text-to-Text and 27K ASR models available. Many benchmarks focus on short-form English, often missing key areas like multilingual performance and model throughput for long-form audio. The leaderboard has become a standard for comparing model accuracy and efficiency. 🔍 #ASR #MachineLearning #AI #TechUpdates #DataScience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AnyLanguageModel: One API for Local and Remote LLMs on Apple Platforms</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12889/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12889/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Apple developers! Introducing AnyLanguageModel, a new Swift package that simplifies the integration of local and remote LLMs. This tool offers a single API that replaces Apple’s Foundation Models framework, streamlining the process for AI-powered app development. Developers often face challenges with multiple APIs and integration patterns. AnyLanguageModel aims to reduce this friction, encouraging the use of local, open-source models. For more details, check the update on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Easily Build and Share ROCm Kernels with Hugging Face</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12209/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12209/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Build and share ROCm kernels easily with Hugging Face! Custom kernels enhance deep learning performance, allowing tailored GPU operations. However, compiling them can be challenging due to various complexities. Hugging Face&amp;rsquo;s kernel-builder simplifies this process, supporting multiple backends like ROCm. This guide focuses on building efficient kernels for AMD GPUs, covering best practices for testing and deployment. #DeepLearning #ROCm #HuggingFace #GPU #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building for an Open Future - our new partnership with Google Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12076/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12076/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Hugging Face has announced a new partnership with Google Cloud to help companies build their own AI using open models. Jeff Boudier emphasizes the importance of this collaboration, stating it simplifies AI customization on Google Cloud. 🌐 With over 2 million open models available, this partnership aims to enhance accessibility and development for businesses worldwide. 🤖 #AI #GoogleCloud #OpenModels #HuggingFace #Partnership</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Healthcare Robot from Simulation to Deployment with NVIDIA Isaac</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11380/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11380/</guid>
      <description>Discover how NVIDIA Isaac is transforming healthcare robotics! 🤖 The article details the journey of developing a healthcare robot, starting from simulation to real-world deployment. It highlights the use of advanced AI and simulation tools to enhance the robot&amp;rsquo;s capabilities in patient care. This innovation promises to improve efficiency in healthcare settings. #HealthcareInnovation #Robotics #NVIDIAIsaac #AI #Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice Cloning with Consent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11364/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11364/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting advancements in voice technology are here! A recent blog post discusses the concept of a &amp;lsquo;voice consent gate&amp;rsquo; aimed at promoting ethical voice cloning. This initiative seeks to ensure that voice cloning is performed with consent, helping to mitigate risks associated with misuse, like deepfakes. The article highlights both the advantages and concerns of voice generation, noting its potential to assist those who have lost their ability to speak and support language learning. For more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>huggingface_hub v1.0: Five Years of Building the Foundation of Open Machine Learning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11299/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11299/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in open machine learning! Huggingface_hub has officially launched v1.0 after five years of development. This update supports over 200,000 libraries and provides access to 2 million models, 0.5 million datasets, and 1 million Spaces. Key changes include a new backend with httpx and an improved CLI interface. Upgrade now to enhance your experience! #HuggingFace #MachineLearning #OpenSource #AI #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streaming datasets: 100x More Efficient</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11298/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11298/</guid>
      <description>Discover the latest advancements in streaming datasets, reported to be 100 times more efficient than traditional methods. 📊 This breakthrough can significantly enhance data processing and real-time analytics across various industries. For developers and data scientists, this opens new avenues for improved performance and resource management. Stay updated on tech innovations! 🚀💻 #DataScience #StreamingData #TechInnovation #Efficiency #Analytics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LeRobot v0.4.0: Super Charging OSS Robotics Learning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11249/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11249/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in LeRobot v0.4.0 enhance open-source robotics learning! This release introduces scalable Datasets v3.0 and powerful new VLA models, including PI0.5 and GR00T N1.5. A new plugin system simplifies hardware integration, while support for LIBERO and Meta-World simulations broadens capabilities. Key features also include simplified multi-GPU training and a new Hugging Face collaboration. #OpenSource #Robotics #AI #TechUpdates #LeRobot</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building the Open Agent Ecosystem Together: Introducing OpenEnv</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11196/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11196/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news in the tech world! Meta and Hugging Face have announced the launch of the OpenEnv Hub, aimed at fostering a shared community for agentic environments. 🛠️ This initiative highlights the importance of both compute infrastructure and the developer community in scaling AI. 🧩 Agentic environments provide the necessary tools and context for agents to perform tasks safely and effectively. #OpenEnv #AI #TechCommunity #Meta #HuggingFace</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugging Face and VirusTotal collaborate to strengthen AI security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11186/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11186/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in AI security! Hugging Face has teamed up with VirusTotal to enhance the safety of files on the Hugging Face Hub. 🔍 This partnership ensures that over 2.2 million public model and dataset repositories are continuously scanned for potential threats, protecting the machine learning community. 🛡️ AI models can carry risks, from disguised malicious files to compromised assets. With VirusTotal’s trusted malware intelligence, users gain an additional layer of security. #AISecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sentence Transformers is joining Hugging Face!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11150/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11150/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Sentence Transformers is now part of Hugging Face! This transition from the UKP Lab at TU Darmstadt to Hugging Face marks a new chapter for the popular library, which has been maintained by Tom Aarsen since late 2023. With Hugging Face&amp;rsquo;s robust infrastructure, Sentence Transformers will enhance its capabilities in Information Retrieval and NLP. 💡 Since 2019, it has offered over 16,000 models for tasks like semantic search and clustering, serving a million users monthly&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercharge your OCR Pipelines with Open Models</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11122/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11122/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Supercharge your OCR pipelines with open models! The rise of vision-language models is changing the document AI landscape. This guide helps you navigate the choices, focusing on cost efficiency and privacy with open-weight models. Learn when to fine-tune models, key selection factors, and how to enhance OCR with multimodal retrieval and document QA. Get started today! 📄🔍 #OCR #DocumentAI #OpenModels #TechGuide #AIInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlock the power of images with AI Sheets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11108/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11108/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of images with AI Sheets! 📸✨ This article discusses how to generate and transform text and images seamlessly. It provides a step-by-step guide for users to enhance their visual content effortlessly. Stay ahead in your creative projects by leveraging AI tools for better storytelling through images. #AISheets #ImageTransformation #TechInnovation #CreativeTools #VisualStorytelling</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Cloud C4 Brings a 70% TCO improvement on GPT OSS with Intel and Hugging Face</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10981/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10981/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Google Cloud&amp;rsquo;s new C4 Virtual Machine showcases a significant 70% improvement in Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) for OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s GPT OSS, thanks to collaboration with Intel and Hugging Face. Key findings include a 1.7x TCO improvement over the previous C3 VM. The C4 VM also offers enhanced throughput and a lower hourly rate. #GoogleCloud #Intel #HuggingFace #AI #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get your VLM running in 3 simple steps on Intel CPUs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10926/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10926/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of Vision Language Models (VLMs) on Intel CPUs! 🌐 This article outlines three simple steps to set up a VLM locally. You can analyze images, generate captions, and answer visual content questions—all while keeping your data private and secure. 🔒 Tools like Optimum Intel and OpenVINO make this process accessible, even without high-end hardware. Check out the full guide for a seamless setup! 🖥️ #AI #VisionLanguageModels #DataPrivacy #Intel #TechGuide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SOTA OCR on-device with Core ML and dots.ocr</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10377/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10377/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in on-device OCR technology have emerged with dots.ocr from RedNote, a model outperforming Gemini 2.5 Pro. This 3B parameter model is designed for seamless on-device performance, eliminating the need for API keys and internet access. Key to this is Apple&amp;rsquo;s Neural Engine, which offers impressive power efficiency. 🔋 However, converting models to Core ML can be challenging. Apple also provides MLX for GPU targeting, enhancing flexibility. Stay tuned for a three-part&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing RTEB: A New Standard for Retrieval Evaluation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10326/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10326/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing RTEB: A New Benchmark for Retrieval Evaluation! The Retrieval Embedding Benchmark (RTEB) is designed to accurately evaluate the retrieval accuracy of embedding models. It combines open and private datasets to address the limitations of existing benchmarks. This approach aims to ensure fair and transparent measurement of how models perform on unseen data, enhancing the quality of AI applications. Learn more about RTEB and its impact on retrieval evaluation! 📊🔍 #RTEB #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Qwen3-8B Agent on Intel® Core™ Ultra with Depth-Pruned Draft Models</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10234/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10234/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in AI with the Qwen3-8B model! Recent updates reveal a significant acceleration in performance on Intel® Core™ Ultra using Depth-Pruned Draft Models. By implementing speculative decoding, generation speeds have improved by approximately 1.4x. These enhancements enable the efficient operation of a fast, local AI agent. #AI #MachineLearning #Intel #Qwen3 #OpenVINO</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VibeGame: Exploring Vibe Coding Games</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10226/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10226/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Discover VibeGame, a new platform focused on coding games that enhance programming skills through interactive play. The initiative aims to make coding accessible and enjoyable for all levels, encouraging creativity and problem-solving. Explore how VibeGame is shaping the future of learning in tech! 🌐💡 #VibeGame #CodingGames #TechEducation #LearnToCode #GameDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swift Transformers Reaches 1.0 — and Looks to the Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10155/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10155/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Swift Transformers has reached version 1.0! Launched two years ago, this library aims to support Apple developers in integrating local LLMs into their applications. The team has gathered insights from the community and is now focusing on enhancing features, particularly for MLX and agentic use cases. Stay tuned for more updates! #SwiftTransformers #AppleDevelopers #MachineLearning #TechUpdate #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smol2Operator: Post-Training GUI Agents for Computer Use</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9914/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9914/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Smol2Operator: a vision-language model that learns GUI skills and evolves into an agentic GUI coder. The project shares training recipes, data-processing tools, and demo datasets to support reproducibility and further research. Check out the full collection on GitHub! 🖥️📊🤖 #AI #MachineLearning #Research #GitHub #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaia2 and ARE: Empowering the community to study agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9867/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9867/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Introducing Gaia2 and the Meta Agents Research Environments (ARE)! This new framework aims to empower the community in evaluating AI agents. It offers a more realistic approach to testing agent behaviors in complex scenarios, moving beyond traditional evaluation environments. Gaia2 allows for deep analysis of agent capabilities, while ARE provides customizable conditions for studying behaviors. Both tools are now available for public use! #AIEvaluation #Gaia2 #MetaAgents&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaleway on Hugging Face Inference Providers 🔥</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9813/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9813/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Scaleway is now an official Inference Provider on the Hugging Face Hub! This addition expands serverless inference capabilities, allowing users to access a variety of models seamlessly through client SDKs for JS and Python. Explore popular models like gpt-oss and Qwen3 directly from Scaleway&amp;rsquo;s Hub page. Check them out at the link below! 🔗 &lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/scaleway&#34;&gt;https://huggingface.co/scaleway&lt;/a&gt; #AI #MachineLearning #HuggingFace #Scaleway #InferenceProviders</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratizing AI Safety with RiskRubric.ai</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9789/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9789/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news in AI safety! The launch of RiskRubric.ai aims to enhance trust in AI models by providing standardized risk assessments. With over 500,000 models on the Hugging Face hub, users often struggle to evaluate security and privacy aspects. This initiative, led by Cloud Security Alliance and Noma Security, seeks to ensure transparent security reporting as AI adoption grows. #AISafety #RiskAssessment #AIModels #CloudSecurity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Public AI on Hugging Face Inference Providers 🔥</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9765/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9765/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Public AI is now a supported Inference Provider on Hugging Face Hub. This integration enhances serverless inference capabilities and simplifies access to public models from institutions like the Swiss AI Initiative and AI Singapore. Explore trending models and learn more at: &lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/publicai&#34;&gt;https://huggingface.co/publicai&lt;/a&gt; #PublicAI #HuggingFace #AIModels #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>`LeRobotDataset`: Bringing large-scale datasets to lerobot</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9695/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9695/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from the world of robotics! The LeRobotDataset team has released version 3.0, improving how large-scale datasets are managed. This new version allows multiple episodes to be packed into a single file, overcoming previous file-system limitations. It also supports streaming mode for efficient data processing. A simple utility is available to convert existing datasets to this new format. Check it out and enhance your projects! #LeRobotDataset #Robotics #DataScience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visible Watermarking with Gradio</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9696/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9696/</guid>
      <description>✨ Introducing Visible Watermarking with Gradio! Watermarking generative AI content is becoming essential as AI-generated images, videos, and audio grow increasingly lifelike. Distinguishing real from generated content is challenging, making watermarking a vital solution. Learn more about the importance of this approach and its implementation in the latest update. #Watermarking #AI #Gradio #ContentCreation #GenerativeAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tricks from OpenAI gpt-oss YOU 🫵 can use with transformers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9549/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9549/</guid>
      <description>OpenAI has launched the GPT-OSS series of models, featuring advancements like MXFP4 quantization and efficient kernels. 🚀 The transformers library has been upgraded significantly to enhance model loading, running, and fine-tuning. This allows for better community understanding and implementation. Key updates include Zero-build Kernels, Tensor Parallelism, and more. Explore these enhancements and their impact on future models! 🔍💻 #OpenAI #GPTOSS #Transformers #MachineLearning #AIInnovations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jupyter Agents: training LLMs to reason with notebooks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9512/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9512/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Jupyter Agents aim to enhance LLMs by enabling code execution directly in Jupyter Notebooks. This integration helps tackle complex data science tasks more efficiently. The initiative focuses on improving smaller models to compete with larger ones through high-quality training data and fine-tuning methods. Stay tuned for updates on this innovative project! 🧠💻 #Jupyter #LLM #DataScience #AI #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mmBERT: ModernBERT goes Multilingual</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9477/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9477/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting developments in AI! The article discusses mmBERT, a new multilingual model built on ModernBERT. It aims to enhance language processing across various languages. Key features include improved understanding and generation of text in multiple languages, making it a versatile tool for global applications. For more details, check out the full article! #AI #MachineLearning #NLP #mmBERT #Multilingual</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome EmbeddingGemma, Google&#39;s new efficient embedding model</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7747/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7747/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in AI! Google has introduced EmbeddingGemma, a new embedding model designed for efficiency. This model aims to enhance various applications by improving performance while reducing resource consumption. Developers can explore its capabilities on GitHub. Stay tuned for more updates on AI advancements! #Google #EmbeddingGemma #AI #MachineLearning #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make your ZeroGPU Spaces go brrr with PyTorch ahead-of-time compilation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7606/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7606/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of ZeroGPU Spaces with PyTorch ahead-of-time (AoT) compilation! 🚀 AoT improves performance by optimizing models once for faster reloading, making demos snappier. Users can expect speed boosts ranging from 1.3× to 1.8× on various models. Explore advanced techniques like FP8 quantization and dynamic shapes for an enhanced experience. Check out live demos on the zerogpu-aoti organization! #ZeroGPU #PyTorch #MachineLearning #AI #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generate Images with Claude and Hugging Face</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5075/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5075/</guid>
      <description>Discover how to generate images using Claude and Hugging Face! 🤖✨ The article outlines step-by-step methods for utilizing these tools effectively. It highlights key features and provides tips for best practices in image generation. Explore the potential of AI in creative projects! #AI #ImageGeneration #HuggingFace #Claude #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Zero to GPU: A Guide to Building and Scaling Production-Ready CUDA Kernels</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5077/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5077/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited to enhance your GPU capabilities? Check out the guide on building production-ready CUDA kernels! It introduces the kernel-builder library, designed to simplify the development of custom kernels for various architectures. Learn how to create efficient and maintainable systems while overcoming deployment challenges. Perfect for those looking to elevate their models! #CUDA #GPUs #Programming #TechGuide #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP for Research: How to Connect AI to Research Tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5078/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5078/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Academic research often requires navigating multiple platforms like arXiv and GitHub. The Model Context Protocol (MCP) offers a solution by enabling AI to communicate with these research tools. This allows for natural language requests, streamlining the discovery process and reducing the need for manual switching between sites. Explore how MCP can enhance your research experience! 📊🤖 #AIinResearch #ModelContextProtocol #ResearchInnovation #AcademicTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>🇵🇭 FilBench - Can LLMs Understand and Generate Filipino?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4916/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4916/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the capabilities of LLMs in Filipino languages is essential. 🇵🇭 FilBench, a new evaluation suite, assesses LLM fluency, translation, and cultural knowledge in Tagalog and Cebuano. Despite high ChatGPT usage in the Philippines, systematic evaluations are lacking. The study evaluates over 20 LLMs, aiming to provide clear insights. 📄 Read the paper: &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2508.03523&#34;&gt;arxiv.org&lt;/a&gt; 🖥️ Check GitHub: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/filbench/filbench-eval&#34;&gt;github.com&lt;/a&gt; #FilBench #LLMs&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TextQuests: How Good are LLMs at Text-Based Video Games?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4915/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4915/</guid>
      <description>📚 The article explores the capabilities of Large Language Models (LLMs) in text-based video games. It highlights that while LLMs excel in static knowledge benchmarks, they face challenges in dynamic, interactive environments. Developing effective evaluation methods for these models remains crucial. Two main approaches are suggested: real-world environments with specific skills and simulated open-world settings. The article introduces TextQuests as a new benchmark to assess LLM performance in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate ND-Parallel: A Guide to Efficient Multi-GPU Training</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4739/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4739/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Training large models on multiple GPUs can be complex. The article &amp;ldquo;Accelerate ND-Parallel&amp;rdquo; discusses how to simplify this process using the Accelerate library and Axolotl. It provides a step-by-step guide to integrate various parallelism strategies in your training script, enhancing efficiency. Key configurations for parallelism include Fully Sharded Data Parallel and Data Parallel degrees. This approach requires at least 2 nodes with 8 GPUs each for optimal performance. #MultiGPU&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AI Sheets: a tool to work with datasets using open AI models!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4738/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4738/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data enthusiasts! Hugging Face has launched AI Sheets, an open-source tool designed to build, enrich, and transform datasets using AI models without any coding required. You can deploy it locally or access it directly on the Hub, utilizing thousands of models, including gpt-oss from OpenAI. Explore the tool for free here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/spaces/aisheets/sheets&#34;&gt;AI Sheets&lt;/a&gt; or install it locally from GitHub! #AISheets #OpenSource #DataScience #MachineLearning&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vision Language Model Alignment in TRL ⚡️</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4695/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4695/</guid>
      <description>🔍 The article discusses the alignment of Vision Language Models (VLMs) in the context of Technology Readiness Levels (TRL). It highlights the importance of aligning VLMs with real-world applications to enhance their effectiveness. 💡 The piece outlines key strategies for achieving this alignment, focusing on practical implementation and evaluation methods. For those interested in AI development, this is a valuable read! #VisionLanguageModel #AIAlignment #TechnologyReadiness #MachineLearning&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome GPT OSS, the new open-source model family from OpenAI!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-577/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-577/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from OpenAI! They have launched GPT OSS, a new open-source model family featuring two versions: gpt-oss-120b with 117B parameters and gpt-oss-20b with 21B parameters. Both models utilize a mixture-of-experts design for efficient performance. These models are licensed under Apache 2.0, promoting safe and responsible use. OpenAI aims to enhance accessibility in AI through this release. #OpenAI #GPTOSS #MachineLearning #AICommunity #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build an AI Shopping Assistant with Gradio MCP Servers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-578/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-578/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Python developers can supercharge their LLMs with Gradio&amp;rsquo;s Model Context Protocol (MCP)! Gradio simplifies the integration of AI models from Hugging Face, enabling LLMs to tackle real-world problems. Key features include automatic conversion of functions into LLM tools, real-time notifications, and seamless file uploads. Imagine an AI shopping assistant that finds clothes for you and even shows virtual try-ons! #AI #Python #Gradio #MachineLearning #Ecommerce</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
