<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Databricks-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/databricks-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Databricks-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:50:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/databricks-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Public Preview of Distributed ML on Serverless and Standard Clusters</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12780/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12780/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the world of machine learning! The Public Preview of Apache Spark MLlib (Python) and Optuna is now available on serverless notebooks and jobs. This development aims to enhance distributed machine learning capabilities. This preview offers users a chance to explore new functionalities in a flexible environment. #MachineLearning #ApacheSpark #DataScience #Optuna #Serverless</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Python User-Defined Table Functions (UDTFs) in Unity Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12736/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 22:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12736/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data professionals! Unity Catalog now supports Python User-Defined Table Functions (UDTFs). This feature enables users to create custom functions, simplifying query construction and enhancing data processing capabilities. Explore how UDTFs can improve your workflow and expand your data handling skills! #Python #DataScience #UnityCatalog #UDTFs #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azure Databricks at Microsoft Ignite 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12737/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12737/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Azure Databricks participated as a Visionary-level sponsor at Microsoft Ignite 2025 in San Francisco. They highlighted strategies for organizations to unify data, analytics, and AI on the Azure platform. This collaboration aims to enhance business intelligence and streamline operations. Stay updated on these advancements! #AzureDatabricks #MicrosoftIgnite #DataAnalytics #AI #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing the Lakehouse with Apache Iceberg v3 on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12738/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12738/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks has integrated Apache Iceberg v3 into its Data Intelligence Platform. This update enhances the Lakehouse architecture, providing users with a unified and high-performance data layer. The new features aim to improve interoperability and overall efficiency for data management. Explore how this advancement can benefit your data strategy! #Databricks #ApacheIceberg #DataIntelligence #Lakehouse #DataManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks Achieves Awardability on the DoD’s Tradewinds Solutions Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12150/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12150/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks has achieved &amp;ldquo;Awardable&amp;rdquo; status on the DoD’s Tradewinds Solutions Marketplace. This recognition highlights the capabilities of the Databricks Data Intelligence Platform. The &amp;ldquo;Awardable&amp;rdquo; status indicates that Databricks can now effectively support various Department of Defense initiatives. This milestone opens pathways for further collaboration with the DoD. #Databricks #DoD #TradewindsMarketplace #DataIntelligence #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Native OpenAI Models Now Generally Available on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-11940/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-11940/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data enthusiasts! OpenAI models, including GPT-5, are now generally available on Databricks. This integration aims to enhance data processing and analytics capabilities. Users can leverage these advanced models for various applications, streamlining workflows and improving efficiency. Explore the potential of AI in your data projects! #OpenAI #Databricks #AIModels #DataAnalytics #GPT5</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Secure, Interoperable Identity Collaboration: The Trade Desk and Databricks Partnership</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12087/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12087/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks has partnered with The Trade Desk to enhance secure and interoperable identity solutions. This collaboration aims to streamline identity management and improve data connectivity for better marketing outcomes. The integration is designed to support businesses in navigating the evolving digital landscape efficiently. #DataIntegration #IdentityManagement #TechPartnership #MarketingSolutions #Databricks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Explore Data Instantly with Databricks Assistant in Unity Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12089/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12089/</guid>
      <description>Unlock data exploration with the new Databricks Assistant in Unity Catalog! This tool allows analysts to ask questions in plain English, making it easier to visualize data without needing SQL. Say goodbye to context switching and hello to instant insights! 📊🔍✨ #DataAnalytics #Databricks #UnityCatalog #DataVisualization #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to scale data governance with Attribute-Based Access Control in Unity Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12088/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12088/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking data access efficiently is crucial for organizations focusing on analytics and AI. 🌐 The article discusses how Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC) in Unity Catalog can enhance data governance. It emphasizes the importance of balancing data democratization with security and compliance. 🔐 Implementing ABAC allows organizations to tailor access based on specific attributes, ensuring the right data reaches the right people. #DataGovernance #ABAC #UnityCatalog #Analytics #AIEthics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Databricks Cross-Industry Partner Accelerators for Agentic AI, GenAI and LLMOps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12090/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12090/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks has launched Cross-Industry Partner Accelerators aimed at enhancing the adoption of Agentic AI, GenAI, and LLMOps. These accelerators are designed to support businesses in leveraging generative AI for growth and innovation. This initiative highlights the current relevance of generative AI in transforming industries. #Databricks #AI #GenAI #BusinessGrowth #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Data and AI with Google Axion C4A VMs on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12091/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 22:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12091/</guid>
      <description>Unlock faster workloads on Google Cloud! 🚀 Databricks introduces Axion-based C4A VMs, designed to enhance data and AI capabilities. These virtual machines aim to optimize performance and efficiency for Databricks customers in Classic compute environments. Discover how these advancements can transform your data workflows. 📊💡 #GoogleCloud #Databricks #AI #DataIntelligence #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building an Agentic Food Label Reader for Greater Transparency</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12092/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12092/</guid>
      <description>Customer expectations for food labeling are changing. The article discusses the creation of an &amp;ldquo;Agentic Food Label Reader&amp;rdquo; aimed at enhancing transparency in food labeling. This solution utilizes data and AI to automate label processing efficiently. By simplifying these processes, it aims to meet consumer demands for clearer information about food products. For businesses, this means greater operational efficiency and improved trust with customers. 🌱📊 #FoodTransparency #DataAI #FoodLabeling&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the future of the Automotive Industry (Part 2): Implementing Scalable Geospatial Analytics &amp; AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12093/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12093/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking the future of the automotive industry involves key advancements in geospatial analytics and AI. This article highlights the shift from theoretical concepts to practical applications, demonstrating how real-time data can enhance mobility innovation. Scalable analytics are becoming essential for making informed decisions in manufacturing. 🚗📊 #AutomotiveInnovation #GeospatialAnalytics #AI #Mobility #DataDriven</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking the future of the Automotive Industry (Part 1): Understanding Scalable Geospatial Analytics &amp; AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12094/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12094/</guid>
      <description>The automotive industry is evolving through data-driven strategies. Real-time geospatial data and AI are playing key roles in enhancing automotive and mobility innovation. These technologies enable scalable analytics, which can optimize operations and improve decision-making. Stay tuned for more insights on this transformation! 🚗✨ #AutomotiveInnovation #GeospatialData #AI #DataAnalytics #MobilitySolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PDFs to Production: Announcing state-of-the-art document intelligence on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12095/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12095/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news from Databricks! They have introduced advanced document intelligence with Agent Bricks, enhancing how PDFs are processed. The new feature, ai_parse_document, allows users to parse and understand PDFs directly in SQL. This development promises leading quality at a significantly lower cost—3 to 5 times cheaper! #DataIntelligence #Databricks #DocumentProcessing #AI #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Leading Companies Are Delivering Trusted, AI-Powered Self-Service Analytics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11932/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11932/</guid>
      <description>Leading companies are leveraging Databricks AI/BI to enhance self-service analytics. In just over a year, many organizations have adopted this tool to accelerate insights and ensure governed self-service capabilities. These real-world applications demonstrate the growing importance of AI in analytics. 📊🤖 #DataAnalytics #AI #SelfService #Databricks #BusinessIntelligence</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks Launches First Multi-AI Indemnity to Protect Enterprise AI Innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11933/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11933/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks has introduced the first Multi-AI Indemnity, designed to protect enterprises using various AI models, including OpenAI GPT, Anthropic Claude, Meta Llama, and Google Gemini. 🛡️ This new coverage aims to foster innovation by providing businesses with the confidence to explore AI technologies without fear of liability. #AI #Innovation #Databricks #EnterpriseAI #Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI In Advertising: Custom Ad Images from Segmentation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11934/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11934/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.databricks.com/feed&#34;&gt;Databricks Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.databricks.com/blog/generative-ai-advertising-custom-ad-images-segmentation&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercharging AI Model Building: Data and Task Parallelism with Ray and Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11935/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:50:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11935/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.databricks.com/feed&#34;&gt;Databricks Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.databricks.com/blog/supercharging-ai-model-building-data-and-task-parallelism-ray-and-databricks&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate AI Development with Databricks: Discover, Govern, and Build with MCP and Agent Bricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11936/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11936/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of AI with Databricks! 🚀 The new MCP Catalog and Databricks Marketplace enable organizations to connect AI agents to a wide range of governed external services. This advancement in data intelligence is set to enhance operational efficiency across enterprises. Explore how these tools can drive AI development forward. #Databricks #AIDevelopment #DataIntelligence #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How HP Industrial Print Transformed Its Data Platform with Databricks SQL</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11937/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11937/</guid>
      <description>HP’s Industrial Print Software Solutions (IPSS) has updated its data platform using Databricks SQL. This transformation aims to enhance data accessibility and analytics capabilities. The move is expected to streamline operations and improve decision-making processes within the organization. Explore how HP is leveraging technology for better insights and efficiency. 📊✨ #DataTransformation #HP #Databricks #BusinessIntelligence #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks Free Edition Hackathon: show the world what’s possible in data and AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-05-11854/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-05-11854/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Databricks Free Edition Hackathon is now live! This event encourages developers and students to explore the possibilities in data and AI. Participants can build AI applications, data science projects, and machine learning models using the Free Edition. Join the movement and showcase your skills! 🌍💻 #Databricks #Hackathon #AI #DataScience #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>De-identifying Medical Images Cost-Effectively with Vision Language Models on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11842/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11842/</guid>
      <description>De-identifying medical images is crucial for patient privacy. The article discusses how Vision Language Models (VLMs) excel in this area while being cost-effective on Databricks. With VLMs, the process of ensuring confidentiality in medical imaging is becoming more efficient. This innovation could change the landscape of medical data management. 📊💡🖼️ #MedicalImages #DataPrivacy #Innovation #HealthcareTech #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Custom LLM Judges for AI Agent Accuracy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11833/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11833/</guid>
      <description>MLflow has introduced new LLM-as-a-Judge capabilities aimed at improving the accuracy of AI agents. These enhancements allow organizations to create custom judges tailored to specific domains, ensuring better performance as AI moves into production. Stay updated on advancements in AI quality assurance! 🤖📈 #AI #MachineLearning #MLflow #Innovation #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Pilot to Production with Custom Judges</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11835/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11835/</guid>
      <description>Many teams face challenges in moving GenAI projects from pilot to production due to unmet quality requirements. Databricks offers solutions like Judge Builder to help build evaluation infrastructure, enabling safer iterations and consistent output quality. This system supports faster deployment and enhances AI applications across enterprises. The article emphasizes the importance of designing a judge portfolio, accurately capturing expertise, and ensuring robust technical execution for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Modern Risk &amp; Compliance with Moody’s Risk Data Suite on the Databricks Data Intelligence Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11834/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11834/</guid>
      <description>Discover how Moody&amp;rsquo;s Risk Data Suite, in collaboration with the Databricks Data Intelligence Platform, is addressing the challenges faced by financial executives. This integration assists banks in managing risk and compliance while adapting to evolving regulations and customer demands. Stay informed and navigate the complexities of modern finance with these innovative tools. #RiskManagement #FinancialServices #Compliance #Databricks #Moody&amp;rsquo;s 📊🔍💼</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Trusted AI Agents: New Capabilities to Choose, Govern, and Scale with Confidence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11667/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:24:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11667/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New advancements in AI are here! The article discusses the importance of selecting, governing, and scaling AI agents effectively. It emphasizes building a secure AI ecosystem that ensures accuracy and reliability. Companies can gain a competitive edge by leveraging these new capabilities. Stay informed about the future of AI! 🤖✨ #AI #TechTrends #Innovation #GenAI #DigitalTransformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinventing Government with the Databricks Data Intelligence Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11524/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11524/</guid>
      <description>Transforming government operations is now possible with the Databricks Data Intelligence Platform. This innovative tool enhances data management and decision-making processes. The article discusses how the platform supports efficiency and transparency in government sectors, enabling better service delivery to citizens. Discover how data-driven insights can lead to improved outcomes in public administration. #DataIntelligence #GovernmentInnovation #Databricks #PublicSector 🌐📊🚀</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Frankfurt to the Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11519/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11519/</guid>
      <description>Databricks is transforming the landscape of banking and payments. Their innovative approaches help firms compete more effectively in a rapidly evolving market. The article discusses how Databricks collaborates with partner ecosystems to shape the future of global banking. This partnership aims to enhance efficiency and drive growth within the industry. 📈💳🌍 #BankingInnovation #Databricks #FinancialServices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Databricks Managed Disaster Recovery Helps Capital One Achieve Lakehouse Resilience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11520/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11520/</guid>
      <description>Databricks has collaborated with Capital One for over a year to enhance disaster recovery strategies. This partnership aims to strengthen Lakehouse resilience, ensuring data integrity and availability. By implementing managed solutions, they are improving operational efficiency and reducing risks associated with data management. #DataRecovery #Lakehouse #CapitalOne #Databricks #TechPartnerships 🌐🔒💡</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delta Sharing Top 10 Frequently Asked Questions, Answered - Part 1</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11497/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11497/</guid>
      <description>Delta Sharing is experiencing significant growth, with a remarkable 300% increase year-over-year. 📈 This article addresses the top 10 frequently asked questions regarding Delta Sharing, the leading open sharing protocol. It aims to clarify common inquiries and provide valuable insights for users. Stay informed about this important development in data sharing! #DeltaSharing #DataSharing #OpenProtocol #TechTrends #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Generative to Agentic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11484/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11484/</guid>
      <description>AI technology is evolving from generative models to agentic systems. Enterprise leaders are focusing on building and scaling effective AI strategies. This shift highlights the importance of data leadership in navigating the changing landscape of AI. Understanding these advancements is crucial for organizations aiming to leverage AI effectively. 🔍🤖📈 #AI #DataStrategy #TechnologyTrends #Innovations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Public Preview of Zerobus Ingest</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11498/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11498/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Zerobus Ingest is now in public preview as part of Lakeflow Connect. This new tool simplifies event data ingestion, allowing a direct path from sources to Delta tables without the need for a message bus. Explore how this can enhance your data management processes! #ZerobusIngest #LakeflowConnect #DataIngestion #TechInnovation #EventData</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the Partnership: How 100&#43; Customers Are Already Transforming Business with Databricks and Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11500/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11500/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments are underway as over 100 customers leverage the partnership between Databricks and Palantir. This collaboration focuses on unlocking value at scale, helping enterprises achieve real-world results. The article highlights various ways businesses are transforming operations and enhancing efficiency using these powerful tools. Stay tuned for more updates! 📈🤝 #Databricks #Palantir #BusinessTransformation #Innovation #Partnerships</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build Digital Twins for Operational Efficiency</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11499/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11499/</guid>
      <description>Discover the benefits of Digital Twins in manufacturing and industrial operations. 🌐 The article outlines how organizations can enhance operational efficiency through real-time insights and predictive maintenance. The new Digital Twin Solution Accelerator is highlighted as a key tool for achieving these goals. Explore the potential of this technology for your operations. 🔧📈 #DigitalTwins #Manufacturing #OperationalEfficiency #PredictiveMaintenance #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brickster Voices: Meet Maggie Chu, Sr. Manager, Field Engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11461/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 20:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11461/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Maggie Chu, Sr. Manager of Field Engineering at Brickster! In the latest Brickster Voices feature, she shares her journey in building and scaling alongside customers. Her insights highlight the importance of collaboration and innovation in the engineering field. Discover more about the experiences that shape our team! #BricksterVoices #FieldEngineering #Leadership #CareerJourney #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Business Intelligence Drives Smart Decision-Making</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11365/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 17:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11365/</guid>
      <description>📊 Business Intelligence (BI) is essential for organizations navigating vast amounts of data. It helps transform raw data into actionable insights, supporting informed decision-making. 💡 By leveraging BI tools, businesses can analyze trends, improve efficiency, and enhance customer experiences. This strategy is crucial in today’s competitive landscape. #BusinessIntelligence #DataDriven #SmartDecisions #Analytics #DataStrategy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices and Methods for LLM Evaluation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11366/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 17:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11366/</guid>
      <description>Exploring best practices for evaluating large language models (LLMs) is crucial as the technology gains traction. The article outlines key methods for assessment, emphasizing the importance of both quantitative metrics and qualitative analysis. Understanding these evaluation techniques can help companies enhance their use of LLMs effectively. 📊💡 #LLMEvaluation #DataScience #MachineLearning #TechTrends #AIInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLflow System Tables: Analyze Data Across All Your Experiments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11332/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11332/</guid>
      <description>🚀 MLflow introduces System Tables to streamline data analysis across experiments. This feature allows ML teams to build dashboards, set up SQL alerts, and gain insights into their MLflow data efficiently. Explore how these tools can enhance your workflow and decision-making. #MLflow #DataAnalysis #MachineLearning #AI #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing General Availability of Python Data Source API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11325/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 21:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11325/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The General Availability of PySpark’s Data Source API for Apache Spark™ 4.0 is here. This new feature enhances custom data connectivity, allowing for simpler integration using Python. Explore the potential of this API to unlock new data solutions! #PySpark #DataSourceAPI #ApacheSpark #Python #DataConnectivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s New in AI/BI - October 2025 Roundup</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11345/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 15:42:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11345/</guid>
      <description>🍂 Exciting updates in Databricks AI/BI this fall! October 2025 brings new innovations in AI/BI dashboards and Genie features to enhance your workspace. These advancements aim to improve speed and intelligence in data handling. Stay tuned for more updates on these tools! #Databricks #AI #BusinessIntelligence #Innovation #DataManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find Sensitive Data at Scale with Data Classification in Unity Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11322/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11322/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of data classification with Unity Catalog! This tool helps organizations automatically detect, tag, and track personally identifiable information (PII) across their data environments. By utilizing AI agents, it eliminates the need for manual tagging and scripts. Stay compliant and secure your sensitive data efficiently! 📊🔍 #DataSecurity #UnityCatalog #AI #DataManagement #SensitiveData</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Agent Supervisor Architecture: Orchestrating Enterprise AI at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11232/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11232/</guid>
      <description>BASF is leveraging a Multi-Agent Supervisor Architecture to enhance its enterprise AI capabilities. This approach aims to accelerate the deployment of Agentic AI within BASF Coatings. The focus is on delivering faster value, improving productivity, ensuring compliance, and supporting scalable growth. This innovative strategy highlights the potential of AI in transforming business operations. 🤖✨ #BASF #AI #Innovation #EnterpriseAI #Growth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upgrade Your Lakehouse: Your How-To Guide for Converting to Unity Catalog Managed Tables</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11233/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 14:41:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11233/</guid>
      <description>Transform your lakehouse with the new SET MANAGED command! 🔄 This guide explains how to convert external tables to Unity Catalog Managed Tables, enhancing query speed and reducing costs. Learn the steps to streamline your data management process effectively. #DataManagement #UnityCatalog #Lakehouse #TechGuide #Efficiency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents In Advertising for Contextual Content Placement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11182/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 22:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11182/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming advertising by improving contextual content placement. The article discusses how AI agents can effectively determine the best spots for ads, addressing a significant challenge in the industry. By utilizing platforms like Databricks, advertisers can enhance their strategies and reach their target audiences more effectively. Discover how AI is reshaping the advertising landscape! 🤖📈 #Advertising #AI #DigitalMarketing #ContextualMarketing #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling Business Users on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11170/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 19:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11170/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of your workforce with Databricks! 🚀 The article highlights the importance of empowering business users to leverage data effectively. It offers insights on building a data-driven culture within organizations. Key strategies include training programs and user-friendly tools to enhance data accessibility. Discover how to transform your team into data-savvy professionals! 📊💡 #Databricks #DataDriven #BusinessIntelligence #SaaS #Empowerment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic AI and the Future of Advertising: Why the Next Frontier Runs on Unified Data</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11163/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11163/</guid>
      <description>The advertising landscape is evolving rapidly. Agentic AI is transforming traditional marketing by shifting from a reactive approach to continuous optimization. This change is driven by unified data, which enhances decision-making and improves campaign performance. Stay informed about the future of advertising! 📈🤖 #Advertising #AI #MarketingTrends #DataDriven #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast PEFT Serving at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11127/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 17:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11127/</guid>
      <description>At Databricks, we&amp;rsquo;ve developed a custom inference engine that significantly enhances AI performance for our customers. 🚀 Our engine not only doubles the speed of some open-source alternatives but also reduces errors on common benchmarks. This achievement supports the efficient serving of fine-tuned AI models. We focus on building an infrastructure that ensures scalability, reliability, and security, addressing various challenges like load balancing and health monitoring. With this innovative&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Customer Support: Swiggy’s Enterprise-Scale AI Agent Built with Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11171/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 05:44:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11171/</guid>
      <description>Swiggy has launched a new enterprise-scale AI agent, designed to enhance customer support. This innovation focuses on full automation and hyper-scalability, aiming to improve engagement and personalization for users. The AI solution is built on Databricks, showcasing Swiggy’s commitment to redefining customer experience in the industry. Stay tuned for more updates on this exciting development! 🤖📈 #Swiggy #CustomerSupport #AI #Innovation #Databricks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing table update triggers in Lakeflow Jobs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11078/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11078/</guid>
      <description>📢 Databricks has announced the general availability of table update triggers in Lakeflow Jobs! This new feature allows jobs to run only when a table updates, helping to reduce costs. Stay updated and optimize your workflows with this enhancement! #Databricks #LakeflowJobs #DataManagement #CostEfficiency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Risk Management: 5 Key Insights from the 2025 Gartner®  Risk Report</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-18-11042/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-18-11042/</guid>
      <description>🔍 The 2025 Gartner® Risk Report highlights key insights for the future of risk management. 1️⃣ Organizations must embrace technology to enhance their risk assessment processes. 2️⃣ A proactive approach is essential for identifying potential risks early. 3️⃣ Collaboration across departments improves risk awareness and response. 4️⃣ Continuous education on evolving risks is crucial. 5️⃣ Data-driven strategies will shape effective risk management frameworks. Stay informed and prepared! 📊🔒&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI Agent Paradigm: What It Means for the Future of Advertising</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11045/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11045/</guid>
      <description>AI Agents are transforming the advertising landscape by enhancing marketing strategies and improving consumer engagement. As these technologies evolve, they are expected to play a significant role in how brands connect with audiences, personalizing experiences on a broader scale. The impact of AI Agents on the advertising industry is set to shape future campaigns and interactions. 🤖📈 #Advertising #AI #Marketing #ConsumerEngagement #FutureTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise-Scale Governance: Migrating from Hive Metastore to Unity Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11035/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11035/</guid>
      <description>📊 Businesses are navigating complex data landscapes as they scale their digital capabilities. This article discusses the process of migrating from Hive Metastore to Unity Catalog. It highlights how organizations can manage large-scale workloads while maintaining data governance and optimizing performance. Learn more about this migration strategy to enhance your data management! 🔄📈 #DataGovernance #UnityCatalog #HiveMetastore #DataManagement #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Lakehouse to Digital Mind: Architecting a Multi-Agent AI Ecosystem on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 01:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11015/</guid>
      <description>Discover how Edmunds transformed its data lakehouse into a multi-agent AI platform using Databricks. This shift enables enhanced activation, automation, and ongoing innovation in enterprise operations. The article highlights the importance of a unified data approach in today’s digital landscape. Learn more about this innovative architecture and its impact on business. 🌐💡 #DataLakehouse #AI #Innovation #Databricks #DigitalTransformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How 7‑Eleven, Inc. Built a Game-Changing GenAI Creative Assistant for Marketing with Mosaic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11013/</guid>
      <description>7‑Eleven, Inc. has launched a new GenAI creative assistant developed by their AI Center of Excellence. This tool aims to enhance marketing efforts by streamlining campaign ideation. By using this tailored AI solution, 7‑Eleven is saving analysts time and achieving measurable results across marketing teams. #7Eleven #GenAI #MarketingInnovation #AI #BusinessImpact</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Master AI Agents with New Databricks Training</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 20:44:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11022/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks has launched a new training program aimed at helping teams master AI agents. The article discusses common challenges that teams face when working with generative AI and offers insights on closing these gaps. This initiative aims to empower organizations to leverage AI effectively in their operations. #AI #Databricks #GenerativeAI #Training #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pipeline Flow Monitoring</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10970/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10970/</guid>
      <description>🔍 &lt;strong&gt;Pipeline Flow Monitoring&lt;/strong&gt; is transforming predictive maintenance for gas pipelines. Recent advancements aim to enhance safety and efficiency, reducing the risk of ruptures and leaks. This technology enables real-time monitoring, allowing for timely interventions and maintenance. Stay informed about developments in energy and pipeline safety! #GasPipelines #PredictiveMaintenance #EnergyInnovation #SafetyFirst 🛢️⚙️</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn, Experiment, and Build with Databricks Free Edition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10633/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 20:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10633/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks has launched a Free Edition, making advanced data tools accessible to everyone! This edition, introduced at the Data + AI Summit, is designed for users to learn, experiment, and build projects without cost. Get started with your first projects and explore production experiments easily. #Databricks #AI #DataScience #FreeEdition #TechForAll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build High-Quality, Domain-Specific Agents at 95% Lower Cost</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10945/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10945/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking the potential of high-quality GenAI agents just got more affordable! A recent article discusses a new token-based pricing model for MLflow GenAI evaluation, which can reduce costs by 95%. This innovation emphasizes the importance of continuous evaluation for scaling these agents effectively. Stay ahead in the GenAI landscape! 💡 #GenAI #MachineLearning #Innovation #CostReduction #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating from Redshift to Databricks: A Field Guide for Data Teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10946/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 21:04:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10946/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Migrating from Amazon Redshift to Databricks can enhance data handling for teams. The article outlines practical steps for planning your migration, validating outcomes, and optimizing the process for scalability and flexibility. Key considerations include assessing data volumes and workloads to ensure a smooth transition. 📊 #DataMigration #Databricks #Redshift #DataTeams #DataManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Banks and Insurers: Open Ecosystems, AI and Curiosity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10885/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 09:16:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10885/</guid>
      <description>Discover insights from a recent Databricks webinar on the future of banks and insurers. Industry leaders discussed how open ecosystems and agentic AI are essential for driving growth. They emphasized the importance of innovation in future-proofing financial services organizations. Learn actionable lessons to stay ahead in a rapidly evolving landscape. 💼🤖📈 #Banking #Insurance #Innovation #AI #FinancialServices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powering the Future: Data and AI in Action Across the Energy Industry</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10877/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10877/</guid>
      <description>Energy companies are adapting to rising global demand and operational complexities by leveraging data and AI technologies. These advancements are enhancing efficiency, optimizing resource management, and improving decision-making processes. The integration of AI in energy operations is transforming how companies approach challenges and opportunities in the sector. Stay informed about the evolving landscape of energy technology! ⚡️💡 #EnergyInnovation #DataDriven #AI #Sustainability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build and Scale Multimodal AI Systems on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10872/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10872/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of multimodal AI systems on Databricks! 🌐 This article discusses the significance of multimodal AI for enterprises, emphasizing that real-world applications require diverse data types. Learn about best practices for building and scaling these systems effectively to enhance AI capabilities. #AI #Databricks #MultimodalAI #TechTrends #EnterpriseAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn, Experiment, and Build with Databricks Free Edition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10633/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 21:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10633/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks has launched a Free Edition, making advanced data tools accessible to everyone! This edition, introduced at the Data + AI Summit, is designed for users to learn, experiment, and build projects without cost. Get started with your first projects and explore production experiments easily. #Databricks #AI #DataScience #FreeEdition #TechForAll</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Reliability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10634/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10634/</guid>
      <description>Data reliability is essential for organizations today. It impacts decision-making and overall business performance. With the rise of data-driven strategies, ensuring accurate and consistent data is vital for success. Businesses must prioritize data integrity to maintain trust and efficiency. 🔍📊💼 #DataReliability #BusinessStrategy #DataIntegrity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercharge your Enterprise BI: How to approach your migration to AI/BI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10635/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 20:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10635/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to transform your Business Intelligence? Databricks successfully migrated over 1,300 dashboards to AI/BI in just 5 months. This transition led to a remarkable 5x performance increase and annual savings of $880K. Explore the key steps and benefits of modernizing your enterprise BI. #BusinessIntelligence #AIMigration #DataStrategy #CostSavings #PerformanceBoost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic Pricing in Airlines: How AI Can Reshape Revenue Strategy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10631/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 17:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10631/</guid>
      <description>Delta Airlines has introduced an AI-driven dynamic pricing system, significantly changing its revenue strategy. This approach allows for real-time price adjustments based on demand, competition, and other factors. The implementation aims to optimize ticket sales and enhance customer satisfaction by providing competitive pricing. This shift highlights the growing role of AI technology in the airline industry. ✈️📈🤖 #DynamicPricing #AirlineIndustry #AI #DeltaAirlines #RevenueStrategy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Variant: A New Open Standard for Semi-Structured Data in Apache Parquet™, Delta Lake, and Apache Iceberg™</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10614/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 10:37:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10614/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Introducing Variant, a new open standard designed for semi-structured data in Apache Parquet™, Delta Lake, and Apache Iceberg™. This standard aims to enhance data interoperability and accessibility across various platforms. With the growing presence of semi-structured data in fields like AI and telemetry, Variant seeks to streamline data handling processes. Learn more about how Variant can impact data management! #DataManagement #OpenStandard #ApacheParquet #DeltaLake #ApacheIceberg</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Lakes vs Data Warehouses: What Your Organization Needs to Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10602/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 17:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10602/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving data landscape, organizations must choose between data lakes and data warehouses. Data lakes store vast amounts of raw data, allowing for flexibility and scalability. In contrast, data warehouses focus on structured data, optimizing for quick access and analysis. Understanding the differences is crucial for effective data management. 📊🔍 #DataManagement #DataArchitecture #Analytics #BusinessIntelligence #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks&#39; Commitment to European Sovereignty and Growth</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10517/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10517/</guid>
      <description>Databricks is reinforcing its commitment to European sovereignty and growth. 🌍 The company emphasizes the importance of innovation within the EU and aims to support local enterprises by providing advanced data solutions. Their initiatives are designed to enhance data security and foster collaboration among European businesses. #Databricks #EuropeanSovereignty #Innovation #DataSolutions #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examining Versionless Apache Spark™: AI-powered upgrades and seamless stability for 2 billion workloads</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10499/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10499/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Versionless Apache Spark™ revolutionizes how we handle upgrades! The article discusses the challenges of upgrading Spark and introduces a new approach that eliminates manual upgrades. This innovation aims to enhance performance and maintain stability across 2 billion workloads. Stay tuned for more on AI-powered advancements in data engineering! #ApacheSpark #DataEngineering #TechInnovation #AI #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the General Availability of SAP Business Data Cloud Connect to Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10456/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 13:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10456/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Databricks users! SAP Business Data Cloud Connect is now generally available, enabling seamless access to SAP data within Databricks lakehouses. This integration simplifies data management with just a few clicks. Explore new possibilities for your data-driven projects! #SAP #Databricks #DataIntegration #BusinessIntelligence #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Loan Processing with AI on Databricks: How Vantage Bank Texas Transformed Lending Workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10425/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10425/</guid>
      <description>Vantage Bank Texas has successfully transformed its loan processing workflows by partnering with Cavallo Technologies to develop an AI lending assistant on Databricks. This innovative solution has achieved an impressive accuracy rate of 94%, significantly speeding up the loan approval process. Shawn Main, Chief Business Architect at Vantage Bank, played a key role in this transformation. #Fintech #AI #BankingInnovation #LoanProcessing #Databricks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smarter Supply Chains With Data and AI: Why It’s Time to Rethink Inventory Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10334/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10334/</guid>
      <description>Rethinking inventory management is essential for modern supply chains. 📦 The article discusses how complexity in supply chains impacts business success. It emphasizes the importance of leveraging data and AI technologies to enhance efficiency and decision-making. 📊 Adopting these innovations can help businesses navigate challenges and improve overall performance. #SupplyChain #Data #AI #InventoryManagement #BusinessSuccess</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnite and Databricks Announce New Partnership to Transform Ad Data Activation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10327/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10327/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Magnite and Databricks have formed a partnership aimed at enhancing ad data activation for marketers. This collaboration focuses on secure and efficient onboarding of audience data, enabling smarter targeting across various channels. The integration is set to streamline processes in the advertising landscape. #Marketing #DataIntegration #AdTech #Partnership #AudienceTargeting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mooncake Labs joins Databricks to accelerate the vision of Lakebase</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10317/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10317/</guid>
      <description>🌙 Exciting news in the tech world! Mooncake Labs is officially joining Databricks to enhance the development of Lakebase. This collaboration aims to streamline data management and analytics, supporting innovative solutions in the industry. Stay tuned for updates on how this partnership will shape the future of data platforms! #MooncakeLabs #Databricks #Lakebase #DataManagement #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Kubernetes Load Balancing at Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10304/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10304/</guid>
      <description>At Databricks, Kubernetes is central to our systems. The article discusses our innovative approach to client-side load balancing, which utilizes real-time service discovery for both internal and ingress traffic. This method enhances efficiency and performance. Future directions include further exploration of load balancing strategies. #Kubernetes #LoadBalancing #Databricks #TechInnovation #CloudComputing 🚀🔧✨</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setting the Stage: AI Governance for Insurance in 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10285/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10285/</guid>
      <description>As the insurance industry embraces artificial intelligence, regulatory scrutiny is increasing. The article discusses how Databricks and Deloitte are assisting insurers in navigating the NAIC’s proposed AI Model Law. They focus on governance, risk management, and trusted AI practices to ensure compliance and ethical use of technology. These developments highlight the importance of robust AI governance in the sector. 🤖📊 #AIGovernance #Insurance #RiskManagement #AI #Compliance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Supply Chain Management with AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10286/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10286/</guid>
      <description>Transforming supply chain management is crucial for industries facing complexity and uncertainty. AI agents are emerging as valuable tools that support teams in making effective decisions. These technologies enhance efficiency and streamline processes, addressing long-standing challenges in supply chains. Stay informed on the evolving landscape of supply chain management. 🤖📦 #SupplyChain #AI #Innovation #Business #Efficiency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Data Intelligence for Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10254/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10254/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the cybersecurity world! A new platform, Data Intelligence for Cybersecurity, has been launched. This unified platform focuses on AI agents and real-time response to enhance security measures. Stay informed and protect your data effectively! 🔒💻 #Cybersecurity #DataIntelligence #AI #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing Car Measurement Data Storage and Analysis: Mercedes-Benz&#39;s Petabyte-Scale Solution on the Databricks Intelligence Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10244/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10244/</guid>
      <description>Mercedes-Benz is enhancing car measurement data storage and analysis with a new petabyte-scale solution on the Databricks Intelligence Platform. This advancement aims to utilize the growing data from connected vehicles, improving data management and insights in the automotive sector. Stay tuned for more updates on this innovative approach! 🚗📊🔍 #MercedesBenz #DataAnalytics #AutomotiveInnovation #Databricks #ConnectedVehicles</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Sonnet 4.5 Is Here</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10227/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10227/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Claude Sonnet 4.5 has officially launched! This new version is now accessible in DBSQL and Agent Bricks, enhancing data processing capabilities for users. Customers are managing vast amounts of data daily on Databricks, and the integration of generative AI continues to evolve. Stay updated! #ClaudeSonnet #Databricks #GenerativeAI #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing SQL Server connector from Lakeflow Connect, now Generally Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10096/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10096/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Lakeflow Connect! The SQL Server connector is now Generally Available, allowing users to seamlessly unlock and analyze SQL Server data. This integration aims to enhance business insights and drive results effectively. Stay updated on how this tool can benefit your data strategy! #SQLServer #DataIntegration #BusinessInsights #LakeflowConnect #Databricks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run OpenAI Models Directly on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10056/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10056/</guid>
      <description>🚀 OpenAI and Databricks have teamed up to enable users to run OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s latest models, including GPT-5, directly on the Databricks platform. This collaboration offers dedicated capacity and seamless integration with Agent Bricks and Model Serving, enhancing the development of high-quality AI agents. Stay tuned for more innovations! 🤖💡 #OpenAI #Databricks #AI #GPT5 #Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brickster Voices: Meet Cindy Nicola, VP Global Talent Acquisition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10097/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 07:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10097/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Cindy Nicola, VP of Global Talent Acquisition at Databricks! In the latest Brickster Voices feature, Cindy shares her insights on career growth, collaboration, and leadership. Her journey highlights the importance of fostering a strong company culture and guiding talent development. Discover how Cindy&amp;rsquo;s experiences shape the future of talent acquisition at Databricks! #Leadership #TalentAcquisition #CareerGrowth #Databricks #BricksterVoices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building State-of-the-Art Enterprise Agents 90x Cheaper with Automated Prompt Optimization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10042/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 21:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10042/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of AI with Databricks Agent Bricks! 🚀 This platform enables the creation and deployment of high-quality AI agents tailored for enterprise workflows. Key features include automated prompt optimization, which enhances prompt performance while reducing costs significantly. Recent evaluations show that open-source models can outperform proprietary ones at a fraction of the cost. 💡 Learn how to leverage these techniques for superior quality-cost tradeoffs in your AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brickster Voices: Meet Chao Cai, Sr. Director, Engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10043/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10043/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Chao Cai, Sr. Director of Engineering at Brickster! In the latest installment of Brickster Voices, Chao shares insights into his career journey and the role of AI in today&amp;rsquo;s tech landscape. Discover how he leads at the intersection of innovation and engineering, shaping the future of the industry. #BricksterVoices #Leadership #AI #Engineering #CareerJourney</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivering the Right Care at the Right Time</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10036/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10036/</guid>
      <description>Discover how the &amp;ldquo;right care at the right time&amp;rdquo; approach is transforming health plans and provider strategies. The article explores how FHIR-powered advanced analytics can enhance member experiences throughout their care journey. This method aims to ensure timely interventions and improved health outcomes. Stay informed about the latest in healthcare innovation! 🏥📊💡 #HealthcareInnovation #RightCare #FHIR #HealthAnalytics #MemberImpact</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Lag to Agility: Reinventing Freshworks’ Data Ingestion Architecture</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9961/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9961/</guid>
      <description>Freshworks is transforming its data ingestion architecture to enhance data processing capabilities. 🌐 This shift aims to improve agility in handling data at scale using Databricks, a platform designed for efficient data streaming. 🚀 The focus is on implementing intuitive, AI-driven solutions for better business outcomes. #DataIngestion #SaaS #AI #Databricks #BusinessSolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adaptive Identity Resolution on Databricks with Hightouch</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9945/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9945/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking customer engagement is essential for businesses today. The article discusses how Hightouch leverages Databricks for adaptive identity resolution. This approach transforms fragmented data into a unified customer view, enabling long-term relationships. By integrating various data sources, companies can enhance their understanding of customer behavior and preferences. Learn more about this innovative strategy to improve customer engagement! 📊🤝 #DataIntegration #CustomerEngagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enforce consistent, secure tagging across data and AI assets with Governed Tags in Unity Catalog (Public Preview)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9946/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9946/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news! Governed Tags are now in Public Preview for Unity Catalog. This feature aims to enhance tagging consistency and security for data and AI assets. It will help streamline processes like discovery, compliance, and cost attribution. Stay updated as this innovation unfolds! #DataManagement #AI #UnityCatalog #GovernedTags #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How KPMG uses Delta Sharing to access and audit tens of billions of transactions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9834/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9834/</guid>
      <description>KPMG is leveraging Delta Sharing to enhance data access and auditing for billions of transactions. This approach addresses the significant challenges organizations face in managing secure data access. The article discusses practical applications of this technology, particularly in the energy supply sector, highlighting its impact on improving audit processes. 🔍💼📊 #DataAccess #KPMG #DeltaSharing #Auditing #EnergySector</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fueling the Next Generation of AI: Announcing the Databricks AI Accelerator Program</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9772/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9772/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Databricks! The company has launched the AI Accelerator Program aimed at supporting early-stage founders. This initiative will provide essential capital, mentorship, and access to a robust ecosystem for building innovative AI solutions using the Databricks Data Intelligence Platform. This program is designed to empower builders who are pushing the boundaries of data. #AI #Databricks #StartupSupport #Innovation #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Databricks Helps Banks Navigate Interest Rate Changes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9750/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9750/</guid>
      <description>Banks are facing challenges with interest rate changes. Databricks offers solutions by providing unified data, real-time analytics, and AI-driven actions. This helps banks make quicker and smarter decisions regarding interest rates. Learn more about how these tools can enhance financial strategies. 📊💡 #Banking #DataAnalytics #InterestRates #AI #Databricks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Public Preview of Databricks One</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9739/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9739/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from the Data + AI Summit! Databricks has announced the public preview of Databricks One, designed to enhance employee experiences by making insights more accessible. This innovative platform aims to streamline data discovery for teams across organizations. Stay tuned for more updates on this development! #DatabricksOne #DataAI #Innovation #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Databricks at Sibos in Frankfurt!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9714/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 23:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9714/</guid>
      <description>Join Databricks at Sibos in Frankfurt! 🌍 Sibos is a key event where leaders in banking and payments come together to connect and innovate. This year, the focus is on transforming finance through data and AI. Engage in insightful sessions, dynamic conversations, and enjoy a lively rooftop happy hour. Don’t miss out! 🍹💡 #Sibos2025 #Databricks #FinanceInnovation #Banking #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating Data Documentation with AI: How 7-Eleven Bridged the Metadata Gap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9672/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9672/</guid>
      <description>7-Eleven has tackled its complex data ecosystem by automating data documentation with AI. 🤖 By using intelligent agents, the company has streamlined the migration of thousands of data definitions. This approach aims to enhance the reliability and quality of insights for better decision-making. 📊 Learn more about the steps 7-Eleven is taking to bridge the metadata gap. #DataAutomation #AI #BusinessIntelligence #7Eleven #MetadataManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The key to production AI agents: Evaluations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9625/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 23:30:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9625/</guid>
      <description>Organizations are increasingly looking to implement GenAI agents for workflow automation and efficiency. A significant focus is on evaluations, which play a crucial role in ensuring these AI agents meet performance standards and align with business goals. Understanding the importance of thorough assessments can help organizations maximize the benefits of AI technology. 🤖📈 #AI #Automation #GenAI #BusinessEfficiency #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customizing Databricks Assistant with Instructions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9626/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 21:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9626/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of Databricks Assistant! The article discusses how to customize the Assistant by adding specific instructions for conversations. This feature allows users to incorporate preferences, such as using &amp;ldquo;snake_case&amp;rdquo; in responses, enhancing communication efficiency. Explore how these customizations can improve your experience! 🤖✨ #Databricks #DataScience #AI #Customization #TechTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks on Databricks: Scaling Database Reliability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9623/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 19:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9623/</guid>
      <description>Databricks engineers share insights on enhancing database reliability through big data analytics tools. The article discusses strategies employed to scale their systems effectively, showcasing the role of advanced analytics in ensuring dependable performance. Learn how these techniques can benefit database management. 📊🔍 #Databricks #DatabaseReliability #BigData #DataEngineering #Analytics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Performance Ratelimiting at Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9593/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9593/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks engineers are tackling the complexities of distributed ratelimiting. The article outlines innovative approaches to enhance performance in this area, showcasing the team&amp;rsquo;s commitment to solving challenging problems. This could lead to significant improvements in data processing efficiency. Stay tuned for more insights from their engineering efforts! #Databricks #Engineering #DataProcessing #TechInnovation #Ratelimiting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Investment Regime Is Here. Are You Ready for It?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9534/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9534/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The global economy is undergoing a significant transformation, moving beyond traditional market cycles. 📦 Trade flows and supply chains are being rewired, with a renewed focus on industrial policies. 🔍 This new investment regime poses both challenges and opportunities for stakeholders. Stay informed and adjust your strategies accordingly. #InvestmentRegime #GlobalEconomy #SupplyChain #IndustrialPolicy #TradeFlows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Observability in Lakeflow Helps You Build Reliable Data Pipelines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9535/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9535/</guid>
      <description>Lakeflow offers a suite of observability features designed for data engineers. These tools help maintain efficient and reliable data pipelines, even as data volume increases. By utilizing Lakeflow, teams can confidently manage the health of their data systems, reducing risks associated with stale pipelines. #DataPipelines #Observability #Lakeflow #DataEngineering #DataManagement 📊🔍💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Identity Management for Entra ID is now Generally Available in Azure Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9529/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9529/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Automatic Identity Management (AIM) for Entra ID is now generally available on Azure Databricks. This feature allows for instant connection of users, groups, and service principals, streamlining setup and enhancing collaboration. Explore how AIM can improve your workflow! #AzureDatabricks #IdentityManagement #CloudComputing #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI as a conduit for management cybernetics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9493/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9493/</guid>
      <description>AI is emerging as a crucial tool in management cybernetics, enhancing decision-making processes in organizations. The article discusses how AI can optimize operations and improve efficiency by providing insights into complex data systems. As businesses look to the future, understanding AI’s role in decision science becomes vital for effective management. 🔍🤖📊 #AI #Management #DecisionScience #Cybernetics #BusinessInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Search to Sale: How AI Is Redefining Customer Engagement and Loyalty in Retail</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7760/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7760/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming retail by enhancing customer engagement and loyalty. Key advancements include: 🤖 AI-driven personalization that tailors shopping experiences. 🛒 Retail media networks that connect brands with consumers. 💬 Intelligent customer service improving support throughout the shopping journey. These innovations are reshaping how we shop. #RetailInnovation #CustomerExperience #AI #Ecommerce #CustomerLoyalty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kythera Labs, a Databricks Built-On Partner, saves $2M&#43;/year using Delta Sharing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7730/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7730/</guid>
      <description>Kythera Labs, a partner of Databricks, has achieved significant savings by utilizing Delta Sharing. The healthcare sector deals with vast amounts of sensitive data, and Kythera Labs has streamlined data sharing across the cloud. This innovation is projected to save the company over $2 million annually. Learn more about their approach and its impact on healthcare data management. 💻📊 #DataSharing #HealthcareInnovation #Databricks #CostSavings #DeltaSharing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now GA: Share Materialized Views and Streaming Tables with Delta Sharing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7691/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7691/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in data sharing! Delta Sharing now supports Materialized Views and Streaming Tables, allowing seamless sharing of real-time and pre-aggregated data. This feature enhances security and accessibility across different clouds, regions, and platforms. Connect with your customers and partners more effectively! #DeltaSharing #DataManagement #CloudComputing #RealTimeData #DataSharing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Databricks Assistant Data Science Agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7700/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7700/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Databricks! The Databricks Assistant has evolved into a powerful Data Science Agent. This tool streamlines the process from data exploration to actionable results in just minutes. Since its launch two years ago, it has become essential for data teams. Stay ahead in data science with the latest advancements! #Databricks #DataScience #Innovation #AI #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architecting a High-Concurrency, Low-Latency Data Warehouse on Databricks That Scales</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7642/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 07:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7642/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of your data with a high-concurrency, low-latency data warehouse on Databricks. The article outlines key architectural considerations and a technical solution breakdown for implementing production-grade analytics. It also discusses real-world scenarios and trade-offs to keep in mind. Explore practical insights to achieve cost-efficient performance at scale. 📊💡 #DataWarehouse #Databricks #Analytics #BigData #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use Lakebase as a transactional data layer for Databricks Apps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7496/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:43:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7496/</guid>
      <description>Explore how to effectively use Lakebase as a transactional data layer for Databricks Apps. The article discusses the integration of Lakebase in building internal tools and AI applications. It highlights key strategies for optimizing data management and enhancing application performance. For developers and data professionals, this approach can streamline processes and improve efficiency. #Databricks #Lakebase #DataManagement #AI #TechSolutions 🌊📊💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Foundation for Enterprise AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7450/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7450/</guid>
      <description>Enterprise AI has shifted from being a trial to a necessity for businesses. Global organizations must now integrate AI into their operations to maintain a competitive edge. Connecting SAP with your entire data estate can streamline this process and enhance efficiency. Stay ahead in the evolving tech landscape! 🌐🤖 #EnterpriseAI #SAP #DataIntegration #BusinessStrategy #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Approach to Data Exfiltration Protection on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7446/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7446/</guid>
      <description>Data exfiltration poses a significant security risk for organizations. A recent article outlines a comprehensive framework for protecting against unauthorized data movement on Databricks. The recommendations focus on unified strategies to enhance data security and prevent breaches. Implementing these measures can help safeguard sensitive information effectively. 🔒🛡️ #DataSecurity #Databricks #CyberSecurity #DataProtection #InformationSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracking Complex Contracts with GenAI on Azure Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7287/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 07:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7287/</guid>
      <description>At a top diagnostic healthcare manufacturer, contract management has been transformed using GenAI on Azure Databricks. The implementation of advanced analytics has reduced contract review time by 92%, enabling quicker decision-making. This innovation has also revealed valuable business insights. #Healthcare #Analytics #GenAI #AzureDatabricks #BusinessInsights 🌟📄💡</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivering Agentic BI: How to Unify Infrastructure, Data and Semantics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7229/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7229/</guid>
      <description>Unifying infrastructure, data, and semantics is key to delivering effective Business Intelligence (BI). The article discusses strategies for data teams and professionals to enhance their BI efforts. It emphasizes the importance of collaboration and the integration of various data sources. Explore these best practices to streamline your BI processes. 📊🔗💡 #BusinessIntelligence #DataIntegration #BestPractices #DataManagement #Analytics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tecton is Joining Databricks to Power Real-Time Data for Personalized AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6318/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 23:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6318/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news in the data world! Tecton is set to join forces with Databricks to enhance real-time data capabilities for personalized AI agents. This partnership aims to streamline data operations and improve AI performance across various applications. Stay tuned for advancements in AI technology! #DataScience #ArtificialIntelligence #TechNews #Databricks #Tecton</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing the Future: How Databricks Powers Financial Services</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6309/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6309/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving financial services landscape, data security and compliance are vital for growth. Databricks enables financial institutions to build resilience and accelerate innovation while ensuring adherence to regulations. This approach supports the safe use of data and AI technologies in the sector. Understanding these elements is crucial for navigating future challenges. 📊🔐✨ #DataSecurity #FinancialServices #Innovation #Compliance #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Processing Millions of Events from Thousands of Aircraft with One Declarative Pipeline</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6310/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6310/</guid>
      <description>A new article discusses how tens of thousands of aircraft generate IoT events every second. It highlights the use of Lakeflow declarative pipelines and PySpark custom data sources to process millions of these events efficiently. The focus is on building scalable systems to manage this vast amount of data effectively. ✈️🌐📊 #Aviation #DataProcessing #IoT #CloudComputing #ScalableSystems</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Booking to Bon Voyage: How AI Is Redefining the Travel &amp; Hospitality Experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5102/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5102/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming the travel and hospitality industry, enhancing guest experiences from booking to arrival. With advanced data analytics, businesses can offer personalized services that cater to individual preferences. This technology also streamlines operations, making travel more efficient. Stay ahead in the evolving travel landscape! ✈️🌍 #TravelTech #AI #Hospitality #Innovation #CustomerExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Public Preview of Request for Access in Unity Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5103/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5103/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Databricks! The public preview of the Request for Access feature in Unity Catalog has been announced. This tool aims to enhance self-service data discovery and simplify access provisioning for users in security-focused enterprises. Stay informed and empower your teams with better data access! 📊🔐 #DataAccess #UnityCatalog #Databricks #DataSecurity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI is Transforming the Way Retailers Connect With Consumers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5104/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5104/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming retail by enhancing connections between brands and consumers. Companies like Pilot, adidas, and PRADA Group are utilizing the Databricks Data Intelligence Platform to harness data effectively. From personalized experiences to accurate forecasting, AI is paving the way for innovative strategies in the retail sector. Stay tuned for more insights on the impact of technology in retail! 🤖🛍️📊 #RetailInnovation #AI #ConsumerExperience #DataIntelligence #TechnologyTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse ETL with Lakebase: Activate your lakehouse data for operational analytics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5105/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5105/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of your lakehouse data with Reverse ETL using Lakebase! 🌊 This approach allows you to serve data to applications efficiently and at scale, eliminating the need for custom pipelines. It bridges the gap between analytics and operations, enhancing decision-making processes. Explore how to activate your data for seamless operational analytics! 📊🔄 #DataAnalytics #Lakehouse #ReverseETL #OperationalExcellence #Lakebase</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Real-Time Mode in Apache Spark™ Structured Streaming</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5107/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5107/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data engineers! Apache Spark™ Structured Streaming now features a Real-Time Mode that processes events in milliseconds. This upgrade enhances the ability to manage mission-critical data pipelines efficiently. Stay updated with the latest in streaming technology! #ApacheSpark #StructuredStreaming #RealTimeData #DataEngineering #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reranking in Mosaic AI Vector Search for Faster, Smarter Retrieval in RAG Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5108/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5108/</guid>
      <description>Unlock faster, smarter retrieval in AI with the latest advancements in Mosaic AI Vector Search. Organizations can now enhance their RAG agents to deliver more relevant answers efficiently, all with a simple line of code. This innovation addresses challenges faced in handling unstructured data. Stay ahead in AI technology! 🚀💡 #AI #Mosaic #VectorSearch #Innovation #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing SQL Stored Procedures in Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5109/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5109/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks is enhancing its platform with SQL Stored Procedures! These procedures aim to simplify repetitive SQL tasks such as data cleaning and updating business rules. This feature will streamline workflows, making it easier for teams to manage their data. Explore how this advancement can benefit your operations! #Databricks #SQLStoredProcedures #DataManagement #TechUpdates #DataAnalytics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks Assistant Edit Mode: The Fastest Way to Transform Your Notebooks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5110/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5110/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Databricks! They have launched the Assistant Edit Mode, which allows users to make AI-driven edits across notebooks with just one prompt. This feature aims to enhance efficiency and consistency in data processing. This innovation is designed to streamline workflows and improve productivity for users. #Databricks #AI #DataScience #Productivity #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Bricks in Action: Smarter Offer Targeting for Sales Teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4949/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4949/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking smarter sales strategies! 🚀 The article discusses how the Agent Bricks Multi-Agent Supervisor is enhancing sales delivery. By using data-driven methods, sales teams can achieve faster and more targeted offers. This approach aims to improve overall effectiveness in reaching potential clients. Discover how technology is reshaping sales tactics! 💼📊 #SalesStrategy #DataDriven #AgentBricks #SalesInnovation #TargetedMarketing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How UiPath Built a Scalable Real-Time ETL pipeline on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4950/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 08:12:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4950/</guid>
      <description>🚀 UiPath has developed a scalable real-time ETL pipeline using Databricks to enhance automation processes. This pipeline aims to deliver fast and reliable data processing, which is crucial for effective decision-making. By leveraging Databricks, UiPath is focused on improving operational efficiency and customer satisfaction. #UiPath #Databricks #ETL #Automation #DataProcessing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passing the Security Vibe Check: The Dangers of Vibe Coding</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4951/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4951/</guid>
      <description>In a recent article from Databricks, the concept of &amp;ldquo;vibe coding&amp;rdquo; is examined in relation to software security. The piece discusses how developers often rely on intuition or &amp;ldquo;vibes&amp;rdquo; when assessing security risks, which can lead to vulnerabilities. It emphasizes the importance of structured security practices over subjective judgments. Understanding these risks is crucial for building safer software systems. 🔒💻 #CyberSecurity #SoftwareDevelopment #VibeCoding #TechInsights #DataProtection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judging with Confidence: Meet PGRM, the Promptable Reward Model</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4952/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4952/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the Prompt-Guided Reward Model (PGRM) from Databricks! This innovative tool enhances AI monitoring and evaluation, offering a flexible solution for businesses. PGRM adapts to new rules, flags uncertain cases, and provides confidence-backed scores for AI decisions. 📊✨ It combines the strengths of LLM judges and reward models, achieving high accuracy in judgment quality while facilitating scalable oversight. With PGRM, companies can ensure safety, accuracy, and alignment with brand&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing Materialized Views Recomputes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4953/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4953/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover strategies for optimizing the incremental computation of materialized views in data management. The article discusses techniques that digital-native companies can implement to enhance efficiency. It highlights the importance of improving performance while managing data effectively. Learn how to leverage these strategies for better data handling and quicker insights! 📊🔍 #DataManagement #MaterializedViews #Optimization #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching AI to Fix Your Code: My Summer Improving Quick Fix at Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4779/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4779/</guid>
      <description>This summer, I interned at Databricks, focusing on enhancing AI capabilities for coding assistance. The project aimed to improve the Quick Fix feature, helping developers identify and resolve coding issues more efficiently. This experience highlighted the potential of AI in software development and its real-world applications. 🤖💻 #AI #Coding #Internship #Databricks #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7x Faster Medical Image Ingestion with Python Data Source API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4758/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4758/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in medical imaging! A recent article discusses a new Python Data Source API that enhances DICOM data ingestion speed by seven times. This development utilizes industry-standard libraries like pydicom and zipfile. This improvement aims to streamline processes in healthcare and life sciences, addressing the challenges of handling medical images effectively. #MedicalImaging #HealthcareInnovation #Python #DICOM #DataScience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personalizing Players&#39; Experiences with Recommendation Systems</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4759/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4759/</guid>
      <description>Discover how recommendation systems enhance player experiences in gaming! These systems analyze player behavior to offer personalized content, improving engagement and satisfaction. By tailoring experiences, games can better connect with their audiences. Explore the impact of these technologies on player-centric design. 🎮📈 #Gaming #RecommendationSystems #PlayerExperience #TechInGames #GameDesign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build with GPT-5 on Databricks with AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4760/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4760/</guid>
      <description>🚀 OpenAI has launched GPT-5, their latest and most advanced language model! This new model can be integrated with Databricks through the AI Gateway, allowing users to harness its capabilities securely and at scale. Developers can now leverage Mosaic AI Gateway to enhance their applications effectively. #OpenAI #GPT5 #Databricks #AIGateway #MosaicAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing OpenAI’s New Open Models on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-3180/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-3180/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from OpenAI! They&amp;rsquo;ve partnered with Databricks to launch new open weight models, gpt-oss 20B and gpt-oss 120B. These models will help developers build intelligent, domain-specific AI agents securely. Stay tuned for updates on how these advancements can transform AI applications! #OpenAI #Databricks #AI #MachineLearning #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent Learning from Human Feedback (ALHF): A Databricks Knowledge Assistant Case Study</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-3181/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-3181/</guid>
      <description>Discover the innovative concept of Agent Learning from Human Feedback (ALHF) in the latest Databricks blog. ALHF allows agents to learn from minimal natural language feedback, enhancing their adaptability in specialized enterprise environments. The case study highlights its application in the Databricks Agent Bricks Knowledge Assistant, showcasing significant improvements in answer quality with limited expert feedback. This approach addresses the challenges of tuning AI systems by enabling&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Databricks Vancouver Development Center</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3182/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3182/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news! Databricks is expanding its R&amp;amp;D efforts with a new development center in Vancouver. This initiative aims to enhance capabilities in data and AI, fostering innovation in the tech community. Stay tuned for updates on projects and opportunities coming from this new location! #Databricks #Vancouver #DataInnovation #AI #TechExpansion</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
