<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cisco-Developer-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/cisco-developer-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cisco-Developer-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/cisco-developer-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SE Labs Names Cisco Secure Firewall Best Enterprise NGFW 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11394/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11394/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://blogs.cisco.com/feed&#34;&gt;Cisco Developer Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://blogs.cisco.com/security/se-labs-names-cisco-secure-firewall-best-enterprise-ngfw-2025&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber resilience for all: How Cisco and NIIT Foundation are securing India’s digital future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11391/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 08:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11391/</guid>
      <description>🚀 As India embraces digital transformation, Cisco and NIIT Foundation are addressing cybersecurity challenges with their Cyber Suraksha initiative. Their goal is to train over one million individuals in cybersecurity, aiming to build a safer digital landscape. The program includes three key courses: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Cyber Awareness&lt;/strong&gt; for youth. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Cyber Smart&lt;/strong&gt; for college students. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Cyber Workforce&lt;/strong&gt; focused on employability. This partnership highlights the importance of equipping citizens with&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Nexus Delivers New AI Innovations with NVIDIA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11369/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:30:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11369/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is addressing the demands of AI-driven data traffic with its new innovations, including the Cisco N9100 Series Switches. These advancements offer high-performance, secure, and adaptable networking infrastructures essential for modern AI workloads. The common Nexus operating model simplifies operations and enhances visibility across diverse environments. Explore how these changes can empower organizations in their AI journeys. 🌐🤖⚡️ #Cisco #AI #DataCenter #Networking #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco AI Defense Integrates with NVIDIA AI Enterprise Software to Secure AI Applications Using NVIDIA NeMo Guardrails</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11370/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:30:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11370/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has announced a new integration of Cisco AI Defense with NVIDIA NeMo Guardrails to enhance security for generative AI applications. As businesses adopt advanced AI solutions, ensuring security and compliance becomes vital. The integration aims to provide comprehensive protection throughout the AI lifecycle. Guardrails act as safety mechanisms, monitoring AI behavior to prevent harmful outputs and maintain compliance. This development is crucial for organizations transitioning from AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking AI Performance: Splunk Observability for Cisco Secure AI Factory with NVIDIA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11371/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11371/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking AI performance is crucial for organizations. Cisco AI PODs provide a scalable infrastructure for AI initiatives, ensuring quick deployment and optimal operation. With Splunk Observability Cloud, teams gain essential visibility into performance and health, enabling faster troubleshooting and focus on business outcomes. Explore how these solutions enhance AI environments! 🌐🔍 #AI #Cisco #Splunk #TechInnovation #Observability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco drives AI networking innovation with NVIDIA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11372/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11372/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco and NVIDIA have announced major advancements in AI networking. They introduced new Nexus 9100 switches designed for AI data centers and the general availability of Nexus Hyperfabric AI, which simplifies complex AI cluster deployment. These milestones reflect their ongoing partnership, enhancing flexibility for enterprises in AI data center investments. #Cisco #NVIDIA #AINetworking #DataCenters #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From AI Pilots to Production: Building Infrastructure That Makes AI Real</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11373/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:30:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11373/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is enhancing its Secure AI Factory in collaboration with NVIDIA, focusing on robust infrastructure for AI. With Isovalent validated for Kubernetes on Cisco AI PODs, enterprises can expect improved connectivity and policy enforcement for AI workflows. NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s latest GPUs expand server options, supporting training and inferencing use cases. The integration of tools like NVIDIA Run:ai and Nutanix NKP/NUS further strengthens this ecosystem. #AI #Cisco #NVIDIA #Kubernetes #Infrastructure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading the Next Era of Intelligent Connectivity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11374/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:29:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11374/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco is pioneering the future of intelligent connectivity with AI-native wireless networks. These networks are evolving beyond traditional data channels to become intelligent systems that can sense, reason, and act in real-time. 📈 As the demand for AI applications grows, telecom operators face challenges like increased uplink traffic and the need for low latency. 🔍 Cisco&amp;rsquo;s solution includes a two-pronged approach: integrating AI into wireless networks and utilizing wireless capabilities&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Network as the Foundation for Unlocking Value in the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11356/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 16:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11356/</guid>
      <description>📡 In the AI era, a strong network foundation is crucial for unlocking new insights and automating operations. Cisco emphasizes that routing, switching, and wireless technologies are key to connecting users to AI applications. 🤝 As customers pursue AI, they require reliable guidance to build secure and scalable networks. Cisco partners play a vital role, receiving training and tools to excel in AI-ready networking discussions. 🚀 The goal is to empower partners to enhance their skills and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partner Study Shows Greater Urgency to Realize AI’s Value, Emerging Opportunities with Agentic and Edge AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11339/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11339/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco&amp;rsquo;s 2025 partner survey highlights the urgent demand for AI value among customers. Key findings show: 📈 42% of partners predict over 75% of their revenue will come from AI in the next 4 years. 🔍 Customers expect AI to enhance efficiency, improve experiences, and provide value. 🛠️ Challenges remain in IT infrastructure, data governance, and talent. Explore how partners can leverage Cisco&amp;rsquo;s AI training for growth. #AI #Cisco #Technology #PartnerSurvey #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefine Security and Speed for High-Performance AI-Ready Data Centers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11357/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 12:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11357/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has introduced the Secure Firewall 6100 Series, setting a new standard for high-performance firewalls. This series addresses the needs of modern AI-driven data centers and telecom infrastructures, overcoming the limitations of traditional firewalls. With Layer 4 firewalling at up to 800 Gbps and IPS performance at 400 Gbps, it promises exceptional speed and modular scalability. Learn more about this innovative solution! #Cisco #Cybersecurity #DataCenters #AI #Firewall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Bonds Beyond Business: How Human Connection Defines Cisco Culture</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11334/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 12:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11334/</guid>
      <description>Cole A. shares his experience in India, attending a teammate&amp;rsquo;s wedding, highlighting Cisco&amp;rsquo;s people-first culture. He reflects on the importance of human connections in achieving success, emphasizing that behind every project are dedicated individuals. His trip enriched his understanding of different cultures and reinforced his philosophy: people come first. 🤝🌍💼 #CiscoCulture #HumanConnection #PeopleFirst #Diversity #Teamwork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Answering the AI Data Center Bottleneck with Efficiency and Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11330/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 08:23:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11330/</guid>
      <description>AI data centers face significant challenges as workloads grow. Current infrastructure struggles with interconnectivity, energy demands, and performance. Innovations and policies, like the EU&amp;rsquo;s Digital Networks Act, are being explored to enhance efficiency and scalability. This aims to create a secure and high-performance digital environment. Stay updated on these developments! 🌐⚡️ #AIDevelopment #DataCenters #EnergyEfficiency #TechInnovation #PublicPolicy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Striving for Sustainability: Meet Ajay</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11319/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:05:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11319/</guid>
      <description>Meet Ajay Ranjith Vempati, Circular Design Lead at Cisco. 🌱 He is dedicated to integrating circular design into Cisco’s products. Ajay’s journey began on his ancestral farm in India, where he learned the importance of sustainability. Cisco aims to apply Circular Design Principles to all new products and packaging by fiscal 2025. Follow Ajay’s work as he contributes to a more sustainable future! ♻️ #Sustainability #CircularDesign #Cisco #EcoFriendly #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Customer Achievement Awards: APJC 2025 Finalists</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11310/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:38:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11310/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Cisco! The inaugural Cisco Customer Achievement Awards for the APJC region have been launched to honor organizations driving innovation and digital transformation. These awards expand on the previous CX Customer Hero Awards. Congratulations to the finalists in the AI Infrastructure Innovation Award and CX AI Trailblazer Award categories! 🎉 Stay tuned for the awards ceremony at Cisco Live Melbourne on November 10, 2025. #CiscoAwards #DigitalTransformation #Innovation #APJC&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Perimeter to SOC: How Integrating Cisco Firewalls with Splunk Delivers End-to-End Threat Visibility and Compliance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11290/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11290/</guid>
      <description>Organizations face increasing cyber threats and compliance demands. Traditional perimeter defenses are inadequate against modern attacks. 🔒 Integrating Cisco Firewalls with Splunk enhances security operations center (SOC) visibility, enabling better threat detection and compliance readiness. This integration helps manage the vast amounts of log data generated daily, reducing noise and improving alert prioritization. 📊 By connecting telemetry and threat analytics, teams can gain actionable&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSE That Thinks in Identity and Adapts Access</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11248/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11248/</guid>
      <description>Cisco Secure Access is redefining security by prioritizing identity in a dynamic environment. 🌐 Traditional security methods focused on IP addresses are outdated. Cisco emphasizes that identity is now the new perimeter. Their approach adapts access decisions based on real-time identity data and behavior, enhancing security. 🔒 Static views of identity can leave organizations vulnerable. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s integration with Identity Intelligence allows for dynamic policies, ensuring continuous risk&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One night changed everything: Why I sleep out for Covenant House</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11227/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11227/</guid>
      <description>I participated in my sixth Sleep Out for Covenant House, an event raising funds for homeless youth. 🌙 Each year, I learn more about the challenges faced by the 4.2 million young people experiencing homelessness. My first Sleep Out opened my eyes to the urgency of their needs. 🚶‍♂️💧 Join me in supporting this cause and raising awareness. #CovenantHouse #EndYouthHomelessness #SleepOut #SupportYouth #Community</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieve Digital Resilience Through AI-Powered Observability and Assurance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11267/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:54:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11267/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s complex digital landscape, organizations face challenges in network performance and resilience. 🚀 The Cisco 2025 Networking Research reveals that 77% of IT leaders experienced major outages in the past two years, impacting revenue and productivity. To combat this, integrated, AI-powered observability and assurance are essential. Observability provides insights on system health, while assurance ensures consistent performance and SLA compliance. Together, they enhance digital&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing the AI agent supply chain with Cisco’s open-source MCP Scanner</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11206/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11206/</guid>
      <description>🚀 As enterprises adopt AI agents, reliance on external tools grows. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Model Context Protocol (MCP) simplifies access to these tools but also introduces new security risks. 🔍 To address this, Cisco has launched MCP Scanner, an open-source tool aimed at securing the AI agent supply chain. This tool is part of Cisco AI Defense, which focuses on enhancing security across AI systems. 🔒 With MCP&amp;rsquo;s growing popularity, it&amp;rsquo;s essential for companies to be aware of potential vulnerabilities,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Black Belt Academy: AI Validated Perfect Pitch</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11192/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:02:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11192/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco Black Belt Academy is enhancing partner enablement through AI-validated assessments. The focus is on performance-based evaluations, like Perfect Pitch submissions, where AI measures competence and confidence. This innovation reduces validation time significantly, enabling quicker success. Last year, the Academy saw a 75% increase in training submissions and over 236,000 certifications, thanks to scalable AI solutions. 🌍 AI also supports multilingual assessments, breaking down barriers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Architectural Convergence of Hybrid Mesh Firewall and Universal Zero Trust</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11193/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11193/</guid>
      <description>🌐 The evolution of campus networks has led to increased vulnerabilities. Cisco addresses this with the Hybrid Mesh Firewall and Universal Zero Trust Access. 🔒 These solutions embed security into the network, reducing attack surfaces and protecting against advanced threats. Key features include: - Baseline controls for foundational protections - Access controls for microsegmentation - Business-aligned controls for operational needs Explore how these advancements enhance security in complex&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Cisco Segmentation Report Sheds Light on Evolving Technology</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11188/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11188/</guid>
      <description>📊 The 2025 Cisco Segmentation Report reveals key insights on the state of segmentation in organizations. While segmentation is crucial for security, few organizations have fully implemented both macro- and micro-segmentation strategies. With 84% of businesses experiencing breaches in the past year, enhancing these practices is essential. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s global survey of 1,000 respondents highlights the gap between the priority placed on segmentation and its execution. Understanding these dynamics can&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco’s circular design goal: Our journey to 100%</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11174/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 22:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11174/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has reached a significant milestone by incorporating Circular Design Principles into 100% of new products and packaging by the end of the 2025 fiscal year. This achievement, established in 2019, highlights years of collaboration and innovation. Cisco has also received the 2025 Reuters Global Sustainability Award for Circularity. 🌍 With a framework of 25 Circular Design Principles and extensive training for over 7,000 employees, Cisco is committed to minimizing waste and enhancing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Standard for Accurate Power Measurement in AI Data Centers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11144/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11144/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Power measurement is crucial for smart infrastructure decisions in AI data centers. Cisco researchers have developed a new methodology that increases measurement accuracy to +/- 2%, a significant improvement over traditional methods. This advancement addresses common inaccuracies that can lead to costly errors in energy consumption, which currently reaches $350 million annually. Find out more about this breakthrough in their three-part white paper series. 🔋💡 #PowerMeasurement #AIEnergy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future-Proof Your Wi-Fi Network with These Three AI-Driven Innovations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11145/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11145/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Wi-Fi networks are essential for modern businesses, especially in high-density areas like campuses and hospitals. Cisco introduces AI-driven innovations to enhance network management: 1️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;AI Radio Resource Management (AI-RRM)&lt;/strong&gt; optimizes RF in real time. 2️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Intelligent Packet Capture&lt;/strong&gt; automates troubleshooting. 3️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Adaptive Policy&lt;/strong&gt; streamlines network access control. These solutions help IT teams improve performance and user experience. #WiFi #Cisco #AI #NetworkManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powering Your AI-Ready Campus of the Future: Join us at EDUCAUSE 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11140/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11140/</guid>
      <description>Join Cisco at EDUCAUSE 2025 from October 28-31 in Nashville! Discover how Cisco’s AI-ready solutions empower higher education institutions to harness AI securely. Learn about intelligent assistants and operational insights designed to enhance productivity and campus experiences. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss our lunch and learn session featuring insights from leading universities. #EDUCAUSE2025 #AI #HigherEd #CiscoInnovation #CampusTransformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic AI Security: How Cisco AI Defense Protects Against New Threats</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11129/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 22:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11129/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The evolution of AI is remarkable, but it brings new security challenges. Cisco AI Defense addresses the risks by offering a multi-layered approach to protect businesses. With 84% of companies facing AI-related security incidents last year, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to adapt to this dynamic threat landscape. Their framework includes threat intelligence operations, unified data correlation, and a release platform for timely protections. #AISecurity #CiscoAI #Cybersecurity #TechInnovation #BusinessSafety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showcasing Innovation and Commitment at NetAcad’s European Partner Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11116/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 16:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11116/</guid>
      <description>🌍 At the recent Cisco NetAcad European Partner Conference in Thessaloniki, leaders gathered to discuss the future of workforce training. Cisco aims to equip 1.5 million Europeans with essential digital skills by 2030, focusing on AI readiness. With 3,841 academies supporting 5.1 million students, the commitment to education is strong. AI is reshaping job roles, with 78% of tech positions now needing AI skills. #CiscoNetAcad #AIFuture #DigitalSkills #WorkforceDevelopment #EducationInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleash(ed) AI: The Rise of Cognitive Security Operations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11117/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 15:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11117/</guid>
      <description>Cognitive Security is transforming cyber defense, moving organizations from reactive to proactive measures. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s experts discuss the increasing sophistication of AI-driven threats and the need for innovative solutions. They emphasize that traditional security tools are no longer enough to protect against these evolving risks. Learn more about how Cisco is shaping the future of cybersecurity. 🔐💻 #CyberSecurity #CognitiveSecurity #AI #Cisco #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Investments, Stronger Grids: Elevating Rural Electric Cooperative Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11103/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11103/</guid>
      <description>Rural electric cooperatives are essential to America&amp;rsquo;s power grid, providing energy to millions. 🌍 With the rise of cyber threats, a federal investment of $20 million is aimed at enhancing their security through advanced technologies. These funds will help co-ops modernize operations and improve cyber resilience. ⚡️ Key focus areas include enhanced monitoring, network control, and secure remote access. This initiative allows cooperatives the flexibility to choose solutions that fit their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Steps to Building Resilient Industrial Networks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11104/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11104/</guid>
      <description>🔐 Securing industrial networks is crucial as they face increasing cyber threats. Cisco outlines a 5-step framework to enhance cybersecurity practices. 1️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Visibility&lt;/strong&gt;: Gain a real-time view of all connected OT assets to identify vulnerabilities and risks effectively. 2️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Segmentation&lt;/strong&gt;: Divide the network into smaller, secure zones to limit threat movement. Explore more about building resilient industrial networks in the full article! #Cybersecurity #IndustrialIoT #NetworkSecurity #Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Secure Firewall 1220: Snort3 – Uncompromised Performance in Rigorous Testing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11100/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11100/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco Secure Firewall 1220 has proven its capabilities with 100% effectiveness against exploits and evasions, achieving malware protection of up to 99.5%. Rigorous testing, adhering to NetSecOPEN standards, confirms its exceptional performance in complex traffic scenarios and application-specific conditions. This evaluation highlights its ability to proactively defend against sophisticated cyber threats while maintaining necessary speed for businesses. #CyberSecurity #Cisco #Firewall1220&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Machine Speed Needs Machine Trust</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11063/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11063/</guid>
      <description>AI is changing IT operations by enabling faster problem resolution with new paradigms like AgenticOps. 🌐 However, as AI acts quicker than humans can verify, ensuring trust in these decisions is crucial. Assurance mechanisms must validate AI actions in real time to prevent unintended consequences. ⚙️ Learn more about balancing speed and trust in AI systems in our latest e-book. 📘 #MachineTrust #AI #ITOperations #Assurance #Automation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating 10 Years of Lifecycle Advantage: A Decade of Innovation and Success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11064/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 14:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11064/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Celebrating 10 years of Cisco Lifecycle Advantage! This milestone highlights a decade of innovation in digital customer experiences. What started as a pilot has evolved into a global program used by over 7,000 partners, empowering them to enhance customer engagement through automated digital journeys. As the landscape shifts, the focus remains on supporting partners in a digital-first world. #Cisco #LifecycleAdvantage #DigitalTransformation #CustomerEngagement #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco IT’s network observability transformation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11065/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11065/</guid>
      <description>Cisco IT has transformed its network observability by unifying telemetry data across its extensive environment. This shift allows for automation to manage 99.998% of alerts, resulting in zero major incidents. Previously, reliance on outsourced monitoring led to data overload and limited insights. By bringing operations in-house, Cisco gained control to enhance visibility and improve user experience. #NetworkObservability #DataManagement #CiscoIT #Automation #TechTransformation 🌐🔍📊</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering the Course of Wireless Transformation with Cisco and USGA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11026/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11026/</guid>
      <description>Cisco played a crucial role in powering the 125th U.S. Open with advanced technology. They deployed 550 access points and used Wi-Fi 7 to ensure seamless connectivity for over 225,000 attendees. This infrastructure supported various digital interactions, from ticketing to social media sharing, enhancing the fan experience. The setup faced challenges of high demand and an outdoor environment, yet Cisco successfully managed the complexities to deliver reliable connectivity. #USOpen #Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find Yourself in the Future: How Generative AI is Reshaping Entry-Level Cybersecurity Job Roles</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10996/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10996/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This Cybersecurity Awareness Month, Cisco Networking Academy highlights the role of AI in transforming entry-level cybersecurity jobs. Experts Giuseppe Cinque and Matt Berndt discuss how Generative AI is enhancing tasks like report writing and data analysis, while Agentic AI is revolutionizing threat detection and response. For those pursuing a career in cybersecurity, check out the curated job board by Indeed and Cisco for relevant opportunities. #Cybersecurity #AI #JobOpportunities&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Betting on the Next Decade: Why Cisco’s Innovation Strategy Should Shape Your Partner Roadmap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10997/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10997/</guid>
      <description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s innovation strategy is setting the stage for the next decade. 🤖🌐 Their approach focuses on building for future markets, not just optimizing existing products. The Outshift by Cisco initiative explores emerging technologies like agentic AI and quantum-safe networking. Partners who engage early can gain a competitive edge in this evolving landscape. #Cisco #Innovation #TechTrends #Partnerships #FutureReady</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Igniting our future workforce: Shaping the future in Europe through Cisco Networking Academy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10985/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10985/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The Cisco Networking Academy Partner Conference in Thessaloniki recently gathered educators, government officials, and industry partners to celebrate the past year’s achievements and discuss future goals. 🤝 This event highlighted the importance of collaboration in shaping the future workforce in Europe. The spirit of community and support was evident, emphasizing the shared commitment to education and skill development. #CiscoNetworkingAcademy #FutureWorkforce #Collaboration #Education&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing a New Framework for Securing AI-Generated Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10986/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10986/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Software teams are increasingly using AI coding agents to enhance productivity, but security is lagging behind. Many AI-generated codes lack essential protections, which leads to vulnerabilities. To address this, Cisco has introduced Project CodeGuard, an open-source framework aimed at securing AI-generated code. Project CodeGuard integrates secure defaults into coding workflows, offering community-driven rules, translators for popular AI agents, and automatic security validators. This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Guest WiFi into a Premier Marketing Channel with Cisco and Cloud4Wi</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10954/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10954/</guid>
      <description>Discover how Boisset Collection transformed their guest WiFi into a powerful marketing tool with Cisco and Cloud4Wi. 📧 By leveraging their network, they captured 3,000 new emails and achieved a 7% conversion rate, enhancing guest relationships. This innovative approach showcases the potential of using existing resources for business growth. #Marketing #GuestExperience #WiFi #Innovation #Cisco</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Recognized as a Leader in the IDC MarketScape for Enterprise WLAN</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10955/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:56:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10955/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Cisco has been recognized as a Leader in the IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Enterprise Wireless LAN 2025. This acknowledgment highlights the trust customers have in Cisco and underscores its commitment to innovation in connectivity. Such recognition reflects Cisco&amp;rsquo;s efforts to support organizations in enhancing their operations. #Cisco #WirelessLAN #Innovation #Leadership #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco UCS C880A M8: HGX B300 &#43; Intel Xeon 6 — The New Vanguard of AI Infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10935/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10935/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has launched the UCS C880A M8 Rack Server, featuring NVIDIA HGX B300 GPUs and Intel Xeon 6th-Gen CPUs. This new server is designed for AI performance and scalability, making it ideal for large language model inference and enterprise AI tasks. 🔍 The HGX B300 offers significant enhancements, delivering up to 11x higher throughput and 4x faster training speeds for large-scale AI models. Its architecture reduces bottlenecks, facilitating efficient scaling. 💡 The Intel Xeon 6th-Gen CPUs&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Run Fast, Secure Apps at the Edge with Cisco Smart Switches</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10936/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10936/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco Smart Switches are transforming network management by integrating edge compute directly into the switch. This innovation allows applications to run locally, enhancing security and troubleshooting. 🔒 With built-in firewall capabilities, these switches provide robust protection for users and devices, ensuring seamless connectivity across diverse environments. 🌐 This marks a significant shift in how networks operate, bringing intelligence closer to the edge. #Cisco #SmartSwitches&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think Like an Adversary: How Cisco Safely Finds the Flaws Attackers *Will* Exploit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10937/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10937/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Your security systems need a workout! Cisco’s Assessment and Penetration Testing (APT) team helps organizations identify weaknesses by simulating real-world attacks safely. 🛡️ This proactive approach allows businesses to fix vulnerabilities before they can be exploited. October is Cybersecurity Awareness Month, making it a perfect time to reassess your defenses. 📚 Interested in gaining offensive skills? Check out Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Certificate in Ethical Hacking program! #Cybersecurity #Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Threat Themes: Defending Against Lateral Movement (Part 1)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10931/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10931/</guid>
      <description>Cybersecurity is a continuous battle as defenders enhance their strategies against evolving threats. Lateral movement is identified as a key tactic in 70% of cyber breaches, highlighting a critical area for improvement. Organizations are encouraged to adopt strong, prescriptive controls to combat this risk effectively. Investing in network and application segmentation can significantly enhance security without disrupting operations. #CyberSecurity #LateralMovement #DataProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>20 years of Cisco Crisis Response: Reflecting on resilience from Hurricane Katrina to Helene</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10923/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 07:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10923/</guid>
      <description>🌍 As we celebrate 20 years of Cisco Crisis Response (CCR), we reflect on resilience from Hurricane Katrina to Hurricane Helene. In 2005, CCR began by restoring communications in disaster-struck areas. Over the years, it has evolved to meet the growing needs of communities affected by crises. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s partnership with BBC StoryWorks highlights CCR&amp;rsquo;s vital role in reconnecting people and rebuilding hope. 👉 Watch the video to learn more about CCR’s impactful work! #CiscoCrisisResponse #Resilience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco research warns EU infrastructure debt could be the emerging drag on AI value</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10922/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 07:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10922/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest AI Readiness Index reveals that only 7% of EU organizations are fully prepared to harness AI effectively. The report highlights a concerning trend: rising AI workloads, insufficient GPU capacity, and challenges in data centralization. This accumulation of &amp;ldquo;AI infrastructure debt&amp;rdquo; could hinder future value. With 45% of EU respondents anticipating workload increases, operational readiness is critical. Organizations that proactively invest in their infrastructure are gaining a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Views from an Insider on the CCNP Automation Track: DCNAUTO 2.0 Edition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10912/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10912/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The final installment of the blog series on the CCNP Automation Track, focusing on the new DCNAUTO 2.0 specialization, is now available! This update highlights significant changes in exam topics aimed at assisting learners. The previous DCAUTO exam faced challenges with broad technology coverage and team separation. The DCNAUTO 2.0 aims to streamline these complexities and include current technologies like Kubernetes and containers. #CCNP #Cisco #DCNAUTO #Automation #Networking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Future, Powered by AI: Cisco’s Game-Changing Partner Experience Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10899/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 17:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10899/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has launched its AI-powered Partner Experience Platform (PXP), set to transform the partner journey. PXP serves as the &amp;ldquo;front door&amp;rdquo; to the Cisco 360 Partner Program, providing real-time support and insights for partners. With features designed from partner feedback, PXP aims to empower growth and informed decision-making in the AI era. Discover the future with Cisco! 🌐💡 #Cisco #AI #PartnerExperience #Innovation #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra Ethernet for Scalable AI Network Deployment</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10889/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10889/</guid>
      <description>Cisco, alongside the Ultra Ethernet Consortium (UEC), is tackling networking challenges in AI and HPC data centers. Their solutions include link layer retry, credit-based flow control, and congestion signaling to enhance reliability and performance. The Cisco Nexus 9000 Series Switches enable organizations to build scalable infrastructures for the future of AI. 🌐🔗 #Cisco #UltraEthernet #AI #DataCenters #NetworkingSolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco &amp; NetApp: Powering Enterprise Data Centers with AI Networking and Storage</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10890/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 13:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10890/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Cisco and NetApp are leading the way in AI transformation for enterprises. Their partnership offers a unified, scalable infrastructure solution that meets the growing demands of AI. 🔍 At the heart of this collaboration is NetApp AFX, a disaggregated storage architecture designed for high-performance data management. 💻 Together with Cisco’s AI Networking, they enable businesses to build AI-ready data centers that enhance innovation and simplify operations. #Cisco #NetApp #AI #DataCenters&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Two Years Ago, I Took a Chance — Now I’m at Cisco Living the Dream</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10886/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10886/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Two years ago, Jordan B. took a leap from the FinTech industry to Cisco, inspired by its people-first culture. He reflects on his journey of growth and mentorship that led him to a fulfilling role as an Inside Account Executive. Jordan emphasizes the importance of connections and the value of a supportive network. #Cisco #CareerJourney #Mentorship #Growth #PeopleFirst</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco research warns EU infrastructure debt could be the emerging drag on AI value</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10922/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 07:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10922/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest AI Readiness Index reveals that only 7% of EU organizations are fully prepared to harness AI effectively. The report highlights a concerning trend: rising AI workloads, insufficient GPU capacity, and challenges in data centralization. This accumulation of &amp;ldquo;AI infrastructure debt&amp;rdquo; could hinder future value. With 45% of EU respondents anticipating workload increases, operational readiness is critical. Organizations that proactively invest in their infrastructure are gaining a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Joins Forces with OCP in the Ethernet for Scale-Up Networking (ESUN) Collaboration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10880/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 23:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10880/</guid>
      <description>Cisco has joined the Open Compute Project (OCP) as a founding member of the Ethernet for Scale-Up Networking (ESUN) collaboration. This initiative aims to advance Ethernet technology to support AI workloads in modern data centers. The collaboration focuses on open standards and best practices for Ethernet switching, specifically for high-bandwidth scale-up networking. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s new 51.2T router is designed to enhance connectivity across data centers for AI applications. By participating in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlock GPU Clouds with Cisco AI PODs and Rafay</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10876/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 19:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10876/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco AI PODs and Rafay are transforming AI infrastructure! These solutions provide secure, self-service GPU cloud platforms that streamline the deployment of AI technologies. Cisco AI PODs offer a solid foundation with integrated compute, storage, and networking. Rafay enhances this by turning hardware into a governed, multi-tenant GPU Platform as a Service (PaaS), enabling organizations to leverage AI faster while maintaining control. Discover how this partnership addresses the challenges&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Computing Future Is at the Edge: Are You Ready for AI’s New Frontier?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10583/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:00:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10583/</guid>
      <description>The article highlights the crucial role of edge infrastructure in the current AI landscape. Edge computing brings processing power closer to data sources, enhancing customer experiences and operational efficiency. As AI workloads increase, organizations need to adapt their edge systems to meet these demands. According to IDC, 53% of organizations plan to upgrade their edge compute for AI by 2025. The time to invest in robust edge infrastructure is now. 🌐💻 #EdgeComputing #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Rural Healthcare: How Cisco and HCF Drive Digital Transformation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10577/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10577/</guid>
      <description>🚑 Empowering rural healthcare is crucial for better patient outcomes. The Rural Healthcare Connect Fund (HCF) aids providers in modernizing their networks and enhancing care through affordable access to high-speed broadband. 🌐 Cisco supports this initiative with solutions like Cisco Meraki for simplified operations and advanced security features to protect patient data. Discover how connectivity transforms rural healthcare! #RuralHealthcare #DigitalTransformation #Cisco #PatientCare&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SVS Engineers: Who are the people that test-drive your network?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10575/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 09:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10575/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Ever wondered who ensures your network runs smoothly? Meet Cisco Solution Validation Services (SVS) engineers. They design tailored test blueprints and validate complex network deployments to deliver reliable solutions. By engaging with customers and assessing unique needs, they create strategies to mitigate risks. With a focus on continuous improvement, SVS engineers push the limits of technology to ensure seamless connections. #Cisco #NetworkValidation #TechExperts #FutureProof&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the ‘Let’s Break It Down’ Series for Network Newbies</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10565/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 21:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10565/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Excited to share insights from Yasmeen Seddeek&amp;rsquo;s article on her new video series, “Let’s Break It Down.” This series is designed for those new to networking, especially for CCST exam candidates. Yasmeen emphasizes the importance of understanding complex concepts through clear content. In the first episode, she explains key topics for the CCST Networking exam, including various network hardware devices. What seems simple often has layers of complexity. Check out her series for a clearer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building the workforce of tomorrow: How collaboration and continuous learning power the AI revolution in APJC</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10539/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10539/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-changing economy, the &amp;ldquo;future of work&amp;rdquo; is already here. 🌍 Lynn Bloomer from Cisco emphasizes that innovation is reshaping industries and job roles, requiring new skills. Collaboration among governments, educators, and businesses is essential for workforce development. 🤝 The 2025 AI Workforce Consortium report highlights that 78% of ICT roles now need AI skills, with significant changes expected in core skills by 2030. 📊 Cisco aims to train 25 million people globally by 2032&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charting the Course: Resilience and Innovation at AFCEA TechNet Indo Pacific 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10540/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 14:14:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10540/</guid>
      <description>Join Cisco at AFCEA TechNet Indo Pacific 2025 from October 28-30 in Hawai’i! 🌺 This year&amp;rsquo;s theme, &amp;ldquo;Sword &amp;amp; Shield: Ensuring a Secure, Free, and Prosperous Indo-Pacific,&amp;rdquo; focuses on overcoming challenges in mission connectivity and security. Visit Booth #1222 for demos on digital resiliency and AI-driven NetOps. Discover how Cisco’s solutions help maintain operations in tough environments. 💻✨ #AFCEA2025 #Cisco #Cybersecurity #Innovation #TechEvent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Direct Line to Cisco Automation: Ask Ed Novak About Workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10541/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 13:25:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10541/</guid>
      <description>📅 Join us on October 8 for a live Q&amp;amp;A with Ed Novak, a Cisco Technical Marketing Engineer! This interactive session will focus on Cisco Workflows, allowing you to ask questions and explore real-world use cases. Prepare your queries and gain insights to enhance your network operations. 🕘 Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to engage directly with an expert! #Cisco #Automation #Workflows #Networking #LiveQandA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The third dimension of AI networking has arrived</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10529/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 12:50:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10529/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has introduced the Cisco 8223, powered by Cisco Silicon One P200, to meet the demands of the evolving AI landscape. AI workloads are expanding rapidly, leading data centers to migrate to remote locations for power access. This move requires high-bandwidth networks to connect large AI clusters effectively. The new &amp;ldquo;scale-across&amp;rdquo; approach enables AI workloads to function seamlessly across multiple data centers, ensuring reliability and security. 🌐🔗 #Cisco8223 #AINetworking&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Benchmark for Distributed AI Networking</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10530/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 12:50:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10530/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco introduces the Cisco 8223, a new fixed router designed for the growing needs of distributed AI networking. This router supports a &amp;ldquo;scale-across&amp;rdquo; approach, allowing AI workloads to extend across multiple data centers. With 51.2 Tbps capacity, it&amp;rsquo;s optimized for high performance and energy efficiency. Key features include deep-buffer architecture and the Cisco Silicon One P200 chip, enabling seamless connectivity for AI applications. #Cisco8223 #AINetworking #DataCenter #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Silicon One P200 Powers the First 51.2T Scale-Across Routing Systems</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10531/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 12:50:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10531/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has launched the Cisco 8223, powered by Silicon One P200, achieving a groundbreaking 51.2 Tbps capacity. This innovation sets a new standard for &amp;ldquo;scale-across&amp;rdquo; routing systems, essential for distributing AI workloads geographically. 🌍 With power constraints impacting AI scaling, this system combines routing and switching for enhanced efficiency and security, allowing hyperscalers to build expansive AI environments. 🔗 Explore how Cisco is addressing the challenges of modern networks&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Duo MSP: Your Trusted Identity and Access Management is Available Through Distribution</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10494/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:17:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10494/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Managed Service Providers! Cisco Duo for MSPs is now available through the Secure MSP Center Managed Services Licensing Program (MSLA). This allows MSPs to deliver cloud-based security and identity solutions easily via their Cisco Authorized Distributor. Key benefits include: - A simplified buying experience with centralized ordering - Access to a comprehensive portfolio of Cisco security products - Enhanced operational efficiency with a unified management console Learn&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionizing Farming: Planet Farms and Cisco Industrial Networks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10486/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 13:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10486/</guid>
      <description>🌱 Planet Farms is transforming agriculture with its innovative vertical farming model. By utilizing Cisco URWB technology, they achieve reliable, ultra-low latency connectivity for robots and automated guided vehicles (AGVs). This approach allows for farming to be demand-led rather than supply-led, breaking free from traditional limitations like geography and seasonal cycles. Discover how technology is reshaping the future of farming! 🌾🤖 #VerticalFarming #SustainableAgriculture #IoT&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Tech Career That Makes Room for Life — and a Book</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10487/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 12:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10487/</guid>
      <description>Discover how Ana N., a Marketing Networking Manager at Cisco, found the balance between her career and personal life. After 20 years in public relations, she turned her dream of writing a book into reality with Cisco&amp;rsquo;s supportive culture. The flexibility allowed her to excel at work while being a mother and a wife. Her journey shows how a positive work environment can help achieve personal goals. 📚💼✨ #Cisco #CareerGrowth #WorkLifeBalance #AuthorJourney #SupportiveCulture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining a Standard Taxonomy for Segmentation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10495/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10495/</guid>
      <description>Segmentation is essential for enhancing cybersecurity by preventing threats from spreading across networks. As segmentation solutions multiply, organizations face challenges in selecting the right approach. A new blog series will address these topics, offering insights into use cases, challenges, and strategies for effective implementation. Stay tuned for valuable information to strengthen your security posture and align with business goals. 🔒💻 #Cybersecurity #Segmentation #ZeroTrust&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future-Ready WAN: New Innovations in Cisco SD-WAN</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10451/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10451/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has launched new innovations in its SD-WAN solutions, aimed at simplifying operations and enhancing security. This update introduces features that help IT teams manage network complexity, improve cloud connectivity, and drive innovation. Key enhancements include a global search capability for quick access to network objects and a guided task flow for easy setup. The new tools aim to support faster deployments and provide insights for proactive network management. #Cisco #SDWAN&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust and Talent: The Human Foundations for AI Adoption</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10441/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 12:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10441/</guid>
      <description>Building trust and developing skills are essential for the successful adoption of AI. 🤝 Recent discussions in Brussels highlight that AI&amp;rsquo;s true potential relies on our collective efforts. Without trust, adoption may stall, and without the necessary skills, opportunities could be limited. As AI continues to evolve, 78% of ICT roles now require AI skills, indicating a shift in job requirements. 📈 #AIAdoption #TrustInTech #SkillsDevelopment #Collaboration #FutureOfWork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racing Against Threats: How Cisco Security Powers McLaren’s F1 Prowess</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10442/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10442/</guid>
      <description>🚀 McLaren&amp;rsquo;s success in the 2025 F1 season is backed by a strong partnership with Cisco. Since 2021, Cisco has provided essential cybersecurity and networking solutions, ensuring McLaren’s data remains secure and operations efficient. The collaboration emphasizes trust and innovation, crucial for facing modern security challenges. Together, they enhance performance on and off the track. 🏎️🔐 #F1 #Cybersecurity #McLaren #Cisco #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Awareness Month: Become a Champion of Digital Resilience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10355/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 15:00:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10355/</guid>
      <description>🌐 October marks Cybersecurity Awareness Month! This year, Cisco is offering training and certification giveaways to help you enhance your skills in cybersecurity. You can enter the sweepstakes for a chance to win valuable e-learning bundles. 🎓 Additionally, enjoy a 25% discount on cybersecurity learning products from October 13–20, 2025. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to boost your professional journey! 🚀 #CybersecurityAwareness #Cisco #DigitalResilience #CybersecurityTraining #CareerGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Digital Backbone: How States Can Modernize Rural Healthcare with RHTP Funding</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10356/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:43:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10356/</guid>
      <description>🌐 The Rural Health Transformation Program (RHTP) offers $50 billion in federal funding over five years for states to modernize rural healthcare. 🏥 This initiative emphasizes a hub and spoke model, allowing central hospitals to support smaller facilities, enhancing care coordination and access to specialists. 🔌 Key investments in digital infrastructure, including broadband and telehealth platforms, are essential for improving healthcare delivery in rural areas. ⏰ States are encouraged to apply&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust: The Foundation of Industrial Cyber Defense</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10357/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10357/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Industrial cybersecurity is crucial as threats evolve. A zero trust architecture is recommended for protecting operational technology (OT) in sectors like energy and manufacturing. CISA emphasizes the need for micro-segmentation and accurate asset inventory to enhance security. Zero trust can reduce attack surfaces and limit lateral movement, which is vital for maintaining operations. Cisco offers solutions to implement zero trust at scale without disrupting production. #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exceeding Expectations: How Partner Managed Services and the Cisco 360 Partner Program Accelerate Revenue Growth</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10333/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:32:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10333/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Cisco 360 Partner Program emphasizes managed services as a key growth driver for partners. With evolving customer demands, simplicity and agility in technology adoption are crucial. 📊 A recent Canalys survey shows that 49% of B2B IT partners view managed services as their top revenue opportunity, surpassing hardware sales. 💼 Cisco aims to empower partners to meet these expectations and enhance profitability through this integrated approach. #Cisco360 #ManagedServices #RevenueGrowth&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Craft your Next-Gen, Open, and AI-Ready Data Center with SONiC and Cisco 8000</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10321/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10321/</guid>
      <description>Transform your data center for the AI era with SONiC and Cisco 8000 Series switches. 🌐 Cisco supports open-source solutions, allowing organizations to choose the network operating system that meets their unique needs. This flexibility is crucial as AI/ML demands evolve. Disaggregated architectures enable independent scaling and resource control, promoting efficiency and adaptability. Explore how Cisco&amp;rsquo;s innovations can enhance your operations. 💻✨ #DataCenter #AI #Cisco #Networking #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Miss Out: Attend the 2025 OCP Global Summit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10322/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 15:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10322/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The 2025 OCP Global Summit is just around the corner! Cisco will showcase innovations in AI networking, security, and open networking. Key topics include AI infrastructure, P4 programmability, and SONiC, all aimed at supporting organizations in the AI era. Don’t miss this opportunity to see how Cisco is helping to shape the future of data centers. 🚀 #OCPSummit2025 #Cisco #AINetworking #DataCenter #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Bacon Cybersecurity: SharePoint Vulnerabilities and Vulnerabilities in General</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10312/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10312/</guid>
      <description>📢 Understanding SharePoint Vulnerabilities The article highlights vulnerabilities in Microsoft SharePoint and how they can be exploited by adversaries. Key factors include remotely accessible systems and weak endpoint protections. To mitigate these risks, patching is essential, though not always timely. Implementing remote access via VPN or zero trust access can enhance security. Stay informed and secure! 🔐 #Cybersecurity #SharePoint #Vulnerabilities #DataProtection #ZeroTrust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connected Intelligence: Building the workplace of today for the workforce of tomorrow​</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10313/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10313/</guid>
      <description>The article &amp;ldquo;Connected Intelligence: Building the workplace of today for the workforce of tomorrow&amp;rdquo; discusses the transformative impact of artificial intelligence on modern work environments. It highlights how collaboration is now defined by the integration of human and artificial intelligence. This evolution changes not just where we work, but how we connect and innovate together. To harness this potential, new models of collaboration are needed, linking people, AI, and even AI systems&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cisco IT streamlined network operations with Cisco Catalyst Center and Splunk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10310/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 11:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10310/</guid>
      <description>Cisco IT has effectively streamlined its network operations using the Catalyst Center and Splunk. By leveraging AI and automation, they achieved a 97% reduction in code vulnerabilities and cut software upgrade times by 59%. This transformation has improved job satisfaction for engineers and enhanced overall network management. With over 200,000 devices to manage, automation has been crucial in reducing manual tasks and minimizing human error. #Cisco #NetworkManagement #Automation #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Workloads to Factories: Rethinking the Data Center for AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10291/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 22:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10291/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Rethinking data centers is essential for AI. Cisco emphasizes transitioning from traditional workloads to AI &amp;ldquo;factories.&amp;rdquo; These factories require standardized, scalable units that ensure consistent performance across hybrid environments. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Secure AI Factory integrates compute, networking, and security for effective AI deployment. Learn more about the future of data centers! #DataCenter #AI #Cisco #Innovation #Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebexOne 2025: Unlocking the Power of Connected Intelligence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10260/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10260/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Today at WebexOne in San Diego, Cisco unveiled its vision for the future of work, emphasizing the importance of AI in the workplace. 🔑 Key challenges like infrastructure constraints, security threats, and data gaps are being addressed with innovative solutions. Webex is central to this strategy, enhancing communication and collaboration. 🤖 The concept of &amp;ldquo;Connected Intelligence&amp;rdquo; will redefine how we interact—blending human and AI communication seamlessly. #WebexOne #Cisco #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Your Virtualization Ready for the Future of AI and Modern Applications?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10261/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 15:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10261/</guid>
      <description>Is your virtualization equipped for future AI demands? 🖥️🤖 Modernizing infrastructure with Cisco and Red Hat can unify VMs and containers, addressing rising costs and operational complexity. Traditional virtualization struggles to meet the needs of modern applications, leading to inefficiencies. Explore how a fresh approach can enhance your IT environment and support innovation. #Virtualization #AI #Infrastructure #Cisco #RedHat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking AI Security: The Dynamic Context Firewall for MCP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10249/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10249/</guid>
      <description>🔒 As AI becomes integral to business workflows, securing interactions with external tools is essential. The Dynamic Context Firewall (DCF) is a proposed security layer for the Model Context Protocol (MCP), enhancing adaptive AI security. Unlike traditional firewalls, the DCF analyzes AI interactions in real-time, considering context and intent to ensure proper access control. This innovative approach aims to tackle risks such as unauthorized data access and consent fatigue. #AISecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How One Cisco Product Inspired Me to Break into Tech</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10250/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10250/</guid>
      <description>Adil S., a CX Product Management Specialist Intern at Cisco, shares his inspiring journey into tech. 🌟 His introduction to Cisco began at age 10 with a Linksys AE1000 wireless adapter, which opened the door to the digital world. This early experience fueled his passion for technology. As a first-generation college student, Adil reflects on how this internship feels like a full-circle moment in his career path. 💻 #Cisco #TechJourney #Internship #Inspiration #FirstGen</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project 525 expands Cisco CCIE certification opportunities in Africa</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10209/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 15:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10209/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news from Cisco! Project 525 has launched in sub-Saharan Africa to expand access to CCIE certification. This initiative aims to provide digital skills training in areas where such opportunities are limited. In partnership with NIL Learning, the program offers an innovative curriculum for IT professionals, helping to bridge the digital divide. Learn more about how Project 525 can change lives and communities! 🌍💻 #Cisco #CCIE #DigitalSkills #Project525 #TechForGood</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kistler Improves Traffic Safety and Extends Pavement Life with Cisco Industrial Switches</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10198/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:58:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10198/</guid>
      <description>🚛 Kistler Group’s KiTraffic Digital, utilizing Cisco industrial switches, enhances traffic safety by identifying overloaded trucks on highways. Authorities struggle with limited resources to weigh every truck, risking road safety and infrastructure. Overloaded vehicles significantly increase braking distances, endangering all road users and accelerating pavement damage. The automated weighing system by Thurgau Traffic and Lake Police effectively addresses this issue. #TrafficSafety&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lessons from an AI-Assisted Content Migration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10199/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:15:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10199/</guid>
      <description>🚀 After a comprehensive documentation migration project, I&amp;rsquo;ve gathered valuable lessons on using AI effectively in content engineering. AI can enhance efficiency, but it requires careful planning and oversight. My experience involved migrating 30,000 HTML files into a single DITA-based help portal. Expertise is essential; AI is a tool, not a replacement. #ContentMigration #AI #DITA #TechDocumentation #Efficiency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Experience the Power of Connection and AI at Cisco Connect Cancun</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10200/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Cisco Connect is back at the Moon Palace Hotel in Cancun! This event unites 3,000 attendees to explore the latest Cisco innovations and reconnect with peers. The focus is on the “One Cisco” strategy, emphasizing integration across networking, security, and services to create value for customers. AI takes center stage, with discussions on its impact on customer experience. Insights reveal that 93% of global respondents see agentic AI enhancing personalized services by 2028. #CiscoConnect #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Query to Action with MCP Servers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10165/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10165/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers transform queries into actions! MCP servers unify automation and observability in Cisco environments. An AI client routes natural-language queries to the correct tools across Catalyst Center clusters and Meraki organizations. Watch the demo by Gabi Zapodeanu to see real-time tool selection and execution, plus practical troubleshooting tips. Learn more about streamlining your workflow with MCP! #Cisco #Automation #AI #Networking #TechDemo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Protecting Innovation Matters</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10104/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10104/</guid>
      <description>Cisco has achieved a significant milestone by being granted its 25,000th U.S. patent, reflecting its long-standing commitment to innovation. This patent covers the new Hypershield technology, marking a step forward in AI-native security architecture. Protecting innovation is crucial for Cisco, as it fosters investment in research and development. Patents serve as recognition of originality and uniqueness, allowing Cisco to maintain a competitive edge and drive industry growth. This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reimagining the modern campus: A university’s leap into the future of learning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10105/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:44:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10105/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Howard University is leading the way in modern education by transforming its campus infrastructure. CIO Olga Osaghae emphasizes the shift towards a digital-first learning environment, focusing on more than just Wi-Fi upgrades. This initiative reflects a commitment to enhancing educational experiences for students. Learn more about this innovative partnership! 🌐📚 #HigherEducation #DigitalTransformation #HBCU #Innovation #LearningEnvironment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IDC Recognizes What We Know: Our Partners Drive Market Leadership</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10072/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10072/</guid>
      <description>Cisco has been named a Leader in the 2025 IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Enterprise Video Conferencing Systems! 🎉 This recognition highlights our innovation, security, and the invaluable role of our partners in achieving market leadership. IDC emphasized our extensive channel reach and the collaboration ecosystem we offer. Key takeaways include: - A complete solutions portfolio for diverse customer needs. - Security standards that are unmatched in critical industries. - AI innovations that&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Quantum Labs Announces Software That Networks Quantum Computers Together and Enables New Classical Applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10073/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 16:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10073/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has unveiled groundbreaking software that enables distributed quantum computing, releasing three research prototypes to enhance its quantum networking strategy. 🔹 The Quantum Compiler allows quantum algorithms to operate across multiple processors. 🔹 Quantum Alert provides eavesdropper-proof security based on physical guarantees. 🔹 Quantum Sync facilitates coordinated decision-making using entanglement. Join Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Quantum Summit next week for live demonstrations! 🌐 #QuantumComputing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Monitoring Your AI Infrastructure Isn’t Optional: A Deep Dive into Performance and Reliability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10152/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:42:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10152/</guid>
      <description>🌐 In today&amp;rsquo;s tech landscape, monitoring AI infrastructure is essential for performance and reliability. AI and machine learning drive innovation, but their effectiveness relies on a robust infrastructure. Minor issues can lead to significant setbacks, impacting model accuracy and increasing latency. A proactive, layer-by-layer monitoring approach ensures that all components work together efficiently, preventing costly downtime. #AIMonitoring #TechInfrastructure #AI #MachineLearning&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Unveils the Latest Security Innovations for Modern Data Center Networks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10074/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10074/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has introduced the N9300 Series Smart Switches, which integrate networking and security into one platform for data centers. These switches allow for robust L4 segmentation, enhancing security and simplifying operations. With advanced features like Cisco Hypershield, data centers can now scale securely and efficiently. Explore the future of data center networks! 💻🔒 #Cisco #DataCenter #Networking #Cybersecurity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highlight Platform Assures Horizon River’s 99.9% SLA Secure Uptime Service</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10075/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 15:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10075/</guid>
      <description>Horizon River is enhancing its network performance with the Highlight Service Observability Platform. This integration supports their commitment to a 99.9% network uptime for clients in various sectors, including retail and healthcare. Key improvements include a 5% reduction in SLA report production time and a 60% decrease in support escalations. Additionally, they’ve doubled support capacity and saved $100,000 in operational costs. This strategic move ensures proactive monitoring and rapid&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No fiber? No problem! 3 Use Cases Wireless Backhaul Solves Easily</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10076/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10076/</guid>
      <description>Need to expand your network without the hassle of fiber installation? 🌐 Wireless backhaul offers an efficient solution for connecting buildings, parking lots, and communities. It eliminates challenges like high costs, long installation times, and geographic obstacles. This technology enables quick setup, making it ideal for smart cities and rural areas. With Cisco’s access points, you can easily implement URWB to enhance connectivity. #WirelessBackhaul #NetworkExpansion #SmartCities&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents for Network and Security: Expectations vs Reality</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10040/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 22:24:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10040/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the role of AI agents in networking and security reveals a gap between expectations and reality. AI agents are autonomous systems that learn and adapt to achieve specific goals, unlike traditional software. They utilize tools for complex tasks such as network monitoring and threat analysis. The article discusses design choices, model selection, and the importance of benchmarks, particularly for networking and security tasks. Notable models include Foundation-Sec-8B for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The origins, impact and future of AI Agents: A conversation with David White</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9970/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9970/</guid>
      <description>🚀 David White, a Distinguished Engineer at Cisco, shares insights into the evolution of AI Agents and their future in a recent conversation. He reflects on his journey since joining Cisco in 2000, emphasizing the importance of innovation and problem-solving in tech. With nearly 100 patents, David is focused on creating solutions to enhance customer experiences. AI Agents are now a prominent part of our tech landscape, but their origins reveal a fascinating story of progress. #AI #Innovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A turning point in how Europe builds and protects its sovereign critical infrastructure in the AI era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9971/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9971/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco is addressing digital sovereignty in Europe with its new Sovereign Critical Infrastructure portfolio. This initiative responds to the demand for greater choice and control among European customers in sectors like banking and healthcare. The portfolio offers configurable infrastructure with EU-based certifications, enabling secure, on-premises operation of sensitive data. #DigitalSovereignty #Cisco #CriticalInfrastructure #DataSecurity #AIera</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap: Cisco’s Blueprint for Developer-Centric Cloud Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9972/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9972/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco is transforming cloud security by integrating it into the developer workflow. They focus on reducing friction between developers and security teams through high-fidelity alerts, pre-configured solutions, and clear communication. This approach fosters collaboration and trust, making security a natural part of development. Empathy is emphasized to ensure security measures truly support developers. #CloudSecurity #DevOps #Cisco #Collaboration #SecuritySolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cisco IT is redefining Zero Trust in the AI Era as customer zero</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9966/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 11:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9966/</guid>
      <description>Cisco IT is redefining Zero Trust in the AI era by implementing Cisco Secure Access across its global workforce. By collaborating with product teams, Cisco improved security operations while enhancing user experiences. This shift addresses the challenges of a hyper-distributed environment, supporting 130,000 employees and contractors. Transitioning from a custom-built solution, Cisco embraced a SASE/SSE approach to focus on innovation and emerging security threats, particularly those related&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Magic of Building a Hybrid RAG AI Assistant for Automation Certification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9954/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 21:42:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9954/</guid>
      <description>At Learn with Cisco, we are advancing the use of AI in practical ways for tech learners. The article highlights the evolution of automation and AI, emphasizing the rapid changes from early digital technology to today&amp;rsquo;s sophisticated tools. Machine learning, a key aspect of AI, allows machines to recognize patterns and generate results efficiently. This technology is becoming more accessible, impacting various sectors. Engineers are encouraged to embrace these innovations and harness their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Moment is Now: Harnessing the Power of the Cisco 360 Partner Program</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9927/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 17:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9927/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Cisco 360 Partner Program marks a pivotal shift in partnership dynamics. It empowers partners with tools for profitable growth and AI-driven solutions. This program focuses on delivering outcomes rather than just technology, aligning with customer expectations in a changing market. The goal is to redefine partner value and foster collaboration for sustainable growth. 🌱 #Cisco360 #PartnerProgram #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Striving for Sustainability: Meet Tom</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9928/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9928/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Meet Tom Jackson, Senior Director at Cisco, who leads efforts in circular design and sustainability. With 25 years at Cisco, Tom&amp;rsquo;s diverse experience shapes his commitment to eco-friendly practices. He integrates circular design principles into product development, aiming to reduce environmental impact and enhance innovation. Tom&amp;rsquo;s passion for the outdoors drives his mission. He believes in a comprehensive approach to sustainability that evolves continuously. 🌱 #Sustainability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Network: From Foundation to AI Catalyst</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9909/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9909/</guid>
      <description>Unlock new opportunities with Cisco and NTT DATA as they lead the way in AI-ready networking solutions. 🌐 Their recent announcements highlight the importance of agile and intelligent networks in driving digital transformation. As AI reshapes business strategies, the right infrastructure can enhance security and connectivity. Explore how these innovations can benefit your organization. #Cisco #NTTDATA #AI #DigitalTransformation #NetworkingSolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Human Network – My Journey with Cisco</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9910/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9910/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Shweta Takate reflects on her journey with Cisco, highlighting her transformation since joining in 2007. She describes the supportive culture that felt like family in Bangalore, which fueled her passion and growth. After a brief hiatus for further education in New York, Shweta returned to Cisco, where she found the same welcoming atmosphere. Her story emphasizes the importance of human connection in the workplace. #Cisco #CareerJourney #HumanConnection #WorkCulture</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming a Historic Campus with Cisco Technology</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9878/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 15:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9878/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Texas A&amp;amp;M’s RELLIS campus is transforming a WWII-era airbase into a research hub, powered by Cisco technology. Bradley Hoover, the Chief Information Officer, is leading this initiative with a focus on modern infrastructure. A key step was implementing a private 5G core, enabling groundbreaking 5G research. The team is also unifying the network with comprehensive Cisco solutions to support ongoing research needs. This approach enhances flexibility and scalability across the 2300-acre&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Agentic AI Era Demands a New Network</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9879/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9879/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The rise of agentic AI requires a new approach to enterprise network design. Current networks, built for human productivity, face challenges in speed, reliability, and security needed by autonomous AI agents. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s AI-Ready Secure Network Architecture aims to provide the low latency and automation essential for efficient machine-speed operations. As AI agents become more prevalent, adapting network infrastructure is crucial. #AgenticAI #NetworkDesign #Cisco #AI #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 80/20 Rule Doesn’t Apply to Security: How Cisco SASE Bridges the Gap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9865/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9865/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s IT landscape, relying on the 80/20 rule for security is risky. Focusing only on the majority can leave vulnerabilities exposed. 🌐🔒 With hybrid work and evolving tech, organizations need a security strategy that protects 100% of their digital presence at all times. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s SASE offers a solution by merging networking and security in a cloud-based framework. 🌥️ This innovative approach establishes micro-perimeters for enhanced protection, ensuring secure access no matter where users&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Bets on Austin: Celebrating Our New Downtown Office</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9862/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 11:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9862/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Cisco! Today, they opened their new downtown office in Austin, showcasing advanced workplace technologies. Nearly 30 years in Austin, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s commitment to the city continues to grow. The new office symbolizes their belief in Austin&amp;rsquo;s potential and innovation. With over 1,400 employees in the area, Cisco is focused on driving innovation and shaping the future of work. #Cisco #Austin #Innovation #FutureOfWork #TechCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing for data: Inside Cisco’s new future-proofed workplace in Austin</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9863/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 11:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9863/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco is transforming its Austin office into a data-driven workplace. The new design focuses on productivity, employee well-being, and sustainability, utilizing real-time insights from Cisco’s smart office solutions. This initiative aims to reshape corporate real estate and establish a benchmark for future workplaces. Discover how data is shaping the future of work! 🌍✨ #Cisco #FutureOfWork #SmartOffice #WorkplaceWellbeing #Sustainability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It’s Splunkin’ Time to Rev Up Your Security Skills</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9836/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 21:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9836/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for networking professionals! Cisco has launched the Rev Up to Recert: Security Solutions program, offering free access to the Enhancing Cisco Security Solutions with Data Analytics Learning Path. Earn up to 32 Continuing Education credits! 📚 This initiative runs until October 31, 2025, just in time for Cybersecurity Awareness Month. Perfect for both beginners and seasoned pros looking to enhance their Splunk skills. Join now and elevate your career! 💼 #Cisco #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Government Operations: Cisco Security Cloud Control Achieves FedRAMP Authorization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9826/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9826/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for U.S. government agencies! Cisco Security Cloud Control has received FedRAMP Authorization, enhancing security management for critical infrastructure. This cloud-native solution supports agencies in navigating today’s complex threat landscape. The FedRAMP Authorization signifies high security standards, ensuring that Cisco&amp;rsquo;s solution is compliant and reliable for federal operations. #Cybersecurity #GovTech #FedRAMP #Cisco #CloudSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating a decade of Connected Conservation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9811/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9811/</guid>
      <description>Celebrating a decade of impactful partnership! 🌍 For ten years, Cisco and the Connected Conservation Foundation (CCF) have worked together to enhance wildlife conservation. Their efforts have provided essential technology to monitor and protect species like rhinos and elephants across 46 protected areas in Africa. This World Rhino Day, we reflect on the progress made and the ongoing commitment to safeguarding these animals and their habitats. 🦏✨ #ConnectedConservation #WildlifeProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleashing the Power of AI: A Transformational Opportunity for SMBs with Cisco</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9780/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 15:56:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9780/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking AI for Small and Medium Businesses with Cisco! 🤖 Cisco is making AI accessible and secure for SMBs, enabling them to automate tasks, enhance customer service, and improve decision-making without high costs or complexity. AI is transforming how businesses operate, from optimizing inventory in retail to enhancing patient engagement in healthcare. However, challenges like limited IT expertise and data privacy concerns persist. Cisco is addressing these issues by providing AI-ready&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From AIOps to AgenticOps: The Autonomous Evolution of Firewall Operations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9769/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 12:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9769/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is transforming firewall operations with its new AIOps for Firewalls. This approach shifts from reactive troubleshooting to proactive management. By leveraging AI-driven insights, the system detects anomalies and configuration drifts in real-time. This evolution aims to enhance security and reduce the fatigue of IT teams. Stay updated with these advancements in cybersecurity! 🔐✨ #Cybersecurity #AI #Firewall #AIOps #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Composable Infrastructure: What It Means in the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9733/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9733/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming infrastructure needs, making traditional setups inadequate. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s UCS X-Series with X-Fabric Technology 2.0 offers a solution through modular, dynamic composability. This allows resources to adapt to the evolving demands of AI workloads, enhancing performance and scalability. Stay ahead with infrastructure designed for the AI era! 💡🚀 #AI #ComposableInfrastructure #Cisco #Innovation #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusing Security into Networks: The Next Evolution in Enterprise Protection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9734/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9734/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving landscape of enterprise networks, traditional security tools are proving inadequate. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s AI-Ready Secure Network Architecture embeds multilayered security within the network itself, enhancing protection against a range of threats. This integrated approach utilizes Zero Trust, post-quantum encryption, and real-time threat prevention to simplify operations and improve threat response. It addresses vulnerabilities across various domains, including user edge and industrial&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlock Unified Network and Security Analytics with Cisco and Splunk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9708/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 21:13:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9708/</guid>
      <description>Unlock unified network and security analytics with Cisco and Splunk! 🌐🔍 Join the livestream on September 17 at 9 a.m. PT, hosted by Adrian Illiesiu. Learn from Technical Marketing Engineer Taylor Cook as he demonstrates the Cisco Enterprise Networking app for Splunk. Discover how it integrates data from various Cisco platforms for enhanced network visibility and security management. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on the chance to ask your questions live! #Cisco #Splunk #NetworkSecurity #DevNet #LiveDemo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Profitable Partners Do Differently</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9701/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 19:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9701/</guid>
      <description>Join us at the Cisco Partner Summit 2025 in San Diego from November 3-5 to explore how profitable partnerships can enhance your business growth. The summit will focus on key questions guiding collaboration and the framework of &amp;ldquo;durable growth&amp;rdquo; to drive success. Gain insights from industry leaders and learn effective strategies for partnership profitability. 🌟🤝 #CiscoPartnerSummit #BusinessGrowth #Partnerships #Innovation #Cisco</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco AI Networking &amp; Splunk: Enhanced Data Center Network Visibility</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9691/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9691/</guid>
      <description>Cisco and Splunk have teamed up to enhance data center network visibility with the new Cisco Data Fabric. 🌐 This innovative architecture focuses on unifying data center analytics, providing cross-domain visibility and real-time insights. The integration of AI-driven monitoring aims to optimize and secure enterprise infrastructure. 📊🔍 Stay informed about the latest in digital infrastructure! #Cisco #Splunk #DataCenter #AINetworking #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning: Our Greatest AI Advantage</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9678/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9678/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The AI Workforce Consortium&amp;rsquo;s 2025 report highlights the evolving landscape of ICT roles influenced by AI integration. 📊 Key findings reveal that 78% of analyzed job roles now require AI skills, with 7 of the 10 fastest-growing positions being AI-related. 💼 Human capabilities like communication and leadership remain vital in this tech-driven era. #AIWorkforce #SkillDevelopment #AIIntegration #ICTJobs #FutureOfWork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn with Cisco Introduces New AI Training for the Evolving Skills of Today’s Workforce</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9679/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:30:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9679/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news from Learn with Cisco! They have launched new AI training programs aimed at equipping professionals with the skills needed to integrate AI into their workplaces. The Cisco AI Business Practitioner and Cisco AI Technical Practitioner certifications will help workers use AI safely and effectively. This initiative responds to the evolving job landscape shaped by AI technology. With over 28 million people trained globally, Cisco continues to lead in digital skills development. 🌍💻&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Splunk to Cisco: A Seamless Transition in Career and Family</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9680/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9680/</guid>
      <description>Excited to share insights from Vikram U.&amp;rsquo;s journey transitioning from Splunk to Cisco. He highlights the strong bond formed between both teams during the acquisition. Vikram also emphasizes the importance of Cisco&amp;rsquo;s generous parental leave, which allowed him and his wife to welcome their baby girl and navigate parenthood seamlessly. This supportive culture has made a significant impact on their family life. 👶❤️ #CareerTransition #ParentalLeave #Cisco #FamilySupport #WorkLifeBalance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ansible Workflows for Cisco Automation: Watch the First NetGru Replay</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9670/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 20:59:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9670/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into automation with the latest NetGru episode! This week, Adrian Illiesiu hosts a session on using Ansible workflows for Cisco Catalyst Center. Pawan Singh shares insights on simplifying playbooks and enhancing deployment reliability. Catch the replay and join us every Wednesday for more! 📅 #CiscoAutomation #Ansible #NetGru #TechTuesday #DevNet</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ignite Your Reach: Cisco’s Campaign Transforms Partners’ Data Center Conversations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9662/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:42:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9662/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has launched the Data Center Modernization &amp;amp; Optics Campaign to help partners address the rising infrastructure demands from AI technologies. With 93% of IT leaders anticipating increased demands, this campaign offers ready-to-use marketing tools to support partners in promoting scalable solutions. Explore customizable resources and engage your audience effectively. #Cisco #DataCenter #AI #Modernization #MarketingTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we’re building tomorrow’s tech force, today with Camden Dream Center</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9663/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:34:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9663/</guid>
      <description>Cisco and the Camden Dream Center are partnering to address the digital divide in tech education. This collaboration offers students practical learning experiences in engineering and cybersecurity. Pastor Keith Davis founded the Camden Dream Center to create opportunities for vulnerable communities. The initiative aims to prepare students for future careers in technology. #TechEducation #DigitalDivide #Cisco #CamdenDreamCenter #Cybersecurity 🚀📚💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Isn’t Coming. It’s Already Here</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9653/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9653/</guid>
      <description>AI is not a future concept; it is actively transforming enterprise networks today. 🌐 From sales teams using AI to draft proposals to security teams leveraging models for threat detection, AI is integrated into daily workflows across various industries. The shift in network demand is significant, with both cloud-based and edge-based AI tools creating new traffic patterns that require low latency and high performance. Cameras now perform real-time analytics, enhancing security and operational&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EU Data Act: Streamlined Data Laws Can Help Boost Europe’s AI and Digital Leadership</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9547/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9547/</guid>
      <description>📢 The EU Data Act, effective September 12, introduces new data sharing requirements across Europe. Cisco supports these changes but advocates for regulatory simplification to enhance data-driven innovation and AI. 🤝 By streamlining complex rules, businesses can innovate with confidence and invest in new technologies, benefiting society as a whole. 🔍 Cisco has updated its legal terms to align with the new regulations and promote open data sharing, crucial for responsible AI development. 🚫&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SnortML: Cisco’s ML-Based Detection Engine Gets Powerful Upgrade</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9548/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 12:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9548/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco&amp;rsquo;s SnortML, a machine learning engine for the Snort IPS, has been upgraded to enhance the detection of evolving exploits like SQL Injection and XSS. This engine operates on-device, ensuring data privacy by processing information locally without cloud dependency. 🌐 SnortML leverages deep neural networks to identify new attack patterns, addressing the rise in vulnerabilities from 18,375 in 2020 to over 40,000 in 2024. 🔒 #CyberSecurity #MachineLearning #DataPrivacy #IntrusionPrevention&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digitally empowering communities in India with Cisco and Indus Action</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9543/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 07:58:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9543/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Cisco and Indus Action are working to enhance social protection systems in India. Their partnership aims to simplify school admissions for underserved families and improve access to maternal health and labor welfare. By leveraging digital solutions, they help vulnerable communities navigate essential services more effectively. Together, they are building a brighter future for many. #DigitalEmpowerment #SocialWelfare #CommunitySupport #Cisco #IndusAction</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sustainability 101: What is packaging sustainability?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9459/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:52:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9459/</guid>
      <description>🌍 &lt;strong&gt;Understanding Packaging Sustainability&lt;/strong&gt; 🌱 Packaging plays a significant role in our daily lives, but much of it becomes waste quickly. The OECD reports that 31% of plastic production is for packaging, often single-use. This waste can lead to environmental issues, including toxin emissions and greenhouse gases from landfills. Research highlights that non-recyclable items, like certain foams and food-contaminated aluminum, add to the problem. These materials can disrupt ecosystems and harm&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Training for Network Engineers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9460/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9460/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Staying ahead in the tech world is essential, especially for network engineers. Cisco emphasizes the importance of AI training as the landscape shifts towards more precise solutions. 🔍 A foundational understanding of AI is now critical, influencing areas like cybersecurity and business decisions. 💡 Cisco offers free AI training resources, including courses that prepare engineers for certification and practical applications. Explore the future of networking with AI! #AITraining&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving IT Sustainability in the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9461/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9461/</guid>
      <description>🌍 As we move into an AI-driven future, Cisco and NTT DATA emphasize the need for IT sustainability. 🚀 Their recent discussions highlight that sustainable IT is a collective responsibility that demands innovation and collaboration. Clients can shape sustainable outcomes by making informed decisions early in the design process. 💡 Efficiency and sustainability go hand-in-hand. For instance, NTT DATA&amp;rsquo;s consolidation of office sites with Cisco’s support resulted in over 30% reduction in hosting&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packing More Power Into Cisco XDR’s Integration Toolkit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9462/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9462/</guid>
      <description>Cisco XDR is likened to a Swiss Army knife, emphasizing its versatility in cybersecurity. Just as the iconic tool combines multiple functions for various tasks, Cisco XDR integrates numerous security features—like firewalls and email protection—into one cohesive platform. This design allows users to effectively address diverse cybersecurity challenges. 🛠️🔒 #CiscoXDR #Cybersecurity #Integration #Versatility #CyberTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cisco Supports Work-Life Balance: My 21-Day Motorcycle Dream Trip</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9463/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9463/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Namita J., a Meraki Technical Leader at Cisco, shares her inspiring journey of a 21-day motorcycle trip across Europe. Cisco’s culture of trust and flexibility allowed her to take 30 days off without concerns about work. Her manager and team fully supported her adventure, ensuring a seamless workflow in her absence. This experience highlights how Cisco promotes work-life balance, empowering employees to pursue their dreams. 🏍️✨ #WorkLifeBalance #Cisco #EmployeeWellbeing #DreamBig&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine data: The next frontier in AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9441/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 22:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9441/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At #SplunkConf25, Cisco and Splunk introduced new innovations to harness the potential of machine-generated data. 🔍 Machine data is crucial for AI, yet it remains underutilized due to challenges like data silos and the complexity of integration. 💡 Cisco aims to address these obstacles, providing the infrastructure needed for AI success. #AI #DataInnovation #Splunk #Cisco #MachineData</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empowering Brazil’s next generation of cybersecurity talent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9442/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:51:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9442/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco is dedicated to empowering Brazil’s cybersecurity talent. Their Cyber Education program, now in its 11th year, has successfully reached over one million students via the Networking Academy. This initiative addresses the urgent need for skilled professionals in a digital era. By partnering with educational institutions and industry leaders, Cisco is building a robust talent pipeline to support Brazil’s digital transformation and the global cybersecurity landscape. 🔐🌍 #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Comply-to-Connect (C2C) Training Now Supports Third-Party Integrations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9443/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9443/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has updated its Comply-to-Connect (C2C) training to now support third-party integrations. This training is crucial for deploying C2C solutions in mixed-vendor environments. The program includes both instructor-led courses and e-learning options, featuring hands-on labs and instructional videos. 📚 Key integrations with Microsoft MECM, Tenable, and Trillex enhance endpoint compliance and access control. This update aligns with the Department of Defense&amp;rsquo;s Zero Trust initiatives. 🔒 For&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered APIs and API-Enabled AI: A Symbiotic Evolution Driving Mutual Innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9436/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9436/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving digital landscape, APIs are crucial for innovation, connecting services and sharing data. However, the growing complexity of API ecosystems poses challenges. AI is emerging as a solution, enhancing API discovery through intent-based searches, which makes finding relevant documentation easier. Additionally, AI is improving API specifications by refining clarity and compliance, ensuring high-quality documentation. 🌐🔗✨ #APIs #AI #Innovation #TechTrends #Development</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tech Unscripted: Your Front-Row Seat for Honest Talk Between CIOs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9425/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:38:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9425/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover Tech Unscripted, a new video series featuring candid conversations with IT leaders tackling today&amp;rsquo;s challenges. Gain insights on managing ISP outages, securing remote work, and addressing AI demands. Each episode offers actionable tips for strategists, engineers, and security professionals. Tune in for valuable lessons straight from the experts. 📈💡 #TechUnscripted #CIOInsights #ITLeadership #Cybersecurity #DigitalTransformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Launching the 2nd Edition of the Cisco Cybersecurity Academy in Portugal</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9426/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9426/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for cybersecurity enthusiasts in Portugal! Cisco is launching the 2nd Edition of the Cybersecurity Academy, expanding on the success of the first edition. This six-month program aims to equip high-potential talent with hands-on training and industry-recognized certifications. Yves Mertens emphasizes that this initiative strengthens relationships among Cisco, customers, and partners, addressing the growing cybersecurity skills gap. Special thanks to the project team and Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Infrastructure for the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9427/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9427/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Cisco is leading the way in transforming network infrastructure for the AI era. As AI evolves, the need for high-speed interconnects in data centers is crucial. Cisco focuses on using pluggable optics to enhance performance and reliability across all distances, addressing the demands of AI applications. With projected AI investments reaching $5.2 trillion by 2030, the pressure on networks is increasing. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive technology stack positions it well to meet these challenges,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Fused into the Network to Protect OT at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9428/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9428/</guid>
      <description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest update enhances OT security by integrating asset visibility and secure remote access into industrial switches. This approach aims to eliminate security blind spots and reduce costs for organizations managing numerous sites and assets. With the new Cyber Vision offering, users gain comprehensive visibility and enforce zero-trust remote access seamlessly. This solution is now standard in Cisco&amp;rsquo;s IE3500 and IE9300 Rugged Series Switches, making OT security more accessible&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPv6 in 2025 – The Freedom of Address Space</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9392/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9392/</guid>
      <description>🌐 IPv6 is shaping the future of networking. As we move towards a more IPv6-dominant landscape, organizations must prioritize training and inventory assessments. 📈 The switch from IPv4 to IPv6 offers an astronomical increase in address space, freeing us from previous constraints. 🔗 Cisco is committed to supporting this transition, ensuring that businesses can fully leverage IPv6&amp;rsquo;s potential. #IPv6 #Networking #Cisco #ITInfrastructure #FutureTech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust in the Era of Agentic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9393/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9393/</guid>
      <description>Zero Trust is evolving to address the unique challenges posed by Agentic AI. 🤖 As AI agents utilize the same networks as users and apps, current security measures must adapt to ensure safe communication. Traditional security solutions have limitations, primarily focusing on intercepting traffic and analyzing data context. To protect these intelligent agents effectively, a shift towards enhanced zero trust frameworks is essential. 🔐 #ZeroTrust #AI #CyberSecurity #AgenticAI #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Validated Design for Panasonic: A Blueprint for IP Media Success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7779/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7779/</guid>
      <description>Cisco and Panasonic have collaborated to create a Cisco Validated Design (CVD) aimed at enhancing IP infrastructure for media broadcasters. This design ensures reliable, scalable support for high-resolution video formats like UHD/4K and beyond. The CVD is rigorously tested for interoperability, providing a trusted blueprint for organizations. It helps accelerate deployments while minimizing risk, ensuring all components work seamlessly together for high-quality live production. This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the New Nexus Dashboard for Simplifying Data Center Operations in the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7780/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7780/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data center operations! Nexus Dashboard 4.1 is now available, offering complete lifecycle management for multiple data center networks through a single interface. This solution simplifies provisioning and enhances visibility while providing diagnostics and automation. It supports various environments, including NX-OS, ACI, AI fabrics, and more. The dashboard also enables VXLAN EVPN automation on Cisco Catalyst switches. #DataCenter #NexusDashboard #AI #NetworkManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the New Nexus Dashboard for Simplifying Data Center Operations in the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7817/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7817/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news in data center management! The Nexus Dashboard 4.1 is now available for unified lifecycle management of multiple data center networks. This single interface streamlines provisioning and enhances visibility, making it easier for teams to manage diverse environments. It supports various network fabrics, including NX-OS and ACI, while offering robust automation and diagnostics. This advancement aims to simplify operations in an increasingly AI-driven landscape. #DataCenter&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The data catalyst: Blended finance paving the way for climate AI solutions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7754/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7754/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The Cisco Foundation highlights the role of blended finance in addressing the data-to-scale gap for climate AI solutions. AI can significantly impact climate innovation, but it requires access to diverse, quality data, which is often costly. Cisco recently hosted an AI + Climate Innovation Lab, uniting over 100 experts to explore data needs in various climate sectors. Together, these efforts aim to enhance climate tech funding and innovation. 💡📊 #ClimateAI #BlendedFinance #DataForClimate&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The data catalyst: Blended finance paving the way for climate AI solutions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7818/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7818/</guid>
      <description>The Cisco Foundation is exploring blended finance to tackle the data accessibility challenges for climate AI solutions. 🌍 During the AI + Climate Innovation Lab at San Francisco Climate Week 2025, over 100 experts discussed the critical need for diverse and high-quality data across various climate sectors. This initiative aims to bridge the gap in funding and data for climate tech innovation. 💡 #ClimateAI #DataForGood #Sustainability #Innovation #BlendedFinance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing U.S. AI Leadership: Cisco to Skill 1 Million People</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7755/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7755/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is committed to enhancing AI education in the U.S. 🌟 As part of the White House&amp;rsquo;s Pledge to America’s Youth, they plan to train 1 million people in AI and digital skills over the next four years via Learn with Cisco. This initiative highlights the importance of preparing individuals for an AI-driven future. Cisco aims to equip educators with the necessary tools and curricula to effectively teach AI. Together, we can empower a new generation for the evolving job market! 💻🤝 #AI #Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing U.S. AI Leadership: Cisco to Skill 1 Million People</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7819/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7819/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is committed to advancing AI skills in the U.S. by training 1 million people over the next four years through their Learn with Cisco initiative. This effort aligns with the White House’s Pledge to America’s Youth, focusing on enhancing AI education for all ages. Cisco aims to equip educators and students with the necessary tools and curricula to thrive in an AI-driven economy. #AI #Education #Cisco #DigitalSkills #FutureOfWork 🤖📚🌍</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Some Source of Truth to Your NetAI Agentic Playground</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7735/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7735/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the integration of AI in network engineering, Hank Preston discusses the importance of source-of-truth data for NetAI agents. In his latest article, he reflects on using Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers to enhance AI&amp;rsquo;s ability to interact with network devices. The focus is on providing AI agents access to essential data, boosting their effectiveness. NetBox, an open-source tool, is highlighted for its role in this process, enabling better data accessibility for AI applications&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Some Source of Truth to Your NetAI Agentic Playground</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7820/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7820/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the integration of AI in network engineering, the article discusses the importance of providing source-of-truth data to AI agents. The author shares insights on using Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers to enhance AI interactions with network devices. A key focus is on leveraging NetBox, an open-source tool, to supply vital data for AI operations. This approach aims to empower AI agents to function like human engineers. #NetAI #AIinNetworking #NetworkAutomation #TechInsights&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Reactive IT Finally Dead?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7719/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7719/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Is Reactive IT Finally Dead? 🚨 In a recent article, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Jason Coleman highlights the challenges of reactive IT. Engineers often spend over 150 hours a year addressing unexpected outages, leading to high costs and operational risks. Cisco is shifting towards AI-powered, preemptive IT solutions to combat these issues, aiming to minimize downtime and enhance efficiency. Learn more about this important shift in IT management! #Cisco #ReactiveIT #AITechnology #ITManagement #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Reactive IT Finally Dead?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7821/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7821/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Is Reactive IT Finally Dead? 🚨 Jason Coleman from Cisco discusses the challenges of reactive IT, where engineers spend over 150 hours annually fixing unexpected outages. This approach leads to high costs and operational risks for businesses. Cisco is shifting towards AI-powered, preemptive IT solutions to enhance network reliability and reduce downtime. Learn more about this important transition in IT management! #ITManagement #Cisco #AI #TechTrends #NetworkReliability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conference Hopping: Training Attendee Scanning Def Con</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7665/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7665/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The Black Hat NOC faces unique challenges, as it operates in a cybersecurity hub where scanning and ethical hacking are expected. Cisco is enhancing security with network-based telemetry to monitor diverse personal devices at the conference. An alert recently identified suspicious activity linked to a training session targeting an external IP associated with Def Con. #Cybersecurity #BlackHat2025 #Cisco #ThreatDetection #EthicalHacking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving Cisco XDR Integration With Third-Party Partners at Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7666/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7666/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is the Official Security Cloud provider at Black Hat USA 2025, showcasing its latest advancements in XDR integration. These integrations enhance the Security Operations Center&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, allowing analysts to quickly investigate Indicators of Compromise (IOC) with a single search. Special thanks to alphaMountain.ai and Pulsedive for their contributions to the event. #Cisco #CyberSecurity #BlackHat2025 #XDR #MalwareAnalysis 🚀🔍💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Secure Firewall: SnortML at Black Hat USA 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7667/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7667/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is the Security Cloud Provider for Black Hat USA 2025! Attendees can participate in hands-on training sessions, using cloud resources for real-time attack simulations. The Cisco team ensures stable connectivity and monitors traffic to protect against unauthorized attacks. SnortML, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s machine learning tool, demonstrated high accuracy, detecting over 100 attacks with only 21 false positives. Stay informed about cybersecurity innovations! 🔒💻 #Cisco #BlackHat2025 #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat Investigation: Attempted Exploitation of Registration Server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7668/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7668/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Black Hat Conference Update 🚨 Recent investigations revealed attempted exploitation of the registration server at the Black Hat conference. Operating within the unique Security and Network Operations Center (NOC) environment, Cisco faces distinct challenges due to the conference&amp;rsquo;s focus on cybersecurity research and ethical hacking. 🔍 The NOC anticipates various activities that might appear suspicious elsewhere. The Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) policy complicates monitoring, emphasizing the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Value of PCAP in Firewall Investigations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7669/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7669/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The article highlights the importance of PCAP (packet capture) in firewall investigations, emphasizing its time-consuming nature. Key steps include finding a suitable platform, executing the capture, and analyzing large files. At Black Hat USA 2025, the ‘Endace PCAP Pivot’ feature enabled easier access to packet-level data, enhancing SOC analyst investigations significantly. 📊🔍 #CyberSecurity #PacketCapture #NetworkAnalysis #BlackHat2025 #SOCInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat Training Attendees Scan Aviation Organization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7670/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7670/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Black Hat conference highlights the unique challenges of cybersecurity, particularly within its Security and Network Operations Center (NOC). Attendees engage in ethical hacking, leading to expected scanning and exploitation activities. This dynamic environment differs from typical corporate settings where such actions are seen as malicious. With a Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) policy, comprehensive monitoring becomes challenging. The focus shifts to robust network-based telemetry for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat USA 2025: 10 Years Protecting Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7671/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7671/</guid>
      <description>Cisco celebrates a decade as the Official Security Cloud Provider for Black Hat USA! 🎉 Partnering with companies like Arista, Corelight, Lumen, and Palo Alto Networks, Cisco helps build and secure the Black Hat network. The NOC focuses on continuous network stability, delivering seamless security and visibility through an embedded SOC. 🔒🌐 #BlackHat2025 #CyberSecurity #Cisco #NetworkOperations #TechPartnerships</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refining SSO at Black Hat USA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7672/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7672/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Black Hat USA 2025! Cisco Duo has enhanced its role as the multifactor authentication (MFA) and single sign-on (SSO) provider for the Network Operations Center (NOC). The successful deployment of Duo Directory has expanded user access, supporting over 100 users at the event. This upgrade improves identity and access management for both users and admins. Key features include streamlined password management and a new Global Enrollment Policy to simplify onboarding. 🔐&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing DNS With Umbrella at Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7673/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7673/</guid>
      <description>Cisco continues to enhance security at Black Hat, focusing on DNS monitoring since 2017. 🌐 With Umbrella, they route DNS traffic through a centralized service, gaining insights into potential threats like malware and phishing. At Black Hat USA 2025, encrypted DNS requests were blocked to improve visibility into user traffic. 🔍 The team prioritized monitoring the ApateWeb PUP delivery and phishing campaign, noting specific domain patterns. #Cisco #BlackHat2025 #CyberSecurity #DNS #Umbrella</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebuilding homes and a resilient community in Western North Carolina</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7627/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7627/</guid>
      <description>In Western North Carolina, Cisco Crisis Response and 40 Communities are aiding in the recovery from Hurricane Helene. 🌪️ After the storm caused severe damage, affecting over 73,000 homes, a coalition was formed to support local leaders and nonprofits in the rebuilding efforts. 🏠 Nearly a year later, the focus remains on restoring homes, especially for low-income families, while ensuring vital services are accessible. 🤝 #CommunitySupport #HurricaneHelene #RebuildingTogether #CrisisResponse&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start your career in IT with CCST certification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7628/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7628/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to kickstart your IT career? Cisco&amp;rsquo;s CCST certification is your gateway! This entry-level certification offers three paths: IT Support, Networking, and Cybersecurity. With no prerequisites, anyone can start learning and gain essential skills. Join over 1.8 million students who have begun their journey with Cisco Networking Academy! #Cisco #ITCareers #CCST #TechTraining #Cybersecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Velocity Reimagined Wins Triple Industry Recognition!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7611/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7611/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco’s Marketing Velocity Reimagined has achieved a remarkable feat by winning three industry awards in 2025! 🏆 The program received the 2025 Killer Content Award for Channel Partner Marketing, recognizing its innovative digital co-marketing experience that empowers partners with learning and customizable campaigns. 📈 It also earned the 2025 Sammy Award for Sales and Marketing, celebrating the team&amp;rsquo;s efforts to enhance connections with partners and drive growth through data-driven&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Backdoor in TACACS&#43;: Why Full-Session Encryption Matters More Than Ever</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7607/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7607/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Recent cyber threats highlight the risks of weak TACACS+ encryption. Attackers exploited vulnerabilities, targeting network operators to steal credentials and blend in as legitimate admins. By harvesting TACACS+ traffic, they captured sensitive data, allowing unauthorized access and evading detection. Cisco ISE with TLS 1.3 and Duo MFA offers solutions to enhance security and close these backdoors. 🔒🛡️ #Cybersecurity #TACACS #DataProtection #CiscoISE #MFA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Exposed LLM Servers: A Shodan Case Study on Ollama</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7583/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7583/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A recent case study reveals over 1,100 exposed Ollama LLM servers, with 20% hosting open models. This highlights critical security vulnerabilities in LLM deployments. 🔍 The study utilized Shodan to identify these unsecured endpoints, emphasizing the need for stronger security measures. 🛡️ As LLMs become more popular, addressing these gaps is essential for protecting sensitive data. #CyberSecurity #LLM #DataProtection #Ollama #Shodan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safeguard Against Data Breaches in Our Next Cisco U. Capture the Flag Challenge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7487/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7487/</guid>
      <description>🛡️ Learn about SQL Injection (SQLi) attacks and their impact on database security. These attacks exploit application vulnerabilities to manipulate SQL queries, leading to unauthorized access and data theft. Consequences include credential theft, data alteration, and even system access. Stay informed and protect your digital data! 🔐 #CyberSecurity #EthicalHacking #SQLInjection #DataProtection #TechAwareness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uninterrupted Motion: Why Factories Need a New Class of Wireless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7460/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7460/</guid>
      <description>Factories are increasingly using Automated Guided Vehicles (AGVs) and Autonomous Mobile Robots (AMRs) to boost productivity. These vehicles rely on robust wireless networks to operate effectively. 📈🤖 A reliable connection is vital for real-time inspections and safety alerts. Any interruption can lead to missed defects or safety risks, potentially halting production. 🛑⚠️ Companies like BMW and Samsung are already utilizing these technologies to enhance quality assurance and operational safety&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Demand Skills for the Modern Network Engineer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7473/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7473/</guid>
      <description>📈 Staying current in the tech industry is vital for network engineers. Cisco emphasizes the importance of continuous skill development amid rapid technological changes. 🔍 Their research highlights that networking, cybersecurity, and AI skills are essential for future job roles. 🧠 Critical thinking also emerges as a key skill, helping professionals grasp the &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; behind tech advances. #NetworkEngineering #Cybersecurity #AITechnology #SkillDevelopment #Cisco</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Ahead of the HIPAA Security Rule Update With Secure Workload</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7193/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7193/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for Healthcare Organizations! 🚨 On January 6, 2025, the Office of Civil Rights will introduce new cybersecurity requirements as part of the HIPAA Security Rule Update. This will shift the focus from reactive measures to a risk-based approach to enhance cybersecurity in healthcare. The update aims to strengthen the protection of electronic personal health information (ePHI) and address the increasing number of cyberattacks. Organizations must prepare to implement effective&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dedicated Cisco Wireless Certification Track Is on the Horizon</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7194/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7194/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for wireless professionals! Cisco is launching a dedicated Wireless Certification Track in March 2026. This includes the new CCNP Wireless and CCIE Wireless certifications, designed to align with modern wireless technologies. From foundational courses to expert levels, these certifications will equip you with essential skills for managing complex networks. Start your journey with the Understanding Cisco Wireless Foundations training to build the necessary knowledge for WLAN&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Velocity: Comstor’s Powerful Engine Driving Partner Success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7195/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7195/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Marketing Velocity, in partnership with Comstor, fuels business growth through demand generation and co-branded campaigns. This initiative focuses on AI, digital resilience, and future-proof workplaces, showcasing partner success stories to highlight effective strategies. Learn more about driving sustainable growth in the tech industry! 🌐📈 #MarketingVelocity #PartnerSuccess #Cisco #Comstor #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Enterprise AI: Closing the Infrastructure Gap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7196/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7196/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Enterprise AI is evolving beyond just GPU power. Success now relies on integrating data, security, and operations effectively. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Secure AI Factory and Modular AI PODs enable organizations to transition from experimentation to production smoothly. Despite the potential for $4.4 trillion in corporate profits, only 13% of enterprises feel ready for AI at scale. Learn more about addressing the infrastructure gap in AI. 💡 #EnterpriseAI #Cisco #AIInfrastructure #DataSecurity #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you ready for some football? Cisco Triples NFL Franchise and Stadium Partnerships Ahead of 2025-2026 Season</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7197/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7197/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is expanding its role in the NFL by tripling its partnerships with franchises and stadiums for the upcoming 2025-2026 season. New additions include the Arizona Cardinals, Buffalo Bills, Carolina Panthers, Chicago Bears, Las Vegas Raiders, and Miami Dolphins. This growth highlights Cisco&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing advanced technology solutions for fan engagement and security. With a focus on high-density wireless networks and cyber threat protection, Cisco aims to enhance the overall&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Cisco’s front lines with AI-powered Email Threat Defense and Splunk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7198/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7198/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is enhancing email security with a layered approach using AI and Splunk. 💻✉️ Facing over 326 million emails quarterly, Cisco recognized the need to defend against phishing and malware while improving user productivity. The FBI reported a staggering rise in email cyberattacks, highlighting the urgency for robust security measures. By integrating Cisco Email Threat Defense with Splunk’s analytics, Cisco aims to provide comprehensive protection against evolving threats. #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living My Childhood Dream — Thanks to Cisco’s Time2Give Benefit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7199/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7199/</guid>
      <description>Rana K., a Technical Consulting Engineer at Cisco, shares her inspiring journey of fulfilling a childhood dream through the company&amp;rsquo;s Time2Give benefit. 🌍✨ This initiative allows employees to dedicate 80 hours annually to volunteer for causes they care about. Rana, originally from Egypt and now living in Poland, has embraced this opportunity to teach and give back globally. She reflects on the connections she&amp;rsquo;s made, highlighting that cultural differences have not hindered her ability to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fragmented SSE Is a Risk You Can’t Afford</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7200/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7200/</guid>
      <description>Fragmented security solutions can create significant risks. Many organizations rely on multiple vendors for their security needs, leading to complex systems that may leave gaps in protection. Cisco Secure Access addresses this issue by providing a unified architecture. This ensures consistent policy enforcement regardless of where users connect from, enhancing overall security. No more silos or inconsistent access experiences! #Cybersecurity #Cisco #SecureAccess #SSE #DataProtection 🔐🌐💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Views from an Insider on the CCNP Automation Certification Track: ENAUTO 2.0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7201/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7201/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are coming to the CCNP Automation Certification Track with the ENAUTO 2.0 exam, effective February 3, 2026. Quinn Snyder shares insights from his experience as part of the team that developed the exam. The goal was to create a valuable certification for learners focused on enterprise automation. Stay tuned for the detailed exam topics that reflect extensive discussions and expert input. #CCNP #Automation #Cisco #Certification #ENAUTO2.0</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Bolsters Security for Government With New FedRAMP Authorizations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6333/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6333/</guid>
      <description>Cisco has announced three new FedRAMP-authorized cloud security solutions designed for federal, state, and local agencies. These solutions respond to the growing need for secure, adaptable systems in complex digital environments. The new offerings include Cisco Secure Access for Government, Cisco Security Cloud Control for Government, and Cisco Multicloud Defense for Government. These tools aim to enhance security while supporting compliance and zero trust initiatives. As government agencies&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging technology to transform homeless services</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6330/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6330/</guid>
      <description>Cisco and Destination: Home have partnered to address homelessness in Santa Clara County since 2018. Their initiative focuses on developing supportive housing while leveraging technology to improve access to vital resources for those experiencing homelessness. A recent assessment evaluated the technology needs of the supportive housing system in the area. 🌐🏠🤝 #Homelessness #TechnologyForGood #SupportiveHousing #SantaClara #CommunitySupport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reimagine Your Data Center With Cisco Nexus Hyperfabric on Black Belt Academy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6294/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6294/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data center professionals! Cisco Nexus HyperFabric, co-developed with NVIDIA, offers scalable AI data center solutions. This cloud-managed network fabric is designed to simplify the management of infrastructure and software. 🌐 Partners can now access enablement resources on Cisco Black Belt Academy, covering everything from solution overviews to deployment guidance. Learn how to leverage Nexus HyperFabric for diverse use cases and enhance your offerings in the evolving AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The power of ten — and the power of Purpose</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5283/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5283/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco empowers employees through the Time2Give program, offering ten days off to volunteer and $10,000 in matching donations. In FY25, 81% of employees participated, contributing over 566,000 volunteer hours. This initiative not only supports communities but also enhances employee retention and recognition. Learn more about our impact and future goals for FY26! 🌍🤝 #Cisco #CorporateResponsibility #Volunteerism #CommunityImpact #EmployeeEngagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Scalable E-Commerce Platform at Cisco: From DevNet to Company-Wide Impact</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5284/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5284/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco&amp;rsquo;s DevNet initiative has transformed into a scalable e-commerce framework that benefits the entire company. Over two years, the team navigated complex legal and security processes to onboard payment vendors like Stripe and VeriFone, ensuring compliance with international regulations. 🌍 This groundwork allows Cisco Learning to easily integrate new payment solutions, showcasing the importance of strategic planning for future needs. #Cisco #Ecommerce #DevNet #BusinessGrowth #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrangling the Wild West of MCP Servers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5285/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 23:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5285/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to build your own Model Context Protocol (MCP) server? In a recent article, Kareem Iskander explains how to leverage your existing APIs using OpenAPI specs. This approach allows you to create an AI-powered gateway for your product with minimal effort. Just a few lines of Python and a FastMCP wrapper can transform your APIs into role-based AI tools without the need for custom definitions. #MCPServer #OpenAPI #AI #APIs #TechTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Findings Report From the SOC at RSAC™ 2025 Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5286/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5286/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Exciting updates from the RSAC™ 2025 Conference! 🚨 The Findings Report from the Security Operations Center reveals key insights into network security. Cisco and Endace monitored the Moscone Center&amp;rsquo;s wireless network, showcasing how an open network operates. The SOC utilized advanced tools, including the EndaceProbe packet capture platform and Cisco Security Cloud, to enhance security measures. Learn more about these innovations and watch the session replay! #RSAC2025 #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading the Future of IoT Mobility: Cisco Wins Frost &amp; Sullivan Award Two Years Running</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5287/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5287/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Cisco has been awarded Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan’s 2025 Global Company of the Year for Mobile IoT Platforms, marking a second consecutive win. This honor reflects the trust of customers and partners in Cisco&amp;rsquo;s innovative solutions for IoT mobility. The Cisco Mobility Services Platform serves as a comprehensive resource for enterprise mobility, supporting advanced technologies like 5G and NB-IoT. Thank you to our partners and customers for your collaboration and trust! Together, we are&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling the Future of Work Together</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5288/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5288/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco is redefining the future of work with innovative office transformations globally. From New York to London, these spaces highlight what hybrid work can be with cutting-edge technology. Partners like Softcat in London are leading the way, creating immersive experiences that showcase Cisco&amp;rsquo;s capabilities. 🌍 With over 70 partner offices demonstrating these advancements, Cisco has launched a Collaboration Partner Workspace Catalog to connect teams with hands-on Cisco technology demos&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco and KDDI Partner to Deliver Japan’s First Fully Managed SASE Solution</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5289/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5289/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco and KDDI have announced Japan&amp;rsquo;s first fully managed SASE solution, enhancing secure access for businesses adapting to digital changes. This partnership aims to simplify SASE adoption, providing integrated and scalable solutions for secure connectivity. Service providers like KDDI are essential in navigating this transition, leveraging Cisco’s expertise to ensure streamlined operations and robust security. #Cisco #KDDI #SASE #Cybersecurity #CloudSolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleash the Power of Storage Networking for Mainframe Environments with Cisco MDS 9000 Series</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5290/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5290/</guid>
      <description>🌐 As enterprises increasingly rely on mainframes, efficient storage networking solutions become crucial. The Cisco MDS 9000 Series, now z17 qualified, enhances FICON support and is designed for modern mainframe environments. This series promises exceptional reliability and performance, handling today&amp;rsquo;s growing data demands. 📊 With mainframes like IBM&amp;rsquo;s z17 at the forefront of AI integration, the need for robust SANs is more important than ever. #StorageNetworking #CiscoMDS9000 #Mainframe&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure and Modernize your Roadways with Cisco</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5291/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5291/</guid>
      <description>🚦 Modernizing roadways is essential for enhancing safety and efficiency. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s networking solutions are at the forefront of Intelligent Transportation Systems (ITS), enabling real-time data and connectivity. Join us at ITS World Congress 2025 in Atlanta (Aug 24-28) at Booth #1741 to explore our innovations in traffic management and public safety. Discover how our secure solutions can improve communication through digital signage and support a connected roadway network. #Cisco #ITS2025&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
