<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cisco-Developer-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/cisco-developer-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cisco-Developer-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:34:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/cisco-developer-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Validated Design for Panasonic: A Blueprint for IP Media Success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7779/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7779/</guid>
      <description>Cisco and Panasonic have collaborated to create a Cisco Validated Design (CVD) aimed at enhancing IP infrastructure for media broadcasters. This design ensures reliable, scalable support for high-resolution video formats like UHD/4K and beyond. The CVD is rigorously tested for interoperability, providing a trusted blueprint for organizations. It helps accelerate deployments while minimizing risk, ensuring all components work seamlessly together for high-quality live production. This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the New Nexus Dashboard for Simplifying Data Center Operations in the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7780/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7780/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data center operations! Nexus Dashboard 4.1 is now available, offering complete lifecycle management for multiple data center networks through a single interface. This solution simplifies provisioning and enhances visibility while providing diagnostics and automation. It supports various environments, including NX-OS, ACI, AI fabrics, and more. The dashboard also enables VXLAN EVPN automation on Cisco Catalyst switches. #DataCenter #NexusDashboard #AI #NetworkManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the New Nexus Dashboard for Simplifying Data Center Operations in the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7817/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7817/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news in data center management! The Nexus Dashboard 4.1 is now available for unified lifecycle management of multiple data center networks. This single interface streamlines provisioning and enhances visibility, making it easier for teams to manage diverse environments. It supports various network fabrics, including NX-OS and ACI, while offering robust automation and diagnostics. This advancement aims to simplify operations in an increasingly AI-driven landscape. #DataCenter&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The data catalyst: Blended finance paving the way for climate AI solutions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7754/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7754/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The Cisco Foundation highlights the role of blended finance in addressing the data-to-scale gap for climate AI solutions. AI can significantly impact climate innovation, but it requires access to diverse, quality data, which is often costly. Cisco recently hosted an AI + Climate Innovation Lab, uniting over 100 experts to explore data needs in various climate sectors. Together, these efforts aim to enhance climate tech funding and innovation. 💡📊 #ClimateAI #BlendedFinance #DataForClimate&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The data catalyst: Blended finance paving the way for climate AI solutions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7818/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7818/</guid>
      <description>The Cisco Foundation is exploring blended finance to tackle the data accessibility challenges for climate AI solutions. 🌍 During the AI + Climate Innovation Lab at San Francisco Climate Week 2025, over 100 experts discussed the critical need for diverse and high-quality data across various climate sectors. This initiative aims to bridge the gap in funding and data for climate tech innovation. 💡 #ClimateAI #DataForGood #Sustainability #Innovation #BlendedFinance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing U.S. AI Leadership: Cisco to Skill 1 Million People</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7755/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7755/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is committed to enhancing AI education in the U.S. 🌟 As part of the White House&amp;rsquo;s Pledge to America’s Youth, they plan to train 1 million people in AI and digital skills over the next four years via Learn with Cisco. This initiative highlights the importance of preparing individuals for an AI-driven future. Cisco aims to equip educators with the necessary tools and curricula to effectively teach AI. Together, we can empower a new generation for the evolving job market! 💻🤝 #AI #Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing U.S. AI Leadership: Cisco to Skill 1 Million People</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7819/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:52:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7819/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is committed to advancing AI skills in the U.S. by training 1 million people over the next four years through their Learn with Cisco initiative. This effort aligns with the White House’s Pledge to America’s Youth, focusing on enhancing AI education for all ages. Cisco aims to equip educators and students with the necessary tools and curricula to thrive in an AI-driven economy. #AI #Education #Cisco #DigitalSkills #FutureOfWork 🤖📚🌍</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Some Source of Truth to Your NetAI Agentic Playground</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7735/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7735/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the integration of AI in network engineering, Hank Preston discusses the importance of source-of-truth data for NetAI agents. In his latest article, he reflects on using Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers to enhance AI&amp;rsquo;s ability to interact with network devices. The focus is on providing AI agents access to essential data, boosting their effectiveness. NetBox, an open-source tool, is highlighted for its role in this process, enabling better data accessibility for AI applications&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Some Source of Truth to Your NetAI Agentic Playground</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7820/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:43:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7820/</guid>
      <description>Exploring the integration of AI in network engineering, the article discusses the importance of providing source-of-truth data to AI agents. The author shares insights on using Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers to enhance AI interactions with network devices. A key focus is on leveraging NetBox, an open-source tool, to supply vital data for AI operations. This approach aims to empower AI agents to function like human engineers. #NetAI #AIinNetworking #NetworkAutomation #TechInsights&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Reactive IT Finally Dead?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7719/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7719/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Is Reactive IT Finally Dead? 🚨 In a recent article, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Jason Coleman highlights the challenges of reactive IT. Engineers often spend over 150 hours a year addressing unexpected outages, leading to high costs and operational risks. Cisco is shifting towards AI-powered, preemptive IT solutions to combat these issues, aiming to minimize downtime and enhance efficiency. Learn more about this important shift in IT management! #Cisco #ReactiveIT #AITechnology #ITManagement #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Reactive IT Finally Dead?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7821/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7821/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Is Reactive IT Finally Dead? 🚨 Jason Coleman from Cisco discusses the challenges of reactive IT, where engineers spend over 150 hours annually fixing unexpected outages. This approach leads to high costs and operational risks for businesses. Cisco is shifting towards AI-powered, preemptive IT solutions to enhance network reliability and reduce downtime. Learn more about this important transition in IT management! #ITManagement #Cisco #AI #TechTrends #NetworkReliability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conference Hopping: Training Attendee Scanning Def Con</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7665/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7665/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The Black Hat NOC faces unique challenges, as it operates in a cybersecurity hub where scanning and ethical hacking are expected. Cisco is enhancing security with network-based telemetry to monitor diverse personal devices at the conference. An alert recently identified suspicious activity linked to a training session targeting an external IP associated with Def Con. #Cybersecurity #BlackHat2025 #Cisco #ThreatDetection #EthicalHacking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving Cisco XDR Integration With Third-Party Partners at Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7666/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7666/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is the Official Security Cloud provider at Black Hat USA 2025, showcasing its latest advancements in XDR integration. These integrations enhance the Security Operations Center&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, allowing analysts to quickly investigate Indicators of Compromise (IOC) with a single search. Special thanks to alphaMountain.ai and Pulsedive for their contributions to the event. #Cisco #CyberSecurity #BlackHat2025 #XDR #MalwareAnalysis 🚀🔍💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Secure Firewall: SnortML at Black Hat USA 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7667/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7667/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is the Security Cloud Provider for Black Hat USA 2025! Attendees can participate in hands-on training sessions, using cloud resources for real-time attack simulations. The Cisco team ensures stable connectivity and monitors traffic to protect against unauthorized attacks. SnortML, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s machine learning tool, demonstrated high accuracy, detecting over 100 attacks with only 21 false positives. Stay informed about cybersecurity innovations! 🔒💻 #Cisco #BlackHat2025 #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat Investigation: Attempted Exploitation of Registration Server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7668/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7668/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Black Hat Conference Update 🚨 Recent investigations revealed attempted exploitation of the registration server at the Black Hat conference. Operating within the unique Security and Network Operations Center (NOC) environment, Cisco faces distinct challenges due to the conference&amp;rsquo;s focus on cybersecurity research and ethical hacking. 🔍 The NOC anticipates various activities that might appear suspicious elsewhere. The Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) policy complicates monitoring, emphasizing the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Value of PCAP in Firewall Investigations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7669/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7669/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The article highlights the importance of PCAP (packet capture) in firewall investigations, emphasizing its time-consuming nature. Key steps include finding a suitable platform, executing the capture, and analyzing large files. At Black Hat USA 2025, the ‘Endace PCAP Pivot’ feature enabled easier access to packet-level data, enhancing SOC analyst investigations significantly. 📊🔍 #CyberSecurity #PacketCapture #NetworkAnalysis #BlackHat2025 #SOCInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat Training Attendees Scan Aviation Organization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7670/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7670/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Black Hat conference highlights the unique challenges of cybersecurity, particularly within its Security and Network Operations Center (NOC). Attendees engage in ethical hacking, leading to expected scanning and exploitation activities. This dynamic environment differs from typical corporate settings where such actions are seen as malicious. With a Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) policy, comprehensive monitoring becomes challenging. The focus shifts to robust network-based telemetry for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat USA 2025: 10 Years Protecting Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7671/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7671/</guid>
      <description>Cisco celebrates a decade as the Official Security Cloud Provider for Black Hat USA! 🎉 Partnering with companies like Arista, Corelight, Lumen, and Palo Alto Networks, Cisco helps build and secure the Black Hat network. The NOC focuses on continuous network stability, delivering seamless security and visibility through an embedded SOC. 🔒🌐 #BlackHat2025 #CyberSecurity #Cisco #NetworkOperations #TechPartnerships</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refining SSO at Black Hat USA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7672/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7672/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Black Hat USA 2025! Cisco Duo has enhanced its role as the multifactor authentication (MFA) and single sign-on (SSO) provider for the Network Operations Center (NOC). The successful deployment of Duo Directory has expanded user access, supporting over 100 users at the event. This upgrade improves identity and access management for both users and admins. Key features include streamlined password management and a new Global Enrollment Policy to simplify onboarding. 🔐&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing DNS With Umbrella at Black Hat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7673/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7673/</guid>
      <description>Cisco continues to enhance security at Black Hat, focusing on DNS monitoring since 2017. 🌐 With Umbrella, they route DNS traffic through a centralized service, gaining insights into potential threats like malware and phishing. At Black Hat USA 2025, encrypted DNS requests were blocked to improve visibility into user traffic. 🔍 The team prioritized monitoring the ApateWeb PUP delivery and phishing campaign, noting specific domain patterns. #Cisco #BlackHat2025 #CyberSecurity #DNS #Umbrella</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rebuilding homes and a resilient community in Western North Carolina</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7627/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:44:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7627/</guid>
      <description>In Western North Carolina, Cisco Crisis Response and 40 Communities are aiding in the recovery from Hurricane Helene. 🌪️ After the storm caused severe damage, affecting over 73,000 homes, a coalition was formed to support local leaders and nonprofits in the rebuilding efforts. 🏠 Nearly a year later, the focus remains on restoring homes, especially for low-income families, while ensuring vital services are accessible. 🤝 #CommunitySupport #HurricaneHelene #RebuildingTogether #CrisisResponse&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Start your career in IT with CCST certification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7628/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7628/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to kickstart your IT career? Cisco&amp;rsquo;s CCST certification is your gateway! This entry-level certification offers three paths: IT Support, Networking, and Cybersecurity. With no prerequisites, anyone can start learning and gain essential skills. Join over 1.8 million students who have begun their journey with Cisco Networking Academy! #Cisco #ITCareers #CCST #TechTraining #Cybersecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Velocity Reimagined Wins Triple Industry Recognition!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7611/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7611/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco’s Marketing Velocity Reimagined has achieved a remarkable feat by winning three industry awards in 2025! 🏆 The program received the 2025 Killer Content Award for Channel Partner Marketing, recognizing its innovative digital co-marketing experience that empowers partners with learning and customizable campaigns. 📈 It also earned the 2025 Sammy Award for Sales and Marketing, celebrating the team&amp;rsquo;s efforts to enhance connections with partners and drive growth through data-driven&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Backdoor in TACACS&#43;: Why Full-Session Encryption Matters More Than Ever</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7607/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7607/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Recent cyber threats highlight the risks of weak TACACS+ encryption. Attackers exploited vulnerabilities, targeting network operators to steal credentials and blend in as legitimate admins. By harvesting TACACS+ traffic, they captured sensitive data, allowing unauthorized access and evading detection. Cisco ISE with TLS 1.3 and Duo MFA offers solutions to enhance security and close these backdoors. 🔒🛡️ #Cybersecurity #TACACS #DataProtection #CiscoISE #MFA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Exposed LLM Servers: A Shodan Case Study on Ollama</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7583/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7583/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A recent case study reveals over 1,100 exposed Ollama LLM servers, with 20% hosting open models. This highlights critical security vulnerabilities in LLM deployments. 🔍 The study utilized Shodan to identify these unsecured endpoints, emphasizing the need for stronger security measures. 🛡️ As LLMs become more popular, addressing these gaps is essential for protecting sensitive data. #CyberSecurity #LLM #DataProtection #Ollama #Shodan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safeguard Against Data Breaches in Our Next Cisco U. Capture the Flag Challenge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7487/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 17:39:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7487/</guid>
      <description>🛡️ Learn about SQL Injection (SQLi) attacks and their impact on database security. These attacks exploit application vulnerabilities to manipulate SQL queries, leading to unauthorized access and data theft. Consequences include credential theft, data alteration, and even system access. Stay informed and protect your digital data! 🔐 #CyberSecurity #EthicalHacking #SQLInjection #DataProtection #TechAwareness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uninterrupted Motion: Why Factories Need a New Class of Wireless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7460/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7460/</guid>
      <description>Factories are increasingly using Automated Guided Vehicles (AGVs) and Autonomous Mobile Robots (AMRs) to boost productivity. These vehicles rely on robust wireless networks to operate effectively. 📈🤖 A reliable connection is vital for real-time inspections and safety alerts. Any interruption can lead to missed defects or safety risks, potentially halting production. 🛑⚠️ Companies like BMW and Samsung are already utilizing these technologies to enhance quality assurance and operational safety&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In-Demand Skills for the Modern Network Engineer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7473/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:12:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7473/</guid>
      <description>📈 Staying current in the tech industry is vital for network engineers. Cisco emphasizes the importance of continuous skill development amid rapid technological changes. 🔍 Their research highlights that networking, cybersecurity, and AI skills are essential for future job roles. 🧠 Critical thinking also emerges as a key skill, helping professionals grasp the &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; behind tech advances. #NetworkEngineering #Cybersecurity #AITechnology #SkillDevelopment #Cisco</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Ahead of the HIPAA Security Rule Update With Secure Workload</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7193/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7193/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for Healthcare Organizations! 🚨 On January 6, 2025, the Office of Civil Rights will introduce new cybersecurity requirements as part of the HIPAA Security Rule Update. This will shift the focus from reactive measures to a risk-based approach to enhance cybersecurity in healthcare. The update aims to strengthen the protection of electronic personal health information (ePHI) and address the increasing number of cyberattacks. Organizations must prepare to implement effective&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dedicated Cisco Wireless Certification Track Is on the Horizon</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7194/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7194/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for wireless professionals! Cisco is launching a dedicated Wireless Certification Track in March 2026. This includes the new CCNP Wireless and CCIE Wireless certifications, designed to align with modern wireless technologies. From foundational courses to expert levels, these certifications will equip you with essential skills for managing complex networks. Start your journey with the Understanding Cisco Wireless Foundations training to build the necessary knowledge for WLAN&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Velocity: Comstor’s Powerful Engine Driving Partner Success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7195/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7195/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Marketing Velocity, in partnership with Comstor, fuels business growth through demand generation and co-branded campaigns. This initiative focuses on AI, digital resilience, and future-proof workplaces, showcasing partner success stories to highlight effective strategies. Learn more about driving sustainable growth in the tech industry! 🌐📈 #MarketingVelocity #PartnerSuccess #Cisco #Comstor #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Enterprise AI: Closing the Infrastructure Gap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7196/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7196/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Enterprise AI is evolving beyond just GPU power. Success now relies on integrating data, security, and operations effectively. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Secure AI Factory and Modular AI PODs enable organizations to transition from experimentation to production smoothly. Despite the potential for $4.4 trillion in corporate profits, only 13% of enterprises feel ready for AI at scale. Learn more about addressing the infrastructure gap in AI. 💡 #EnterpriseAI #Cisco #AIInfrastructure #DataSecurity #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you ready for some football? Cisco Triples NFL Franchise and Stadium Partnerships Ahead of 2025-2026 Season</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7197/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7197/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is expanding its role in the NFL by tripling its partnerships with franchises and stadiums for the upcoming 2025-2026 season. New additions include the Arizona Cardinals, Buffalo Bills, Carolina Panthers, Chicago Bears, Las Vegas Raiders, and Miami Dolphins. This growth highlights Cisco&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing advanced technology solutions for fan engagement and security. With a focus on high-density wireless networks and cyber threat protection, Cisco aims to enhance the overall&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Cisco’s front lines with AI-powered Email Threat Defense and Splunk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7198/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7198/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is enhancing email security with a layered approach using AI and Splunk. 💻✉️ Facing over 326 million emails quarterly, Cisco recognized the need to defend against phishing and malware while improving user productivity. The FBI reported a staggering rise in email cyberattacks, highlighting the urgency for robust security measures. By integrating Cisco Email Threat Defense with Splunk’s analytics, Cisco aims to provide comprehensive protection against evolving threats. #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living My Childhood Dream — Thanks to Cisco’s Time2Give Benefit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7199/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7199/</guid>
      <description>Rana K., a Technical Consulting Engineer at Cisco, shares her inspiring journey of fulfilling a childhood dream through the company&amp;rsquo;s Time2Give benefit. 🌍✨ This initiative allows employees to dedicate 80 hours annually to volunteer for causes they care about. Rana, originally from Egypt and now living in Poland, has embraced this opportunity to teach and give back globally. She reflects on the connections she&amp;rsquo;s made, highlighting that cultural differences have not hindered her ability to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fragmented SSE Is a Risk You Can’t Afford</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7200/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7200/</guid>
      <description>Fragmented security solutions can create significant risks. Many organizations rely on multiple vendors for their security needs, leading to complex systems that may leave gaps in protection. Cisco Secure Access addresses this issue by providing a unified architecture. This ensures consistent policy enforcement regardless of where users connect from, enhancing overall security. No more silos or inconsistent access experiences! #Cybersecurity #Cisco #SecureAccess #SSE #DataProtection 🔐🌐💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Views from an Insider on the CCNP Automation Certification Track: ENAUTO 2.0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7201/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7201/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are coming to the CCNP Automation Certification Track with the ENAUTO 2.0 exam, effective February 3, 2026. Quinn Snyder shares insights from his experience as part of the team that developed the exam. The goal was to create a valuable certification for learners focused on enterprise automation. Stay tuned for the detailed exam topics that reflect extensive discussions and expert input. #CCNP #Automation #Cisco #Certification #ENAUTO2.0</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Bolsters Security for Government With New FedRAMP Authorizations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6333/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6333/</guid>
      <description>Cisco has announced three new FedRAMP-authorized cloud security solutions designed for federal, state, and local agencies. These solutions respond to the growing need for secure, adaptable systems in complex digital environments. The new offerings include Cisco Secure Access for Government, Cisco Security Cloud Control for Government, and Cisco Multicloud Defense for Government. These tools aim to enhance security while supporting compliance and zero trust initiatives. As government agencies&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging technology to transform homeless services</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6330/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6330/</guid>
      <description>Cisco and Destination: Home have partnered to address homelessness in Santa Clara County since 2018. Their initiative focuses on developing supportive housing while leveraging technology to improve access to vital resources for those experiencing homelessness. A recent assessment evaluated the technology needs of the supportive housing system in the area. 🌐🏠🤝 #Homelessness #TechnologyForGood #SupportiveHousing #SantaClara #CommunitySupport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reimagine Your Data Center With Cisco Nexus Hyperfabric on Black Belt Academy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6294/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6294/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data center professionals! Cisco Nexus HyperFabric, co-developed with NVIDIA, offers scalable AI data center solutions. This cloud-managed network fabric is designed to simplify the management of infrastructure and software. 🌐 Partners can now access enablement resources on Cisco Black Belt Academy, covering everything from solution overviews to deployment guidance. Learn how to leverage Nexus HyperFabric for diverse use cases and enhance your offerings in the evolving AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The power of ten — and the power of Purpose</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5283/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5283/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco empowers employees through the Time2Give program, offering ten days off to volunteer and $10,000 in matching donations. In FY25, 81% of employees participated, contributing over 566,000 volunteer hours. This initiative not only supports communities but also enhances employee retention and recognition. Learn more about our impact and future goals for FY26! 🌍🤝 #Cisco #CorporateResponsibility #Volunteerism #CommunityImpact #EmployeeEngagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Scalable E-Commerce Platform at Cisco: From DevNet to Company-Wide Impact</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5284/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5284/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco&amp;rsquo;s DevNet initiative has transformed into a scalable e-commerce framework that benefits the entire company. Over two years, the team navigated complex legal and security processes to onboard payment vendors like Stripe and VeriFone, ensuring compliance with international regulations. 🌍 This groundwork allows Cisco Learning to easily integrate new payment solutions, showcasing the importance of strategic planning for future needs. #Cisco #Ecommerce #DevNet #BusinessGrowth #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrangling the Wild West of MCP Servers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5285/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 23:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5285/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to build your own Model Context Protocol (MCP) server? In a recent article, Kareem Iskander explains how to leverage your existing APIs using OpenAPI specs. This approach allows you to create an AI-powered gateway for your product with minimal effort. Just a few lines of Python and a FastMCP wrapper can transform your APIs into role-based AI tools without the need for custom definitions. #MCPServer #OpenAPI #AI #APIs #TechTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Findings Report From the SOC at RSAC™ 2025 Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5286/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5286/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Exciting updates from the RSAC™ 2025 Conference! 🚨 The Findings Report from the Security Operations Center reveals key insights into network security. Cisco and Endace monitored the Moscone Center&amp;rsquo;s wireless network, showcasing how an open network operates. The SOC utilized advanced tools, including the EndaceProbe packet capture platform and Cisco Security Cloud, to enhance security measures. Learn more about these innovations and watch the session replay! #RSAC2025 #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading the Future of IoT Mobility: Cisco Wins Frost &amp; Sullivan Award Two Years Running</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5287/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5287/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Cisco has been awarded Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan’s 2025 Global Company of the Year for Mobile IoT Platforms, marking a second consecutive win. This honor reflects the trust of customers and partners in Cisco&amp;rsquo;s innovative solutions for IoT mobility. The Cisco Mobility Services Platform serves as a comprehensive resource for enterprise mobility, supporting advanced technologies like 5G and NB-IoT. Thank you to our partners and customers for your collaboration and trust! Together, we are&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling the Future of Work Together</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5288/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5288/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco is redefining the future of work with innovative office transformations globally. From New York to London, these spaces highlight what hybrid work can be with cutting-edge technology. Partners like Softcat in London are leading the way, creating immersive experiences that showcase Cisco&amp;rsquo;s capabilities. 🌍 With over 70 partner offices demonstrating these advancements, Cisco has launched a Collaboration Partner Workspace Catalog to connect teams with hands-on Cisco technology demos&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco and KDDI Partner to Deliver Japan’s First Fully Managed SASE Solution</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5289/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5289/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco and KDDI have announced Japan&amp;rsquo;s first fully managed SASE solution, enhancing secure access for businesses adapting to digital changes. This partnership aims to simplify SASE adoption, providing integrated and scalable solutions for secure connectivity. Service providers like KDDI are essential in navigating this transition, leveraging Cisco’s expertise to ensure streamlined operations and robust security. #Cisco #KDDI #SASE #Cybersecurity #CloudSolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleash the Power of Storage Networking for Mainframe Environments with Cisco MDS 9000 Series</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5290/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5290/</guid>
      <description>🌐 As enterprises increasingly rely on mainframes, efficient storage networking solutions become crucial. The Cisco MDS 9000 Series, now z17 qualified, enhances FICON support and is designed for modern mainframe environments. This series promises exceptional reliability and performance, handling today&amp;rsquo;s growing data demands. 📊 With mainframes like IBM&amp;rsquo;s z17 at the forefront of AI integration, the need for robust SANs is more important than ever. #StorageNetworking #CiscoMDS9000 #Mainframe&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure and Modernize your Roadways with Cisco</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5291/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5291/</guid>
      <description>🚦 Modernizing roadways is essential for enhancing safety and efficiency. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s networking solutions are at the forefront of Intelligent Transportation Systems (ITS), enabling real-time data and connectivity. Join us at ITS World Congress 2025 in Atlanta (Aug 24-28) at Booth #1741 to explore our innovations in traffic management and public safety. Discover how our secure solutions can improve communication through digital signage and support a connected roadway network. #Cisco #ITS2025&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
