<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/aws-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:42:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/aws-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup:  Amazon Bedrock, AWS Outposts, Amazon ECS Managed Instances, AWS Builder ID, and more (October 6, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10458/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10458/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from AWS last week! Anthropic&amp;rsquo;s Claude Sonnet 4.5 is now available in Amazon Q CLI and Kiro, enhancing developer productivity significantly. A recent workshop highlighted its potential, allowing a new feature to be added in just one day! Also, AWS Outposts now supports Dell and HPE storage integration, streamlining data residency and migration processes. Lastly, Amazon ECS Managed Instances are here, simplifying container management and improving performance. Join us at AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Amazon ECS Managed Instances for containerized applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10289/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10289/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon has introduced Amazon ECS Managed Instances, a new compute option for containerized applications. This service allows developers to harness the full capabilities of Amazon EC2 while minimizing infrastructure management tasks. It combines the simplicity of serverless with the flexibility of self-managed EC2 instances. AWS handles provisioning, scaling, and security, enabling teams to focus on application development. Explore the new options in the AWS Management Console to optimize&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing AWS Outposts third-party storage integration with Dell and HPE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10275/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10275/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AWS Outposts users! AWS has integrated Dell PowerStore and HPE Alletra MP B10000 systems, allowing seamless use of on-premises storage with AWS services. This enhancement aids in maintaining data residency while transitioning workloads. Organizations can now utilize AWS tools to manage their storage easily. This builds on previous milestones, expanding options for customers. Learn more about the improved integration capabilities! #AWS #CloudComputing #DataStorage #Dell #HPE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Claude Sonnet 4.5 in Amazon Bedrock: Anthropic’s most intelligent model, best for coding and complex agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10230/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10230/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Amazon Web Services! Claude Sonnet 4.5 is now available in Amazon Bedrock. This advanced model enhances coding and agent capabilities, improving tool handling, memory management, and context processing. Developers can now access a managed service that ensures data security while enabling complex software project execution across various industries, including cybersecurity, finance, and research. Explore the powerful features of Sonnet 4.5 and transform your workflows!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon S3, Amazon Bedrock AgentCore, AWS X-Ray and more (September 29, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10220/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10220/</guid>
      <description>AWS re:Invent is just around the corner, happening from December 1-5 in Las Vegas! 🎉 Secure your tickets for an inside look at our latest innovations. If you can&amp;rsquo;t attend, stay updated via the AWS News Blog. Recent highlights include updates to Amazon S3, with new features like bulk target selection, conditional deletes, and enhanced malware protection. 🚀 Additionally, Amazon Bedrock AgentCore has improved enterprise integration with new connectivity options. Stay tuned for more updates! #AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate AI agent development with the Nova Act IDE extension</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9952/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 16:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9952/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing the Nova Act extension for IDEs! This new tool enables developers to create browser automation agents using natural language without leaving their preferred environment. Key features include Builder Mode for modular script development, integrated testing, and seamless API integration. It supports IDEs like Visual Studio Code, Kiro, and Cursor. Begin by installing the extension and obtaining your API key to start building. #NovaAct #AIdevelopment #BrowserAutomation #IDETools&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Q Developer, AWS Step Functions, AWS Cloud Club Captain deadline, and more (September 22, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9886/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 16:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9886/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This week&amp;rsquo;s AWS Roundup highlights key developments from a recent trip to New Zealand, where several events showcased local tech talent. 🌍 A new feature in Amazon Q CLI, called tangent mode, allows users to maintain focus while exploring side topics. It&amp;rsquo;s currently in experimental mode. 📈 Notable launches include: - New models in Amazon Bedrock for enhanced text and image tasks. - Expansion of VPC Reachability Analyzer to seven new regions for better network diagnostics. - Remote MCP server&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen models are now available in Amazon Bedrock</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9807/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9807/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon Bedrock has launched Qwen 3 foundation models, enhancing its model offerings for users. These models, available in a fully managed, serverless environment, include both mixture-of-experts (MoE) and dense architectures, catering to various applications such as code generation and business automation. Notable models include Qwen3-Coder-480B, optimized for coding tasks, and the dense Qwen3-32B, ideal for real-time environments. Learn more about how these models can enhance your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek-V3.1 model now available in Amazon Bedrock</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9808/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 21:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9808/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from AWS! DeepSeek-V3.1 is now available in Amazon Bedrock as a fully managed model. This hybrid open weight model offers two modes: a detailed thinking mode for in-depth analysis and a non-thinking mode for quicker responses. DeepSeek-V3.1 shows improved performance over its predecessor, DeepSeek-R1-0528, with significant gains in multi-step reasoning and efficiency. It also supports over 100 languages with near-native proficiency. #AWS #DeepSeek #AmazonBedrock #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS named as a Leader in 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud-Native Application Platforms and Container Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9669/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9669/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has been named a Leader in the 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud-Native Application Platforms for the second consecutive year, ranking highest on &amp;ldquo;Ability to Execute.&amp;rdquo; Additionally, AWS is recognized for its leadership in Container Management for three years, showcasing its strong vision in the cloud space. This recognition highlights AWS&amp;rsquo;s extensive range of services supporting various cloud technologies. #AWS #GartnerMagicQuadrant #CloudComputing #CloudNative #ContainerManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Strands Agents 1M&#43; downloads, Cloud Club Captain, AI Agent Hackathon, and more (September 15, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9660/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9660/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from AWS! Last week, Strands Agents reached over 1 million downloads and gained 3,000+ GitHub Stars since its preview launch in May 2025. This open-source SDK allows users to create multi-agent AI systems quickly. Key improvements include support for A2A protocol and Amazon Bedrock AgentCore. Users can access sample implementations and contribute feedback to enhance the project. Additionally, AWS announced new Mac instances offering better performance for app development&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Amazon EC2 M4 and M4 Pro Mac instances</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9618/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9618/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has launched new EC2 M4 and M4 Pro Mac instances, enhancing performance for iOS/macOS development. These instances, built on Apple M4 Mac mini, feature up to 48GB memory and 2TB storage, making them ideal for complex build processes and multiple iOS simulators. With improved performance—up to 20% better than M2 instances—developers can streamline their workflows and run tests more efficiently. Explore seamless integration with AWS services like CodeBuild and CloudFormation. #AWS #EC2&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate serverless testing with LocalStack integration in VS Code IDE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9564/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9564/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has announced LocalStack integration in the AWS Toolkit for Visual Studio Code, simplifying local testing and debugging of serverless applications. This update enhances the Lambda development experience and allows developers to connect directly to LocalStack endpoints. This eliminates the need for complex setups and multiple tool switches. Getting started is easy—developers can use the LocalStack Free version and follow the guided walkthrough in VS Code for installation and setup. #AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Transform, Amazon Neptune, and more (September 8, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9440/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9440/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting updates in the AWS community! AWS Community Day 2025 is set for September 24 in Utrecht, bringing together over 500 cloud practitioners. The event will feature 25 breakout sessions focused on serverless architectures and container optimization. 📈 Recent AWS announcements include enhancements to AWS Transform, which now analyzes detached storage infrastructure for migration cost comparisons. Additionally, Amazon Bedrock introduces Global Cross-Region inference for Claude Sonnet 4,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Open — AWS Asia Pacific (New Zealand) Region</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7601/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 22:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7601/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has officially launched its first New Zealand Region with three Availability Zones! This new infrastructure allows local organizations to store data and run workloads securely within New Zealand, enhancing performance and reducing latency. The investment of NZD $7.5 billion is projected to boost the GDP by NZD $10.8 billion and create 1,000 jobs annually. Since establishing its presence in 2013, AWS has expanded its services to improve connectivity and support compliance with multiple&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon EC2, Amazon Q Developer, IPv6 updates, and more (September 1, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7588/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7588/</guid>
      <description>📅 This week, the AWS Heroes Summit in Seattle highlighted the contributions of the AWS Heroes community. These exceptional individuals share their expertise through content creation, speaking, and open-source projects. 🤝 The summit provided a platform for networking and collaboration, with discussions on AWS roadmaps and direct feedback opportunities to AWS service teams. 🚀 Notable launches included IPv6 support for AWS App Runner, AWS Client VPN, and RDS Data API, enhancing connectivity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New general-purpose Amazon EC2 M8i and M8i Flex instances are now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7497/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7497/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for cloud users! Amazon has launched the M8i and M8i-Flex EC2 instances powered by Intel Xeon processors. These new instances offer up to 15% better price performance and 20% higher performance than previous generations. They&amp;rsquo;re designed for general workloads like web applications, databases, and AI models. M8i instances also provide enhanced network and EBS bandwidth, improving performance across various applications. #AmazonEC2 #CloudComputing #TechUpdates #AWS #IntelXeon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS services scale to new heights for Prime Day 2025: key metrics and milestones</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7254/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7254/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon Prime Day 2025 set new sales records, driven by enhanced AI features and AWS infrastructure. Prime members enjoyed billions in savings, utilizing tools like Alexa+ and AI Shopping Guides for a seamless shopping experience. Key AWS metrics include 1.7 trillion Lambda invocations and a 160% increase in robot commands, showcasing massive scalability. #AmazonPrimeDay #AWS #AIShopping #Ecommerce #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Aurora 10th anniversary, Amazon EC2 R8 instances, Amazon Bedrock and more (August 25, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6537/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6537/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting week in AWS! Amazon Aurora celebrates 10 years of innovation, revolutionizing database technology with features like serverless capabilities and generative AI support. 🎉 New AWS launches include customizable dashboards in Billing and Cost Management, and enhanced access to OpenAI models through Amazon Bedrock. Check out the latest advancements! 🚀 #AWS #AmazonAurora #CloudComputing #DatabaseInnovation #OpenAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best performance and fastest memory with the new Amazon EC2 R8i and R8i-flex instances</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5167/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5167/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon has launched the new R8i and R8i-flex instances, optimized for memory and powered by Intel Xeon processors. These instances offer 15% better price performance, 20% higher performance, and 2.5 times more memory throughput than previous generations. Ideal for memory-intensive workloads like SQL databases and real-time analytics, R8i instances scale up to 96xlarge with impressive capabilities for various applications. Check it out! 💻🔍 #AmazonEC2 #CloudComputing #IntelXeon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Single GPU P5 instances, Advanced Go Driver, Amazon SageMaker HyperPod and more (August 18, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5168/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5168/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from AWS this week! The upcoming BeSA (Become a Solutions Architect) cohort starts on September 6, offering free mentoring to enhance cloud careers. Learn more on the BeSA website. New launches include: - &lt;strong&gt;Amazon EC2 Single GPU P5 instances&lt;/strong&gt; for cost-effective ML and HPC. - &lt;strong&gt;AWS Advanced Go Driver&lt;/strong&gt; for improved database performance. - Enhanced &lt;strong&gt;Cilium support&lt;/strong&gt; for Amazon EKS Hybrid Nodes. For AI enthusiasts, &lt;strong&gt;Amazon SageMaker HyperPod&lt;/strong&gt; now supports advanced features&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS named as a Leader in 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Strategic Cloud Platform Services for 15 years in a row</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5169/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5169/</guid>
      <description>🎉 AWS has been named a Leader in the 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Strategic Cloud Platform Services for the 15th year in a row! Gartner recognized AWS for its strong “Ability to Execute,” highlighting its commitment to delivering extensive capabilities, security, and performance for critical applications. AWS boasts the largest global cloud community, custom silicon designs, and a robust network of integration partners, all contributing to successful cloud adoption. Explore the AWS Builder&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating 10 years of Amazon Aurora innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5170/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5170/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Celebrating 10 years of Amazon Aurora! Join us for a livestream event on August 21, 2025, marking a decade of innovation in database technology. Amazon Aurora revolutionized the industry with its unique architecture, offering high performance and 99.99% availability at a fraction of the cost. Key milestones include the launch in 2015, the introduction of serverless capabilities in 2018, and ongoing enhancements focused on security, scalability, and cost management. #AmazonAurora&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet our newest AWS Heroes — August 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4965/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4965/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! We proudly introduce the latest cohort of AWS Heroes for August 2025. These individuals are recognized for their outstanding contributions to the AWS community. 🌍 From AI and machine learning to serverless architectures, they bring diverse expertise and a strong commitment to knowledge sharing. Join us in welcoming Kristine Armiyants, Nadia Reyhani, and Raphael Manke, who are shaping the future of cloud computing and inspiring the next generation! 💡 #AWSHeroes #CloudComputing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: OpenAI models, Automated Reasoning checks, Amazon EVS, and more (August 11, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4856/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4856/</guid>
      <description>🌍 AWS Summits in Mexico City and Jakarta brought together the community for learning and networking. 🚀 Key highlights include the availability of OpenAI models on AWS, which excel in coding and analysis. 🛠️ The new Amazon Elastic VMware Service allows running VMware environments in Amazon VPC. 🔍 Automated Reasoning checks are now available to validate content accuracy from AI models. 📈 Additional updates include expanded Amazon SQS message sizes and AWS Lambda support for GitHub Actions. #AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimize AI hallucinations and deliver up to 99% verification accuracy with Automated Reasoning checks: Now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4149/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4149/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI developers! Amazon has launched Automated Reasoning checks, a new feature in Amazon Bedrock Guardrails. This tool offers up to 99% verification accuracy to minimize AI hallucinations and ensure data accuracy. Key features include support for large documents, simplified policy validation, and automated scenario generation. This will enhance the reliability of AI-generated content. Learn how to create policies using this tool to maintain strict adherence to rules in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI open weight models now available on AWS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4102/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4102/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s open weight models are now available on AWS through Amazon Bedrock and Amazon SageMaker JumpStart. These models, gpt-oss-120b and gpt-oss-20b, are designed for text generation and reasoning tasks, providing flexibility and control over your projects. With a 128K context window and adjustable reasoning levels, they offer enhanced capabilities for coding, scientific analysis, and more. Explore and innovate with ease in a seamless environment! #OpenAI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Amazon Elastic VMware Service for running VMware Cloud Foundation on AWS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2486/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2486/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for organizations looking to migrate VMware workloads to the cloud! AWS has launched the Amazon Elastic VMware Service (Amazon EVS), which allows users to run VMware Cloud Foundation environments directly within Amazon VPCs. This service simplifies migration while maintaining existing tools and practices. With Amazon EVS, you can deploy fully functional environments in just a few hours, ensuring minimal disruption and full control over your cloud resources. 🌥️ Key features&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon DocumentDB, AWS Lambda, Amazon EC2, and more (August 4, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2487/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2487/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This week, AWS announced several key updates across its services. 🔹 Amazon DocumentDB Serverless is now live, providing a fully managed MongoDB API-compatible database. 🔹 The Amazon Q Developer CLI allows for custom agent creation to streamline specialized tasks. 🔹 Amazon Bedrock now supports DOC/DOCX files and H.265 video files for enhanced data processing. 🔹 AWS Lambda increases response streaming payload size to 200 MB, improving performance. For the full details, check the article! #AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Amazon Application Recovery Controller Region switch: A multi-Region application recovery service</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2488/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2488/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing the Amazon Application Recovery Controller (ARC) Region switch! This feature allows organizations to efficiently plan and execute failover operations between AWS Regions. It automates workflows and continuously validates recovery processes, enhancing confidence in your Region failover strategy. With ARC Region switch, you can create detailed recovery plans for seamless transitions, ensuring your critical applications remain resilient during operational events. Learn more about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon DocumentDB Serverless is now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2489/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2489/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Amazon DocumentDB Serverless is now available. This new configuration automatically adjusts compute and memory based on your application&amp;rsquo;s needs, leading to potential cost savings of up to 90% compared to peak provisioning. It supports the same MongoDB compatible APIs and offers seamless scaling without data migration. Key benefits include handling variable workloads, managing multi-tenant environments, and balancing mixed-use workloads efficiently. For steady&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
