<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AWS-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/aws-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in AWS-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 02:17:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/aws-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top announcements of AWS re:Invent 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13141/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 02:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13141/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS re:Invent 2025 has unveiled significant innovations across various domains! Key highlights include: 📊 &lt;strong&gt;Analytics&lt;/strong&gt;: AWS Clean Rooms enables privacy-preserving dataset generation for ML training. ⚙️ &lt;strong&gt;Compute&lt;/strong&gt;: AWS Lambda Managed Instances combine serverless simplicity with EC2 flexibility. ☁️ &lt;strong&gt;Containers&lt;/strong&gt;: Amazon EKS enhances Kubernetes development with managed capabilities. 🔒 &lt;strong&gt;Security&lt;/strong&gt;: IAM Policy Autopilot simplifies policy creation with AI assistance. For ongoing updates,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Amazon Route 53 Global Resolver for secure anycast DNS resolution (preview)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13142/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 01:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13142/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon has launched the Route 53 Global Resolver, enhancing DNS resolution for hybrid environments. This service simplifies management by resolving both public and private domains globally, reducing operational complexity and costs. It offers built-in security features, including DNS traffic filtering and encrypted queries. With support for various protocols and integrated security controls, network administrators can streamline operations while maintaining compliance. Learn more about this&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Clean Rooms launches privacy-enhancing synthetic dataset generation for ML model training</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13143/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 01:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13143/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from AWS Clean Rooms! They have launched a new feature for generating privacy-enhancing synthetic datasets. This allows organizations to train machine learning models on sensitive collaborative data without compromising individual privacy. By preserving statistical patterns, this technology addresses the challenges of using granular data while ensuring compliance with privacy regulations. Organizations can now control privacy parameters and gain insights into the quality of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Partner Central now available in AWS Management Console</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13144/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 01:55:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13144/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AWS customers! AWS Partner Central is now integrated into the AWS Management Console. This change simplifies the transition from customer to Partner, allowing easy access to solutions, opportunities, and AWS Marketplace listings—all in one place. The new console experience enables existing customers to explore partnership benefits without needing separate logins. You can manage your infrastructure and AWS Marketplace business together, streamlining workflows for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AWS Lambda Managed Instances: Serverless simplicity with EC2 flexibility</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13145/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 01:55:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13145/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has introduced Lambda Managed Instances, allowing users to run Lambda functions on EC2 while enjoying serverless simplicity. This new capability enables access to specialized hardware and cost optimizations without the typical infrastructure management burden. AWS manages instance lifecycle, OS patching, and scaling. Lambda Managed Instances also support multiple requests per environment, leading to reduced compute consumption and potential savings of up to 72% through EC2 pricing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify IAM policy creation with IAM Policy Autopilot, a new open source MCP server for builders</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13146/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 01:55:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13146/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing IAM Policy Autopilot, an open-source tool designed to streamline your AWS development! This new Model Context Protocol (MCP) server analyzes your application code to generate accurate IAM policies, integrating seamlessly with AI coding assistants like Kiro and Claude Code. With IAM Policy Autopilot, you can quickly create valid policies, reducing time spent on permission management. It stays updated with the latest AWS services, ensuring you have the necessary permissions to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Amazon EKS Capabilities for workload orchestration and cloud resource management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13147/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 01:55:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13147/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon has announced new capabilities for Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS) to improve workload orchestration and cloud resource management. These fully managed solutions, including Argo CD, AWS Controllers for Kubernetes, and Kube Resource Orchestrator, simplify Kubernetes development by eliminating the need for infrastructure maintenance. With AWS handling scaling and updates, developers can focus on building applications without worrying about underlying components. #AmazonEKS #Kubernetes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Route 53 launches Accelerated recovery for managing public DNS records</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13072/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 16:21:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13072/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon Route 53 has introduced Accelerated Recovery for public DNS records, enhancing business continuity with a 60-minute recovery time objective (RTO) during service disruptions in the US East (N. Virginia) Region. This feature allows customers to make critical DNS changes and provision infrastructure even during outages, improving resilience for essential applications. Designed for industries like banking and SaaS, it meets business continuity and regulatory needs without altering&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: How to join AWS re:Invent 2025, plus Kiro GA, and lots of launches (Nov 24, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:58:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13018/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting updates from AWS! Join us next week for AWS re:Invent from Dec. 1-5, 2025, in Las Vegas. Whether attending in person or tuning in via livestream, be ready for the latest AWS news and insights. Check the agenda and session catalog before you arrive! Kiro, the AI coding tool, is now generally available with new features, including property-based testing and centralized management for enterprise teams. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss other recent launches, including Amazon EC2 P6-B300 instances and new&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New one-click onboarding and notebooks with a built-in AI agent in Amazon SageMaker Unified Studio</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-22-12967/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 01:23:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-22-12967/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon SageMaker Unified Studio has launched new features for easier access to analytics and AI. One-click onboarding allows users to start projects seamlessly, utilizing existing AWS data permissions. You can now launch SageMaker directly from various AWS services, enhancing workflow efficiency. The serverless notebook, equipped with a built-in AI agent, supports multiple languages, making it a versatile tool for data professionals. Explore the new capabilities and streamline your data&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build production-ready applications without infrastructure complexity using Amazon ECS Express Mode</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12964/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 21:34:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12964/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon ECS Express Mode is here to simplify containerized application deployment! This new feature allows developers to launch scalable applications with just one command. It automates infrastructure setup, including load balancing and networking, letting you focus on building your app. To get started, visit the Amazon ECS console and streamline your deployment process today! 🌐💻 #AmazonECS #ContainerDeployment #CloudComputing #AWS #DevOps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing VPC encryption controls: Enforce encryption in transit within and across VPCs in a Region</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12946/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:23:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12946/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has introduced VPC encryption controls to help organizations ensure encryption in transit for all traffic within and across VPCs. This new capability simplifies compliance with regulations like HIPAA, PCI DSS, and FedRAMP by offering automated monitoring and enforcement modes. With these controls, users can audit encryption status and manage resources effectively, reducing operational complexity in cloud environments. 🔒 Learn more about how VPC encryption controls can enhance your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing attribute-based access control for Amazon S3 general purpose buckets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12926/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 01:02:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12926/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has launched Attribute-Based Access Control (ABAC) for S3 general purpose buckets! This feature allows administrators to manage access permissions automatically using tag-based policies. This means no more constant updates to IAM policies as teams grow and change. ABAC simplifies permissions management by granting access based on tags related to projects, teams, or data classification. To get started, enable ABAC in the S3 console or via the AWS CLI. #AWS #S3 #CloudComputing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify access to external services using AWS IAM Outbound Identity Federation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12876/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 23:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12876/</guid>
      <description>AWS IAM has introduced outbound identity federation, allowing developers to authenticate AWS workloads with external services using short-lived JSON Web Tokens (JWTs). This eliminates the need for long-term credentials like API keys, reducing security risks. With this feature, IAM roles and users can obtain cryptographically signed JWTs that verify their AWS identity. External services can validate these tokens to enable secure access. To get started, enable outbound identity federation in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate workflow development with enhanced local testing in AWS Step Functions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12868/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 22:13:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12868/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for AWS Step Functions! The enhanced TestState API now supports local testing with new features including mocking support, comprehensive validation, and the ability to test individual states. This allows for automated test suites on your development machine without needing AWS deployment or IAM permissions. Key highlights: - &lt;strong&gt;Mocking Support&lt;/strong&gt;: Test state logic without invoking services. - &lt;strong&gt;Support for All State Types&lt;/strong&gt;: Validate control flow across your entire workflow&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamlined multi-tenant application development with tenant isolation mode in AWS Lambda</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12856/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:12:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12856/</guid>
      <description>AWS Lambda has launched a new tenant isolation mode, enhancing multi-tenant application security. This feature allows separate execution environments for each tenant within a single function, simplifying resource management. This mode meets strict security requirements for SaaS platforms, ensuring tenant-specific code runs in isolated environments without the complexity of managing multiple functions. To enable tenant isolation, select the option during function creation in the AWS Lambda&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New business metadata features in Amazon SageMaker Catalog to improve discoverability across organizations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12857/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:09:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12857/</guid>
      <description>📊 Exciting updates in Amazon SageMaker Catalog enhance data management! The new features include column-level metadata forms and enforced glossary requirements. These tools will help organizations improve data classification, discoverability, and governance. Users can now create custom metadata forms for individual columns, allowing for better documentation and business context. Additionally, metadata enforcement rules ensure standardized vocabulary for asset publishing, enhancing compliance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Control Tower introduces a Controls Dedicated experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12858/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12858/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS Control Tower has launched a new Controls Dedicated experience! This feature allows users to access AWS managed controls without needing a full landing zone setup, streamlining governance for established multi-account environments. Now, customers can enhance their governance stance quickly and flexibly, making it easier to adopt AWS Control Tower. Learn more about how to get started with this new setup! 🌐 #AWS #CloudComputing #Governance #AWSControlTower #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New AWS Billing Transfer for centrally managing AWS billing and costs across multiple organizations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12859/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12859/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has introduced Billing Transfer, a new feature for managing billing across multiple organizations centrally. This tool allows billing administrators to transfer payment responsibilities while keeping individual security and governance intact. It simplifies invoice collection and payment processing within multi-organization environments. The feature is particularly beneficial for AWS Partners reselling services, enhancing efficiency and scalability in billing operations. To get started,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor network performance and traffic across your EKS clusters with Container Network Observability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12860/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:05:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12860/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon EKS has launched Container Network Observability, enhancing visibility into Kubernetes workload traffic. This new feature helps teams monitor and troubleshoot microservices more effectively, addressing the complexities of network performance in scaling environments. With tools like service maps and performance metrics, organizations can gain deeper insights into network behavior. To enable, simply navigate to your EKS cluster settings and activate the feature. #AmazonEKS #Kubernetes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Amazon Bedrock service tiers help you match AI workload performance with cost</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12795/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12795/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon Bedrock has launched three new service tiers: Priority, Standard, and Flex. These options help businesses optimize AI workload costs while ensuring the performance needed for different applications. - &lt;strong&gt;Priority&lt;/strong&gt;: For mission-critical tasks requiring fast response times. - &lt;strong&gt;Standard&lt;/strong&gt;: Ideal for everyday AI tasks with consistent performance. - &lt;strong&gt;Flex&lt;/strong&gt;: Cost-effective for workloads that can tolerate longer processing times. Learn more about selecting the right tier for your needs!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate large-scale AI applications with the new Amazon EC2 P6-B300 instances</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12796/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 22:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12796/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon has launched EC2 P6-B300 instances, featuring NVIDIA Blackwell Ultra GPUs. These instances offer 2x networking bandwidth and 1.5x GPU memory compared to previous models, making them ideal for large-scale AI applications. They support advanced techniques like Mixture of Experts and are well-suited for training trillion-parameter models across distributed GPU clusters. 🌐 Key features include 6.4Tbps EFA networking and 2.1TB GPU memory, enhancing performance and efficiency. #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Lambda, load balancers, Amazon DCV, Amazon Linux 2023, and more (November 17, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12727/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 17:59:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12727/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from AWS! In preparation for AWS re:Invent, three new talks will cover Apple Silicon optimization with EC2 Mac, and AI development in Swift. 🎉 Welcome to the new AWS Heroes: Dimple, Rola, and Vivek! The GenAI Loft is now open in Tel Aviv, offering tailored sessions for startups and developers until November 19. 🔧 Key launches include AWS Lambda now supporting Rust and Java 25, along with a new Provisioned Mode for SQS event source mapping. #AWS #CloudComputing #Serverless&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Lambda enhances event processing with provisioned mode for SQS event-source mapping</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12178/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 17:45:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12178/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS Lambda has introduced a new provisioned mode for Amazon SQS Event Source Mapping. This feature allows for dedicated polling resources, offering 3x faster scaling and 16x higher concurrency. It helps manage traffic spikes and maintain low latency in event processing. Enterprises can now configure minimum and maximum event pollers, ensuring consistent performance during peak usage. 🌐 This enhancement is designed for businesses needing reliable, real-time event processing. #AWS #Lambda&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AWS IoT Core Device Location integration with Amazon Sidewalk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12136/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:09:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12136/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for IoT developers! AWS IoT Core now integrates with Amazon Sidewalk, allowing devices to resolve location data without GPS. This enhances asset tracking while reducing costs and power consumption. Devices can leverage BLE, Wi-Fi, and GNSS info to report location efficiently, extending battery life and simplifying development. Amazon Sidewalk enhances connectivity for a variety of applications, benefiting communities across the U.S. 🌍 #AWSIoT #AmazonSidewalk #IoT&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Our Final AWS Heroes of 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12137/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 20:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12137/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news as we approach AWS re:Invent! We&amp;rsquo;re celebrating three remarkable AWS Heroes: Dimple Vaghela, Rola Dali, and Vivek Velso. Each has made significant contributions to the cloud community through their unique journeys and commitment to knowledge sharing. Dimple leads AWS User Groups in India, empowering women in tech and rural communities. Rola, an expert in AI and data, mentors women and students in Montreal. Vivek specializes in generative AI, sharing his extensive knowledge&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure EKS clusters with the new support for Amazon EKS in AWS Backup</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 21:30:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12138/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Kubernetes users! AWS Backup now supports Amazon EKS, simplifying backup and restoration of your Kubernetes clusters. This integration provides a centralized solution for securing both cluster configurations and application data without the need for custom scripts. 🛡️ Now, you can easily manage backups and recoveries alongside other AWS services, enhancing data protection and compliance. This includes options for creating new EKS clusters during restores. 🔄 Learn more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: OpenAI partnership, Jane Goodall Institute research archive, and more (November 10, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12139/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:38:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12139/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Excitement builds for AWS re:Invent 2025, happening December 1-5 in Las Vegas! With registration still open, attendees can look forward to keynotes, breakout sessions, and networking opportunities. 🤝 AWS and OpenAI have announced a $38 billion partnership to optimize AI workloads using AWS infrastructure. This includes access to advanced GPU resources for enhanced performance. 📚 Additionally, AWS is investing $1 million to digitize the Jane Goodall Institute’s 65 years of primate research&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AWS Capabilities by Region for easier Regional planning and faster global deployments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11968/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11968/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/feed/&#34;&gt;AWS Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/introducing-aws-capabilities-by-region-for-easier-regional-planning-and-faster-global-deployments/&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Project Rainier online, Amazon Nova, Amazon Bedrock, and more (November 3, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11669/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11669/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Last week at AWS Shenzhen Community Day, Jeff Barr highlighted the global experimentation in generative AI and encouraged local developers to innovate. 👩‍💻 Attendees engaged in discussions on model grounding and applications, showcasing Kiro-themed demos and AI IoT projects. 🌐 Project Rainier, a powerful AI supercomputer, is now operational, utilizing nearly 500,000 Trainium2 chips for advanced model training. 🔍 Key launches include Amazon Nova&amp;rsquo;s new web retrieval tools and enhancements in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build more accurate AI applications with Amazon Nova Web Grounding</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11389/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 23:59:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11389/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from AWS! Amazon has launched &lt;strong&gt;Web Grounding&lt;/strong&gt;, a new tool for Nova models on Amazon Bedrock. This feature automatically retrieves current, cited information, helping to enhance accuracy and reduce AI hallucinations in applications. Web Grounding is ideal for developers needing well-cited, factual responses in applications like chat assistants and content generation tools. It simplifies the process by managing information retrieval, allowing developers to focus on building&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Nova Multimodal Embeddings: State-of-the-art embedding model for agentic RAG and semantic search</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11352/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 15:12:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11352/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Amazon Nova Multimodal Embeddings! This new model in Amazon Bedrock is the first to support text, documents, images, video, and audio through one unified system. It enables efficient cross-modal retrieval and semantic search with leading accuracy. This innovation helps organizations unlock insights from diverse unstructured data formats. 📊 Nova offers a context length of up to 8K tokens and supports 200 languages, along with synchronous and asynchronous API inputs. Explore how&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS RTB Fabric, AWS Customer Carbon Footprint Tool, AWS Secret-West Region, and more (October 27, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11318/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:37:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11318/</guid>
      <description>🚨 This week, AWS faced service disruptions in the North Virginia region affecting DynamoDB and others due to a DNS issue. The problem is now resolved, and lessons learned will enhance service reliability. ✨ Exciting updates include the launch of AWS RTB Fabric, a managed service for real-time bidding, and an enhanced Customer Carbon Footprint Tool now tracking Scope 3 emissions. 🌐 Additionally, the new AWS Secret-West Region supports mission-critical workloads with improved security and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AWS RTB Fabric for real-time advertising technology workloads</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11187/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 08:32:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11187/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in AdTech! AWS has launched RTB Fabric, a fully managed service for real-time bidding (RTB) advertising workloads. This service enables efficient connections between AdTech companies and partners like Amazon Ads and GumGum. With single-digit millisecond performance and up to 80% lower networking costs, RTB Fabric eliminates the need for colocated infrastructure. It supports containerized applications and enhances transaction efficiency through dedicated modules. This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customer Carbon Footprint Tool Expands: Additional emissions categories including Scope 3 are now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11165/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 17:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11165/</guid>
      <description>🌍 AWS has enhanced its Customer Carbon Footprint Tool (CCFT) to include Scope 3 emissions, providing customers a broader view of their carbon impact. Now, users can track emissions from fuel-related activities, IT hardware, buildings, and transportation via the AWS Billing console. The tool supports sustainability efforts by delivering updated Scope 1 and 2 data. This update aims to give a complete picture of carbon emissions to help organizations in their environmental initiatives. 📊💡&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Kiro waitlist, EBS Volume Clones, EC2 Capacity Manager, and more (October 20, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11081/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11081/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from the tech world! The global tech community is wrapping up the year with events like the Amazon Q Developer coding challenges in South Africa. The first event in Johannesburg was a success, with more to come in Durban and Cape Town. Key launches include: - &lt;strong&gt;Kiro&lt;/strong&gt;: Open to all developers now, with over 100,000 on the waitlist. - &lt;strong&gt;EC2 Capacity Manager&lt;/strong&gt;: A centralized tool for managing capacity across multiple accounts and regions. - &lt;strong&gt;EBS Volume Clones&lt;/strong&gt;: Create&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monitor, analyze, and manage capacity usage from a single interface with Amazon EC2 Capacity Manager</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11004/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 15:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11004/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New from AWS: Amazon EC2 Capacity Manager! This centralized solution allows users to monitor and manage capacity across all AWS accounts and regions from a single interface. It consolidates data, eliminating the need for manual collection and improving efficiency. With hourly updates, users can identify underutilized resources and optimize spending effectively. Key metrics are displayed clearly, enabling informed decisions on rightsizing infrastructure. Explore streamlined capacity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Amazon EBS Volume Clones: Create instant copies of your EBS volumes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10920/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 21:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10920/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has launched Amazon EBS Volume Clones, enabling users to create instant copies of EBS volumes with just one API call. This new feature simplifies the process of duplicating production data for development and testing. Previously, users had to take snapshots and create new volumes, adding operational overhead. Now, Volume Clones provide quick access to copied data with low latency, ideal for setting up test environments. Currently, only encrypted volumes can be cloned. Start creating&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Transfer Family SFTP connectors now support VPC-based connectivity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10915/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 19:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10915/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS Transfer Family SFTP connectors now support VPC-based connectivity! This enhancement allows secure file transfers between Amazon S3 and remote SFTP servers without exposing endpoints to the internet. Organizations can connect to private SFTP servers directly within their VPC environments. Key benefits include improved security, compliance, and performance, with connections configured in minutes. #AWSTransfer #SFTP #VPC #CloudSecurity #FileTransfer</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Quick Suite, Amazon EC2, Amazon EKS, and more (October 13, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10875/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 16:24:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10875/</guid>
      <description>This week marked the inaugural AWS AI in Practice meetup hosted by the AWS User Group UK, focusing on AI-assisted software development and agents. Next week, the excitement continues in Italy with sessions on AI agents and context engineering at Codemotion in Milan and an AWS User Group meetup in Rome. 🇮🇹 Notable recent launches include the Amazon Quick Suite for enhanced AI-driven insights, new EC2 instances powered by AMD and Intel processors, and updates to Amazon EKS supporting Kubernetes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Amazon Quick Suite: your agentic teammate for answering questions and taking action</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10596/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 15:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10596/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon has introduced Quick Suite, an AI-powered workspace designed to enhance data analysis and streamline workflows. This tool integrates research, business intelligence, and automation capabilities, allowing users to gather insights without switching between applications. Quick Suite enables natural language queries, critical information retrieval, and process automation. Key features include: - &lt;strong&gt;Quick Research:&lt;/strong&gt; Combines enterprise knowledge and third-party data for in-depth insights&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New general-purpose Amazon EC2 M8a instances are now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10561/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 19:03:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10561/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Amazon! Amazon EC2 has launched the new M8a instances, powered by 5th Generation AMD EPYC processors. These instances offer up to 30% better performance and 19% improved price performance compared to the previous M7a instances. With enhanced memory bandwidth, networking, and storage capabilities, M8a instances are designed for general-purpose workloads including financial applications, gaming, and real-time analytics. Available in ten sizes and two bare metal options, M8a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing new compute-optimized Amazon EC2 C8i and C8i-flex instances</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10475/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:33:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10475/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has launched new compute-optimized Amazon EC2 C8i and C8i-flex instances. These instances feature custom Intel Xeon 6 processors, offering up to 15% better price-performance and 20% higher performance compared to earlier models. Ideal for compute-intensive tasks, they support workloads like web servers, AI models, and high-performance computing. Explore these powerful instances today! 💻✨ #AWS #EC2 #CloudComputing #TechInnovation #ComputeOptimized</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS IAM Identity Center now supports customer-managed KMS keys for encryption at rest</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10476/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 19:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10476/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS IAM Identity Center now supports customer-managed KMS keys for encryption at rest! You can now use your own AWS KMS keys to encrypt user data and passwords in AWS IAM Identity Center. This enhancement allows organizations in regulated industries to maintain control over their encryption key management for compliance. Customer-managed keys (CMKs) provide full control over the key lifecycle, improving security with granular access controls. Integration with AWS CloudTrail ensures detailed&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup:  Amazon Bedrock, AWS Outposts, Amazon ECS Managed Instances, AWS Builder ID, and more (October 6, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10458/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10458/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from AWS last week! Anthropic&amp;rsquo;s Claude Sonnet 4.5 is now available in Amazon Q CLI and Kiro, enhancing developer productivity significantly. A recent workshop highlighted its potential, allowing a new feature to be added in just one day! Also, AWS Outposts now supports Dell and HPE storage integration, streamlining data residency and migration processes. Lastly, Amazon ECS Managed Instances are here, simplifying container management and improving performance. Join us at AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Amazon ECS Managed Instances for containerized applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10289/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10289/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon has introduced Amazon ECS Managed Instances, a new compute option for containerized applications. This service allows developers to harness the full capabilities of Amazon EC2 while minimizing infrastructure management tasks. It combines the simplicity of serverless with the flexibility of self-managed EC2 instances. AWS handles provisioning, scaling, and security, enabling teams to focus on application development. Explore the new options in the AWS Management Console to optimize&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing AWS Outposts third-party storage integration with Dell and HPE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10275/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:39:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10275/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AWS Outposts users! AWS has integrated Dell PowerStore and HPE Alletra MP B10000 systems, allowing seamless use of on-premises storage with AWS services. This enhancement aids in maintaining data residency while transitioning workloads. Organizations can now utilize AWS tools to manage their storage easily. This builds on previous milestones, expanding options for customers. Learn more about the improved integration capabilities! #AWS #CloudComputing #DataStorage #Dell #HPE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Claude Sonnet 4.5 in Amazon Bedrock: Anthropic’s most intelligent model, best for coding and complex agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10230/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10230/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Amazon Web Services! Claude Sonnet 4.5 is now available in Amazon Bedrock. This advanced model enhances coding and agent capabilities, improving tool handling, memory management, and context processing. Developers can now access a managed service that ensures data security while enabling complex software project execution across various industries, including cybersecurity, finance, and research. Explore the powerful features of Sonnet 4.5 and transform your workflows!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon S3, Amazon Bedrock AgentCore, AWS X-Ray and more (September 29, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10220/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:42:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10220/</guid>
      <description>AWS re:Invent is just around the corner, happening from December 1-5 in Las Vegas! 🎉 Secure your tickets for an inside look at our latest innovations. If you can&amp;rsquo;t attend, stay updated via the AWS News Blog. Recent highlights include updates to Amazon S3, with new features like bulk target selection, conditional deletes, and enhanced malware protection. 🚀 Additionally, Amazon Bedrock AgentCore has improved enterprise integration with new connectivity options. Stay tuned for more updates! #AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate AI agent development with the Nova Act IDE extension</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9952/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 16:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9952/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing the Nova Act extension for IDEs! This new tool enables developers to create browser automation agents using natural language without leaving their preferred environment. Key features include Builder Mode for modular script development, integrated testing, and seamless API integration. It supports IDEs like Visual Studio Code, Kiro, and Cursor. Begin by installing the extension and obtaining your API key to start building. #NovaAct #AIdevelopment #BrowserAutomation #IDETools&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Q Developer, AWS Step Functions, AWS Cloud Club Captain deadline, and more (September 22, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9886/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 16:21:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9886/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This week&amp;rsquo;s AWS Roundup highlights key developments from a recent trip to New Zealand, where several events showcased local tech talent. 🌍 A new feature in Amazon Q CLI, called tangent mode, allows users to maintain focus while exploring side topics. It&amp;rsquo;s currently in experimental mode. 📈 Notable launches include: - New models in Amazon Bedrock for enhanced text and image tasks. - Expansion of VPC Reachability Analyzer to seven new regions for better network diagnostics. - Remote MCP server&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qwen models are now available in Amazon Bedrock</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9807/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 22:02:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9807/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon Bedrock has launched Qwen 3 foundation models, enhancing its model offerings for users. These models, available in a fully managed, serverless environment, include both mixture-of-experts (MoE) and dense architectures, catering to various applications such as code generation and business automation. Notable models include Qwen3-Coder-480B, optimized for coding tasks, and the dense Qwen3-32B, ideal for real-time environments. Learn more about how these models can enhance your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek-V3.1 model now available in Amazon Bedrock</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9808/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 21:49:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9808/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from AWS! DeepSeek-V3.1 is now available in Amazon Bedrock as a fully managed model. This hybrid open weight model offers two modes: a detailed thinking mode for in-depth analysis and a non-thinking mode for quicker responses. DeepSeek-V3.1 shows improved performance over its predecessor, DeepSeek-R1-0528, with significant gains in multi-step reasoning and efficiency. It also supports over 100 languages with near-native proficiency. #AWS #DeepSeek #AmazonBedrock #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS named as a Leader in 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud-Native Application Platforms and Container Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9669/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:53:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9669/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has been named a Leader in the 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Cloud-Native Application Platforms for the second consecutive year, ranking highest on &amp;ldquo;Ability to Execute.&amp;rdquo; Additionally, AWS is recognized for its leadership in Container Management for three years, showcasing its strong vision in the cloud space. This recognition highlights AWS&amp;rsquo;s extensive range of services supporting various cloud technologies. #AWS #GartnerMagicQuadrant #CloudComputing #CloudNative #ContainerManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Strands Agents 1M&#43; downloads, Cloud Club Captain, AI Agent Hackathon, and more (September 15, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9660/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9660/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from AWS! Last week, Strands Agents reached over 1 million downloads and gained 3,000+ GitHub Stars since its preview launch in May 2025. This open-source SDK allows users to create multi-agent AI systems quickly. Key improvements include support for A2A protocol and Amazon Bedrock AgentCore. Users can access sample implementations and contribute feedback to enhance the project. Additionally, AWS announced new Mac instances offering better performance for app development&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Amazon EC2 M4 and M4 Pro Mac instances</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9618/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:30:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9618/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has launched new EC2 M4 and M4 Pro Mac instances, enhancing performance for iOS/macOS development. These instances, built on Apple M4 Mac mini, feature up to 48GB memory and 2TB storage, making them ideal for complex build processes and multiple iOS simulators. With improved performance—up to 20% better than M2 instances—developers can streamline their workflows and run tests more efficiently. Explore seamless integration with AWS services like CodeBuild and CloudFormation. #AWS #EC2&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate serverless testing with LocalStack integration in VS Code IDE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9564/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:06:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9564/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has announced LocalStack integration in the AWS Toolkit for Visual Studio Code, simplifying local testing and debugging of serverless applications. This update enhances the Lambda development experience and allows developers to connect directly to LocalStack endpoints. This eliminates the need for complex setups and multiple tool switches. Getting started is easy—developers can use the LocalStack Free version and follow the guided walkthrough in VS Code for installation and setup. #AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: AWS Transform, Amazon Neptune, and more (September 8, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9440/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 17:20:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9440/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting updates in the AWS community! AWS Community Day 2025 is set for September 24 in Utrecht, bringing together over 500 cloud practitioners. The event will feature 25 breakout sessions focused on serverless architectures and container optimization. 📈 Recent AWS announcements include enhancements to AWS Transform, which now analyzes detached storage infrastructure for migration cost comparisons. Additionally, Amazon Bedrock introduces Global Cross-Region inference for Claude Sonnet 4,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Open — AWS Asia Pacific (New Zealand) Region</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7601/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 22:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7601/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has officially launched its first New Zealand Region with three Availability Zones! This new infrastructure allows local organizations to store data and run workloads securely within New Zealand, enhancing performance and reducing latency. The investment of NZD $7.5 billion is projected to boost the GDP by NZD $10.8 billion and create 1,000 jobs annually. Since establishing its presence in 2013, AWS has expanded its services to improve connectivity and support compliance with multiple&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon EC2, Amazon Q Developer, IPv6 updates, and more (September 1, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7588/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:59:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7588/</guid>
      <description>📅 This week, the AWS Heroes Summit in Seattle highlighted the contributions of the AWS Heroes community. These exceptional individuals share their expertise through content creation, speaking, and open-source projects. 🤝 The summit provided a platform for networking and collaboration, with discussions on AWS roadmaps and direct feedback opportunities to AWS service teams. 🚀 Notable launches included IPv6 support for AWS App Runner, AWS Client VPN, and RDS Data API, enhancing connectivity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New general-purpose Amazon EC2 M8i and M8i Flex instances are now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7497/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7497/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for cloud users! Amazon has launched the M8i and M8i-Flex EC2 instances powered by Intel Xeon processors. These new instances offer up to 15% better price performance and 20% higher performance than previous generations. They&amp;rsquo;re designed for general workloads like web applications, databases, and AI models. M8i instances also provide enhanced network and EBS bandwidth, improving performance across various applications. #AmazonEC2 #CloudComputing #TechUpdates #AWS #IntelXeon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS services scale to new heights for Prime Day 2025: key metrics and milestones</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7254/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7254/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon Prime Day 2025 set new sales records, driven by enhanced AI features and AWS infrastructure. Prime members enjoyed billions in savings, utilizing tools like Alexa+ and AI Shopping Guides for a seamless shopping experience. Key AWS metrics include 1.7 trillion Lambda invocations and a 160% increase in robot commands, showcasing massive scalability. #AmazonPrimeDay #AWS #AIShopping #Ecommerce #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Aurora 10th anniversary, Amazon EC2 R8 instances, Amazon Bedrock and more (August 25, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6537/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6537/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting week in AWS! Amazon Aurora celebrates 10 years of innovation, revolutionizing database technology with features like serverless capabilities and generative AI support. 🎉 New AWS launches include customizable dashboards in Billing and Cost Management, and enhanced access to OpenAI models through Amazon Bedrock. Check out the latest advancements! 🚀 #AWS #AmazonAurora #CloudComputing #DatabaseInnovation #OpenAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best performance and fastest memory with the new Amazon EC2 R8i and R8i-flex instances</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5167/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5167/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon has launched the new R8i and R8i-flex instances, optimized for memory and powered by Intel Xeon processors. These instances offer 15% better price performance, 20% higher performance, and 2.5 times more memory throughput than previous generations. Ideal for memory-intensive workloads like SQL databases and real-time analytics, R8i instances scale up to 96xlarge with impressive capabilities for various applications. Check it out! 💻🔍 #AmazonEC2 #CloudComputing #IntelXeon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Single GPU P5 instances, Advanced Go Driver, Amazon SageMaker HyperPod and more (August 18, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5168/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5168/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from AWS this week! The upcoming BeSA (Become a Solutions Architect) cohort starts on September 6, offering free mentoring to enhance cloud careers. Learn more on the BeSA website. New launches include: - &lt;strong&gt;Amazon EC2 Single GPU P5 instances&lt;/strong&gt; for cost-effective ML and HPC. - &lt;strong&gt;AWS Advanced Go Driver&lt;/strong&gt; for improved database performance. - Enhanced &lt;strong&gt;Cilium support&lt;/strong&gt; for Amazon EKS Hybrid Nodes. For AI enthusiasts, &lt;strong&gt;Amazon SageMaker HyperPod&lt;/strong&gt; now supports advanced features&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS named as a Leader in 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Strategic Cloud Platform Services for 15 years in a row</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5169/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5169/</guid>
      <description>🎉 AWS has been named a Leader in the 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Strategic Cloud Platform Services for the 15th year in a row! Gartner recognized AWS for its strong “Ability to Execute,” highlighting its commitment to delivering extensive capabilities, security, and performance for critical applications. AWS boasts the largest global cloud community, custom silicon designs, and a robust network of integration partners, all contributing to successful cloud adoption. Explore the AWS Builder&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating 10 years of Amazon Aurora innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5170/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5170/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Celebrating 10 years of Amazon Aurora! Join us for a livestream event on August 21, 2025, marking a decade of innovation in database technology. Amazon Aurora revolutionized the industry with its unique architecture, offering high performance and 99.99% availability at a fraction of the cost. Key milestones include the launch in 2015, the introduction of serverless capabilities in 2018, and ongoing enhancements focused on security, scalability, and cost management. #AmazonAurora&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet our newest AWS Heroes — August 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4965/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4965/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! We proudly introduce the latest cohort of AWS Heroes for August 2025. These individuals are recognized for their outstanding contributions to the AWS community. 🌍 From AI and machine learning to serverless architectures, they bring diverse expertise and a strong commitment to knowledge sharing. Join us in welcoming Kristine Armiyants, Nadia Reyhani, and Raphael Manke, who are shaping the future of cloud computing and inspiring the next generation! 💡 #AWSHeroes #CloudComputing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: OpenAI models, Automated Reasoning checks, Amazon EVS, and more (August 11, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4856/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4856/</guid>
      <description>🌍 AWS Summits in Mexico City and Jakarta brought together the community for learning and networking. 🚀 Key highlights include the availability of OpenAI models on AWS, which excel in coding and analysis. 🛠️ The new Amazon Elastic VMware Service allows running VMware environments in Amazon VPC. 🔍 Automated Reasoning checks are now available to validate content accuracy from AI models. 📈 Additional updates include expanded Amazon SQS message sizes and AWS Lambda support for GitHub Actions. #AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimize AI hallucinations and deliver up to 99% verification accuracy with Automated Reasoning checks: Now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4149/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4149/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI developers! Amazon has launched Automated Reasoning checks, a new feature in Amazon Bedrock Guardrails. This tool offers up to 99% verification accuracy to minimize AI hallucinations and ensure data accuracy. Key features include support for large documents, simplified policy validation, and automated scenario generation. This will enhance the reliability of AI-generated content. Learn how to create policies using this tool to maintain strict adherence to rules in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI open weight models now available on AWS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4102/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4102/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s open weight models are now available on AWS through Amazon Bedrock and Amazon SageMaker JumpStart. These models, gpt-oss-120b and gpt-oss-20b, are designed for text generation and reasoning tasks, providing flexibility and control over your projects. With a 128K context window and adjustable reasoning levels, they offer enhanced capabilities for coding, scientific analysis, and more. Explore and innovate with ease in a seamless environment! #OpenAI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Amazon Elastic VMware Service for running VMware Cloud Foundation on AWS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2486/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2486/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for organizations looking to migrate VMware workloads to the cloud! AWS has launched the Amazon Elastic VMware Service (Amazon EVS), which allows users to run VMware Cloud Foundation environments directly within Amazon VPCs. This service simplifies migration while maintaining existing tools and practices. With Amazon EVS, you can deploy fully functional environments in just a few hours, ensuring minimal disruption and full control over your cloud resources. 🌥️ Key features&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon DocumentDB, AWS Lambda, Amazon EC2, and more (August 4, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2487/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2487/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This week, AWS announced several key updates across its services. 🔹 Amazon DocumentDB Serverless is now live, providing a fully managed MongoDB API-compatible database. 🔹 The Amazon Q Developer CLI allows for custom agent creation to streamline specialized tasks. 🔹 Amazon Bedrock now supports DOC/DOCX files and H.265 video files for enhanced data processing. 🔹 AWS Lambda increases response streaming payload size to 200 MB, improving performance. For the full details, check the article! #AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Amazon Application Recovery Controller Region switch: A multi-Region application recovery service</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2488/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2488/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing the Amazon Application Recovery Controller (ARC) Region switch! This feature allows organizations to efficiently plan and execute failover operations between AWS Regions. It automates workflows and continuously validates recovery processes, enhancing confidence in your Region failover strategy. With ARC Region switch, you can create detailed recovery plans for seamless transitions, ensuring your critical applications remain resilient during operational events. Learn more about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon DocumentDB Serverless is now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2489/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2489/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Amazon DocumentDB Serverless is now available. This new configuration automatically adjusts compute and memory based on your application&amp;rsquo;s needs, leading to potential cost savings of up to 90% compared to peak provisioning. It supports the same MongoDB compatible APIs and offers seamless scaling without data migration. Key benefits include handling variable workloads, managing multi-tenant environments, and balancing mixed-use workloads efficiently. For steady&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
