<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CrowdStrike-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/crowdstrike-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CrowdStrike-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/crowdstrike-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Complete Hub Turns MDR Visibility into Action</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9604/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9604/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has launched Falcon Complete Hub, a new feature within Falcon Complete Next-Gen MDR. This unified interface offers security teams crucial insights and prioritized actions to enhance threat response. With cyber threats evolving rapidly, the Hub transforms raw data into actionable guidance, helping organizations react effectively. Stay ahead in the fight against cybercrime! 🔒💻 #CyberSecurity #MDR #CrowdStrike #ThreatResponse #FalconComplete</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September 2025 Patch Tuesday: Two Publicly Disclosed Zero-Days and Eight Critical Vulnerabilities Among 84 CVEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9506/</guid>
      <description>📅 In September 2025, Microsoft released a significant security update addressing 84 vulnerabilities. This includes two publicly disclosed zero-day vulnerabilities and eight critical ones. 🔍 The primary risks involve elevation of privilege (45% of patches), remote code execution (26%), and information disclosure (16%). Many critical vulnerabilities require user interaction to exploit. 🖥️ Microsoft Windows received the majority of the patches, totaling 58, followed by Extended Security Updates&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe, Q3 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7759/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7759/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe for Q3 2025. The company excelled in 16 evaluation criteria, including endpoint detection and threat hunting. This highlights the importance of AI-driven technology and human expertise in today’s complex threat landscape. CrowdStrike Falcon® Complete Next-Gen MDR offers robust AI-accelerated threat detection and response across various platforms. #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe, Q3 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-8087/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-8087/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in The Forrester Wave™ for Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe, Q3 2025. The company excelled in 16 key criteria, including endpoint and identity detection, cloud detection, and threat hunting. This highlights the importance of combining AI technology with human expertise to combat evolving cyber threats. CrowdStrike Falcon® Complete Next-Gen MDR ensures comprehensive protection across various attack surfaces. #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMBER2024: Advancing the Training of Cybersecurity ML Models Against Evasive Malware</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7710/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7710/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news in cybersecurity! CrowdStrike has released EMBER2024, an updated open-source dataset aimed at enhancing machine learning models for malware detection. It features over 3.2 million files across six formats and includes advanced malware samples that can evade antivirus solutions. The dataset&amp;rsquo;s details were shared in a recent academic paper at the KDD-2025 conference. EMBER2024 aims to overcome challenges in public dataset release while promoting research in malware&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure AI at Machine Speed: Defending the Growing Attack Surface</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7658/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7658/</guid>
      <description>As AI integrates into various business functions, it significantly broadens the enterprise attack surface. 📈 Adversaries are increasingly targeting AI tools and their supporting infrastructure, exploiting vulnerabilities in APIs and models. Many organizations struggle with visibility and lack adequate protection for these evolving threats. 🔍 To tackle these challenges, innovative, real-time security solutions tailored for AI are essential. The CrowdStrike Falcon® platform offers insights on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in 2025 IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Incident Response Services</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7435/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7435/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in the 2025 IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Incident Response Services. This acknowledgment highlights their rapid response capabilities, powered by the AI-native CrowdStrike Falcon® platform, and their global 24/7 incident response model. With the rise of AI-driven threats, CrowdStrike combines expertise and technology to effectively counteract these challenges. Their integrated approach ensures organizations can detect and manage incidents swiftly&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike to Acquire Onum to Transform How Data Powers the Agentic SOC</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7436/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7436/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has announced its agreement to acquire Onum, enhancing its Falcon® platform. This acquisition aims to transform how data powers the agentic SOC by leveraging real-time data architecture. 📊 Onum&amp;rsquo;s technology will enable faster, high-fidelity intelligence, addressing the data crisis security teams face today. Legacy SIEMs struggle with overwhelming volumes of data, often leading to costly decisions. 💡 With Onum, CrowdStrike promises to improve processing speed and reduce storage&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in 2025 IDC MarketScape for Exposure Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7437/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7437/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for cybersecurity! CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in the 2025 IDC MarketScape for Exposure Management. This recognition highlights their innovative approach to addressing modern threats, where adversaries use advanced techniques to exploit vulnerabilities. Unlike traditional tools, CrowdStrike Falcon® offers real-time visibility and prioritizes risks based on actual adversary behavior, streamlining response and remediation processes. Learn more about how they are&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MURKY PANDA: A Trusted-Relationship Threat in the Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-7438/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-7438/</guid>
      <description>🚨 MURKY PANDA is a China-nexus adversary targeting various sectors in North America, including government and technology. Since late 2024, they have used trusted-relationship compromises in the cloud, showcasing deep knowledge of cloud environments. Their tactics include exploiting vulnerabilities and deploying malware like CloudedHope. 💻 CrowdStrike has tracked MURKY PANDA&amp;rsquo;s operations, which are driven by intelligence-collection goals, often resulting in the exfiltration of sensitive&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Platform Prevents COOKIE SPIDER’s SHAMOS Delivery on macOS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-7439/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-7439/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The CrowdStrike Falcon® platform has successfully blocked a sophisticated malware campaign by COOKIE SPIDER targeting macOS users. Between June and August 2025, over 300 customer environments were at risk due to the SHAMOS variant of the Atomic macOS Stealer. This malware was distributed through malvertising, tricking users into executing a harmful installation command. The campaign highlighted the use of one-line installation commands, which can bypass security checks, raising concerns&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against SCATTERED SPIDER with Falcon Next-Gen SIEM</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7440/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7440/</guid>
      <description>🚨 SCATTERED SPIDER continues to pose a significant threat, launching attacks on organizations globally since 2022. This adversary uses refined social engineering tactics to compromise sensitive information. 🔍 CrowdStrike&amp;rsquo;s Falcon Next-Gen SIEM offers real-time detection across various domains, enhancing defenses against these evolving threats. It integrates third-party telemetry for improved visibility and tailored protection. 📊 The blog details key phases of SCATTERED SPIDER’s kill chain and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Next-Gen Identity Security Unifies Protection Across All Identities and Domains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7441/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7441/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in identity security! CrowdStrike has launched Falcon Next-Gen Identity Security, a comprehensive solution designed to protect all identities—human, non-human, and AI—across various environments. This new platform unifies critical capabilities, including initial access prevention, privileged access security, and identity threat detection. It addresses the evolving landscape of identity threats as organizations increasingly adopt SaaS applications and AI agents. With Falcon,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>August 2025 Patch Tuesday: One Publicly Disclosed Zero-Day and 13 Critical Vulnerabilities Among 107 CVEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7443/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7443/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Microsoft has released its August 2025 Patch Tuesday updates, addressing 107 vulnerabilities. Among these are one publicly disclosed zero-day and 13 critical vulnerabilities. The most common risk types involve elevation of privilege (39%), remote code execution (33%), and information disclosure (15%). Windows received the largest share of patches with 67 updates. #PatchTuesday #CyberSecurity #MicrosoftUpdates #Vulnerabilities #InfoSec</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named the Only Leader in GigaOm Radar for SaaS Security Posture Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7442/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7442/</guid>
      <description>🌟 CrowdStrike has been named the sole Leader in the 2025 GigaOm Radar Report for SaaS Security Posture Management (SSPM). The report highlights CrowdStrike as the most innovative platform in the field, excelling in protecting identities and SaaS environments. With the rise of SaaS applications, the need for robust security has never been greater. CrowdStrike’s Falcon® platform addresses challenges like identity-based threats and misconfigurations, offering real-time threat detection and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike’s Approach to Better Machine Learning Evaluation Using Strategic Data Splitting</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-7444/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-7444/</guid>
      <description>CrowdStrike is enhancing machine learning evaluation by tackling data leakage, which can lead to inaccurate threat detection in cybersecurity. To combat this, they implement strategic data splitting during model training. This method carefully manages how data is divided, ensuring that similar data points do not skew results, ultimately leading to more reliable detection of new threats. By focusing on this strategy, CrowdStrike aims to improve the performance of their AI-native platform&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
