<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CrowdStrike-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/crowdstrike-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CrowdStrike-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/crowdstrike-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Expands Agentic Security Workforce with New Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-05-11852/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-05-11852/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.crowdstrike.com/blog/feed/&#34;&gt;CrowdStrike Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.crowdstrike.com/en-us/blog/crowdstrike-expands-agentic-security-workforce-with-new-agents/&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike 2025 European Threat Landscape Report: Extortion Rises, Nation-State Activity Intensifies</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11643/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11643/</guid>
      <description>Europe faces a growing threat from eCrime and nation-state activities, as highlighted in the CrowdStrike 2025 European Threat Landscape Report. The report reveals a significant increase in ransomware and extortion attacks, with Europe being the second most-targeted region after North America. Notably, the UK, Germany, Italy, France, and Spain are among the most affected countries. Key sectors like manufacturing and technology are vulnerable, attracting financially motivated adversaries who&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Falcon Achieves 100% Protection and Accuracy in SE Labs Endpoint Protection Evaluation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11460/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11460/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for CrowdStrike! The Falcon platform has achieved 100% Protection and Accuracy in SE Labs’ Endpoint Protection Evaluation. In the recent evaluation, it earned the AAA EPS certification, with no false positives recorded. This highlights its effectiveness in blocking both targeted and general attacks. Additionally, CrowdStrike secured three awards at the 2025 SE Labs Security Awards, showcasing its industry-leading capabilities. 🏆 #CrowdStrike #EndpointSecurity #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named the Leader in 2025 Frost Radar for SaaS Security Posture Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11331/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11331/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! CrowdStrike has been named the Growth and Innovation Leader in the 2025 Frost Radar™ for SaaS Security Posture Management for the second year in a row. This recognition highlights the importance of addressing security gaps in SaaS applications, which are increasingly targeted by threat actors. With CrowdStrike Falcon® Shield, organizations can enhance their visibility and control over both human and non-human identities in a complex SaaS ecosystem. Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan noted an&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Domain User to SYSTEM: Analyzing the NTLM LDAP Authentication Bypass Vulnerability (CVE-2025-54918)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11161/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11161/</guid>
      <description>A critical vulnerability, CVE-2025-54918, was identified in September 2025, impacting Domain Controllers using LDAP or LDAPS services. This flaw allows attackers to escalate privileges from standard domain users to SYSTEM level, threatening entire Active Directory environments. The vulnerability exploits NTLM relay and coerced authentication techniques. Organizations can enhance their security using CrowdStrike solutions to mitigate risks. 🔒⚠️ #Cybersecurity #Vulnerability #ActiveDirectory&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New User Experience Transforms Interaction with the Falcon Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11132/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11132/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from the Falcon platform! The new dynamic user experience, powered by CrowdStrike Enterprise Graph and Charlotte AI, aims to simplify interactions for security teams. As cyber threats evolve, the need for an intuitive interface is crucial. This upgrade offers unified asset visibility, customizable workspaces, and executive-ready reporting, enhancing risk management in hybrid and multi-cloud environments. 🔍 Learn more about how this AI-driven approach can help streamline&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Reality: Business Confidence Is High, Preparedness Is Low</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11109/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11109/</guid>
      <description>The latest CrowdStrike State of Ransomware Survey reveals a concerning gap in business preparedness. While 50% of security leaders feel “very well prepared,” 78% faced ransomware attacks last year. Only 22% recovered within 24 hours, highlighting a false sense of security. As adversaries leverage AI for faster attacks, organizations must innovate their defenses. 89% see AI-powered protection as key to improving security. #Ransomware #CyberSecurity #AI #BusinessPreparedness #DataProtection 🛡️🔒💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike 2025 APJ eCrime Landscape Report: A New Era of Threats Emerges</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11098/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11098/</guid>
      <description>🌐 The CrowdStrike 2025 APJ eCrime Landscape Report reveals significant changes in the Asia Pacific and Japan region&amp;rsquo;s cyber threat landscape. 👥 Chinese-language underground marketplaces are thriving, enabling the sale of stolen data and illicit services. Notable platforms include Chang’an and Huione Guarantee, which have facilitated billions in transactions. 💻 The rise of AI-driven ransomware campaigns is also a growing concern, targeting high-value sectors like manufacturing, technology, and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Falcon Exposure Management’s ExPRT.AI Predicts What Attackers Will Exploit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11049/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11049/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Nearly 40,000 vulnerabilities were disclosed in 2024, leaving security teams overwhelmed. ExPRT.AI, part of CrowdStrike Falcon® Exposure Management, helps prioritize vulnerabilities based on real-time attack behavior, not just static severity scores. This predictive tool uses live adversary signals to identify which vulnerabilities are most likely to be exploited. By leveraging AI and extensive threat intelligence, ExPRT.AI enables faster remediation of critical vulnerabilities&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Defends Against Git Vulnerability CVE-2025-48384</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11021/</guid>
      <description>🚨 CrowdStrike has reported active exploitation of Git vulnerability CVE-2025-48384. This vulnerability affects macOS and Linux systems and can lead to arbitrary code execution via malicious Git repository cloning. 🛡️ The threat actors utilize social engineering tactics to compromise unpatched Git installations. Organizations are advised to prioritize timely software updates and enhance their security strategies. 🔒 Stay vigilant and protect your systems! #Cybersecurity #GitVulnerability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Insight for ChromeOS Adds Automated Response Actions and GovCloud Support</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10979/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10979/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has enhanced ChromeOS security with new automated response actions and expanded GovCloud support. This upgrade allows for rapid containment of compromised devices, ensuring security teams can act quickly to prevent further issues. The native connector provides unified visibility without the need for additional tools. With these advancements, organizations can protect ChromeOS devices as effectively as other endpoints. #CyberSecurity #ChromeOS #CrowdStrike #GovCloud&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How CrowdStrike Stops Living-off-the-Land Attacks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10928/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10928/</guid>
      <description>CrowdStrike is addressing the rising threat of &amp;ldquo;living-off-the-land&amp;rdquo; attacks, where adversaries misuse legitimate tools instead of traditional malware. Their new capability, Anomalous Process Execution (APEX), enhances defense by using AI to identify and stop the abuse of trusted applications like Windows utilities and remote management tools. This shift in tactics has made detection challenging, as these applications are critical for business operations. APEX aims to improve security by&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October 2025 Patch Tuesday: Two Publicly Disclosed, Three Zero-Days, and Eight Critical Vulnerabilities Among 172 CVEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10929/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10929/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Microsoft has issued its October 2025 security update, addressing a total of 172 vulnerabilities. This is the highest monthly total for the year. This update includes two publicly disclosed vulnerabilities, three zero-day vulnerabilities, and eight critical vulnerabilities, along with 159 others of varying severity. The main risk types involve elevation of privilege (80 patches), remote code execution (31), and information disclosure (28). Most patches were for Microsoft Windows (134),&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 End of Support: How to Stay Protected</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10927/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10927/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for Windows 10 Users! 🚨 As of October 14, 2025, Microsoft will end support for non-LTSC releases of Windows 10. This means no more security updates or feature patches, increasing vulnerability to cyber threats. Many enterprises still rely on Windows 10, holding significant market share. Organizations must plan their migration to supported systems to avoid security risks and compliance issues. Stay informed and protect your systems! 💻🔒 #Windows10 #CyberSecurity #EndOfSupport&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Visionary in 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Security Information and Event Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10638/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10638/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! CrowdStrike Falcon® Next-Gen SIEM has been named a Visionary in the 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Security Information and Event Management. In just a year, it is redefining SIEM with AI and real-time data, improving SOC operations significantly. Customers are experiencing 150x faster searches and over 1PB/day of data ingestion. With the recent acquisition of Onum, CrowdStrike is enhancing its capabilities, achieving even faster incident response. #CrowdStrike #SIEM&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Identifies Campaign Targeting Oracle E-Business Suite via Zero-Day Vulnerability (now tracked as CVE-2025-61882)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10480/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10480/</guid>
      <description>🚨 CrowdStrike has identified a mass exploitation campaign targeting Oracle E-Business Suite applications through a zero-day vulnerability, known as CVE-2025-61882. The campaign is believed to involve the threat actor GRACEFUL SPIDER. Initial exploitation began on August 9, 2025, and ongoing investigations may alter this timeline. Recent disclosures of proof-of-concept exploits are likely to motivate other actors to exploit this vulnerability. Stay vigilant! 🔒💻 #CyberSecurity #Oracle&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike’s Fall 2025 Release Defines the Agentic SOC and Secures the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10379/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10379/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has unveiled its Fall 2025 release, introducing the Falcon agentic security platform. This advancement aims to enhance security in the AI era, where speed and efficiency are crucial. The platform enables humans and AI agents to collaborate seamlessly, transforming analysts into orchestrators who manage intelligent agents. Key features include the new CrowdStrike Enterprise Graph, providing an extensive AI-ready data layer, and Charlotte AI AgentWorks, which allows security teams&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Falcon ASPM Secures GenAI Applications and Lessons from Dogfooding</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10308/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10308/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Falcon Application Security Posture Management (ASPM) enhances the security of generative AI applications by providing essential visibility and context to combat advanced threats. As businesses adopt large language models, traditional security tools may fall short. Falcon ASPM helps organizations understand complex attack surfaces, ensuring robust protection for their GenAI applications. Discover how CrowdStrike&amp;rsquo;s innovative approach addresses the unique challenges of agentic AI and keeps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Boosts SOC Detection Content with Correlation Rule Template Discovery Dashboard</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10243/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10243/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has launched the Correlation Rule Template Discovery dashboard in its Falcon Next-Gen SIEM. This new feature helps security teams quickly find and use detection content tailored to their data sources. With over 1,000 correlation rule templates, users can streamline their detection process, ensuring relevance and efficiency. The dashboard simplifies searches and includes curated insights from CrowdStrike, enhancing the user experience. #CrowdStrike #CyberSecurity #SIEM&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Dawn of the Agentic SOC: Reimagining Cybersecurity for the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10156/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10156/</guid>
      <description>At Fal.Con 2025, George Kurtz discussed the urgent need to rethink cybersecurity in the AI era. The fourth industrial revolution is reshaping our approach to security as AI becomes both a tool and a threat. The rise of AI has made cyberattacks more sophisticated and accessible, with malware capable of customizing attacks in real-time. This demands a shift from traditional security operations that can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with the speed of modern threats. Kurtz highlighted the transition from security&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Frost Radar™ Leader in Cloud Workload Protection Platforms</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10110/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10110/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has been named a leader in the 2025 Frost Radar™ for Cloud Workload Protection Platforms. It scored highest on the Innovation Index, being the only solution offering unified, real-time protection across cloud, identity, and endpoint. With increasing cloud threats, CrowdStrike Falcon® Cloud Security employs AI for proactive defense, ensuring robust protection in hybrid environments. #CloudSecurity #Innovation #CyberDefense #CrowdStrike #FrostRadar</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect AI Development with Falcon Cloud Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9890/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9890/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Falcon Cloud Security is crucial for safeguarding AI development. It detects risks in the CI/CD pipeline and tracks AI workloads in production. As AI becomes integral to applications, it also introduces new security challenges. Without proper visibility, organizations may expose sensitive data or deploy vulnerable code. CrowdStrike&amp;rsquo;s solution offers real-time detection and comprehensive model scanning, ensuring robust protection throughout the AI pipeline. #CloudSecurity #AIDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Advances Next-Gen Identity Security with Three Key Innovations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9797/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9797/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike is enhancing identity security with three key innovations! The launch of Falcon Next-Gen Identity Security introduces phishing-resistant MFA, modern privileged access features, and identity-driven case management. These advancements aim to protect against identity-based attacks in hybrid environments. With a focus on reducing risk and improving efficiency, CrowdStrike addresses the complexities of traditional identity management through unified solutions. #IdentitySecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Stops GenAI Data Leaks with Unified Data Protection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9798/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9798/</guid>
      <description>🌐 CrowdStrike is enhancing data security with its latest innovations in Falcon® Data Protection. As GenAI adoption grows, the risk of data leaks increases. The company introduces four key advancements to secure sensitive data across endpoints, cloud, and AI environments. These innovations include improved GenAI data protection, a unified detection suite, AI-powered data classifications, and a new insider risk dashboard. This aims to empower organizations to manage data movement effectively&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Threat AI: Security’s First Agentic Threat Intelligence System</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9755/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9755/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Threat AI: the first agentic threat intelligence system by CrowdStrike! This innovative system uses AI-powered agents to reason across data and hunt for threats, automating complex workflows. It helps security teams respond faster to AI-driven adversary tactics. The launch includes the Malware Analysis Agent and Hunt Agent, designed to streamline malware analysis and enhance threat hunting. Stay ahead of cyber threats with advanced capabilities! 🔍💻 #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Collaborates with AI Leaders to Secure AI Across the Enterprise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9756/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9756/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike is enhancing AI security with new integrations across the enterprise. Their Falcon® platform now offers unified protection for AI models, data, and applications, addressing risks like data poisoning and model theft. Partnerships with industry leaders like AWS, NVIDIA, and Meta ensure comprehensive security at every layer of the AI stack. This approach enables organizations to innovate with confidence while maintaining essential visibility and control. #CyberSecurity #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon for IT Redefines Vulnerability Management with Risk-based Patching</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9754/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9754/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike is transforming vulnerability management with its new Risk-based Patching feature in Falcon for IT. This innovative approach bridges the gap between security and IT teams, allowing organizations to identify and address critical vulnerabilities more effectively. By leveraging AI and a unified console, teams can prioritize patching based on actual risk instead of outdated methods. This helps streamline processes and improve security across all endpoints. Learn more about how this&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Falcon Platform Evolves to Lead the Agentic Security Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9697/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9697/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The CrowdStrike Falcon platform has launched its Fall release, focusing on the Agentic Security Platform designed to utilize agentic AI for cybersecurity. As organizations increasingly rely on AI, security leaders face the challenge of operationalizing it effectively. The Falcon platform aims to provide a robust AI-native foundation for this new era. Key innovations include the Enterprise Graph for real-time data unification and Charlotte AI AgentWorks, a no-code platform for building and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike to Acquire Pangea to Secure Enterprise AI Use and Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9698/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9698/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has announced its intent to acquire Pangea, aiming to enhance security for enterprise AI use and development. This move will pioneer the AI Detection and Response (AIDR) category. 🔒 The partnership will provide full-stack security, addressing risks from shadow AI and sensitive data leaks. 🌐 Together, they will extend the CrowdStrike Falcon® platform with a comprehensive AIDR solution. #CrowdStrike #Pangea #AIsecurity #AIDR #Cybersecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Complete Hub Turns MDR Visibility into Action</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9604/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9604/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has launched Falcon Complete Hub, a new feature within Falcon Complete Next-Gen MDR. This unified interface offers security teams crucial insights and prioritized actions to enhance threat response. With cyber threats evolving rapidly, the Hub transforms raw data into actionable guidance, helping organizations react effectively. Stay ahead in the fight against cybercrime! 🔒💻 #CyberSecurity #MDR #CrowdStrike #ThreatResponse #FalconComplete</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September 2025 Patch Tuesday: Two Publicly Disclosed Zero-Days and Eight Critical Vulnerabilities Among 84 CVEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9506/</guid>
      <description>📅 In September 2025, Microsoft released a significant security update addressing 84 vulnerabilities. This includes two publicly disclosed zero-day vulnerabilities and eight critical ones. 🔍 The primary risks involve elevation of privilege (45% of patches), remote code execution (26%), and information disclosure (16%). Many critical vulnerabilities require user interaction to exploit. 🖥️ Microsoft Windows received the majority of the patches, totaling 58, followed by Extended Security Updates&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe, Q3 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7759/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7759/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe for Q3 2025. The company excelled in 16 evaluation criteria, including endpoint detection and threat hunting. This highlights the importance of AI-driven technology and human expertise in today’s complex threat landscape. CrowdStrike Falcon® Complete Next-Gen MDR offers robust AI-accelerated threat detection and response across various platforms. #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe, Q3 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-8087/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-8087/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in The Forrester Wave™ for Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe, Q3 2025. The company excelled in 16 key criteria, including endpoint and identity detection, cloud detection, and threat hunting. This highlights the importance of combining AI technology with human expertise to combat evolving cyber threats. CrowdStrike Falcon® Complete Next-Gen MDR ensures comprehensive protection across various attack surfaces. #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMBER2024: Advancing the Training of Cybersecurity ML Models Against Evasive Malware</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7710/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7710/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news in cybersecurity! CrowdStrike has released EMBER2024, an updated open-source dataset aimed at enhancing machine learning models for malware detection. It features over 3.2 million files across six formats and includes advanced malware samples that can evade antivirus solutions. The dataset&amp;rsquo;s details were shared in a recent academic paper at the KDD-2025 conference. EMBER2024 aims to overcome challenges in public dataset release while promoting research in malware&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure AI at Machine Speed: Defending the Growing Attack Surface</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7658/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7658/</guid>
      <description>As AI integrates into various business functions, it significantly broadens the enterprise attack surface. 📈 Adversaries are increasingly targeting AI tools and their supporting infrastructure, exploiting vulnerabilities in APIs and models. Many organizations struggle with visibility and lack adequate protection for these evolving threats. 🔍 To tackle these challenges, innovative, real-time security solutions tailored for AI are essential. The CrowdStrike Falcon® platform offers insights on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in 2025 IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Incident Response Services</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7435/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7435/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in the 2025 IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Incident Response Services. This acknowledgment highlights their rapid response capabilities, powered by the AI-native CrowdStrike Falcon® platform, and their global 24/7 incident response model. With the rise of AI-driven threats, CrowdStrike combines expertise and technology to effectively counteract these challenges. Their integrated approach ensures organizations can detect and manage incidents swiftly&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike to Acquire Onum to Transform How Data Powers the Agentic SOC</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7436/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7436/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has announced its agreement to acquire Onum, enhancing its Falcon® platform. This acquisition aims to transform how data powers the agentic SOC by leveraging real-time data architecture. 📊 Onum&amp;rsquo;s technology will enable faster, high-fidelity intelligence, addressing the data crisis security teams face today. Legacy SIEMs struggle with overwhelming volumes of data, often leading to costly decisions. 💡 With Onum, CrowdStrike promises to improve processing speed and reduce storage&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in 2025 IDC MarketScape for Exposure Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7437/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7437/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for cybersecurity! CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in the 2025 IDC MarketScape for Exposure Management. This recognition highlights their innovative approach to addressing modern threats, where adversaries use advanced techniques to exploit vulnerabilities. Unlike traditional tools, CrowdStrike Falcon® offers real-time visibility and prioritizes risks based on actual adversary behavior, streamlining response and remediation processes. Learn more about how they are&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MURKY PANDA: A Trusted-Relationship Threat in the Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-7438/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-7438/</guid>
      <description>🚨 MURKY PANDA is a China-nexus adversary targeting various sectors in North America, including government and technology. Since late 2024, they have used trusted-relationship compromises in the cloud, showcasing deep knowledge of cloud environments. Their tactics include exploiting vulnerabilities and deploying malware like CloudedHope. 💻 CrowdStrike has tracked MURKY PANDA&amp;rsquo;s operations, which are driven by intelligence-collection goals, often resulting in the exfiltration of sensitive&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Platform Prevents COOKIE SPIDER’s SHAMOS Delivery on macOS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-7439/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-7439/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The CrowdStrike Falcon® platform has successfully blocked a sophisticated malware campaign by COOKIE SPIDER targeting macOS users. Between June and August 2025, over 300 customer environments were at risk due to the SHAMOS variant of the Atomic macOS Stealer. This malware was distributed through malvertising, tricking users into executing a harmful installation command. The campaign highlighted the use of one-line installation commands, which can bypass security checks, raising concerns&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against SCATTERED SPIDER with Falcon Next-Gen SIEM</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7440/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7440/</guid>
      <description>🚨 SCATTERED SPIDER continues to pose a significant threat, launching attacks on organizations globally since 2022. This adversary uses refined social engineering tactics to compromise sensitive information. 🔍 CrowdStrike&amp;rsquo;s Falcon Next-Gen SIEM offers real-time detection across various domains, enhancing defenses against these evolving threats. It integrates third-party telemetry for improved visibility and tailored protection. 📊 The blog details key phases of SCATTERED SPIDER’s kill chain and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Next-Gen Identity Security Unifies Protection Across All Identities and Domains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7441/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7441/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in identity security! CrowdStrike has launched Falcon Next-Gen Identity Security, a comprehensive solution designed to protect all identities—human, non-human, and AI—across various environments. This new platform unifies critical capabilities, including initial access prevention, privileged access security, and identity threat detection. It addresses the evolving landscape of identity threats as organizations increasingly adopt SaaS applications and AI agents. With Falcon,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>August 2025 Patch Tuesday: One Publicly Disclosed Zero-Day and 13 Critical Vulnerabilities Among 107 CVEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7443/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7443/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Microsoft has released its August 2025 Patch Tuesday updates, addressing 107 vulnerabilities. Among these are one publicly disclosed zero-day and 13 critical vulnerabilities. The most common risk types involve elevation of privilege (39%), remote code execution (33%), and information disclosure (15%). Windows received the largest share of patches with 67 updates. #PatchTuesday #CyberSecurity #MicrosoftUpdates #Vulnerabilities #InfoSec</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named the Only Leader in GigaOm Radar for SaaS Security Posture Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7442/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7442/</guid>
      <description>🌟 CrowdStrike has been named the sole Leader in the 2025 GigaOm Radar Report for SaaS Security Posture Management (SSPM). The report highlights CrowdStrike as the most innovative platform in the field, excelling in protecting identities and SaaS environments. With the rise of SaaS applications, the need for robust security has never been greater. CrowdStrike’s Falcon® platform addresses challenges like identity-based threats and misconfigurations, offering real-time threat detection and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike’s Approach to Better Machine Learning Evaluation Using Strategic Data Splitting</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-7444/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-7444/</guid>
      <description>CrowdStrike is enhancing machine learning evaluation by tackling data leakage, which can lead to inaccurate threat detection in cybersecurity. To combat this, they implement strategic data splitting during model training. This method carefully manages how data is divided, ensuring that similar data points do not skew results, ultimately leading to more reliable detection of new threats. By focusing on this strategy, CrowdStrike aims to improve the performance of their AI-native platform&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
