<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unreal-Engine-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/unreal-engine-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unreal-Engine-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/unreal-engine-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Fab October Flash Sale is now on!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10942/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10942/</guid>
      <description>🎉 The Fab October Flash Sale is here! Enjoy discounts of up to 70% on thousands of assets. 🛍️ The sale runs from 10 AM ET on October 15 to 5 PM ET on October 19. Don’t miss out on this opportunity to save! Explore the highlights and get ready to shop! #FlashSale #OctoberDeals #Savings #ShopSmart #Discounts</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MILES AND FLOWERS | Award-Winning Animated Short</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10606/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10606/</guid>
      <description>🎬 Exciting news in the animation world! The award-winning short film &amp;ldquo;Miles and Flowers&amp;rdquo; blends drama with humor for an engaging viewing experience. Created entirely in Unreal Engine, the filmmaker worked on this project for two years, focusing on a captivating story. Check it out and experience the unique storytelling! 🌼✨ #Animation #ShortFilm #UnrealEngine #MilesAndFlowers #FilmMaking</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five years, 35 car models: how Unreal Engine is accelerating HMI innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10590/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10590/</guid>
      <description>Unreal Engine is leading the way in automotive Human-Machine Interface (HMI) innovation. 🚗💻 In just five years, over 35 car models have integrated UE HMI, with more than two million vehicles on the road using this technology. The article highlights the significant advancements in creating immersive and design-focused digital cockpits. #AutomotiveInnovation #UnrealEngine #HMIDesign #DigitalCockpit #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NITRO GEN OMEGA: Bringing the art style of “spaghetti anime” to life with UE5</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10589/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10589/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Dive into the world of NITRO GEN OMEGA! Gian Paolo Vernocchi, CEO of DESTINYbit, shares insights on how Unreal Engine 5 (UE5) has transformed their tactical RPG. The game combines turn-based mechanics with the dynamic feel of directing an anime episode. Discover the innovative approach that brings &amp;ldquo;spaghetti anime&amp;rdquo; art style to life! 🌟 #NITROGENOMEGA #GameDevelopment #UE5 #TacticalRPG #AnimeGaming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highlights from the Unreal Fest Stockholm opening session</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10372/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10372/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Unreal Fest Stockholm kicked off with an exciting look at Unreal Engine 5.7, showcasing its latest features. 🔧 Developers working on Fortnite can expect new tools designed to enhance their creative process. 🤖 Additionally, the Epic Developer Assistant has expanded, providing even more support for developers. #UnrealFest #UnrealEngine #GameDevelopment #Fortnite #EpicGames</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UE5 concept game trailer cinematic | SOJOURN</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10336/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 13:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10336/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from the world of game development! The cinematic trailer for “Sojourn” showcases stunning visuals created in Unreal Engine. The creator, with a background in film and TV, shares insights into the challenges faced during this first Unreal project. Stay tuned for more updates on this journey! 🎮✨ #Sojourn #UnrealEngine #GameDevelopment #CinematicTrailer #Animation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rematch reinvents football using Unreal Engine 5</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10217/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10217/</guid>
      <description>Discover how the Paris-based indie team at Sloclap is using Unreal Engine 5 to transform football gaming. ⚽️ Their innovative approach aims to create an immersive experience that captures the true spirit of the sport. 🌟 Stay tuned for more updates on this exciting development! #Gaming #Football #UnrealEngine5 #IndieDev #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September learning content: Gameplay Ability System, MetaHumans, and more</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10216/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10216/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This month, Epic Games offers free courses to enhance your skills! Learn about the Gameplay Ability System, Character Movement Component, and networked physics. Additionally, dive into creating an optimized MetaHuman. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to expand your knowledge! 🎮 #EpicGames #GameDevelopment #MetaHumans #Learning #FreeCourses</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mafia: The Old Country: Making the old feel new with Unreal Engine 5</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10083/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10083/</guid>
      <description>Discover how Hangar 13 is bringing the Mafia franchise to life with Unreal Engine 5. The team focuses on creating an authentic world and characters, enhancing the gaming experience for players. Stay tuned for more updates on this exciting project! 🎮🌍✨ #MafiaGame #UnrealEngine5 #GameDevelopment #Hangar13</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Register now for the 2025 Epic MegaJam</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10107/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10107/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Exciting news for game developers! The 2025 Epic MegaJam is set to take place, marking 10 years of innovation in the industry. Gather your team and prepare for a week filled with creativity and game development. Participants will have the chance to win fantastic prizes from our sponsors. Don’t miss out on this opportunity to showcase your skills! #EpicMegaJam #GameDev #Innovation #Creativity #JoinUs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ravine | Houdini - Unreal Engine Environment | Unreal Engine 5.7</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10115/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 03:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10115/</guid>
      <description>🌄 Exciting news in game development! The article discusses &amp;ldquo;Ravine,&amp;rdquo; an expansion of the earlier project &amp;ldquo;Clover.&amp;rdquo; This new environment utilizes Houdini-created assets, which were exported to Unreal Engine 5.7. The terrain design features ultra high polygon counts, enhancing the visual quality and detail of the scene. #GameDevelopment #UnrealEngine #Houdini #3DArt #EnvironmentDesign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Engine 5.7 Preview</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9940/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:06:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9940/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Unreal Engine 5.7 Preview has officially launched! You can download it now from the Epic Games Launcher, GitHub, or for Linux. This update introduces new tools and enhancements aimed at improving workflows and expanding creative possibilities. Explore the latest features and elevate your projects! #UnrealEngine #GameDevelopment #EpicGames</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaHuman 5.7 Preview Released!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9941/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 12:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9941/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! The Unreal Engine 5.7 Preview is now live, featuring updates to both MetaHuman Creator and MetaHuman Animator. You can download the new version through the Epic Games Launcher, GitHub, and Linux. Explore the enhancements and take your creative projects to the next level! #UnrealEngine #MetaHuman #GameDevelopment #EpicGames #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beneath Mount Fuji: Springtime Promenade</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9803/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 07:15:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9803/</guid>
      <description>🌸 Exciting news! A new real-time environment titled &amp;ldquo;Beneath Mount Fuji: Springtime Promenade&amp;rdquo; has been created using Unreal Engine 5. The scene beautifully showcases traditional Japanese architecture alongside the vibrant cherry blossom season. Experience the serene blend of culture and nature in this immersive environment! 🌳🏯 #UnrealEngine5 #VirtualReality #JapaneseCulture #CherryBlossoms #GameDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fortnite Developers Will Soon Be Able to Sell In-Game Items</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9804/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9804/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Fortnite developers! Starting in December, they will have the ability to sell in-game items directly from their islands. This opens up new revenue opportunities beyond the current engagement payouts from item shop sales. Stay tuned for more updates on this development! #Fortnite #GameDev #InGameSales #GamingCommunity #RevenueGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing the urban Paris of La Haine to the stage with UE5</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9724/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9724/</guid>
      <description>Silent Partners Studio has utilized 3D scans of Parisian housing projects to recreate the aesthetic of the film La Haine in Unreal Engine. This innovative approach aims to deliver an immersive theater experience that is both technically impressive and emotionally impactful. Explore how technology can enhance storytelling in the arts! 🎭🏙️ #LaHaine #Theater #UnrealEngine #ImmersiveArt #SilentPartnersStudio</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fab in Launcher is now available!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9654/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9654/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Exciting news for creators! Fab in Launcher is now available, allowing users to access Fab&amp;rsquo;s diverse asset library directly within the Epic Games Launcher. With just one click, you can send assets to your preferred DCC tools and easily batch download content. Discover more about this new feature! #FabInLauncher #EpicGames #GameDevelopment #3DAssets #CreativeTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Fellowship: Games—explore the making of six awesome games in three weeks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9613/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9613/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Unreal Fellowship: Games 2025 featured an immersive bootcamp for game developers, focusing on skill enhancement and collaboration. 🌟 Participants created six unique games in just three weeks, showcasing their creativity and technical abilities. Discover the inspiring stories behind these innovative projects! #UnrealFellowship #GameDevelopment #IndieGames #GamingCommunity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sports Broadcast | Motion Design Sample is now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9555/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9555/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Exciting news for motion designers and livestreamers! A new sample project is now available, featuring a fully designed and animated setup. This resource supports various broadcast artist workflows, making it ideal for anyone interested in motion graphics. Explore the possibilities and enhance your skills with this comprehensive tool! #MotionDesign #BroadcastArt #Animation #Livestreaming #Graphics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Built with UE5, Borderlands 4 delivers ambitious scale with World Partition, Nanite, Lumen, and more</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9474/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9474/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements are coming to the Borderlands series with Borderlands 4! Gearbox Software highlights how Unreal Engine 5 features like World Partition and Nanite enhance gameplay. These technologies allow for larger, more detailed environments, improving player experience. Stay tuned for more updates on this ambitious installment! 🎮✨ #Borderlands4 #GameDevelopment #UE5 #GearboxSoftware #GamingNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fan-Made PREDATOR Cinematic: IT ALL ENDS | Unreal Engine 5.6 | MetaHuman</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9537/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 16:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9537/</guid>
      <description>🎬 Exciting news for fans of the Predator franchise! A talented group has released a fan-made cinematic titled &amp;ldquo;PREDATOR: IT ALL ENDS,&amp;rdquo; crafted entirely using Unreal Engine 5.6. This project showcases impressive visuals and storytelling. The creators shared insights about the production process, revealing they completed a total of 108 shots. Check it out and immerse yourself in this indie creation! #Predator #FanFilm #UnrealEngine #Cinematic #IndieFilm</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siili Auto: creating a great HMI experience with Unreal Engine</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7785/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7785/</guid>
      <description>Siili Auto has selected Unreal Engine as their primary tool for designing, developing, and testing Human-Machine Interfaces (HMI). This choice is driven by Unreal Engine&amp;rsquo;s impressive visuals and efficiency. Additionally, it allows Siili Auto to craft unique, branded experiences for the automotive industry. 🚗✨🔧 #SiiliAuto #UnrealEngine #HMI #AutomotiveTech #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New report: explore how real-time tools could transform fashion</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7677/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7677/</guid>
      <description>Discover the latest insights from The Interline’s new report on the evolution of 3D technology in fashion. Supported by Epic Games, this report highlights the advancements made and outlines future possibilities in the industry. Download the report to learn more! 📈👗✨ #FashionTech #3DModeling #Innovation #TheInterline #EpicGames</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cronos: The New Dawn is set to deliver pulse-pounding survival horror using UE5</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7620/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7620/</guid>
      <description>🕹️ Exciting developments in survival horror! The Bloober Team shared insights on &amp;ldquo;Cronos: The New Dawn,&amp;rdquo; highlighting their use of Unreal Engine 5 features like Lumen and Nanite. These technologies enhance combat mechanics and create a chilling atmosphere for players. Stay tuned for more updates on this intense gaming experience! 🎮🌌 #CronosTheNewDawn #SurvivalHorror #UnrealEngine5 #GameDevelopment #BlooberTeam</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fab September Flash Sale is now on!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7619/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7619/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The Fab September Flash Sale is here! 🚨 Enjoy discounts of up to 70% on thousands of assets. 🛍️ The sale kicks off at 10 AM ET on September 2 and will continue until 5 PM ET on September 5. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on these amazing deals! #FabSeptemberSale #Discounts #FlashSale #Savings #ShopNow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaHuman for Houdini Release</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7276/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7276/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for creators! A new version of MetaHuman for Houdini is now available for download from Fab. This update allows users to bring MetaHuman characters to life in SideFX Houdini. This release enhances the integration between Unreal Engine and Houdini, streamlining workflows for developers. #MetaHuman #Houdini #GameDevelopment #3DArt #UnrealEngine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of Riot’s VALORANT is built on UE5</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7215/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7215/</guid>
      <description>Riot Games is upgrading VALORANT from Unreal Engine 4 to Unreal Engine 5. Marcus Reid explains that this shift aims to enhance gameplay and graphics, ensuring the game remains competitive and appealing. The transition is part of Riot&amp;rsquo;s strategy to secure VALORANT&amp;rsquo;s future in the gaming landscape. 🎮✨ #VALORANT #RiotGames #GamingNews #UE5 #GameDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>August learning content: MetaHuman, MetaSounds, and more.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6339/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6339/</guid>
      <description>🚀 August brings new learning opportunities! This month’s free content includes tutorials on MetaHuman, Blueprint-controlled particle effects, and MetaSounds. Perfect for those looking to enhance their skills in these areas. Explore these resources and elevate your knowledge today! #Learning #MetaHuman #MetaSounds #SkillDevelopment #Tutorials</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Watch the premiere of the award-winning animated short NEW IDEA here!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6338/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6338/</guid>
      <description>🎥 Discover &amp;ldquo;NEW IDEA,&amp;rdquo; the award-winning animated short that has captured 26 accolades! This film showcases the inspiring journey of its creator, who faced challenges before finding success. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the chance to watch this imaginative piece and appreciate its unique story! #NewIdea #Animation #FilmAwards #ShortFilm #Inspiration ✨</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forest in a (Water) Bottle | Virtual Aquarium</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-24-7507/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 23:33:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-24-7507/</guid>
      <description>🌳💧 Exploring the potential of Unreal Engine 5, this article discusses a test-bench scene featuring a virtual aquarium. The focus was on experimenting with new features during UE5&amp;rsquo;s Early Access phase. This project highlights the innovative possibilities for developers in creating immersive environments. #UnrealEngine5 #GameDevelopment #VirtualReality #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONGIL: STAR DIVE brings monster collection and solo party play to PC, console, and mobile</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5073/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5073/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the gaming world! Netmarble Monster&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Ken Kim, recently shared insights about their new game, MONGIL: STAR DIVE. This cross-platform collectible action-adventure game is set to launch on PC, console, and mobile, developed using Unreal Engine 5. Stay tuned for more updates on this innovative gaming experience! 🎮✨ #MONGIL #StarDive #GamingNews #Netmarble #ActionAdventure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UE5 Automotive Cinematic</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5074/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5074/</guid>
      <description>🚗✨ Unreal Engine 5 (UE5) showcases its potential in automotive cinematics. The article dives into the technical aspects and features that make UE5 a powerful tool for creating stunning visuals in the automotive industry. It highlights how real-time rendering and advanced lighting techniques enhance vehicle presentations. The use of UE5 allows for greater creativity and efficiency in producing automotive content. #UnrealEngine5 #AutomotiveCinematics #3DRendering #GameDevelopment #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Register now for the Mega Stack-O-Jam game jam</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4913/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4913/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Join the Mega Stack-O-Jam starting August 14! This week-long game jam invites participants to explore level design using the new Stack-O-Bot sample. Learn from industry professionals and compete for exciting prizes. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this chance to showcase your creativity! #GameJam #LevelDesign #StackOBot #CreativityUnleashed #GameDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updated Stack-O-Bot for Unreal Engine 5.6—available now</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4914/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4914/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for game developers! The updated Stack-O-Bot sample game is now available for Unreal Engine 5.6. This version includes numerous new features to enhance your experience. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re new to UE or seeking a strong base for your project, Stack-O-Bot offers valuable resources to boost your game development skills. #UnrealEngine #GameDevelopment #StackOBot #GameDesign #UE5</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cory Williams makes hit children’s YouTube channel featuring Silly Crocodile</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4728/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4728/</guid>
      <description>Cory Williams is thriving as he creates engaging videos for his YouTube channel, Just For Kids, featuring a playful crocodile. 🐊 His innovative real-time pipeline allows him to produce content quickly while maintaining a strong connection with his audience. Discover more about Cory&amp;rsquo;s journey and his unique approach to children&amp;rsquo;s entertainment! 🎥✨ #YouTubeKids #ContentCreation #CoryWilliams #ChildrensEntertainment #SillyCrocodile</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trials 2 – A New First-Person Puzzle Game</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4729/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4729/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Introducing &amp;ldquo;The Trials 2&amp;rdquo;! Ahmad Sultan, an independent game developer from Syria, has launched a new first-person puzzle game. The Trials 2 draws inspiration from well-known titles like The Talos Principle. Get ready to solve intricate puzzles and experience a unique gaming journey! #TheTrials2 #GameDevelopment #IndieGame #PuzzleGame #GamingCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaHuman for Maya Release</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4122/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4122/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for creators! The latest version of MetaHuman for Maya has been launched, featuring the new Pose Editor. This tool allows rigging artists to assemble and customize MetaHuman characters directly in Autodesk Maya. Explore the enhanced capabilities and improve your character creation process! #MetaHuman #Maya #3DAnimation #CharacterDesign #GameDev</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Made with UE5, Wildgate blends emergent gameplay with explosive spaceship combat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4081/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4081/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in gaming! Moonshot Games is using Unreal Engine 5 features like Nanite, Lumen, and Chaos in their debut project, the PvP space shooter Wildgate. These technologies enhance graphics and gameplay. Discover how these tools are shaping the future of gaming. #Wildgate #MoonshotGames #UE5 #GamingNews #SpaceShooter</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check out the winners of the Unreal Engine Dance Animation Challenge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4082/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4082/</guid>
      <description>Discover the remarkable winners of the Unreal Engine Dance Animation Challenge! 🎉 These entries showcase impressive dance animations that highlight creativity and skill. Check out the fantastic moves that have taken the spotlight! 💃🕺 #UnrealEngine #DanceAnimation #AnimationChallenge #Winners #Creativity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>July’s free learning content: non-human digital characters, motion capture, and more</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4083/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4083/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into July&amp;rsquo;s free learning content! Explore how to create non-human characters with MetaHuman, simulate realistic muscles using Chaos Flesh, and design procedural urban environments in Unreal Engine. These resources offer valuable insights for anyone looking to enhance their skills in digital character creation and animation! #GameDevelopment #UnrealEngine #MetaHuman #DigitalArt #LearningResources</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
