<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Industry_analysis on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/categories/industry_analysis/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Industry_analysis on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:40:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/industry_analysis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The New Investment Regime Is Here. Are You Ready for It?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9534/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 19:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9534/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The global economy is undergoing a significant transformation, moving beyond traditional market cycles. 📦 Trade flows and supply chains are being rewired, with a renewed focus on industrial policies. 🔍 This new investment regime poses both challenges and opportunities for stakeholders. Stay informed and adjust your strategies accordingly. #InvestmentRegime #GlobalEconomy #SupplyChain #IndustrialPolicy #TradeFlows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI vs Gen Z: How AI has changed the career pathway for junior developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9517/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9517/</guid>
      <description>The article discusses how AI is reshaping career prospects for Gen Z software developers. Once seen as a secure path, the tech job market has become increasingly volatile, with a notable 25% drop in entry-level tech positions in 2024. Concerns about layoffs are high, with 64% of Gen Z fearing job loss, particularly in a post-pandemic economy. AI&amp;rsquo;s ability to automate roles has significantly impacted opportunities for junior developers. #GenZ #AI #CareerDevelopment #JobMarket #TechJobs 🤖💼📉</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI as a conduit for management cybernetics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9493/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:15:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9493/</guid>
      <description>AI is emerging as a crucial tool in management cybernetics, enhancing decision-making processes in organizations. The article discusses how AI can optimize operations and improve efficiency by providing insights into complex data systems. As businesses look to the future, understanding AI’s role in decision science becomes vital for effective management. 🔍🤖📊 #AI #Management #DecisionScience #Cybernetics #BusinessInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Blackwell Ultra Sets New Inference Records in MLPerf Debut</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9466/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9466/</guid>
      <description>🚀 NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Blackwell Ultra architecture has made a significant impact in the latest MLPerf Inference v5.1 benchmarks. New models like DeepSeek-R1 and Llama 3.1 have set high performance standards, with impressive token processing speeds. The benchmarks highlight the growing need for advanced compute power as large language models evolve. NVIDIA continues to lead with record-breaking results across all tested scenarios. #NVIDIA #MLPerf #AI #MachineLearning #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How MongoDB Helps Your Brand Thrive in the Age of AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9491/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9491/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving landscape of e-commerce, the concept of the Zero Moment of Truth (ZMOT) is changing. With AI agents now influencing shopping decisions, brands must adapt their strategies. The new term, Agentic Moment of Truth (AMOT), reflects this shift where AI assists users in making purchases. To succeed, brands need to ensure their products are discoverable by AI, as traditional marketing methods become less effective. Key solutions include utilizing a remote MCP server powered by MongoDB&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving IT Sustainability in the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9461/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9461/</guid>
      <description>🌍 As we move into an AI-driven future, Cisco and NTT DATA emphasize the need for IT sustainability. 🚀 Their recent discussions highlight that sustainable IT is a collective responsibility that demands innovation and collaboration. Clients can shape sustainable outcomes by making informed decisions early in the design process. 💡 Efficiency and sustainability go hand-in-hand. For instance, NTT DATA&amp;rsquo;s consolidation of office sites with Cisco’s support resulted in over 30% reduction in hosting&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 practical concepts for building trust in government digital strategies with Elastic</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9471/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9471/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Explore how Elastic is enhancing digital strategies in the public sector. The article outlines five key concepts: 1. Open source and open standards 2. Sovereign infrastructure 3. Responsible AI 4. Cybersecurity and resilience 5. Data-driven government Elastic supports organizations in managing their data securely and efficiently. Learn how to build trust with these strategies! #DigitalGovernment #PublicSector #Elastic #DataSecurity #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond backpropagation: JAX&#39;s symbolic power unlocks new frontiers in scientific computing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9501/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9501/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JAX is expanding its role beyond AI model development, now making strides in scientific computing. Researchers are utilizing JAX to tackle complex Partial Differential Equations (PDEs), achieving notable speed and memory efficiency. Its support for composable transformations simplifies the computation of high-order derivatives, essential for advanced research. This shift towards JAX is helping scientists overcome computational challenges in areas like physics-informed machine learning&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered APIs and API-Enabled AI: A Symbiotic Evolution Driving Mutual Innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9436/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:39:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9436/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving digital landscape, APIs are crucial for innovation, connecting services and sharing data. However, the growing complexity of API ecosystems poses challenges. AI is emerging as a solution, enhancing API discovery through intent-based searches, which makes finding relevant documentation easier. Additionally, AI is improving API specifications by refining clarity and compliance, ensuring high-quality documentation. 🌐🔗✨ #APIs #AI #Innovation #TechTrends #Development</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Sustainable Enterprise AI Adoption: Cultural Strategies That Achieved 95% Developer Engagement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9435/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:10:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9435/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In our latest &amp;ldquo;Engineering Energizers&amp;rdquo; Q&amp;amp;A, Scott Yancey, EVP of Software Engineering, shares his insights on driving AI adoption at Salesforce. His team achieved a remarkable 95% engagement from developers despite facing technical challenges. They focused on breaking cultural barriers and enhancing the development process through AI. Key examples include AI in log analysis, UI accessibility scanning, and issue triaging, all aimed at reducing manual effort. Scott emphasizes that AI is not&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Infrastructure for the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9427/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 15:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9427/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Cisco is leading the way in transforming network infrastructure for the AI era. As AI evolves, the need for high-speed interconnects in data centers is crucial. Cisco focuses on using pluggable optics to enhance performance and reliability across all distances, addressing the demands of AI applications. With projected AI investments reaching $5.2 trillion by 2030, the pressure on networks is increasing. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s comprehensive technology stack positions it well to meet these challenges,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPv6 in 2025 – The Freedom of Address Space</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9392/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9392/</guid>
      <description>🌐 IPv6 is shaping the future of networking. As we move towards a more IPv6-dominant landscape, organizations must prioritize training and inventory assessments. 📈 The switch from IPv4 to IPv6 offers an astronomical increase in address space, freeing us from previous constraints. 🔗 Cisco is committed to supporting this transition, ensuring that businesses can fully leverage IPv6&amp;rsquo;s potential. #IPv6 #Networking #Cisco #ITInfrastructure #FutureTech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Validated Design for Panasonic: A Blueprint for IP Media Success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7779/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:34:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7779/</guid>
      <description>Cisco and Panasonic have collaborated to create a Cisco Validated Design (CVD) aimed at enhancing IP infrastructure for media broadcasters. This design ensures reliable, scalable support for high-resolution video formats like UHD/4K and beyond. The CVD is rigorously tested for interoperability, providing a trusted blueprint for organizations. It helps accelerate deployments while minimizing risk, ensuring all components work seamlessly together for high-quality live production. This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin is more than just the Android house language</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7769/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7769/</guid>
      <description>💡 Kotlin is evolving beyond its role as the Android house language. In a recent discussion, Jeffrey van Gogh from Google highlighted its journey from JVM to multiplatform capabilities. The Kotlin Foundation aims to support and enhance the language&amp;rsquo;s development while collaborating with the community to minimize breaking changes. This year, over half of developers expressed interest in adopting Kotlin. #Kotlin #Programming #DeveloperCommunity #Multiplatform #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Siili Auto: creating a great HMI experience with Unreal Engine</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7785/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7785/</guid>
      <description>Siili Auto has selected Unreal Engine as their primary tool for designing, developing, and testing Human-Machine Interfaces (HMI). This choice is driven by Unreal Engine&amp;rsquo;s impressive visuals and efficiency. Additionally, it allows Siili Auto to craft unique, branded experiences for the automotive industry. 🚗✨🔧 #SiiliAuto #UnrealEngine #HMI #AutomotiveTech #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Search to Sale: How AI Is Redefining Customer Engagement and Loyalty in Retail</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7760/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7760/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming retail by enhancing customer engagement and loyalty. Key advancements include: 🤖 AI-driven personalization that tailors shopping experiences. 🛒 Retail media networks that connect brands with consumers. 💬 Intelligent customer service improving support throughout the shopping journey. These innovations are reshaping how we shop. #RetailInnovation #CustomerExperience #AI #Ecommerce #CustomerLoyalty</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The data catalyst: Blended finance paving the way for climate AI solutions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7754/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7754/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The Cisco Foundation highlights the role of blended finance in addressing the data-to-scale gap for climate AI solutions. AI can significantly impact climate innovation, but it requires access to diverse, quality data, which is often costly. Cisco recently hosted an AI + Climate Innovation Lab, uniting over 100 experts to explore data needs in various climate sectors. Together, these efforts aim to enhance climate tech funding and innovation. 💡📊 #ClimateAI #BlendedFinance #DataForClimate&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The data catalyst: Blended finance paving the way for climate AI solutions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7818/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7818/</guid>
      <description>The Cisco Foundation is exploring blended finance to tackle the data accessibility challenges for climate AI solutions. 🌍 During the AI + Climate Innovation Lab at San Francisco Climate Week 2025, over 100 experts discussed the critical need for diverse and high-quality data across various climate sectors. This initiative aims to bridge the gap in funding and data for climate tech innovation. 💡 #ClimateAI #DataForGood #Sustainability #Innovation #BlendedFinance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kythera Labs, a Databricks Built-On Partner, saves $2M&#43;/year using Delta Sharing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7730/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7730/</guid>
      <description>Kythera Labs, a partner of Databricks, has achieved significant savings by utilizing Delta Sharing. The healthcare sector deals with vast amounts of sensitive data, and Kythera Labs has streamlined data sharing across the cloud. This innovation is projected to save the company over $2 million annually. Learn more about their approach and its impact on healthcare data management. 💻📊 #DataSharing #HealthcareInnovation #Databricks #CostSavings #DeltaSharing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Reactive IT Finally Dead?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7719/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7719/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Is Reactive IT Finally Dead? 🚨 In a recent article, Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Jason Coleman highlights the challenges of reactive IT. Engineers often spend over 150 hours a year addressing unexpected outages, leading to high costs and operational risks. Cisco is shifting towards AI-powered, preemptive IT solutions to combat these issues, aiming to minimize downtime and enhance efficiency. Learn more about this important shift in IT management! #Cisco #ReactiveIT #AITechnology #ITManagement #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Reactive IT Finally Dead?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7821/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:23:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7821/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Is Reactive IT Finally Dead? 🚨 Jason Coleman from Cisco discusses the challenges of reactive IT, where engineers spend over 150 hours annually fixing unexpected outages. This approach leads to high costs and operational risks for businesses. Cisco is shifting towards AI-powered, preemptive IT solutions to enhance network reliability and reduce downtime. Learn more about this important transition in IT management! #ITManagement #Cisco #AI #TechTrends #NetworkReliability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How platform engineering accelerates enterprise AI adoption</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7704/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 07:01:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7704/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Platform engineering is reshaping enterprise AI adoption. By integrating technologies like Kafka and service mesh, organizations can enhance AI deployments. 🔍 Key challenges include reproducibility and compliance. Platform engineering addresses these by providing self-service access and standardized environments, enabling developers and data scientists to innovate efficiently. 💻 Red Hat OpenShift and Developer Hub are pivotal in making AI resources accessible while ensuring governance. #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe, Q3 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7759/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7759/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe for Q3 2025. The company excelled in 16 evaluation criteria, including endpoint detection and threat hunting. This highlights the importance of AI-driven technology and human expertise in today’s complex threat landscape. CrowdStrike Falcon® Complete Next-Gen MDR offers robust AI-accelerated threat detection and response across various platforms. #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in The Forrester Wave™: Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe, Q3 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-8087/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-8087/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in The Forrester Wave™ for Managed Detection and Response Services in Europe, Q3 2025. The company excelled in 16 key criteria, including endpoint and identity detection, cloud detection, and threat hunting. This highlights the importance of combining AI technology with human expertise to combat evolving cyber threats. CrowdStrike Falcon® Complete Next-Gen MDR ensures comprehensive protection across various attack surfaces. #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian Research: What Do Developers Think About Code Readability in the Age of LLMs?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7695/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7695/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s research explores the importance of code readability in the era of Large Language Models (LLMs) like RovoDev. Key findings show that 81% of developers still view code readability as essential, primarily for reducing maintenance costs. Despite LLMs writing more code, many practitioners are open to using these tools to enhance readability. The study emphasizes that readable code remains crucial for effective collaboration. #CodeReadability #LLMs #SoftwareDevelopment #Atlassian&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open SDK strategy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7702/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7702/</guid>
      <description>At Vercel, open source is a core principle. They focus on developing high-quality software without the goal of profit. Their approach aims to enhance the overall software landscape for everyone, not just their customers. This philosophy reflects the belief that improving software benefits all users. Learn more about Vercel&amp;rsquo;s commitment to open source. 🌍💻 #OpenSource #SoftwareDevelopment #Vercel #TechCommunity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State of Product in 2026: Navigating Change, Challenge, and Opportunity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7659/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7659/</guid>
      <description>Product work is evolving, becoming more complex and crucial. A recent article reveals insights from product teams in the U.S., France, and Germany. Most professionals feel empowered, with 85% having a strategic role. However, they face pressure to deliver results, with 84% fearing product failure. Challenges include limited time for planning and data analysis, leading to uninformed decisions. Collaboration often suffers as 80% of teams don’t involve engineers early on. AI tools are used&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMBER2024: Advancing the Training of Cybersecurity ML Models Against Evasive Malware</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7710/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7710/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news in cybersecurity! CrowdStrike has released EMBER2024, an updated open-source dataset aimed at enhancing machine learning models for malware detection. It features over 3.2 million files across six formats and includes advanced malware samples that can evade antivirus solutions. The dataset&amp;rsquo;s details were shared in a recent academic paper at the KDD-2025 conference. EMBER2024 aims to overcome challenges in public dataset release while promoting research in malware&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New report: explore how real-time tools could transform fashion</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7677/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7677/</guid>
      <description>Discover the latest insights from The Interline’s new report on the evolution of 3D technology in fashion. Supported by Epic Games, this report highlights the advancements made and outlines future possibilities in the industry. Download the report to learn more! 📈👗✨ #FashionTech #3DModeling #Innovation #TheInterline #EpicGames</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating Stablecoin Innovation in US Banking</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7646/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7646/</guid>
      <description>The stablecoin market is rapidly evolving, with its capitalization exceeding $250 billion recently, and forecasts predict it could reach over $400 billion by 2025 and $2 trillion by 2028. 📈 The U.S. has made strides with the GENIUS Act, the first federal framework for dollar-backed stablecoins, ensuring user protections and transparent operations. This opens doors for banks to innovate in digital assets and services. 💡 MongoDB plays a crucial role by providing a flexible, scalable data layer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Popular Python Frameworks and Libraries in 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7638/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7638/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exploring the evolving landscape of Python in 2025! This year&amp;rsquo;s survey highlights the most popular frameworks and libraries among Python developers. FastAPI stands out with a 38% usage rate, showcasing its strengths in building APIs and supporting AI/ML integrations. Django and Flask continue to be popular, but FastAPI&amp;rsquo;s modern approach and active community are making waves. Stay informed on the latest trends! #Python #FastAPI #WebDevelopment #MachineLearning #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Broadcom’s New Bitnami Restrictions? Migrate Easily with Docker</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-30-7564/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 23:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-30-7564/</guid>
      <description>Bitnami has been crucial in simplifying application deployment for developers. However, significant changes are coming to their distribution model. Starting September 29, access to most versioned images will require a paid subscription under Bitnami Secure Images. Only the :latest tags will remain free, while older images will move to a legacy archive without updates. Docker offers alternatives with their Official Images and Hardened Images, providing robust options for teams facing these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Small Language Models Are Key to Scalable Agentic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7543/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 18:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7543/</guid>
      <description>The rise of agentic AI is transforming how businesses approach automation and productivity. 🤖 Recent insights highlight the potential of small language models (SLMs) as efficient alternatives to large language models (LLMs) in agentic applications. SLMs can reduce costs and improve operational flexibility while maintaining performance. This shift enables enterprises to utilize SLMs for specific tasks, reserving LLMs for more complex scenarios. Tools like NVIDIA’s Nemotron demonstrate the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The crawl-to-click gap: Cloudflare data on AI bots, training, and referrals</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7541/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7541/</guid>
      <description>The landscape of internet traffic is changing dramatically due to AI. By mid-2025, AI training is driving nearly 80% of crawling activity, significantly impacting referral traffic to publishers. 📉 As search engines and AI crawlers consume vast amounts of data, real user engagement is declining. For example, Google&amp;rsquo;s referrals to news sites fell nearly 9% in March 2025 compared to January. Cloudflare data highlights this shift, showing a surge in crawling activity, yet a notable imbalance in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-source is for the people, by the people</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7521/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7521/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments in the world of Python! Travis Oliphant, the creator of NumPy and SciPy, discusses the growth of Python as a data science tool and the significance of community in open-source projects. He highlights recent releases of NumPy 2.3.0 and SciPy 1.16.0, and introduces the OpenTeams Incubator, aimed at supporting sustainable open-source communities. 📊 Connect with Travis for insights on open-source growth! #OpenSource #DataScience #Python #Community #Collaboration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A deeper look at AI crawlers: breaking down traffic by purpose and industry</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7466/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7466/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Cloudflare Radar is enhancing AI insights with new industry-focused data on bot traffic. The article discusses how traditional search platforms are affected by the rise of AI. Users often find answers without clicking through to original sources, impacting ad revenue for publishers. New features include a breakdown of AI bot traffic by purpose, such as training and user action, allowing for better understanding of these trends. 📊🤖 #AIBotTraffic #CloudflareRadar #DigitalMarketing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Uninterrupted Motion: Why Factories Need a New Class of Wireless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7460/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7460/</guid>
      <description>Factories are increasingly using Automated Guided Vehicles (AGVs) and Autonomous Mobile Robots (AMRs) to boost productivity. These vehicles rely on robust wireless networks to operate effectively. 📈🤖 A reliable connection is vital for real-time inspections and safety alerts. Any interruption can lead to missed defects or safety risks, potentially halting production. 🛑⚠️ Companies like BMW and Samsung are already utilizing these technologies to enhance quality assurance and operational safety&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Foundation for Enterprise AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7450/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7450/</guid>
      <description>Enterprise AI has shifted from being a trial to a necessity for businesses. Global organizations must now integrate AI into their operations to maintain a competitive edge. Connecting SAP with your entire data estate can streamline this process and enhance efficiency. Stay ahead in the evolving tech landscape! 🌐🤖 #EnterpriseAI #SAP #DataIntegration #BusinessStrategy #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cracking Complex Contracts with GenAI on Azure Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7287/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 07:19:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7287/</guid>
      <description>At a top diagnostic healthcare manufacturer, contract management has been transformed using GenAI on Azure Databricks. The implementation of advanced analytics has reduced contract review time by 92%, enabling quicker decision-making. This innovation has also revealed valuable business insights. #Healthcare #Analytics #GenAI #AzureDatabricks #BusinessInsights 🌟📄💡</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in 2025 IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Incident Response Services</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7435/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7435/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in the 2025 IDC MarketScape for Worldwide Incident Response Services. This acknowledgment highlights their rapid response capabilities, powered by the AI-native CrowdStrike Falcon® platform, and their global 24/7 incident response model. With the rise of AI-driven threats, CrowdStrike combines expertise and technology to effectively counteract these challenges. Their integrated approach ensures organizations can detect and manage incidents swiftly&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ROI of websites: Metrics that matter to the C-suite</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7403/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7403/</guid>
      <description>Understanding the ROI of websites is crucial for marketing leaders. While they focus on metrics like conversion and engagement, C-suite executives prioritize ROI and revenue impact. Traditional metrics often fall short, as they do not align with executive goals. For effective buy-in, it’s essential to connect website performance to business outcomes. Key metrics such as conversion rate, customer acquisition cost, and customer lifetime value resonate with executives, highlighting the real&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The business impact of Elasticsearch logsdb index mode and TSDS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7401/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7401/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Elasticsearch team has rolled out enhancements in versions 8.19 and 9.1, focusing on storage efficiency and performance. 📊 Key features include the logsdb index mode and time series data streams (TSDS), which address challenges faced by DevOps and security teams. 📈 Benchmark results show a storage efficiency improvement of ~16% and an indexing throughput boost of ~19%. For users not yet on logsdb, storage reductions could exceed 70%. 🔍 Remember, logsdb is available for both Basic and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Industry Collaboration Fosters NVIDIA Co-Packaged Optics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7202/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7202/</guid>
      <description>NVIDIA is transforming data-center connectivity by merging optical and electrical components through strong industry partnerships. 🤝 Their networking platform integrates advanced technologies from top partners, focusing on scalable and efficient optical systems. Key innovations include the Micro Ring Modulator, allowing high data throughput with a compact design. Collaboration with TSMC has addressed manufacturing challenges, ensuring reliable performance essential for modern data centers&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS services scale to new heights for Prime Day 2025: key metrics and milestones</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7254/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:06:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7254/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon Prime Day 2025 set new sales records, driven by enhanced AI features and AWS infrastructure. Prime members enjoyed billions in savings, utilizing tools like Alexa+ and AI Shopping Guides for a seamless shopping experience. Key AWS metrics include 1.7 trillion Lambda invocations and a 160% increase in robot commands, showcasing massive scalability. #AmazonPrimeDay #AWS #AIShopping #Ecommerce #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marketing Velocity: Comstor’s Powerful Engine Driving Partner Success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7195/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7195/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Marketing Velocity, in partnership with Comstor, fuels business growth through demand generation and co-branded campaigns. This initiative focuses on AI, digital resilience, and future-proof workplaces, showcasing partner success stories to highlight effective strategies. Learn more about driving sustainable growth in the tech industry! 🌐📈 #MarketingVelocity #PartnerSuccess #Cisco #Comstor #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redefining Enterprise AI: Closing the Infrastructure Gap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7196/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7196/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Enterprise AI is evolving beyond just GPU power. Success now relies on integrating data, security, and operations effectively. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Secure AI Factory and Modular AI PODs enable organizations to transition from experimentation to production smoothly. Despite the potential for $4.4 trillion in corporate profits, only 13% of enterprises feel ready for AI at scale. Learn more about addressing the infrastructure gap in AI. 💡 #EnterpriseAI #Cisco #AIInfrastructure #DataSecurity #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are you ready for some football? Cisco Triples NFL Franchise and Stadium Partnerships Ahead of 2025-2026 Season</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7197/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7197/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is expanding its role in the NFL by tripling its partnerships with franchises and stadiums for the upcoming 2025-2026 season. New additions include the Arizona Cardinals, Buffalo Bills, Carolina Panthers, Chicago Bears, Las Vegas Raiders, and Miami Dolphins. This growth highlights Cisco&amp;rsquo;s commitment to providing advanced technology solutions for fan engagement and security. With a focus on high-density wireless networks and cyber threat protection, Cisco aims to enhance the overall&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Svelte was built on “slinging code for the sheer love of it”</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7189/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7189/</guid>
      <description>🎙️ In a recent discussion, Rich Harris, creator of Svelte, explored the evolution of web frameworks with Ryan. He highlighted Svelte&amp;rsquo;s development during the mobile boom and the complexities of building efficient web applications. They also touched on the importance of supporting open-source projects and the nuances of asynchronous operations in component frameworks. Stay connected with the Svelte community! #Svelte #WebDevelopment #OpenSource #TechTalk #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The conversion paradox: 3DS trends in regulated markets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7248/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7248/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover the latest insights on 3D Secure (3DS) trends in regulated markets! Our analysis reveals that despite high two-factor authentication rates, countries like France, the UK, and Japan still enjoy strong conversion rates. This challenges the belief that authentication negatively impacts sales. Interestingly, the quality of the authentication process plays a crucial role in driving these results. Explore how these findings can enhance your authentication strategy. #3DS #Ecommerce&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The AI-Native Engineer: How Salesforce’s Next Generation is Redefining Software Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6349/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:22:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6349/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Salesforce Engineering is transforming software development through AI adoption. Key changes include enhanced hiring practices, improved knowledge flow, and a shift in mentorship dynamics. New hires now adapt quickly, using intelligent tools that streamline onboarding. Junior developers are stepping up, showcasing new skills and reshaping traditional mentorship roles. #Salesforce #SoftwareDevelopment #AI #Innovation #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leveraging technology to transform homeless services</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6330/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 07:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6330/</guid>
      <description>Cisco and Destination: Home have partnered to address homelessness in Santa Clara County since 2018. Their initiative focuses on developing supportive housing while leveraging technology to improve access to vital resources for those experiencing homelessness. A recent assessment evaluated the technology needs of the supportive housing system in the area. 🌐🏠🤝 #Homelessness #TechnologyForGood #SupportiveHousing #SantaClara #CommunitySupport</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12 contact center technologies and trends to support your agents and customers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7245/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7245/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Contact center technologies are rapidly evolving. Staying updated on these trends is essential for supporting both agents and customers. 📈 The article highlights 12 key technologies that are shaping the future of contact centers. These advancements aim to enhance efficiency and improve user experiences. Explore the latest in contact center innovation to ensure your operations remain competitive and effective. #ContactCenter #TechTrends #CustomerSupport #Innovation #BusinessSolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named a Leader in 2025 IDC MarketScape for Exposure Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7437/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7437/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for cybersecurity! CrowdStrike has been recognized as a Leader in the 2025 IDC MarketScape for Exposure Management. This recognition highlights their innovative approach to addressing modern threats, where adversaries use advanced techniques to exploit vulnerabilities. Unlike traditional tools, CrowdStrike Falcon® offers real-time visibility and prioritizes risks based on actual adversary behavior, streamlining response and remediation processes. Learn more about how they are&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to AI Week 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-24-6319/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-24-6319/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Welcome to AI Week 2025! AI is transforming industries by enhancing productivity. Customer support agents can now handle up to ten times more tickets, while software engineers focus on reviewing AI-generated code. This shift allows sales teams to prioritize relationship building over administrative tasks. However, the rapid advancement of AI presents governance challenges. Security concerns arise as sensitive data can be mishandled or exposed. Companies face tough decisions on managing AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robots in the skies (and they use Transformer models)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6313/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:41:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6313/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how AI is transforming defense technology! In a recent discussion, Nathan Michael, CTO of Shield AI, shared insights on the Hivemind platform. This technology enables drones to make autonomous decisions while ensuring human oversight. The conversation also touched on software security and the ethical implications of using AI in defense. #AI #DefenseTechnology #Drones #Innovation #Ethics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Hardware Innovations and Open Source Contributions Are Shaping AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6298/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6298/</guid>
      <description>NVIDIA is making strides in AI through open source models like Cosmos, DeepSeek, and Llama. 🌐 These models offer free access to AI methodologies, enabling innovation across the globe. Their new Blackwell GPU architecture enhances AI performance with advanced features like NVFP4 and high-bandwidth interconnects. ⚡️ Additionally, NVIDIA provides a wealth of open source tools and libraries, fostering an environment for developers to build and scale AI efficiently. 💻 Discover more about these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare incident on August 21, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6315/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6315/</guid>
      <description>On August 21, 2025, Cloudflare experienced significant congestion due to a surge of traffic directed at its clients hosted in AWS us-east-1. 🌐 The congestion began at 16:27 UTC and peaked until 19:38 UTC, affecting user connections with high latency and packet loss. This issue was localized and not a result of an attack. The traffic overload was traced back to a single customer. ⚠️ Cloudflare is working on measures to prevent similar incidents in the future. For more details, check out the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How a volunteer-run wildfire site in Portugal stayed online during DDoS attacks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5129/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 17:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5129/</guid>
      <description>🌍🔥 In 2015, fogos.pt began as a volunteer side project to improve access to wildfire data in Portugal. Today, it serves as a vital resource for citizens, media, and government during fire seasons. During the intense 2025 wildfire season, fogos.pt faced DDoS attacks but was protected by Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Project Galileo. This platform provides real-time data and is crucial for public safety. Volunteers and partners keep this initiative running without formal funding. #WildfireTracker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5052/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 15:39:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5052/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Interested in Palantir? Here’s a quick overview! Palantir Technologies, founded in 2003 and headquartered in Denver, offers software for data operations and AI infrastructure. Their solutions support organizations in various sectors, including defense, healthcare, and finance. Their platforms integrate diverse data sources to enhance decision-making, while ensuring customer data remains secure and controlled. Notably, Palantir does not act as a data collector or broker. For more insights,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research roadmap update, August 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5123/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 14:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5123/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Stack Overflow is evolving to better serve developers! The platform is preparing for a redesign aimed at enhancing user experience with a modern UI and features that foster collaboration and skill development. New content types and sub-communities are being explored to address the needs of users. Feedback indicates strong interest in Challenges, with many users eager to engage in coding puzzles and skill growth. As Stack Overflow looks to create focused communities, the goal is to replicate&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Office Infrastructure: Transitioning from Backbone to SD-WAN</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5164/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5164/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Uber is enhancing its global office network by adopting SD-WAN technology. This transition has resulted in an 89% reduction in latency, improved automation, and more efficient connectivity worldwide. Such advancements are set to make operations faster and more cost-effective. #SDWAN #Uber #TechInnovation #GlobalNetwork #Connectivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a Scalable E-Commerce Platform at Cisco: From DevNet to Company-Wide Impact</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5284/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 21:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5284/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco&amp;rsquo;s DevNet initiative has transformed into a scalable e-commerce framework that benefits the entire company. Over two years, the team navigated complex legal and security processes to onboard payment vendors like Stripe and VeriFone, ensuring compliance with international regulations. 🌍 This groundwork allows Cisco Learning to easily integrate new payment solutions, showcasing the importance of strategic planning for future needs. #Cisco #Ecommerce #DevNet #BusinessGrowth #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Booking to Bon Voyage: How AI Is Redefining the Travel &amp; Hospitality Experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5102/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5102/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming the travel and hospitality industry, enhancing guest experiences from booking to arrival. With advanced data analytics, businesses can offer personalized services that cater to individual preferences. This technology also streamlines operations, making travel more efficient. Stay ahead in the evolving travel landscape! ✈️🌍 #TravelTech #AI #Hospitality #Innovation #CustomerExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI is Transforming the Way Retailers Connect With Consumers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5104/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5104/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming retail by enhancing connections between brands and consumers. Companies like Pilot, adidas, and PRADA Group are utilizing the Databricks Data Intelligence Platform to harness data effectively. From personalized experiences to accurate forecasting, AI is paving the way for innovative strategies in the retail sector. Stay tuned for more insights on the impact of technology in retail! 🤖🛍️📊 #RetailInnovation #AI #ConsumerExperience #DataIntelligence #TechnologyTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supply Chain Paradox: When “Hardened” Images Become a Vendor Lock-in Trap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5116/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5116/</guid>
      <description>The demand for pre-hardened container images is rapidly rising as companies seek immediate security solutions with low operational effort. These images offer minimal dependencies, allowing teams to focus on application development. However, this trend may lead to unintended vendor lock-in. Organizations could become overly reliant on a single vendor&amp;rsquo;s systems and processes, complicating operations and potentially weakening security. Additionally, deviations from mainstream distributions can&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking prototyping, requirements, and project delivery at Code and Theory</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5083/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5083/</guid>
      <description>Code and Theory is a digital agency that integrates strategy, design, and engineering. Their team consists of equal parts creatives and engineers, working on projects for major brands like Microsoft and Amazon. They focus on creating scalable digital experiences and utilize a method called v0 to streamline the process from concept to functioning software. Learn more about their innovative approach! 🌐💻 #DigitalAgency #Prototyping #Innovation #Tech #ProjectDelivery</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LY Corporation on AI, a recap of Tech-Verse 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5829/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5829/</guid>
      <description>🌟 I recently attended Tech-Verse 2025 in Tokyo as a &amp;ldquo;LINE DEV Reporter.&amp;rdquo; The focus was on AI, showcasing various presentations and applications of AI in services. It was insightful to see how these advancements can relate to my work at LINE AI LAB. For those who missed it, videos and materials are available on the Tech-Verse 2025 website! 🎥 #TechVerse2025 #AI #LINEAIlab #Innovation #TechConference</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traditional AI vs. generative AI: A guide for IT leaders</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5057/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5057/</guid>
      <description>🌐 The AI landscape is rapidly changing, presenting challenges for IT leaders. This article outlines the key differences between traditional AI and generative AI. Traditional AI has supported enterprise operations for years, while generative AI is redefining creativity and innovation. Key considerations for choosing the right AI include task complexity, creativity needs, and data requirements. Understanding these factors is essential for strategic decision-making. 🔍 #ArtificialIntelligence&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving AI adoption at Dropbox: a conversation with CTO Ali Dasdan</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5166/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5166/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI is transforming how Dropbox operates, enhancing productivity for engineers. In early 2025, a shift occurred, leading to over 90% AI adoption among engineering teams. This change was driven by leadership alignment and a culture of knowledge-sharing. CTO Ali Dasdan emphasizes AI&amp;rsquo;s role in automating tasks and allowing deeper focus on coding and innovation. #AI #Dropbox #Productivity #Innovation #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting Models to Improve Driver Availability at Airports</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5165/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5165/</guid>
      <description>Uber is enhancing driver availability at airports through advanced forecasting models. 📊 These models aim to reduce wait times and minimize queues for passengers. By analyzing data patterns, Uber optimizes driver deployment to meet demand effectively. 🚖 Stay tuned for more updates on innovations in transportation! #Uber #DataScience #AirportTravel #DriverAvailability #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The server-side rendering equivalent for LLM inference workloads</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-6344/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-6344/</guid>
      <description>Join Ryan and Tuhin Srivastava, CEO of Baseten, as they discuss the changing AI infrastructure landscape. They highlight how the shift to large-scale neural networks is impacting GPU usage and the future of hardware optimizations in AI. Baseten offers the tools and expertise needed to accelerate AI product development. 📈🤖💡 #AI #MachineLearning #NeuralNetworks #Baseten #TechTalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data mesh at Grab part I: Building trust through certification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5076/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5076/</guid>
      <description>At Grab, we are evolving our data ecosystem to better serve our diverse operations, including ride-hailing, food delivery, and financial services. 🚀 In 2024, we initiated the Signals Marketplace, a data mesh journey aimed at enhancing data quality and accessibility. This decentralized approach allows domain-specific teams to take ownership of their data, fostering reliability and trust. 📊 Key challenges included high data volume, unclear ownership, and communication gaps. We introduced data&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling AI Factories with Co-Packaged Optics for Better Power Efficiency</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5046/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5046/</guid>
      <description>AI is reshaping the computing landscape, with networks becoming essential for future data centers. NVIDIA is leading this evolution with GPU-driven AI factories that require high bandwidth and low latency. Their networking solutions, including Spectrum-X Ethernet and Quantum InfiniBand, support these advanced needs. Co-packaged optics are now crucial for power efficiency and resilience in AI workloads, marking a significant shift from traditional data center designs. #NVIDIA #AI #DataCenters&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling the Future of Work Together</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5288/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5288/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco is redefining the future of work with innovative office transformations globally. From New York to London, these spaces highlight what hybrid work can be with cutting-edge technology. Partners like Softcat in London are leading the way, creating immersive experiences that showcase Cisco&amp;rsquo;s capabilities. 🌍 With over 70 partner offices demonstrating these advancements, Cisco has launched a Collaboration Partner Workspace Catalog to connect teams with hands-on Cisco technology demos&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If agents are building your app, who gets the W-2?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5087/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5087/</guid>
      <description>Autonomous coding agents are changing the software development landscape. 🤖 These agents can now fully design, build, test, and deploy features without human intervention. However, current U.S. GAAP regulations have not fully adapted to this technology. While third-party software costs can be capitalized, developer tools are often classified as overhead. It&amp;rsquo;s essential to consider how to treat work done by these agents in a manner similar to salaried engineers. #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco and KDDI Partner to Deliver Japan’s First Fully Managed SASE Solution</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5289/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5289/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco and KDDI have announced Japan&amp;rsquo;s first fully managed SASE solution, enhancing secure access for businesses adapting to digital changes. This partnership aims to simplify SASE adoption, providing integrated and scalable solutions for secure connectivity. Service providers like KDDI are essential in navigating this transition, leveraging Cisco’s expertise to ensure streamlined operations and robust security. #Cisco #KDDI #SASE #Cybersecurity #CloudSolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State of Python 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5069/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5069/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting insights from the eighth annual Python Developers Survey, conducted by the Python Software Foundation and JetBrains! Michael Kennedy shares key trends and actions that can enhance your Python career. Notably, 86% of respondents use Python as their main programming language. The survey reveals that many Python developers are relatively new to programming, highlighting a shift in the community. For those relying on Python for their projects, this article offers valuable perspectives&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI needs human partners to elevate its work – and keep it in check</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-6541/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 19:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-6541/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming industries, especially in pharmaceutical innovation. 🧬 Researchers at MIT are using generative AI to design new antibiotics, potentially speeding up drug development and addressing antibiotic resistance. However, AI tools in hiring reveal concerning biases. A recent study found that AI often suggests lower salaries for women and non-white candidates, highlighting the need for human oversight. Understanding these dynamics is crucial for effective human-AI collaboration. 🤖&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS named as a Leader in 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Strategic Cloud Platform Services for 15 years in a row</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5169/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:59:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5169/</guid>
      <description>🎉 AWS has been named a Leader in the 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for Strategic Cloud Platform Services for the 15th year in a row! Gartner recognized AWS for its strong “Ability to Execute,” highlighting its commitment to delivering extensive capabilities, security, and performance for critical applications. AWS boasts the largest global cloud community, custom silicon designs, and a robust network of integration partners, all contributing to successful cloud adoption. Explore the AWS Builder&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The future of Vue is you (and You)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5127/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting insights from Evan You, the creator of Vue.js! In a recent discussion, Evan highlighted the origins of Vue.js and the challenges faced over the past decade. The framework has grown significantly, now ranking as the eighth most popular in the 2025 Developer Survey. They also explored future developments, AI integrations, and the sustainability of open-source projects. Learn more about what’s next for Vue.js and the team at Void Zero. #VueJS #WebDevelopment #OpenSource #JavaScript&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A CDP is the Best Contextual Data Layer for Agentic Systems</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5140/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5140/</guid>
      <description>AI agents thrive on accurate, real-time context. A Customer Data Platform (CDP) like Twilio Segment plays a crucial role in delivering this data. It provides clean, consented information tailored to the agents&amp;rsquo; needs. This enables more informed, efficient, and secure decision-making, ultimately enhancing customer experiences. #AI #CustomerExperience #DataManagement #Twilio #CDP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharks of DigitalOcean: Darian Wilkin, Senior Manager, Solutions Engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4997/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 04:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4997/</guid>
      <description>Meet Darian Wilkin, Senior Manager of Solutions Engineering at DigitalOcean, who has been with the company for over eight years. He has witnessed its evolution from a startup to a public company. 🌟 Darian emphasizes the importance of a supportive culture and talented team, which enhances collaboration and keeps him motivated. He plays a key role in helping customers build efficient cloud solutions. ☁️ He values the quick decision-making process at DigitalOcean, allowing ideas to turn into&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack the planet! A recap of Hack Day 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5831/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5831/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Just wrapped up Hack Day 2025 at LY Corporation in Tokyo! This internal hackathon, running since 2007, allows employees from all departments to collaborate freely on projects. Teams can be formed locally or globally, fostering creativity and innovation. 🙌 Participants shared ideas, planned, and developed products over two days, with a focus on collaboration and fun. Stay tuned for more insights from the concurrent Tech-Verse conference! #HackDay2025 #Innovation #Teamwork #LYCorporation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Businesses Need to Know About iOS 26</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5143/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5143/</guid>
      <description>📱 Businesses should be aware of the recent changes in Apple iOS 26. These updates may significantly affect how companies utilize SMS, MMS, RCS messaging, and voice calls to communicate with customers. Understanding these implications is crucial for maintaining effective customer engagement strategies. Stay informed to adapt your communication approaches accordingly! #iOS26 #BusinessCommunication #CustomerEngagement #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GPT-5 Launch Broke the AI Internet (And Not in a Good Way)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4956/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 17:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4956/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The launch of GPT-5 by OpenAI caused significant disruption in the AI app ecosystem. Many applications failed overnight due to the unexpected removal of older APIs. Developers are reminded that relying too heavily on a single provider or model can lead to system failures. The interconnected nature of AI applications means that even small changes can have wide-reaching impacts. As the landscape evolves, it’s crucial to build resilient systems. Developers should prepare for sudden changes by&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Coxwave delivers GenAI value faster with Vercel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4935/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4935/</guid>
      <description>Coxwave is revolutionizing the development of GenAI products for enterprises. 🚀 Their consulting arm, AX, and analytics platform, Align, serve leading companies like Anthropic, Meta, Microsoft, and PwC. Since 2021, Coxwave has focused on speed—not just in model performance, but in iteration and value delivery. To enhance their web app strategy, they utilized Next.js and Vercel, enabling quicker results for their clients. #GenAI #Coxwave #Nextjs #Vercel #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The three types of AI bot traffic and how to handle them</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4937/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4937/</guid>
      <description>AI bot traffic is on the rise, and recent data identifies three types of AI-driven crawlers. These bots can enhance discoverability but may disrupt teams if not managed properly. 🤖 Understanding the role of these crawlers is vital. While some bots are beneficial, blocking them could lead to missed opportunities, similar to restricting early search engines. 🌐 As user behavior shifts towards seeking direct answers, sites that strategically manage bot access will gain a competitive edge. #AIBots&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purpose, performance, and trust: Inside the culture powering 1Password’s next chapter</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4960/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4960/</guid>
      <description>At 1Password, trust is central to our mission. We&amp;rsquo;ve established a culture focused on shared purpose, clarity, and accountability, prioritizing customer success. Our high-performance culture promotes collaboration and innovation, allowing us to deliver secure, cutting-edge products quickly. This commitment to excellence fosters an environment where employees can learn and grow. Curious about joining a team that values purpose and teamwork? Explore opportunities at 1Password! 🌟🔐 #1Password&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling physician-centered oversight for AMIE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5182/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5182/</guid>
      <description>Introducing guardrailed-AMIE (g-AMIE), a new AI diagnostic tool designed for history-taking in healthcare. 🩺 g-AMIE operates under strict guidelines, preventing it from giving personalized medical advice. Instead, it generates summaries for physicians to review, ensuring patient safety and oversight. This system allows primary care physicians to maintain accountability while leveraging AI for efficiency. The recent study demonstrated g-AMIE&amp;rsquo;s performance being preferred over nurse&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI isn’t stealing your job, it’s helping you find it</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4958/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4958/</guid>
      <description>🔍 AI is reshaping the way we search for jobs on LinkedIn! Wenjing Zhang and Caleb Johnson discuss how LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s job search feature has evolved from keyword-based to semantic search, enhancing the experience for job seekers and employers alike. With over one billion members, LinkedIn continues to leverage AI for better connections. Explore Caleb&amp;rsquo;s blog for more insights! #LinkedIn #JobSearch #AI #SemanticSearch #CareerAdvice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supabase Auth: Build vs. Buy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5293/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5293/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Understanding authentication is key for developers. While it’s essential in almost every app, it&amp;rsquo;s often not the main focus. Supabase Auth provides a ready-made solution, integrating directly with your Postgres database. It offers JWT-based security and seamless Row Level Security integration. Building your own authentication can lead to hidden costs, such as time and maintenance, which can divert resources from core development. Consider your options carefully! 🔒💻 #Supabase #Authentication&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The top industries and business models using AI for fraud prevention</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4962/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4962/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A recent survey reveals that 47% of businesses globally are now using AI tools to detect and prevent fraud, making it the leading application of AI in payments. 📊 Adoption varies by industry, with insurance, SaaS, and travel companies leading the way. These sectors face unique risks and handle high-value transactions, making AI essential for their fraud prevention strategies. 🔍 Insurance firms utilize AI for identity verification, SaaS companies target fraudulent sign-ups, and travel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tooling ≠ Glue: Why changing AI workflows still feels like duct tape</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4852/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4852/</guid>
      <description>Modern AI development presents a contradiction. While we have advanced tools and frameworks like LangChain and Hugging Face, replacing components often leads to system failures. 🔧 The expectation was for modular workflows, but instead, we face a fragmented landscape. Each tool has different assumptions, making integration challenging and time-consuming. 🕒 Abstractions often leak, complicating even simple tasks. What should be seamless can turn into complex issues, leaving developers to write&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remocal and Minimum Viable Models: Why Right-Sized Models Beat API Overkill</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-09-4802/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:30:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-09-4802/</guid>
      <description>💡 Discover a new approach to AI development with Remocal and Minimum Viable Models! Many businesses face high costs and latency issues from API-dependent AI. For example, a simple sentiment analyzer can cost $847/month and take 2.3 seconds per review. Remocal combines local and cloud resources, allowing developers to work efficiently without the hassle of complex cloud setups. This method makes AI development more affordable and speeds up iteration. Minimum Viable Models (MVM) focus on using&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python: Come for the language, stay for the community</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4765/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4765/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In a recent discussion, Ryan welcomed Paul Everitt from JetBrains to delve into Python&amp;rsquo;s journey. They highlighted key moments in its history and growth, particularly its transition from Python 2 to 3. 📊 Python&amp;rsquo;s relevance is growing, especially in academia and data science, making it the fourth most popular language according to the 2025 Developer Survey. 🔧 JetBrains continues to enhance the developer experience with its tools. #Python #JetBrains #ProgrammingCommunity #DataScience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new worst coder has entered the chat: vibe coding without code knowledge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4766/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4766/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving tech landscape, a new trend called &amp;ldquo;vibe coding&amp;rdquo; has emerged, allowing those without coding skills to create applications. This concept, popularized in early 2025, raises questions about its effectiveness and impact on junior developers. The author shares their experience building an app using the vibe coding tool, Bolt, during a Hackathon. While it was easy to start, the lack of technical knowledge revealed flaws in the final product. This highlights the potential limitations&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Restaurants to Retail: Scaling Uber Eats for Everything</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4767/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4767/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments are on the horizon for Uber Eats with the introduction of its new catalog system, INCA (INventory and CAtalog). This innovative system is designed to process billions of updates daily from retailers globally, enhancing the efficiency of service delivery. Stay tuned as Uber Eats expands its offerings beyond restaurants! 🍽️🌍 #UberEats #INCA #RetailInnovation #TechNews #DeliveryServices</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why RCS messaging is the future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5148/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5148/</guid>
      <description>RCS messaging is transforming customer engagement by providing interactive and visual experiences directly within messaging apps. 📱✨ Unlike SMS and MMS, RCS offers features like tap-to-buy buttons and branded profiles, enhancing communication between brands and consumers. Businesses adopting RCS are seeing improved response rates and increased customer loyalty. Explore how RCS can elevate your customer experience. #RCS #CustomerEngagement #DigitalMarketing #MessagingInnovation #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – August 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4118/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4118/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into the latest edition of Java Annotated Monthly for August 2025! This month covers Java, Kotlin, frameworks, and the evolving tech landscape. 📚 Explore insightful articles tailored for developers and teams, along with a special feature by A N M Bazlur Rahman, who shares his reflections on the future of development. 🤖 Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the AI corner, highlighting the readiness of AI integration in Java, especially with the upcoming JDK 25 release. #Java #Kotlin #TechTrends #AI #JavaDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern messaging with RCS: Your webinar recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5150/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5150/</guid>
      <description>Discover the potential of Rich Communication Services (RCS) in engaging customers! 📱 In a recent webinar, Twilio experts highlighted how RCS transforms customer communication. With 89% of consumers preferring messaging, brands can now leverage RCS for a more interactive experience. RCS offers features like verified sender IDs, multimedia content, and secure messaging, enhancing trust and engagement. Learn how to utilize these advancements for your business! 🌟 #RCS #CustomerEngagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Tavily Uses MongoDB to Enhance Agentic Workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-6486/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-6486/</guid>
      <description>Tavily is transforming how AI agents connect with the web to access real-time information. Founded in 2023, Tavily&amp;rsquo;s open-source project, GPT Researcher, gained rapid popularity, highlighting the need for better real-time data retrieval in AI systems. 🌐 The company leverages MongoDB to enhance its performance, focusing on speed, scalability, and context for AI responses. By integrating fresh data from the web, Tavily aims to address the challenges faced by AI in providing accurate answers. 📈&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being unambiguous in what you want: the software engineer in a vibe coding world</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2095/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2095/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Quinn Slack, CEO of Sourcegraph, discusses the impact of AI coding tools on software engineering. He highlights the shift from syntax tasks to higher-level design and management roles for developers. AI&amp;rsquo;s integration into enterprises is set to enhance software development processes. Connect with Quinn on LinkedIn and X for more insights! #SoftwareEngineering #AI #Sourcegraph #TechTalks #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Action Hackathon:  Celebrating the GitLab innovations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-3190/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-3190/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The AI in Action Hackathon, held from May 6 to June 17, 2025, invited developers to explore AI solutions for a chance at a $50,000 prize pool. This collaboration between Google Cloud, MongoDB, and GitLab aimed to enhance DevSecOps practices, allowing participants to leverage powerful tools for innovative projects. 🌟 Notable winners included: - &lt;strong&gt;Pipeline Doctor&lt;/strong&gt;: Uses AI for root cause analysis, improving CI/CD reliability. - &lt;strong&gt;Agentic CICD&lt;/strong&gt;: Automates DevSecOps tasks, enhancing software&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaning into AI, ML, and observability to manage your ever-growing infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-520/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The landscape of IT infrastructure is rapidly changing with AI and ML enhancing software development and orchestration. As systems scale, the need for advanced observability tools has become crucial. This transformation reveals gaps in current tools, affecting data volume, fidelity, and root cause analysis. To address these challenges, the article outlines four key technologies essential for modern observability. #AI #MachineLearning #Observability #ITInfrastructure #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Boosted Performance Engineering Productivity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2183/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:59:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2183/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the latest &amp;ldquo;Engineering Energizers&amp;rdquo; Q&amp;amp;A, we spotlight Zak Zimmerman, Director of Software Engineering at Salesforce. Zak leads the Data Cloud Performance Engineering team, enhancing how they analyze performance data and automate systems using AI tools. The team focuses on ensuring performance, scalability, and reliability within Data Cloud, addressing challenges from massive data influxes. They employ AI to streamline data processing and visualize insights more effectively. Learn how AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-pollination as a strategic advantage for forward-thinking organizations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2096/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2096/</guid>
      <description>Innovation is key for growing organizations, and fostering a culture of cross-pollination can enhance this. 🌱 By sharing knowledge across teams, companies can combat stagnation and encourage fresh ideas. Leaders play a vital role in creating an environment where employees feel safe to share and explore new concepts. 🤝 This approach not only boosts engagement but also helps teams understand how their work contributes to broader goals. #CrossPollination #Innovation #Teamwork #Leadership&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doing hybrid cloud right: Taking the complexity out of infrastructure management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-1995/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-1995/</guid>
      <description>Navigating hybrid cloud management can be challenging. As AI adoption increases, organizations must modernize their cloud infrastructure for effective governance and management. 🌐 Gartner predicts that by 2027, 90% of organizations will embrace hybrid cloud models, yet many face complexities due to fragmented tools and inconsistent processes. 🚧 To improve efficiency, organizations should empower platform teams to standardize workflows and enhance collaboration between infrastructure and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Diving into the results of the 2025 Developer Survey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2097/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2097/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting insights from the 2025 Developer Survey are here! Ryan and Eira speak with Erin Yepis from Stack Overflow about key findings. Notably, there is a decline in trust in AI tools among developers. The survey also highlights shifts in popular programming technologies and trends in salary growth for tech professionals. #DeveloperSurvey #TechTrends #AI #SalaryGrowth #ProgrammingInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the model: A data foundation for a trustworthy AI future in the US</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-522/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-522/</guid>
      <description>The White House&amp;rsquo;s “Winning the Race: America’s AI Action Plan” emphasizes AI as key to the U.S. economy and security. It highlights the need for a transparent data foundation to govern and trust AI technologies. The success of this plan relies on addressing data challenges related to evaluation, bias detection, and cybersecurity. Building a unified data ecosystem is crucial for innovation and accountability. #AIActionPlan #DataGovernance #Innovation #TrustworthyAI #USAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do AI coding tools help with imposter syndrome or make it worse?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2098/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2098/</guid>
      <description>AI coding tools can influence imposter syndrome in developers in complex ways. While tools like Copilot and Codex may ease self-doubt by accelerating learning, they can also lead to overreliance, affecting code quality and understanding. The pressure to continually upskill with these tools can intensify anxiety for some developers. #ImposterSyndrome #AICoding #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTrends #ContinuousLearning 🤖📈🖥️</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>America’s AI Action Plan</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-500/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 14:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-500/</guid>
      <description>🚀 On July 23, 2025, the White House released &amp;ldquo;Winning the AI Race: America’s AI Action Plan,&amp;rdquo; aiming to boost U.S. leadership in AI through 90+ federal policy actions. Key focuses include: - Promoting commercial AI solutions in federal procurement, especially for the DoD. - Streamlining processes for AI system approvals and leveraging existing platforms like Maven and Army Vantage. The plan emphasizes the role of testbeds for efficient AI deployment, ensuring systems meet mission-critical&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The innovation, leadership, and team agility inside U.S. Bank’s cloud journey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2099/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2099/</guid>
      <description>🌐 In the latest episode of Leaders of Code, industry experts discuss U.S. Bank&amp;rsquo;s transition from traditional banking to a multi-cloud strategy. 💡 The bank is focused on innovation while maintaining compliance in a regulated environment. Key topics include team empowerment, collaboration, and cloud migration strategies. 🤝 Leaders highlight the significance of transparency and continuous communication in driving successful change. #CloudComputing #DigitalTransformation #BankingInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming digital experiences: How Liferay&#39;s partnership with Elastic drives revenue and efficiency</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-523/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-523/</guid>
      <description>Liferay partners with Elastic to enhance digital experiences for complex business needs. Since 2015, Liferay has integrated Elasticsearch into its platform, enabling tailored search solutions that improve user interactions across marketing, sales, and services. This OEM partnership simplifies procurement by allowing clients to manage everything through a single agreement. The collaboration not only boosts efficiency but also supports revenue growth for Liferay, making it easier for clients to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
