<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1Password-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/1password-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1Password-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/1password-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bringing secure, just-in-time secrets to Cursor with 1Password</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14056/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14056/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the world of software development! 1Password and Cursor have partnered to create a new integration featuring a Hooks Script that enhances security for developers using AI. This allows secure, just-in-time access to secrets without hardcoding or exposing credentials. 🔒 With this new functionality, 1Password serves as the secure source for secrets, ensuring they are available only when needed and authorized by the user. This integration marks a significant step toward safer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Chasing Entropy Podcast Season One is in the Books</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13818/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13818/</guid>
      <description>Season One of the Chasing Entropy Podcast has wrapped up with 27 episodes featuring insights from CISOs and security leaders. The conversations focused on three key areas: the evolving role of the CISO, the impact of agentic AI, and the daily challenges of security work. The CISO position has expanded beyond mere security oversight to include strategic influence on product and business decisions. Guests highlighted the complexities of risk ownership and budget alignment, shedding light on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The hidden offboarding step draining your budget</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13445/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13445/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Is your IT offboarding process leaking budget? Many companies overlook a crucial step: managing SaaS licenses. Research shows that 38% of former employees still access prior accounts, leading to unnecessary costs. With 52% of employees using unsanctioned apps, it’s time to evaluate SaaS offboarding practices. Implementing a SaaS management platform can streamline deprovisioning and reduce wasted spend. 💼💰 Learn more about optimizing your offboarding process! #SaaS #ITManagement #Offboarding&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS and 1Password: Innovation in AI and beyond</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13230/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13230/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This year marks a significant evolution in the partnership between AWS and 1Password, focusing on secure access amid the rise of AI-driven development. 1Password is now a launch partner for Amazon Nova Act, enhancing secure workflows and simplifying tasks like logging into web apps. 🔑 Additionally, the MCP Server for Trelica improves SaaS visibility within AWS, while AWS Secrets Sync offers seamless integration for managing credentials. This collaboration emphasizes a shared vision for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Social Work to Social Impact: Growing at 1Password</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13040/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13040/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Transitioning from social work to a role at 1Password has been a transformative journey. After seven years in community mental healthcare, the author sought to apply their skills in a new environment. They took a position in People Operations at a cybersecurity startup, where they learned to adapt quickly. Now at 1Password, they focus on corporate social responsibility, enhancing community impact through educational programs and corporate giving. This shift allows for continued advocacy for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying credential security on ChatGPT Atlas</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13047/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13047/</guid>
      <description>AI-powered browsers are changing the way we interact online, making tasks faster and simpler. 🌐 1Password is now available on OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT Atlas, enhancing security and ease of use. The new onboarding process allows users to start quickly, ensuring credentials and data remain protected. 🔒 You can pin 1Password for easy access, and it seamlessly integrates with Atlas for a smooth experience. Get started today! 🚀 #1Password #ChatGPT #AISecurity #DataPrivacy #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving in-page notifications in the 1Password browser extension</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12986/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12986/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for the 1Password browser extension! As it enters its eighth year, the in-page notification system is getting a significant overhaul. Users can now receive multiple notifications at once, improving their experience when managing tasks like saving credentials or detecting breaches. The new system allows notifications to stay visible in a stack, enhancing usability while you navigate. The rollout of these features is underway, with further refinements planned for the future&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating SaaS management: Extend IAM to regain time, trust, and control</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12899/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12899/</guid>
      <description>Security leaders face challenges in managing increasing SaaS apps and shadow IT. Automation is key in enhancing visibility and control. Many companies lack insight into their SaaS usage, leading to security risks. 52% of employees admit to downloading apps without IT approval. SaaS Management Platforms (SMPs) can help by automating the discovery of applications and managing licenses efficiently. Tools like Trelica by 1Password offer a comprehensive view of apps and users. Learn how automation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now available via Renaissance: 1Password Enterprise Password Manager – MSP Edition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12890/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12890/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for MSPs! 1Password Enterprise Password Manager – MSP Edition is now available through Renaissance. This partnership enhances access to enterprise-grade credential security while streamlining procurement and billing processes. The solution helps MSPs manage client credentials effectively, closing the Access-Trust Gap created by unmanaged credentials and shadow IT risks. With features designed for MSP workflows, 1Password improves operational efficiency and profitability. Learn&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the wheel with Max Verstappen and Yuki Tsunoda</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12842/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12842/</guid>
      <description>Dive into episode five of &lt;em&gt;Securing the Win&lt;/em&gt;, where Chris Medland highlights the teamwork behind Oracle Red Bull Racing&amp;rsquo;s success. 🏎️ Max Verstappen and Yuki Tsunoda share insights on how communication, trust, and collaboration drive performance on the track. The importance of secure access and quick feedback loops is crucial for racing success. 🛠️🔑 Discover the behind-the-scenes efforts that support these drivers and keep the team ahead. #Formula1 #RedBullRacing #Teamwork #Innovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing MCP servers with 1Password: Stop credential exposure in your agent configurations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12843/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12843/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Securing MCP servers is crucial to prevent credential leaks. A recent article highlights how to use 1Password to safeguard sensitive information in your projects. Instead of hardcoding API tokens in configuration files, developers can reference secrets stored in 1Password vaults. This method enhances security by injecting credentials at runtime, eliminating plaintext exposure. The approach is beneficial for various AI tools and is easy to implement using the 1Password CLI. For detailed&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s new in 1Password Enterprise Password Manager - Q4, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12765/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12765/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are here for the 1Password Enterprise Password Manager! This latest release focuses on usability, visibility, and control, helping organizations deploy confidently and manage effectively. New App Unlock presets offer admins flexibility while maintaining security. Onboarding is easier with the new Browser Extension policy and Guided Setup, ensuring a smoother user experience. Enhanced policy controls provide admins with fine-grained management of credentials, improving&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Belonging as a catalyst for high performance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12168/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12168/</guid>
      <description>At 1Password, a culture of belonging is key to our success. Since launching Employee Resource Groups (ERGs) in 2021 and expanding to Employee Community Groups (ECGs) in 2023, we’ve built strong connections that enhance our high-performance culture. 🌟 Our ERGs and ECGs, now over 1,300 members strong, promote shared values and diverse perspectives. Recent events have showcased how high performance can look different for everyone, fostering an inclusive environment where all can thrive. 🤝 We’ve&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password habits are worsening, but security leaders see a path to passwordless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12078/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12078/</guid>
      <description>Poorly managed passwords continue to pose significant risks for security teams. The latest findings from the 1Password Annual Report 2025 highlight that 66% of employees exhibit poor password hygiene, contributing to security challenges. However, there is a shift towards passwordless authentication, with 89% of security professionals encouraging the use of passkeys. This strategy aims to minimize user exposure to credentials and enhance security. To address these risks, IT teams are advised&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A simpler, faster way to unlock 1Password</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12080/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12080/</guid>
      <description>🚀 1Password has introduced a new, faster way to unlock your account, enhancing convenience without sacrificing security. You can now unlock 1Password right alongside your device using methods like Face ID or a PIN. This feature is optional and allows you to choose your preferred balance of convenience and security. 🔐 New security presets let you customize your unlock experience, ranging from automatic unlocking with your device to stricter settings for added security. 📱 For peace of mind,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Red Bull Racing CIO Matt Cadieux’s cyber resilience playbook</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12079/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12079/</guid>
      <description>🚗 In Episode 4 of &amp;ldquo;Securing the Win,&amp;rdquo; Matt Cadieux, CIO of Oracle Red Bull Racing, discusses the importance of cyber resilience in Formula 1. 🔐 He emphasizes that speed relies on trust, with a robust digital backbone protecting against threats. Cadieux&amp;rsquo;s approach involves designing for failure and continuously verifying trust. 📊 As the team evolves, they implement layered security measures and focus on business continuity, ensuring safety and efficiency in operations. 🤝 Strategic&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>70% of IT and security pros say SSO is falling short – Here’s how to close the gap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11926/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11926/</guid>
      <description>🔍 IT and security teams face challenges in managing SaaS applications, leading to wasted resources and compliance issues. Recent research by 1Password highlights that many apps operate without IT oversight. 📊 Key findings include that 52% of employees use unauthorized apps, and 34% of company apps lack SSO protection. 💡 To improve SaaS governance, IT leaders should invest in continuous discovery of shadow IT, enforce SSO where possible, and automate access management. Learn more about how&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Identity Security taxonomy for Agentic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11494/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11494/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Understanding Agentic AI is crucial for identity security. This new AI paradigm allows agents to interact dynamically with tools, blending application and user roles. The article outlines a taxonomy to help determine specific security measures based on three categories: 1. Type of AI agent (Browser vs. Programmatic) 2. Where the agent is running (Endpoint vs. Remote) 3. Who the agent serves (Employee, Internal Company, or External Customer) 1Password emphasizes that these classifications&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The enterprise AI crisis: Unsanctioned tools and unenforced policies</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11495/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11495/</guid>
      <description>The 1Password Annual Report 2025 highlights a growing &amp;ldquo;Access-Trust Gap&amp;rdquo; in organizations due to unsanctioned AI tools, patchy access controls, and unmanaged devices. 🔍 Key findings show that while 73% of employees are encouraged to use AI, 37% do not follow company policies. This gap poses risks to compliance and security. 📊 Companies need to establish clear AI governance, maintain an inventory of tools, and educate employees on safe practices. 1Password offers solutions like Trelica for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing new .env file support in 1Password environments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11444/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11444/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the new .env destination in 1Password environments! 🌐 This feature allows developers to securely use and collaborate on .env files directly from the desktop app. It provides a safe workspace for managing project secrets without the risks of plaintext storage. 🔐 Available in beta for Mac and Linux, it integrates seamlessly with AWS Secrets Manager, enhancing collaboration and simplifying workflows. 💻 Experience a secure way to handle environment variables today! #1Password&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed and security: Mark Hazelton on protecting Oracle Red Bull Racing’s most valuable asset – its data</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11445/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11445/</guid>
      <description>In Episode 2 of &amp;ldquo;Securing the Win,&amp;rdquo; Mark Hazelton, CSO of Oracle Red Bull Racing, discusses the impact of a $100 million data breach on Formula 1® security practices. He highlights the shift from insider threats to digital risks and emphasizes the importance of a zero trust approach. With operations spanning multiple sites, the team generates vast data, making cybersecurity a performance necessity. Hazelton underscores that effective security is essential for speed and success. Learn more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1Password for Good: Giving back during cybersecurity awareness month</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11343/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11343/</guid>
      <description>🌐 October is Cybersecurity Awareness Month! 1Password has donated $100,000 to six organizations focusing on technology education, digital literacy, and online safety for young people. These initiatives aim to equip the next generation with essential skills for a digital world. The supported organizations include Actua, Childnet, Digital Moment, Mission Bit, Visions of Science, and Team4Tech. Each plays a vital role in empowering youth through STEM and online safety education. Learn more about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Utah Mammoth and Utah Jazz score with identity security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11344/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11344/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for sports and cybersecurity! 1Password has partnered with Smith Entertainment Group, the parent company of the Utah Jazz and Utah Mammoth, to enhance identity security. This collaboration aims to provide secure, fast access to tools and data for teams, ensuring they can perform effectively on and off the court. The Extended Access Management suite will help both organizations and individuals safeguard their digital identities with ease. 🏀🧊 Learn more about this innovative&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside Oracle Red Bull Racing: CEO and Team Principal Laurent Mekies on the people, process, and technology that power performance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11151/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11151/</guid>
      <description>🚗💨 In the premiere of &amp;ldquo;Securing the Win,&amp;rdquo; Laurent Mekies, CEO and Team Principal of Oracle Red Bull Racing, discusses the critical role of people in achieving success in Formula 1®. He emphasizes that performance is rooted in trust and communication. 🔧 The team uses 1Password to streamline operations and enhance security, allowing focus on performance rather than cybersecurity. Mekies believes that every team member contributes to the quest for excellence, underscoring the importance of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the credential risk gap for AI agents using a browser</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10534/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10534/</guid>
      <description>AI agents are increasingly taking on tasks in browsers, but this raises security concerns regarding credential management. As these agents operate, they need access to sensitive information like passwords and API keys, leading to risks of credential sprawl and exposure. 🔑💻 1Password introduces Secure Agentic Autofill, which allows credentials to be securely injected into browsers without exposing them to AI agents. This method ensures that sensitive data remains protected and requires human&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft and Dropbox password managers are sunsetting: What it means and what to do next</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10498/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10498/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Attention users! Microsoft and Dropbox are discontinuing their built-in password managers, raising concerns about digital security. Without a password manager, you may risk reusing passwords, increasing vulnerability to credential theft. 💻🔒 Microsoft Authenticator will sunset in August 2025, while Dropbox Passwords will end on October 28, 2025. Users can still access saved passwords via Microsoft accounts and export data before the deadline for Dropbox. As security threats grow, consider&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From hackathon nerves to internship wins: Kavya’s journey at 1Password</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9915/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9915/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting journey alert! Meet Kavya, a UBC student who transitioned from a business major to a passionate Computer Science learner. She participated in cmd-f, a hackathon for underrepresented genders in tech, where her team created REALM, a wellness app that integrates personalized health insights and security through Passage by 1Password. 🛡️ After winning the hackathon, Kavya secured an internship at 1Password, where she thrives in a supportive remote culture while contributing to developer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1Password now available in Comet, the AI-powered browser by Perplexity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9725/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9725/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for online security! 1Password has launched its browser extension for Comet, the AI-powered browser by Perplexity. This integration ensures your credentials and sensitive data are protected with top-notch encryption. 🔒 With 1Password in Comet, you can enjoy privacy-first browsing, seamless autofill for logins, and strong password generation—all while keeping your information secure. Explore the AI-powered internet confidently! #1Password #CometBrowser #OnlineSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1Password announces new integration with Zscaler</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9488/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9488/</guid>
      <description>🔒 1Password has announced a new integration with Zscaler, aimed at enhancing Zero Trust practices for their shared customers. This integration allows users to secure access to applications from both managed and unmanaged devices, ensuring only trusted devices can authenticate. Companies with active accounts can set this up via the 1Password Marketplace. Discover more about this integration today! #1Password #Zscaler #ZeroTrust #Cybersecurity #Integration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breaking the mold: Why more women should consider a career in sales</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9449/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9449/</guid>
      <description>🚀 More women are breaking into sales, challenging outdated perceptions and proving success isn&amp;rsquo;t gender-specific. Many women excel in roles that require problem-solving and relationship-building, making sales a promising path. With the potential for financial freedom, transferable skills, and career growth, it&amp;rsquo;s an opportunity worth exploring. 🌟 If you&amp;rsquo;re ready to step into a rewarding career, consider sales! #WomenInSales #CareerGrowth #SalesOpportunities #DiversityInBusiness #Empowerment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What security leaders need to know about mergers and acquisitions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7681/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7681/</guid>
      <description>Mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) present unique security challenges for teams. The integration of two companies involves managing devices, applications, and data, often exposing serious vulnerabilities. Notable cases, like Verizon and Yahoo, highlight the consequences of security oversights that can lead to costly data breaches. Due diligence is crucial. Security leaders should be involved from the start, focusing on identifying risks through thorough discovery and validation processes&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and security at Black Hat: 5 key takeaways from a security expert panel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7251/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7251/</guid>
      <description>🌐 At Black Hat, security leaders discussed the rise of AI in cybersecurity, highlighting key challenges and strategies. 1️⃣ Zero trust principles need to evolve to include AI agents. 2️⃣ Cybercriminals are increasingly using AI for more sophisticated attacks. 3️⃣ Many organizations lack visibility into their AI usage, leading to risks. 4️⃣ Business demand for AI is outpacing security preparedness. 5️⃣ AI can enhance security but also introduces new vulnerabilities. Effective governance is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clickjacking: What it means for 1Password users</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7252/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7252/</guid>
      <description>🔒 1Password has released an important update (version 8.11.7) addressing clickjacking, a technique that can trick users into autofilling sensitive information. This vulnerability does not put 1Password systems at risk, but the update provides users with better control by introducing confirmation alerts for autofill actions. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to update to the latest version and keep autofill enabled for enhanced security. Stay safe online! 🛡️ #1Password #CyberSecurity #Clickjacking #DataProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Do any CISOs feel lucky?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6317/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6317/</guid>
      <description>Cybersecurity events like the RSA Conference and &amp;ldquo;Hacker Summer Camp&amp;rdquo; in Vegas are crucial for industry leaders. This year, CISOs expressed heightened concerns over nation-state threats and the impact of AI on security. Key discussions included resilience and anti-fragility in cybersecurity, with panels addressing AI’s role in enterprise threats. Informal settings also allowed for deeper conversations among CISOs about the practical use of AI and data protection challenges. #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to lead with confidence in the AI era: a conversation with Nancy Wang, VP, Engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5134/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5134/</guid>
      <description>Artificial Intelligence (AI) is transforming leadership and collaboration at 1Password. In a recent conversation, Nancy Wang, VP of Engineering, discussed how AI enhances productivity by handling repetitive tasks, allowing teams to focus on critical decision-making and user trust. She emphasizes the importance of human skills like empathy and trust in leadership, especially as AI becomes more integrated into our work. To foster a culture of confidence with AI, Nancy encourages curiosity and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Device Trust Check makes browser extension enforcement easier</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5135/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5135/</guid>
      <description>🔒 1Password has launched the new Device Trust Check to enhance security in managing browser extensions. This feature allows admins to ensure the 1Password browser extension remains installed and active on user devices. If the extension is missing, users receive prompts to restore it before access to the desktop app is denied. The integration between the Extended Device Compliance feature and EPM strengthens security enforcement continuously, closing gaps for potential compliance issues&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purpose, performance, and trust: Inside the culture powering 1Password’s next chapter</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4960/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4960/</guid>
      <description>At 1Password, trust is central to our mission. We&amp;rsquo;ve established a culture focused on shared purpose, clarity, and accountability, prioritizing customer success. Our high-performance culture promotes collaboration and innovation, allowing us to deliver secure, cutting-edge products quickly. This commitment to excellence fosters an environment where employees can learn and grow. Curious about joining a team that values purpose and teamwork? Explore opportunities at 1Password! 🌟🔐 #1Password&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now available on Pax8 Marketplace: 1Password Enterprise Password Manager - MSP Edition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4961/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4961/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Managed Service Providers! 1Password Enterprise Password Manager - MSP Edition is now available on Pax8 Marketplace. This tool helps MSPs enhance client security, streamline operations, and boost profitability through a user-friendly interface and advanced features. Key benefits include: 🔒 End-to-end encryption for client data 📈 Customized security policies for each client 💼 Centralized management for operational efficiency Start your 14-day free trial today! #1Password&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The security principles guiding 1Password’s approach to AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4745/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4745/</guid>
      <description>AI is reshaping our work landscape, bringing both opportunities and responsibilities, especially in security. 1Password emphasizes building trustworthy AI while maintaining core values of privacy and transparency. Key principles include: 🔒 Keeping secrets secure through strong encryption. 📜 Ensuring predictable authorization processes. 📊 Maintaining audit trails for AI actions. 1Password is committed to integrating AI securely and effectively. #AI #CyberSecurity #1Password #DataPrivacy #Trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify access reviews with Trelica by 1Password</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4679/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4679/</guid>
      <description>Managing access in today&amp;rsquo;s SaaS environment is challenging for organizations. Each time an employee joins or leaves, IT and security teams must adjust permissions to maintain security and compliance. 🔒 Access reviews are essential for verifying user access and meeting compliance standards like SOC 2 and ISO 27001. However, traditional methods often rely on spreadsheets, leading to incomplete processes and errors. 📊 Trelica by 1Password simplifies access reviews with automated workflows, a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Omdia recommends Extended Access Management to secure agentic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2506/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2506/</guid>
      <description>Omdia&amp;rsquo;s recent report highlights significant security challenges in managing access for agentic AI. With the rise of application, device, and identity sprawl, organizations face increased risk. AI agents require extensive access but lack secure management tools, leading to potential data leaks and unauthorized actions. Omdia recommends five strategies to secure access, including the need for robust measures specifically for AI agents. 1Password Extended Access Management offers a solution by&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
