<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lyft-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/lyft-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lyft-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:34:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/lyft-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Migrating Lyft’s Android Codebase to Kotlin</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9494/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 20:34:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9494/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Lyft has successfully migrated its Android codebase to Kotlin, a journey that began in 2018. The Rider, Driver, and Urban Solutions apps are now fully Kotlin-based. This transition offers benefits like concise code, faster compile speeds with the K2 compiler, and support for modern UI frameworks like Compose. To manage the migration, Lyft utilized a tool called Migration Tracker, which monitors progress and helps automate the process. Challenges included issues with the migration tool and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intern Experience at Lyft</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5128/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5128/</guid>
      <description>🚗✨ Discover the journey of two data scientists, Morteza Taiebat and Han Gong, who started as interns at Lyft and now contribute to impactful projects. They share insights on their experiences, focusing on sustainability and driver loyalty. Their work includes evaluating electric vehicle (EV) adoption and designing incentive strategies for drivers. If you&amp;rsquo;re considering an internship at Lyft, their stories highlight the growth opportunities and collaborative culture that await you! 🌱📊&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Dispatch in a Ridesharing Problem Space</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2045/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:43:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2045/</guid>
      <description>🚗💡 Ridesharing platforms like Lyft tackle complex matching challenges daily. Each rider and driver represents a unique piece in a dynamic puzzle, requiring real-time solutions for efficient urban mobility. Graph theory helps model these matches, particularly through bipartite graphs. This allows for flexible connections based on factors like distance and time. Lyft&amp;rsquo;s dispatch team continually processes millions of potential decisions, aiming to optimize pickups and driver earnings. Stay tuned&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
