<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HashiCorp-Solutions-Engineering-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/sources/hashicorp-solutions-engineering-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HashiCorp-Solutions-Engineering-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 11:20:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/sources/hashicorp-solutions-engineering-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Orchestrating Java Spring Boot applications with Nomad</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-7582/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 11:20:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-7582/</guid>
      <description>Discover how HashiCorp Nomad can streamline the orchestration of Java Spring Boot applications alongside modern workloads. This article highlights Nomad&amp;rsquo;s ability to manage diverse applications without requiring complete rewrites, simplifying deployment and scaling processes. Learn about the benefits of using Nomad&amp;rsquo;s Java driver, service discovery, and externalized configuration for efficient application management. 🚀 #Java #SpringBoot #HashiCorp #Nomad #ApplicationManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify file encryption with HashiCorp Vault transit engine</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-7141/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:31:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-7141/</guid>
      <description>🔐 Research institutions face challenges in protecting sensitive data while promoting collaboration. HashiCorp Vault&amp;rsquo;s transit engine offers a solution by providing encryption as a service, allowing unique keys for researchers. Key applications include data protection, file encryption, and compliance with regulations like GDPR and HIPAA. Vault supports both SDK and RESTful API for easy integration. Learn more about how to set up Vault for file encryption and manage sensitive data effectively&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
