<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Railway-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/sources/railway-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Railway-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/sources/railway-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How We Oops-Proofed Infrastructure Deletion on Railway</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-7508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-7508/</guid>
      <description>Railway enhances cloud infrastructure safety with a focus on staged changes and undoable deletions. This approach ensures that destructive actions, such as deleting infrastructure, are carefully managed from the dashboard to the underlying physical resources. Learn more about how these methods protect users and improve overall reliability. #CloudInfrastructure #SafetyFirst #TechInnovation 🌐🔧💡</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring Back the Free Plan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-7294/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-7294/</guid>
      <description>We’ve re-introduced the free plan to all new Railway users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway MCP - Stateful, Serverful, Pay-per-use Infrastructure</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-6360/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-6360/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! A new Railway MCP server has been introduced, enabling AI coding agents to deploy applications and manage infrastructure directly from code editors. This innovative approach aims to streamline the development process. With this tool, developers can enhance their productivity by integrating deployment and infrastructure management seamlessly. #RailwayMCP #AICoding #AppDevelopment #TechInnovation #InfrastructureManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hackathon: Winners Announced!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-6361/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/article-6361/</guid>
      <description>🚆 The winners of the first Railway User Hackathon have been announced! This event showcased innovative projects aimed at improving railway user experiences. Several projects received honorable mentions for their creativity and potential impact. Congratulations to all participants for their hard work and dedication! 🎉 #Hackathon #RailwayInnovation #UserExperience #Winners #TechForGood</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
