<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The-New-Stack on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/the-new-stack/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The-New-Stack on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:00:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/the-new-stack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chrome Switches on AI: The Future of Browsing Begins Now</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9777/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 17:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9777/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Google has begun rolling out AI features in its Chrome browser, starting with Mac and Windows users in the US. 🌐 The new Gemini integration includes AI Mode from the address bar, connections to Google apps, and an ability to ask questions about web pages. 📱 These features will extend to Android and iOS soon, with plans for &amp;ldquo;agentic capabilities&amp;rdquo; that allow AI to perform tasks on users&amp;rsquo; behalf. 💬 Parisa Tabriz, Chrome&amp;rsquo;s GM, emphasized the shift toward a more proactive browsing experience&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zencoder Lets Developers Bring Their CLI Coding Agent of Choice To Its Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9778/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9778/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Zencoder is evolving! The platform now allows developers to integrate their preferred CLI coding agents, like OpenAI’s Codex and Anthropic’s Claude, into its environment. This shift enables users to utilize familiar tools while Zencoder focuses on enhancing other development processes, such as testing and code consistency. For more details, see how Zencoder is transforming coding workflows! 💻✨ #Zencoder #Coding #Developers #AI #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cautionary Tale of the Browser Wars and Why Business Transformations Often Fail</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9779/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 16:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9779/</guid>
      <description>Business transformations are frequent, but many fail, wasting trillions annually. A historical example is the Browser Wars, where Netscape lost market share to Internet Explorer due to a complete rewrite of their browser, losing valuable knowledge in the process. This emphasizes the importance of understanding existing systems before making drastic changes, a principle known as &amp;ldquo;Chesterton&amp;rsquo;s Fence.&amp;rdquo; Before removing or overhauling, it&amp;rsquo;s vital to recognize the reasons behind existing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Containers That Could Be Essential for Your Small Business</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9767/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 14:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9767/</guid>
      <description>Discover how Docker containers can streamline operations for your small business! 🚀 This article highlights the benefits of using containers for tasks like deployment, management, and backups. It suggests several essential containers, including: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Nextcloud&lt;/strong&gt; - A self-hosted cloud solution that offers storage, calendars, and more. Ideal for those looking to move away from big-name services. ☁️ 2. &lt;strong&gt;Invoice Ninja&lt;/strong&gt; - A user-friendly invoicing tool that simplifies billing with customizable&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Changes Developer Portfolios</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9768/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9768/</guid>
      <description>🌐 During the hiring process, Greg Fuller from Skillsoft/Codecademy emphasizes the importance of using AI in developer portfolios. He believes that modern software development requires AI tools. 📄 Portfolios remain vital, especially for junior developers, showcasing adaptability and the use of AI in projects. Fuller advises candidates to explain their AI usage and the technologies involved. 💻 Sean C. Davis from Netlify notes that while portfolios are still relevant, AI tools may shift their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 Reasons Agentic AI Is Failing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9744/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 19:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9744/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Businesses are increasingly adopting AI agents to enhance productivity and streamline tasks. However, successful implementation can be challenging. Key reasons for failure include: 1️⃣ Unrealistic expectations about AI capabilities. 2️⃣ Poor prioritization of use cases. Understanding these factors is essential for effective deployment. #AIAgents #BusinessProductivity #TechTrends #AIImplementation #DigitalTransformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Chasing Low-Stakes Incidents: Let AI Do It</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9745/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9745/</guid>
      <description>🔧 Incident management engineers face overwhelming workloads, often addressing low-priority incidents that divert their attention from critical issues. This can lead to delays during major incidents and impact revenue. 🌐 Implementing AI and automation can help reduce manual tasks, allowing teams to focus on high-priority incidents. Understanding the categorization of incidents, from P1 to P5, is essential for effective management. 💡 By leveraging these technologies, organizations can improve&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How InfluxDB 3 Brings Processing Directly Into the Database</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9729/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9729/</guid>
      <description>InfluxDB 3 transforms database capabilities by integrating intelligence and processing directly into its architecture. With a Python-powered Processing Engine, it enables real-time analytics and active data analysis, moving beyond simple storage. This allows users to monitor complex systems and execute actions instantly. Implementing this at the edge reduces overhead, enhancing efficiency and minimizing points of failure. #InfluxDB #DataAnalytics #RealTimeProcessing #EdgeComputing #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Guide To Fluent Bit’s Health Check API Endpoints</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9730/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9730/</guid>
      <description>Explore the capabilities of Fluent Bit and its Health Check API Endpoints! 📊 This guide details how to implement health checks for containers and Kubernetes pods. It emphasizes the importance of responding to health probes to ensure application stability. A typical healthy response includes an HTTP status code of 200. Learn how to enable a web server in Fluent Bit for effective monitoring. #FluentBit #Kubernetes #HealthCheck #Monitoring #Observability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Python CLI Tool Catches MCP Server Issues Before Agents Do</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9731/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 16:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9731/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Microsoft Research&amp;rsquo;s MCP Interviewer! This new open-source Python CLI tool helps developers maintain Model Context Protocol (MCP) servers. It identifies potential issues before they impact AI agents. Key features include: - Constraint Checking to ensure compliance - Functional Testing with LLM agents - In-depth reporting for usability and performance MCP Interviewer supports effective collaboration between diverse AI agents. #MicrosoftResearch #MCPInterviewer #AI #OpenSource&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Code Generation’s Unexpected Costs for Dev Teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9732/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 15:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9732/</guid>
      <description>Recent research reveals that AI coding tools may not enhance developer productivity as expected. According to METR, developers take 19% longer when using these tools, despite believing they are more efficient. A significant 76% of developers must refactor AI-generated code due to issues like inaccuracies and poor quality, impacting overall productivity. To address these challenges, join the webinar on Oct. 9, 2025, featuring experts discussing ways to overcome bottlenecks in engineering&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Elixir and Phoenix, a JS Alternative</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9719/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 13:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9719/</guid>
      <description>Discover Elixir, a web development alternative to JavaScript that offers faster development and lower costs. 🚀 Developed by Josè Valim in 2011, Elixir runs on the Erlang VM, excelling in concurrency and fault-tolerance. Its Phoenix framework is ideal for building apps needing thousands of simultaneous connections, like chat apps and live dashboards. However, for projects requiring rich client-side interactivity, JavaScript remains a strong option. While my initial experience with Elixir and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hidden Costs of Rushing Open Source Upgrades</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9707/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 21:00:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9707/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The latest Open Source Security and Risk Analysis Report (OSSRA) reveals significant challenges in managing open source components. 🔍 With 97% of scanned codebases containing these components, many organizations face risks from transitive dependencies, often unaware of their usage. 📉 Nearly 86% of codebases have vulnerable components, while 91% are using outdated packages. This poses security threats and operational burdens for teams. Understanding and managing these risks is essential for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agent-Infused MongoDB Tackles Application Modernization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9700/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 20:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9700/</guid>
      <description>🚀 MongoDB has launched its new Application Modernization Platform (AMP) to help businesses modernize legacy applications into scalable services. AMP offers tools for code analysis, conversion, testing, and data migration, supporting various legacy technologies like Oracle and SQL Server. The platform aims to enhance enterprise applications with modern AI techniques and includes a team of experts for user support. This approach may significantly benefit industries like finance and FinTech&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetalBear’s Mirrord Gives AI Agents a Staging Environment To Test Their Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9687/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:30:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9687/</guid>
      <description>MetalBear’s Mirrord is enhancing the way developers test Kubernetes applications. It allows coding directly against a staging environment by intercepting local processes, eliminating the need for local setups. This streamlines the testing process, especially as AI coding agents increase the volume of code to be tested. Mirrord addresses the challenge of integration testing and reduces friction in the development cycle, which is crucial for rapid iteration in today’s competitive landscape&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why the Edge Isn’t Just ‘Cloud Computing, But Closer’</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9688/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9688/</guid>
      <description>The article explores the evolution of enterprise software, highlighting five significant shifts over 30 years, including agile practices and cloud adoption. It emphasizes that containerization at the edge mirrors these shifts, enabling faster deployment and real-time data processing. The edge poses unique challenges, such as limited IT staff, physical constraints, security issues, and connectivity problems. Understanding these factors is crucial for effective deployment. 🌐💻🔧📊 #EdgeComputing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Agent in the Middle To Ride Herd on Wayward AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9689/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9689/</guid>
      <description>Development teams face pressure to adopt AI agents, but concerns about their unpredictable behavior and potential risks are rising. Ilya Sutskever from OpenAI warns that these agents could become &amp;ldquo;ticking time bombs,&amp;rdquo; highlighting the need for better security measures. Eve Security aims to address these challenges with their agent-in-the-loop technology, which monitors agent actions while minimizing false alerts. CISOs express concerns about connecting AI to sensitive systems, emphasizing the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal Developer Portal vs. Platform: What’s the Difference?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9690/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9690/</guid>
      <description>Navigating the complex landscape of DevOps and cloud-native technologies can be challenging for developers. This article explores the roles of Internal Developer Platforms (IDPs) and developer portals. IDPs streamline software development by integrating tools and automating workflows. They simplify deployment and reduce cognitive load, enabling developers to focus on coding. In contrast, developer portals serve as user-friendly interfaces, centralizing access to resources and documentation&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving 3 Enterprise AI Problems Developers Face</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9661/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9661/</guid>
      <description>🔍 A recent Stack Overflow survey reveals that 24% of developers feel happy at work, an increase from 20% last year. 📈 Interestingly, 78.5% of developers are now using AI tools regularly, although trust in AI-generated outputs is declining. 🛠️ Jody Bailey from Stack Overflow notes that better AI tools could enable more people to innovate and solve user problems effectively. #DeveloperSurvey #AI #TechTrends #Innovation #StackOverflow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Launches a New GPT-5 Model for Its Codex Coding Agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9650/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 17:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9650/</guid>
      <description>🚀 OpenAI has launched a major update to Codex, introducing GPT-5-Codex optimized for coding tasks. This update includes a rebuilt Codex CLI, new IDE extensions for tools like VS Code, and GitHub integration for code reviews. Access is available for ChatGPT Plus, Pro, Business, Edu, and Enterprise users with varying usage limits. Notably, GPT-5-Codex features a self-contained router and can operate autonomously on complex problems for extended periods. It aims to enhance coding efficiency&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 Best Practices for Building MCP Servers in Production</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9651/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9651/</guid>
      <description>The article discusses the evolving landscape of generative AI in 2025, focusing on the Model Context Protocol (MCP) as a standard for AI integration in enterprises. It outlines 15 best practices for developing MCP servers, emphasizing clear server boundaries, stateless design, and appropriate transport methods. Key points include the importance of idempotent tool design and robust security measures. For those involved in AI development, these practices aim to enhance system interactions and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Agentic AI Orchestration Is Key To Managing AI Complexity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9652/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 15:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9652/</guid>
      <description>Orkes has emerged as a significant player in AI orchestration, integrating data and microservices into one platform. 🤖 The founders emphasize that agentic AI orchestration is crucial for managing complex AI workflows. This approach enables organizations to build and scale AI agents effectively. Originally created for Netflix Conductor, Orkes now supports long-running workflows, maintaining state better than many frameworks. 🌐 Learn more about how Orkes is shaping the future of AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Build Agentic AI That Ships</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9640/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 14:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9640/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Building successful AI requires understanding common pitfalls. Recent reports show a 95% failure rate in enterprise AI rollouts, not due to technology itself, but from integration challenges. Only 5% achieve their revenue targets by leveraging AI effectively. Key reasons for failure include: assuming technology is complete, underestimating organizational complexity, and pursuing unworthy use cases. Addressing these issues is crucial for navigating the AI landscape. #AI #TechIntegration&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic AI Is Key To Preventing Costly AI Hallucinations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9635/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9635/</guid>
      <description>AI hallucinations can lead to significant risks for businesses, with inaccuracies affecting efficiency and trust. A recent study shows these inaccuracies occur between 0.7% and 29.9% of the time, depending on the AI model used. An example highlights how a manufacturer faced issues when their AI assistant provided incorrect troubleshooting advice due to gaps in its knowledge base. To combat this, the team developed enhanced checks and validation processes, leading to improved accuracy and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the 11-Year-Old Whose Code Was Adopted by a Gaming Giant</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9634/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 13:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9634/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Meet Damir Buldakov, an 11-year-old programmer from Vietnam making waves in the tech world! He developed a Scratch language extension for Playgama, a gaming platform with over 300 million users. This connection allows young coders to share their projects globally. Damir emphasizes that age isn&amp;rsquo;t a barrier to knowledge and hopes to inspire other kids to pursue their coding dreams. 💻✨ #YoungCoders #TechInnovation #Programming #Inspiration #Gaming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your AI Prompts Are Programming the Future So Use Them Wisely</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9632/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 17:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9632/</guid>
      <description>🤖 Every interaction with AI shapes its future. The article emphasizes the need for a more compassionate approach in our exchanges. AI systems learn from feedback much like children do. Instead of criticism, we should encourage growth through constructive responses. This shift in mindset can lead to better AI interactions and outputs. Let&amp;rsquo;s treat AI as a learning partner rather than a flawed tool. 🛠️💡 #ArtificialIntelligence #GrowthMindset #TechEthics #AIInteractions #DigitalLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warp Code Gets Closer to an Emacs for the Modern AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9633/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9633/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Warp Code is evolving as a modern terminal, integrating LLM capabilities to enhance productivity. With a redesigned UI in Rust, it offers efficient tools like file views and search options. The latest features include enhanced terminal commands and agent profiles for better coding experiences. Explore how Warp is moving closer to an all-in-one solution for developers. #WarpCode #TerminalTools #AIIntegration #Coding #DevCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Self-Host Your Notes With Trilium and Docker</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9630/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 14:00:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9630/</guid>
      <description>Looking for a reliable notes app without third-party dependence? 📝 The article explores using Trilium and Docker for self-hosted note-taking. It highlights Trilium&amp;rsquo;s features like a tree structure, WYSIWYG editor, note versioning, and strong encryption. While there’s no official mobile app, it works well on Linux and macOS within a home network. Setup involves installing Docker and deploying the server with a simple command. Learn more about optimizing your note-taking experience! 🔧💻&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 Popular npm Packages Compromised in Attack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9631/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 13:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9631/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Aikido Security has uncovered a serious security breach involving 18 popular npm packages, which have been compromised to include malicious code. These packages, with over 2 billion downloads weekly, can silently intercept crypto and web3 activities, directing funds to attacker-controlled accounts. Key affected packages include chalk, debug, and supports-color. For developers using these tools, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to check for updates and security patches. #CyberSecurity #npm #Malware&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ServiceNow Says Windsurf Gave Its Engineers a 10% Productivity Boost</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9620/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 20:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9620/</guid>
      <description>ServiceNow&amp;rsquo;s CTO, Pat Casey, shared insights on the company&amp;rsquo;s unique approach to infrastructure. Unlike many firms, 90% of ServiceNow&amp;rsquo;s workloads run on their own physical hardware. This strategy allows effective management of their AI infrastructure. The switch from GitHub Copilot to Windsurf has improved developer productivity by 10%. Casey emphasized the importance of reliable infrastructure for AI tasks. 🌐💻 #ServiceNow #AI #Productivity #TechNews #Infrastructure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your APIs Are Costing More Than You Think</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9609/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 17:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9609/</guid>
      <description>APIs play a crucial role in modern software, but their costs can be hidden within complex cloud bills and inefficient practices. Traditional cost monitoring often fails to identify the true drivers of API spend. Steve Rodda from Ambassador highlights issues with historical analysis, which can delay necessary actions for months. To optimize costs effectively, organizations need to shift towards continuous, automated monitoring that connects technical details to business value. #APICosts&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research: eBPF Not Always a ‘Silver Bullet’ for Network Apps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9610/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:30:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9610/</guid>
      <description>A recent research paper raises questions about eBPF&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness for network applications. 📊 Published in the Proceedings of the ACM on Networking, the study reveals that eBPF does not always enhance performance and can sometimes hinder application speed. Researchers conducted benchmarks to assess its impact, finding mixed results. While eBPF is used for various network functions, its benefits depend on the amount of logic offloaded. In some instances, it even slows down applications&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenSSF Experts Weigh in on CISA’s SBOM Minimum Elements Update</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9611/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9611/</guid>
      <description>Experts from OpenSSF highlight the need for an update to CISA&amp;rsquo;s guidance on software bills of materials (SBOMs). Josh Bressers and Michael Lieberman emphasize the importance of clarity in SBOMs to ensure software safety, citing examples from industries like automotive and healthcare. The draft revision is open for public comment until October 3. Your feedback is crucial! 🛠️🔍 #SBOM #SoftwareSecurity #OpenSSF #CISA #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Engineer in the AI Age: The Orchestrator and Architect</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9612/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 15:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9612/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The landscape of software development is changing with the rise of generative AI. Developers are now focusing on orchestration and architectural design rather than just manual coding. A recent survey shows that 70% of developers are adopting AI tools. This shift allows tasks that once took hours to be completed in minutes. AI enhances efficiency by embedding itself in CI/CD pipelines and automating processes. Developers are transitioning to roles that prioritize decision-making and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Maintainer Burnout Is Causing a Kubernetes Security Disaster</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9565/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9565/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes External Secrets Operator (ESO) is facing significant challenges due to maintainer burnout. One active maintainer remains, leading to a halt in official support, including Slack and GitHub discussions. This is concerning, as ESO is crucial for securely managing secrets in Kubernetes environments. ESO connects with external secret providers, fetching sensitive data and injecting it into Kubernetes. Its features include real-time updates and automatic secret rotation, enhancing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How the EU’s Cyber Act Burdens Lone Open Source Developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9566/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 21:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9566/</guid>
      <description>The EU&amp;rsquo;s Cyber Resiliency Act (CRA) poses challenges for lone open source developers, as discussed at the Open Source Summit in Europe. Christopher Robinson highlighted that many developers maintain projects alone despite high demand, with an average of 160 dependencies per project. Companies using open source software are pressing for compliance with various regulations, adding to the pressure on these developers. This situation raises concerns about the implications of the CRA on the open&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Agentic Web: How AI Agents Are Shaping the Web’s Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9567/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 20:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9567/</guid>
      <description>In his memoir, &lt;em&gt;This Is For Everyone&lt;/em&gt;, Sir Tim Berners-Lee emphasizes that AI agents will significantly shape the future of the web. He envisions AI agents interacting with the web to achieve specific goals, a concept he&amp;rsquo;s explored since the 1990s. 🤖🌐 Berners-Lee, the web&amp;rsquo;s inventor, discusses his personal AI assistant, &amp;ldquo;Charlie,&amp;rdquo; designed to enhance user interaction with the web. He highlights the role of Model Context Protocol (MCP) in enabling this innovation, which includes projects like&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Ways Security Teams Can Tame Autonomous AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9568/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9568/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Security teams face new challenges with autonomous AI agents that operate without human consciousness. These systems can expose vulnerabilities in traditional authorization processes. To address this, organizations should implement three key strategies: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Assign Composite Identities&lt;/strong&gt; - This helps clarify the relationship between AI actions and human operators, enhancing accountability. Understanding these risks is crucial for maintaining secure environments. #CyberSecurity #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Log Events: Why Context Is Key</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9569/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9569/</guid>
      <description>Understanding log events is crucial in maximizing their value, especially in production environments. Context is key to interpreting logs accurately. Key points to consider include: - &lt;strong&gt;What&lt;/strong&gt;: Identify if it’s an error or a trace. - &lt;strong&gt;When&lt;/strong&gt;: Be aware of time zones and server clocks. - &lt;strong&gt;Where&lt;/strong&gt;: Know the code and infrastructure source. - &lt;strong&gt;Why&lt;/strong&gt;: Understand the reason behind the log. - &lt;strong&gt;Who&lt;/strong&gt;: Identify who triggered the action. For more insights, check out the full chapter in “Logging Best&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dispelling Myths of Open Source Complexity With Apache Iceberg</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9570/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9570/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking the potential of open source with Apache Iceberg can transform your data strategy! Many believe that adopting open source means sacrificing performance and security. However, Iceberg optimizes cloud data performance and enhances security through its standardized format, allowing for flexibility and interoperability. This modern approach not only simplifies data management but also supports compliance with regulations like GDPR. Explore how Iceberg can drive your AI success! 🚀📊🔍&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Distributed Postgres Solves Cloud’s High-Availability Problem</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9571/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9571/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Application availability is crucial for organizations, as downtime can lead to significant financial losses. Research shows unplanned downtime costs the Global 2000 $400 billion annually, averaging $200 million per company. 🔍 A survey by pgEdge highlights that exceeding downtime goals impacts business operations severely, affecting support volume, requiring emergency fixes, and causing revenue loss. 📈 As cloud infrastructure and open source software become more prevalent, businesses must&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Building Super Agents; Build Effective AI Teams Instead</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9572/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9572/</guid>
      <description>Companies are rapidly adopting agentic AI, but nearly 50% of deployments fail due to poor ROI. Instead of creating a single &amp;lsquo;super agent,&amp;rsquo; businesses should develop specialized agents for specific tasks, like data entry or information retrieval. This approach improves efficiency and allows for better management and transparency. Using multiple agents can enhance collaboration and productivity, as seen with AIG&amp;rsquo;s use of 80 agents for underwriting. #AI #Automation #BusinessStrategy #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe Coding Fails Enterprise Reality Check</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9573/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 23:00:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9573/</guid>
      <description>The concept of &amp;ldquo;vibe coding&amp;rdquo; suggests that you can describe software needs in plain English and AI will generate the code. However, experts like James Gosling and Simon Ritter highlight significant challenges. Firstly, many AI coding tools rely on existing code, which often lacks quality. Training AI on mediocre code leads to mediocre results. Secondly, natural language is inherently ambiguous, making it difficult for AI to interpret instructions accurately. This ambiguity is why programming&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Five Steps to Build AI Agents that Actually Deliver Business Results</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9574/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 17:00:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9574/</guid>
      <description>In the era of digital transformation, AI agents are changing how businesses operate. They allow companies to enhance speed while maintaining human connection. 🌐 A strategic approach is essential for building effective AI agents. The article outlines a five-step process to guide businesses in defining their agents&amp;rsquo; roles, equipping them with relevant data, and ensuring they meet specific goals. 📈 By understanding customer needs and journey, companies can leverage AI to improve customer support&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Work With Local AI in the Zed IDE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9575/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9575/</guid>
      <description>Discover how to leverage local AI in the Zed IDE! 🌟 Zed is a cross-platform code editor designed for collaboration with AI. Currently available for Linux and macOS, it offers both free and Pro versions. The Pro plan enhances AI support significantly. Key features include GPU rendering, Git support, and real-time collaboration. For AI integration, users can connect Zed with local language models like gpt-oss via Ollama. Ready to enhance your coding experience? #AI #ZedIDE #Programming&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Is MCP Actually Worth It?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9576/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9576/</guid>
      <description>The Model Context Protocol (MCP) is gaining traction as a standard for connecting AI agents with external data and services. Since its launch by Anthropic, over 16,000 MCP servers are now listed. MCP excels in complex environments, enhancing scalable, multitenant platforms. However, it&amp;rsquo;s not ideal for every use case; static contexts and strict security often favor traditional API calls. Experts emphasize that while MCP offers advantages for agentic workflows, caution is needed due to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents vs. Agentic AI: A Kubernetes Developer’s Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9577/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9577/</guid>
      <description>Understanding the difference between AI Agents and Agentic AI is crucial for developers in Kubernetes environments. AI Agents are individual software entities that perform specific tasks, similar to microservices. They operate on a request-response basis and often rely on external tools for enhanced functionality. In contrast, Agentic AI involves multiple AI agents collaborating through orchestration, adding complexity and capability. This comparison helps clarify architectural patterns for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qodo Aware Is a ‘Second Brain’ for AI Coding Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9578/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9578/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Qodo Aware, a tool designed to enhance AI coding agents with improved context awareness. While most AI coding agents rely on large language models, Qodo Aware stands out with its context engineering capabilities. It integrates information from various platforms like GitHub and Bitbucket to provide a comprehensive understanding of codebases. The tool features three main agents: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Context Retrieval&lt;/strong&gt; - Uses semantic search to find relevant code snippets. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Deep Research&lt;/strong&gt; -&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clockwork’s FleetIQ Aims To Fix AI’s Costly Network Bottleneck</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9579/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 10:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9579/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Clockwork has launched FleetIQ, targeting the network bottlenecks in AI workloads. As GPU speeds increase, network efficiency becomes crucial. 🌐 FleetIQ provides visibility into GPU clusters, helping identify issues across systems. This can save valuable time during training processes disrupted by network errors. 🔧 The platform also offers stateful fault-tolerance and automatic performance optimizations to enhance uptime and reduce congestion. #AI #Networking #TechInnovation #CloudComputing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JFrog Upgrades AI Tooling, Governance To Speed up Software Delivery</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9580/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 22:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9580/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JFrog is enhancing AI tooling and governance to streamline software delivery. At their swampUP 2025 conference, they introduced key initiatives aimed at simplifying AI-infused software supply chains. Key highlights include: 🔹 &lt;strong&gt;DevGovOps&lt;/strong&gt;: A focus on evidence-based controls for software releases. 🔹 &lt;strong&gt;AI Catalog&lt;/strong&gt;: A governed marketplace for AI and ML models. 🔹 &lt;strong&gt;Agentic Code Remediation&lt;/strong&gt;: Automated fixing of vulnerabilities. 🔹 &lt;strong&gt;JFrog Fly&lt;/strong&gt;: A new approach to versioning and release&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Agentic Coding Is Multiplayer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9581/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9581/</guid>
      <description>The article discusses the varied adoption of AI-coding tools among software developers. Some report increased productivity, while others question their value and express concerns about tech debt. Key issues include lack of context, a steep learning curve, and loss of tribal knowledge within enterprises. As remote AI-coding environments gain traction, the need for improved developer-AI collaboration becomes clear. #AICoding #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTrends #EnterpriseTech #Collaboration 🤖💻🔍</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming LLM Sprawl: Why Enterprises Need an AI Gateway Now</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9582/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9582/</guid>
      <description>As AI transforms industries, IT leaders face new challenges with the rise of large language models (LLMs). 📈 Decentralized innovation is speeding up AI adoption, but it also leads to risks like data exposure and uncontrolled spending. Enterprises need a solution to manage LLM usage effectively. 💼 An AI gateway can provide centralized governance and control, ensuring secure, cost-effective access to AI services. This tool helps track usage and enforce policies without stifling innovation. 🔒&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe Coding: The Productivity Boom Hiding Massive Governance Risks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9583/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9583/</guid>
      <description>The software development landscape is evolving with the rise of &amp;ldquo;vibe coding,&amp;rdquo; a term coined by AI researcher Andrej Karpathy. This approach shifts developers from traditional coding to orchestrating AI-driven workflows. While early adopters report significant productivity increases, a key challenge arises: many organizations struggle to understand what they’re deploying. Recent data from Stack Overflow shows that 76% of developers use AI tools, yet there&amp;rsquo;s a disconnect in measuring&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents and Their Life Cycle: What You Should Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9584/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9584/</guid>
      <description>AI agents are transforming various industries like finance, healthcare, and retail. These systems go beyond traditional software by continuously learning and adapting to improve performance. 🤖 They operate in a cycle of data gathering, analysis, decision-making, and action execution. Different types include reactive, deliberative, learning, and hybrid agents, each tailored for specific tasks. 📊 As AI agents become integral to enterprise operations, they introduce new complexities that need&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are Your AI Co-Pilots Trapping Data in Isolated Silos?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9585/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:00:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9585/</guid>
      <description>AI co-pilots are transforming how we work, offering tools for coding, writing, and design. However, many of these systems operate in isolated silos, limiting their effectiveness. To unlock greater value, AI agents need access to broader organizational data, enabling them to provide deeper insights and recommendations. The challenge lies in ensuring these agents work seamlessly across platforms, enhancing collaboration and decision-making. #AI #DataSilos #TechInnovation #Collaboration&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Development Is Stuck in 1996. Here’s How to Get to the Future.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9586/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9586/</guid>
      <description>AI development is facing challenges reminiscent of the struggles from 1996. Despite advancements like large language models, many organizations remain stuck in basic issues of tool selection and system integration. Currently, 70% of companies are in the experimentation phase of AI, with only 10-15% realizing significant benefits. Those leading in AI are seeing notable revenue growth, with a focus on retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) as a primary approach. As AI agents gain traction,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
