<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LY-Corporation-Tech-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/ly-corporation-tech-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in LY-Corporation-Tech-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 06:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/ly-corporation-tech-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating a domain-specific NL-to-SQL MCP server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13117/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13117/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Enterprise data analysis often struggles with turning business questions into SQL queries due to a lack of data analysts. Generative AI, like large language models (LLMs), offers a potential solution. 💡 However, initial experiments revealed that generic LLMs lack the specific knowledge of business contexts and data semantics, leading to incorrect SQL generation and security issues. 🔍 To address these challenges, a domain-specific NL-to-SQL MCP server was proposed. This system aims to bridge&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 55: The Law of Demeter</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13115/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13115/</guid>
      <description>📢 In the latest article from our &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality&amp;rdquo; series, Munetoshi Ishikawa discusses the Law of Demeter. This programming principle emphasizes that you should only interact with members you directly know, avoiding &amp;ldquo;members of members.&amp;rdquo; For example, accessing properties or methods should be limited to your own class, function arguments, or top-level values. Learn more about how this principle can enhance your coding practices! 💻📈 #CodeQuality #Programming #LawOfDemeter&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 54: Silence may be golden</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12928/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12928/</guid>
      <description>In the latest installment of &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality,&amp;rdquo; Munetoshi Ishikawa discusses the benefits of handling API results effectively. He emphasizes the importance of defining functions like map and flatMap on data models representing potentially failing API calls. This approach enables method chaining for smoother operations. Learn how these improvements can enhance your coding experience! 📱💻 #CodeQuality #APIDevelopment #ProgrammingTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 53: Climb the function mountain with many notifications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12160/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12160/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the latest article from the &amp;ldquo;Improving code quality&amp;rdquo; series by Munetoshi Ishikawa, the focus is on handling asynchronous function execution. When returning results from asynchronous processing, developers can choose several techniques. These include using language features like async/await, returning a promise, or passing a callback. The piece provides an example using a class called Future, demonstrating how results can be managed effectively. #CodeQuality #AsynchronousProgramming&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 52: Prune branches and wither roots</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11925/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11925/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into code quality with insights from Munetoshi Ishikawa! This week’s focus is on structuring code for different account types in an app. The article compares two approaches: separating by account type vs. UI elements. Option 2, which organizes code by UI elements, enhances readability and robustness. For developers looking to improve their coding practices, this session offers valuable techniques! #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment #BestPractices #ProgrammingTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 51: Convincing questions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11523/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11523/</guid>
      <description>In the latest article of the &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality&amp;rdquo; series, Munetoshi Ishikawa discusses a code review scenario. The focus is on the function &lt;code&gt;getOnlineUserStates&lt;/code&gt;, which is designed to return the states of online users. It includes an early return for empty user IDs, but its necessity is questioned. The reviewer suggests that removing this early return could enhance code simplicity, prompting a dialogue about its purpose. #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment #CodeReview #Programming #LINEapp 🚀💻🔍</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 50: The only truth</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11244/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11244/</guid>
      <description>📱 In the latest installment of &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality,&amp;rdquo; Munetoshi Ishikawa discusses effective data modeling in the LINE app. He highlights the importance of separating properties in the UserModel class for better code clarity. Key properties like accountType, displayName, and profileImageUri can be grouped separately from onlineStatus and moodMessage, which have different update frequencies. This approach enhances code robustness by ensuring that feature-specific code relies on more stable,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>End to End Testing on PRs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11058/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 03:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11058/</guid>
      <description>At LY Corporation, we are enhancing our pre-release testing process to minimize outages. Our end-to-end testing tool simulates real network calls, providing better insights than traditional unit tests. Recently, we&amp;rsquo;ve integrated this tool into our PR process to identify issues early and improve test coverage. 🚀 This initiative has been years in the making, leveraging advancements from multiple teams to ensure isolated testing environments. We are excited about the progress and the potential&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 49: Dependency between reality and illusion</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11016/</guid>
      <description>📱 In the latest &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality&amp;rdquo; series, Munetoshi Ishikawa discusses the dependency between reality and illusion in UI development. He illustrates how a common UI component, BazUiComponent, is utilized across different layouts, FooLayout and BarLayout, to maintain consistent logic. This approach promotes efficient code management and reduces redundancy. #CodeQuality #UIDevelopment #MobileDevelopment #LINEApp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 48: Wild arguments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11017/</guid>
      <description>📢 Check out the latest installment of &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality&amp;rdquo; by Munetoshi Ishikawa! This week, the article delves into the concept of &amp;ldquo;wild arguments&amp;rdquo; in code. It explains how to interpret a string format that represents different shapes, using tags for identification. Examples include shapes like circles, rectangles, and lines, along with their attributes. The piece discusses implementing a common factory function to streamline shape creation. 🔍 Read more to enhance your coding skills!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 50: The only truth</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10613/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10613/</guid>
      <description>📢 In the latest article by Munetoshi Ishikawa, we explore effective strategies for improving code quality. The discussion centers on the &lt;strong&gt;UserModel&lt;/strong&gt; class, highlighting how separating data models can lead to clearer and more robust code. The article emphasizes the importance of managing dependencies based on the lifecycle of values. Developers are encouraged to apply aggregation to enhance code structure, specifically by separating frequently updated properties from those with longer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 48: Wild arguments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10302/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10302/</guid>
      <description>📢 In the latest &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality&amp;rdquo; article, Munetoshi Ishikawa discusses handling shape data as strings. The string format includes a &amp;ldquo;tag&amp;rdquo; for the shape type and attributes like coordinates. For example, a circle is represented as &amp;ldquo;circle 10 20 30&amp;rdquo;. Ishikawa presents a code implementation that defines different shape classes and a common factory function for creating these shapes efficiently. Explore more about this approach in the full article! 🛠️✨ #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the scenes: Supporting engineers and designers during Tech Week 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10347/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10347/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Tech Week 2025 brought together over 1,500 participants for a unique celebration of innovation at LINE Yahoo. Held from June 30 to July 4, the event featured Tech-Verse, a tech conference showcasing nearly 130 sessions, and Hack Day, an internal hackathon for creative projects. Support for presenters included comprehensive guides, expert reviews, and practice sessions, fostering a collaborative environment. Tech Week emphasizes teamwork and encourages sharing ideas, contributing to a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside LY Corporation&#39;s &#34;Tech-Verse 2025&#34; conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10303/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10303/</guid>
      <description>🌟 LY Corporation recently held its &amp;ldquo;Tech-Verse 2025&amp;rdquo; conference, focusing on artificial intelligence. The two-day event attracted over 1,200 attendees and featured 131 sessions across 12 categories. Key topics included platform integration post-merger and LY&amp;rsquo;s ambitious AI strategy. CTO Euivin Park outlined the goal of implementing AI across 44 services to enhance user experience. For more insights, check out the presentation slides or archived videos on YouTube! 📊💻 #TechVerse2025&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 47: Breach of non-performance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9809/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9809/</guid>
      <description>📅 In the latest article of &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality,&amp;rdquo; Munetoshi Ishikawa discusses the concept of a Null Object in programming. 💻 He illustrates this with a UserModel definition, showing how to represent an &amp;ldquo;invalid user&amp;rdquo; by using default parameters. This approach simplifies the creation of Null Objects in Kotlin. 🔍 The article emphasizes the importance of avoiding ambiguous definitions, like using an id of 0 to indicate an invalid user. #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment #Kotlin #NullObject&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 46: Functions are not what they seem</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9600/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9600/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into the latest insights from Munetoshi Ishikawa on improving code quality in mobile development! This week&amp;rsquo;s article focuses on the FooItemRepository class, highlighting its functions: getItem and getItemAsync. These functions are designed for data retrieval, with getItem prioritizing cached values to ensure non-blocking calls. Discover how effective caching can enhance performance in your applications! 📱💻 #CodeQuality #MobileDevelopment #Programming #SoftwareEngineering #Caching</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Extracting trending keywords from OpenChat messages</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9457/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9457/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Heewoong Park, a machine learning engineer, shares insights on enhancing LINE OpenChat. The article discusses how the AI Services Lab aims to extract trending keywords from OpenChat messages to improve user engagement. By analyzing message content, they hope to display relevant topics on the main screen, making it more appealing for users to explore new chatrooms. Currently, the focus on chatroom recommendations may not encourage frequent visits. The team’s approach aims to group similar&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 45: All&#39;s well that ends null?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7767/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7767/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the latest installment of &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality,&amp;rdquo; Munetoshi Ishikawa discusses handling Iterators in Java and Kotlin. 📜 It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to check for the existence of the next element using &lt;code&gt;hasNext&lt;/code&gt; before calling &lt;code&gt;next&lt;/code&gt;. Failing to do so results in a &lt;code&gt;NoSuchElementException&lt;/code&gt;. 🔍 To enhance safety, Ishikawa introduces the &lt;code&gt;SafeIterator&lt;/code&gt; class, which returns null when there are no more elements. #CodeQuality #Java #Kotlin #SoftwareDevelopment #ProgrammingTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 44: Misdiagnosis of anemia</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7519/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7519/</guid>
      <description>🛠️ In the latest article by Munetoshi Ishikawa, the focus is on code quality through the lens of anemia misdiagnosis. The discussion revolves around two modules—foo-module and bar-module—each with their own data models: FooModel and BarModel. The article highlights how conversion logic between these models was integrated to avoid an anemic domain model, ensuring better data handling. For developers, this insight emphasizes the importance of architecture in maintaining clean code. #CodeQuality&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 43: Return of values</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6311/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6311/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the latest installment of &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality,&amp;rdquo; Munetoshi Ishikawa discusses the function for registering new users in the LINE app. 🔧 The &lt;code&gt;registerNewUser&lt;/code&gt; function handles two main tasks: creating a user account and uploading a profile image. The process includes validating the account creation request and checking if the profile image is uploaded successfully. For more insights, check out the full article! #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment #MobileApp #LINE #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LY Corporation on AI, a recap of Tech-Verse 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5829/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5829/</guid>
      <description>🌟 I recently attended Tech-Verse 2025 in Tokyo as a &amp;ldquo;LINE DEV Reporter.&amp;rdquo; The focus was on AI, showcasing various presentations and applications of AI in services. It was insightful to see how these advancements can relate to my work at LINE AI LAB. For those who missed it, videos and materials are available on the Tech-Verse 2025 website! 🎥 #TechVerse2025 #AI #LINEAIlab #Innovation #TechConference</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 42: Theoretical testing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5830/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5830/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Session 42 of &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality&amp;rdquo; focuses on theoretical testing in mobile development. Munetoshi Ishikawa discusses how to manage different account types (FREE, PREMIUM, etc.) with icons. If AccountType is solely for UI, icons can be properties. However, for broader usage, a conversion mechanism using a Map is more effective. Explore efficient coding strategies! 💻✨ #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment #MobileDev #Programming #TheoreticalTesting</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack the planet! A recap of Hack Day 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5831/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5831/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Just wrapped up Hack Day 2025 at LY Corporation in Tokyo! This internal hackathon, running since 2007, allows employees from all departments to collaborate freely on projects. Teams can be formed locally or globally, fostering creativity and innovation. 🙌 Participants shared ideas, planned, and developed products over two days, with a focus on collaboration and fun. Stay tuned for more insights from the concurrent Tech-Verse conference! #HackDay2025 #Innovation #Teamwork #LYCorporation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 41: &#34;Architecture&#34; under construction</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-5832/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-5832/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting insights from &amp;ldquo;Improving Code Quality&amp;rdquo; Session 41! Munetoshi Ishikawa discusses application architecture for a messaging app. The article outlines a data model defining messages, featuring various types like Text, Image, and External Resource. The message type is identified by the first character of its ID, which is crucial for maintaining historical compatibility. Discover more about managing different message types and their unique creation logic! #CodeQuality #AppDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving code quality - Session 40: Are two functions better than one?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-5833/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 02:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-5833/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the latest article by Munetoshi Ishikawa, the focus is on code quality and the efficiency of functions in programming. He discusses the utility object FooBarStringParser, which extracts data from strings with multiple formats. The article highlights how the current implementation splits knowledge about &amp;ldquo;Foo ID&amp;rdquo; between functions, leading to potential confusion. Ishikawa suggests that consolidating this knowledge could improve clarity and functionality. Read more about refining your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
