<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DoorDash-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/doordash-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DoorDash-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:41:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/doordash-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Part 2: DoorDash 2025 summer intern projects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9894/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9894/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s software engineering internship! This summer, interns contributed to meaningful projects, including enhancing the Merchant Support Hub. Key improvements were made to streamline communication for merchants, addressing issues like visibility and fragmented support interactions. The new features in Support Hub v1.5 include accessing email content, unread indicators, and the ability to reply directly to support agents. These enhancements aim to boost merchant&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building an anomaly detection platform at DoorDash to catch fraud trends early</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9668/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9668/</guid>
      <description>🚨 DoorDash has developed an anomaly detection platform aimed at identifying fraud trends earlier. The system scans millions of user segments to detect subtle behavioral changes that may indicate emerging fraud patterns. Key concepts include anomalous trend detection, focusing on collective user behavior, and anomalous outlier detection, which identifies individual anomalies. This proactive approach seeks to mitigate potential losses before they escalate. #FraudDetection #DoorDash&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash takes part in the 2025 Disability:IN Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9452/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9452/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This summer, DoorDash participated in the Disability:IN Conference for the first time, joining advocates and leaders focused on disability inclusion in the workplace. Our Able@ DoorDash group led the effort, with speakers Kinzie Keller and Lyndsey Leask sharing valuable insights on neurodiversity and creating accessible environments. We are committed to building inclusive products and practices, and this event provided us with new ideas to enhance our accessibility journey. Learn more about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 1: DoorDash 2025 summer intern projects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7798/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 20:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7798/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s Summer 2025 internship program! Interns are actively involved in impactful projects, enhancing tools for Dashers, merchants, and consumers. One key project focuses on automating the review of never-delivered orders using an in-house language model, improving efficiency and accuracy. This initiative reduces manual workload while addressing data imbalance in ND cases, ensuring better resolution rates. Stay tuned for more insights from our innovative interns!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A scalable LLM approach to enhancing chatbot knowledge with user-generated content</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-7161/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 21:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-7161/</guid>
      <description>DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s support chatbot efficiently addresses numerous questions from Dashers and customers daily. As their marketplace grows, so does the complexity of inquiries. To enhance chatbot knowledge, DoorDash employs large language models (LLMs) paired with clustering algorithms. This method identifies content gaps and drafts articles quickly, streamlining the knowledge base update process. By analyzing escalated chat transcripts, they pinpoint areas needing improvement. This data-driven&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
