<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DoorDash-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/doordash-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DoorDash-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 23:28:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/doordash-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Smarter promotions with causal machine learning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13911/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 23:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13911/</guid>
      <description>📈 At the KDD AI Conference in August 2025, we introduced our research on &amp;ldquo;Causal Machine Learning for Promotions.&amp;rdquo; Our study outlines a two-stage framework to enhance promotion effectiveness. First, we assess individual customer responses to various offers, then optimize promotions within practical business limits. Promotions can boost growth but often lead to inefficiencies, as many discounted orders would happen without incentives. Our approach aims to identify true promotional impacts and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 4: DoorDash 2025 summer intern projects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13412/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:52:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13412/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s 2025 summer interns are making a significant impact through hands-on projects. One notable development is the transition to the Logistics Console, enhancing ETA reliability during high-stress events. This new tool validates uploads and tracks changes, improving safety and transparency. Additionally, a &amp;ldquo;storm mode&amp;rdquo; feature allows for real-time adjustments during demand surges, streamlining operations and enhancing customer experience. #DoorDash #Internship #SoftwareEngineering&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mind the Gap: Using LLMs to bridge behavioral silos in multi-vertical recommendations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13408/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:42:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13408/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s paper at RecSys 2025 discusses bridging behavioral silos in multi-vertical recommendations using large language models (LLMs). As DoorDash expands, many customers show strong preferences in only a few categories. This leads to challenges in personalizing recommendations across diverse offerings. The proposed LLM framework captures user behavior patterns, allowing for better relevance and personalization, even from the start. It translates varied activity data into meaningful user&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When GenAI Meets Personalization: Powering DoorDash’s next-generation homepage experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13271/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 17:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13271/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from DoorDash! We&amp;rsquo;ve launched a GenAI-powered personalized carousel system on our homepage, enhancing your shopping experience. This system tailors recommendations using large language models, creating unique carousels for each user based on their preferences. By analyzing customer data, we&amp;rsquo;re reducing search challenges and helping you make quicker, informed decisions. This means more relevant options and a smoother journey on our platform! #DoorDash #GenAI #Personalization&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Single Agents: How DoorDash is building a collaborative AI ecosystem</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12107/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 21:23:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12107/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DoorDash is advancing its AI capabilities by creating a collaborative ecosystem that integrates vast knowledge sources, including experimentation platforms and team chats. This initiative aims to streamline complex business processes that traditionally required multiple tools and steps. The focus is on developing an agentic AI platform for seamless interactions between specialized AI agents. 🤖 Through an evolutionary approach, DoorDash is enhancing multi-agent systems, starting from basic&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing DoorDash’s in-house search engine platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11836/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 18:13:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11836/</guid>
      <description>In early 2024, DoorDash tackled challenges with its in-house search engine to meet global search demands. They achieved a 50% reduction in latency and a 75% decrease in hardware costs. However, they encountered issues with CPU utilization and latency spikes. By transitioning to a new garbage collector and upgrading Apache Lucene, they reduced hardware costs by an additional 30% and improved latency by up to 30%. This experience illustrates how focused optimizations can enhance overall&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SafeChat: DoorDash’s AI-powered safety feature</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11510/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11510/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DoorDash introduces SafeChat, an AI-driven feature aimed at enhancing safety for users. The system moderates millions of messages daily, identifying and managing inappropriate content between Dashers and customers. SafeChat employs a three-layered AI approach to ensure effective content moderation, allowing immediate actions when necessary. Learn more about how DoorDash is prioritizing safety on its platform! 🔒📱 #DoorDash #AI #SafetyFirst #TechInnovation #SafeChat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging Affordability, Familiarity, and Novelty: DoorDash’s LLM-assisted personalization framework</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11222/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:55:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11222/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DoorDash recently presented at KDD 2025&amp;rsquo;s PARIS Workshop, discussing their LLM-assisted personalization framework for multi-vertical retail. The framework focuses on three key dimensions: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Familiarity&lt;/strong&gt; - highlighting trusted favorites. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Affordability&lt;/strong&gt; - aligning with price preferences. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Novelty&lt;/strong&gt; - introducing new and exciting products. This approach aims to enhance customer discovery, ensuring shopping feels personalized and effortless. #DoorDash #Personalization&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How DoorDash slashed web developer build times</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11080/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 16:30:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11080/</guid>
      <description>DoorDash faced challenges with lengthy CI pipeline durations as web projects grew in complexity. By optimizing tooling and adopting a new monorepo system, they reduced build and test times by 75%, saving over 500 engineering hours monthly. Key strategies included leveraging cobuilds and enhancing parallelization techniques. These changes have significantly improved developer productivity. 🚀💻 #DoorDash #WebDevelopment #ContinuousIntegration #EngineeringEfficiency #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 3: DoorDash 2025 summer intern projects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10882/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10882/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s software engineering internship program! This summer, interns contributed to impactful projects including a user-generated content feedback loop. This system notifies users when their reviews gain visibility, fostering engagement and community trust. The project emphasizes the significance of user feedback and includes a streamlined database design for tracking and notifications. Stay tuned for more highlights from our Summer 2025 interns! #DoorDash&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Door to More: Unlocking Creativity with AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10605/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:29:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10605/</guid>
      <description>Join us on November 6th in San Francisco for an exclusive event with DoorDash marketing leaders! 🚀 Hear from Gina Igwe, Jennifer Richardi, and Shannon Duncan about how AI is transforming creative marketing. This is a great opportunity to learn, network, and enjoy dinner and drinks. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out! RSVP by 10/22. #DoorDash #MarketingInnovation #AI #Networking #CreativeLeadership</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our stance on AI and Interviewing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10580/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:14:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10580/</guid>
      <description>At DoorDash, we embrace AI as a tool to enhance the interview process, not to replace authenticity. Candidates are encouraged to use AI for preparation, like building resumes or exploring interview questions, but must showcase their true selves during interviews. Remember, honesty is key! Misrepresenting your skills could lead to disqualification. For any accommodations regarding AI use, communicate with your recruiter early on. #DoorDash #AIInInterviews #JobPreparation #Authenticity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Autonomy for Local Commerce: Building Dot and the Autonomous Delivery Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10255/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10255/</guid>
      <description>🚚 Autonomy is advancing rapidly, with autonomous vehicles becoming more common in cities. However, local delivery presents unique challenges. The &amp;ldquo;last ten feet&amp;rdquo; problem complicates food and grocery delivery, requiring nimble vehicles to navigate sidewalks and driveways efficiently. Local delivery also involves coordinating busy merchants, diverse consumer preferences, and dynamic marketplace conditions. DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s new Dot robot aims to address these challenges, optimizing local commerce and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using LLMs to infer grocery preferences from DoorDash restaurant orders</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10218/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 16:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10218/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DoorDash is enhancing grocery delivery by leveraging restaurant order histories to recommend items. By using large language models (LLMs), they analyze consumer preferences to provide personalized grocery suggestions. This approach addresses the &amp;ldquo;cold start problem&amp;rdquo; for new customers in grocery shopping. The system translates order history into relevant grocery recommendations, making it easier for users to find items they love. For more details, check out the article! 📦🍜🥡 #DoorDash&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How DoorDash Ads keep consumers first with budget A/B experimentation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9962/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 18:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9962/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DoorDash Ads is enhancing consumer experience by implementing a budget A/B framework for ad testing. This innovative approach helps maintain low delivery fees while ensuring relevant ads. The framework addresses challenges in a three-sided marketplace, where classic A/B tests often fall short due to issues like cannibalization and network effects. By creating separate budget pools, DoorDash can achieve unbiased results. Learn more about how this strategy supports consumers, restaurants, and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 2: DoorDash 2025 summer intern projects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9894/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 20:41:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9894/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s software engineering internship! This summer, interns contributed to meaningful projects, including enhancing the Merchant Support Hub. Key improvements were made to streamline communication for merchants, addressing issues like visibility and fragmented support interactions. The new features in Support Hub v1.5 include accessing email content, unread indicators, and the ability to reply directly to support agents. These enhancements aim to boost merchant&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building an anomaly detection platform at DoorDash to catch fraud trends early</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9668/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9668/</guid>
      <description>🚨 DoorDash has developed an anomaly detection platform aimed at identifying fraud trends earlier. The system scans millions of user segments to detect subtle behavioral changes that may indicate emerging fraud patterns. Key concepts include anomalous trend detection, focusing on collective user behavior, and anomalous outlier detection, which identifies individual anomalies. This proactive approach seeks to mitigate potential losses before they escalate. #FraudDetection #DoorDash&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DoorDash takes part in the 2025 Disability:IN Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9452/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9452/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This summer, DoorDash participated in the Disability:IN Conference for the first time, joining advocates and leaders focused on disability inclusion in the workplace. Our Able@ DoorDash group led the effort, with speakers Kinzie Keller and Lyndsey Leask sharing valuable insights on neurodiversity and creating accessible environments. We are committed to building inclusive products and practices, and this event provided us with new ideas to enhance our accessibility journey. Learn more about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part 1: DoorDash 2025 summer intern projects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7798/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 20:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7798/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s Summer 2025 internship program! Interns are actively involved in impactful projects, enhancing tools for Dashers, merchants, and consumers. One key project focuses on automating the review of never-delivered orders using an in-house language model, improving efficiency and accuracy. This initiative reduces manual workload while addressing data imbalance in ND cases, ensuring better resolution rates. Stay tuned for more insights from our innovative interns!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A scalable LLM approach to enhancing chatbot knowledge with user-generated content</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-7161/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 21:49:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-7161/</guid>
      <description>DoorDash&amp;rsquo;s support chatbot efficiently addresses numerous questions from Dashers and customers daily. As their marketplace grows, so does the complexity of inquiries. To enhance chatbot knowledge, DoorDash employs large language models (LLMs) paired with clustering algorithms. This method identifies content gaps and drafts articles quickly, streamlining the knowledge base update process. By analyzing escalated chat transcripts, they pinpoint areas needing improvement. This data-driven&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
