<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Product_announcements on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/categories/product_announcements/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Product_announcements on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:48:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/product_announcements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate Protein Structure Inference Over 100x with NVIDIA RTX PRO 6000 Blackwell Server Edition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9519/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9519/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking the future of protein structure analysis is now possible with the NVIDIA RTX PRO 6000 Blackwell Server Edition. This new GPU significantly accelerates protein structure inference, enhancing research efficiency and reducing costs for organizations. 🧬💻 With advancements from NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Digital Biology Research labs, researchers can now utilize OpenFold for rapid analysis without sacrificing accuracy compared to AlphaFold2. Discover how this technology can transform large-scale protein&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Scalable AI Inference with NVIDIA NIM Operator 3.0.0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9520/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9520/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of AI with NVIDIA NIM Operator 3.0.0! 🚀 This latest release enhances the deployment of NVIDIA NIM and NeMo microservices in Kubernetes environments, making it easier to manage complex AI inference pipelines. Key features include efficient resource utilization and seamless integration with existing infrastructures, including KServe. 🤖 Collaboration with Red Hat further streamlines NIM deployment, supporting model caching and trusted AI capabilities. #NVIDIA #AI #Kubernetes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Identity Management for Entra ID is now Generally Available in Azure Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9529/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9529/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Automatic Identity Management (AIM) for Entra ID is now generally available on Azure Databricks. This feature allows for instant connection of users, groups, and service principals, streamlining setup and enhancing collaboration. Explore how AIM can improve your workflow! #AzureDatabricks #IdentityManagement #CloudComputing #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers Can Now Get CUDA Directly from Their Favorite Third-Party Platforms</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9522/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9522/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Developers can now access CUDA directly through popular third-party platforms, making application deployment easier. NVIDIA is collaborating with Canonical, CIQ, and others to simplify installation and maintain compatibility across various OS and package managers. This initiative helps streamline the integration of GPU support in applications like PyTorch and OpenCV. Key benefits include consistent CUDA naming, timely updates, and continued free access to CUDA. #NVIDIA #CUDA #DeveloperTools&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB Atlas Now Available in the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9528/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 14:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9528/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! MongoDB Atlas is now available in the Vercel Marketplace. This integration simplifies how developers manage their web applications on Vercel. With MongoDB&amp;rsquo;s flexible document model and Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Cloud tools, building and scaling intelligent applications has never been easier. Developers can now provision MongoDB databases directly from their Vercel dashboard, streamlining the development process. Explore this powerful combination to enhance your application&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB Atlas is now available on the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9524/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9524/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! MongoDB Atlas is now available on the Vercel Marketplace. You can easily set up a fully managed MongoDB database directly from the Vercel dashboard. This integration allows for quick provisioning and seamless connection to your Vercel projects, eliminating the need for separate sign-ups or complex configurations. #MongoDB #Vercel #Developers #TechNews #DatabaseIntegration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB Atlas joins the Vercel Marketplace</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9525/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9525/</guid>
      <description>🚀 MongoDB Atlas is now available on the Vercel Marketplace! You can easily provision a fully managed database directly from the Vercel dashboard. This integration allows developers to connect their MongoDB Atlas databases to Vercel projects seamlessly. Key features include a flexible document model, built-in search capabilities, and options for horizontal scaling. This simplifies the setup process, enabling faster development for web and AI applications. Explore the new integration on the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Sandbox maximum duration extended to 5 hours</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9526/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9526/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Vercel users! Pro and Enterprise teams can now utilize Vercel Sandboxes for up to 5 hours, an increase from the previous limit of 45 minutes. This extension allows for more extensive workloads, including large-scale data processing and end-to-end testing pipelines. To get started with Sandbox or learn more, check out the documentation! #Vercel #TechUpdate #SoftwareDevelopment #DataProcessing #WebDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing News and Conversations Together with Reddit Pro Tools for Publishers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9513/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9513/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting updates for publishers! Reddit has launched Reddit Pro tools to enhance content sharing and engagement. 📰 This new suite includes features like article insights, auto-importing articles, and community recommendations. Publishers can track their stories&amp;rsquo; performance and connect directly with users on Reddit. 📈 With 75% of redditors reading online news regularly, these tools aim to streamline how media outlets share and discuss content. #RedditPro #PublishingTools #MediaEngagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin 2.2.20 Released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9511/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:54:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9511/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kotlin 2.2.20 is here with key updates for web development! Kotlin/Wasm is now in Beta, featuring enhanced exception handling, improved npm dependency management, and built-in browser debugging support. Highlights include: - Swift export for Kotlin Multiplatform - Improved overload resolution for lambdas - Smaller binary sizes in Kotlin/Native - Long values as JavaScript BigInt in Kotlin/JS For detailed changes, check the release notes on GitHub. #Kotlin #WebDevelopment #Programming&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junie Is Now Available in CLion: Supercharge Your C and C&#43;&#43; Development Today</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9509/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 07:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9509/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for C and C++ developers! With CLion version 2025.2.1, Junie, the AI coding agent by JetBrains, is now integrated in Beta. This integration provides enhanced project insights and tooling directly within the IDE. Developers can benefit from improved visibility, automatic task completion, and easy access to project details without leaving CLion. Explore features like Ask mode for Q&amp;amp;A and Code mode for generating tests and README files. #CLion #AI #CProgramming #CPlusPlus #JetBrains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood Unveils Powerful New Tools for Active Traders at HOOD Summit 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9503/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:51:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9503/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Robinhood has launched exciting new tools for active traders at the HOOD Summit 2025! Introducing &lt;strong&gt;Robinhood Social&lt;/strong&gt;, a community feature offering live, verified trades and discussions on strategies. Users can follow traders, track real performance, and connect with market insiders. 🔍 &lt;strong&gt;Robinhood Legend&lt;/strong&gt; also sees enhancements with AI-powered indicators, futures trading, and expanded asset options, all aimed at improving trading analysis. These features will roll out early next year to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Gateway API Support for DigitalOcean Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9479/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9479/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for DigitalOcean Kubernetes users! The Kubernetes Gateway API is now pre-installed in all DOKS clusters at no extra cost. This new traffic management solution offers advanced routing capabilities and superior performance using Cilium’s eBPF technology. Key benefits include zero configuration, header-based routing, and seamless integration with DigitalOcean Load Balancers. The Gateway API also enhances team collaboration by separating infrastructure management from application&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Snapshottable API server cache</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9504/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9504/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 introduces the snapshottable API server cache, now in Beta. This feature enhances the API server&amp;rsquo;s performance and stability by allowing most read requests to be served from cache. Key improvements include consistent reads and efficient handling of large responses. The new cache generates lightweight snapshots, ensuring predictable memory usage and reducing load on etcd. This marks a significant step towards a more resilient Kubernetes environment. 🌐✨ #Kubernetes #API&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating scientific discovery with AI-powered empirical software</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9498/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9498/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in scientific research! A new AI system has been developed to assist scientists in writing empirical software, achieving expert-level results across six challenging benchmarks. This system addresses the bottleneck in hypothesis evaluation by generating high-quality custom software. By leveraging large language models, the AI can propose and implement novel concepts, optimizing performance through extensive code iteration. This innovation spans diverse fields including&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Ways to See Community Activity on Reddit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9478/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 16:00:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9478/</guid>
      <description>📢 Reddit is updating how subreddit activity is displayed! The “Member count” will be replaced with two new metrics: &lt;strong&gt;Visitors&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Contributions&lt;/strong&gt;. This change aims to better showcase active participation in communities. - &lt;strong&gt;Visitors&lt;/strong&gt; tracks unique users in the past week. - &lt;strong&gt;Contributions&lt;/strong&gt; counts posts and comments made in the same timeframe. These updates reflect current engagement rather than just subscriber numbers. #RedditUpdates #CommunityEngagement #SocialMediaMetrics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Rubin CPX Accelerates Inference Performance and Efficiency for 1M&#43; Token Context Workloads</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9467/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9467/</guid>
      <description>NVIDIA is addressing the increasing complexity of AI inference with its new Rubin CPX GPU. This technology supports workloads requiring extensive context, like software development and long-form video generation. The NVIDIA SMART framework optimizes inference across various dimensions, allowing for better resource allocation. This disaggregated approach separates the context and generation phases, improving efficiency and reducing latency. Discover how NVIDIA is redefining AI infrastructure&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPS 2025.2 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9472/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9472/</guid>
      <description>🚀 MPS 2025.2 has officially launched! This update enhances quality and stability while introducing key features. Users can now start MPS with OS-native launchers for easier access. The Show Node Info dialog has been modernized, and resolve-info updates during copy-paste have improved. 🔧 Notable changes include: - New binary launchers for Windows and Linux - FactoryMethodIcon support - Compatibility with Java 21 For more details, visit the What’s New page! #MPS2025 #SoftwareUpdate #Java21&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A more flexible Pro plan for modern teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9480/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9480/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel is enhancing its Pro plan to better support modern team collaboration and evolving workloads, including those driven by AI. Key updates aim to align with how applications now consume infrastructure. Stay tuned for a more flexible approach to managing your projects! #Vercel #ProPlan #TeamCollaboration #AI #Infrastructure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free Viewer seats now available on Pro</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9484/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9484/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Pro teams! You can now add unlimited Viewer seats at no extra cost. This allows team members to collaborate more flexibly without affecting your budget. Viewers can access project dashboards, deployments, and analytics but can&amp;rsquo;t change production settings or see sensitive data. Developer seats remain at $20, while Viewer seats are free. Team members can easily request upgrades from owners directly in the dashboard. #ProUpdates #TeamCollaboration #ViewerSeats #CostEfficient&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Included Pro usage is now credit-based</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9482/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9482/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Big news for Pro users! The Pro plan now features a $20 monthly usage credit, replacing fixed allocations with a flexible system that adjusts to your workload. This update enhances your experience by allowing better management of resources. Additional benefits include free viewer seats, self-serve enterprise features like SAML SSO and HIPAA BA, and improved spend management. #ProPlan #UsageCredit #TechUpdates #EnterpriseFeatures #FlexibleSystem</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No build queues: On-demand concurrent builds now on by default</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9481/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9481/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for teams on the new Pro pricing model! On-demand concurrent builds are now enabled by default, allowing builds to start immediately across projects without queue delays. This applies unless multiple builds target the same Git branch. Teams can manage this setting anytime with the new bulk enable feature, even if not yet on the Pro model. Learn more about these updates and the Pro pricing switch in the documentation! #BuildAutomation #ProPricing #DevOps #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spend Management now enabled by default on Pro</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9483/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9483/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Spend Management is now the default for all Pro teams! New Pro teams will have a budget set based on previous usage, while existing teams will see no changes to their current budgets. You’ll receive email alerts when approaching your spend threshold, helping you manage costs effectively. Adjust settings anytime for flexibility. Stay informed and optimize your spending! #SpendManagement #ProTeams #CostControl #Budgeting #BusinessUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Packing More Power Into Cisco XDR’s Integration Toolkit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9462/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9462/</guid>
      <description>Cisco XDR is likened to a Swiss Army knife, emphasizing its versatility in cybersecurity. Just as the iconic tool combines multiple functions for various tasks, Cisco XDR integrates numerous security features—like firewalls and email protection—into one cohesive platform. This design allows users to effectively address diverse cybersecurity challenges. 🛠️🔒 #CiscoXDR #Cybersecurity #Integration #Versatility #CyberTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>App Store submissions now open for the latest OS releases</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9499/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9499/</guid>
      <description>🚀 App developers, good news! Submissions are now open for iOS 26, iPadOS 26, macOS Tahoe 26, tvOS 26, visionOS 26, and watchOS 26. Utilize Xcode 26 and the latest SDKs to create unique apps and games. Test your creations with TestFlight before submitting for review. Starting April 2026, ensure your submissions meet the required SDK standards for each platform. 📲 Learn more about the new requirements! #AppDevelopment #Apple #iOS26 #Xcode26 #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We built stackoverflow.ai with the community and for the community</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9453/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9453/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news from Stack Overflow! The team has launched stackoverflow.ai, designed to improve your experience by merging human-validated answers with AI. This innovation aims to provide quick and accurate technical solutions, leveraging 16 years of community knowledge. Future plans include enhanced personalization and deeper community integration. 👏 Congratulations to Ketan Ramani for earning a Populist badge for their excellent answer on formatting in Android Studio! #StackOverflow #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1Password announces new integration with Zscaler</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9488/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9488/</guid>
      <description>🔒 1Password has announced a new integration with Zscaler, aimed at enhancing Zero Trust practices for their shared customers. This integration allows users to secure access to applications from both managed and unmanaged devices, ensuring only trusted devices can authenticate. Companies with active accounts can set this up via the 1Password Marketplace. Discover more about this integration today! #1Password #Zscaler #ZeroTrust #Cybersecurity #Integration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A2A Extensions: Empowering Custom Agent Functionality</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9500/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9500/</guid>
      <description>A2A Extensions enhance agent-to-agent communication by allowing developers to add custom functionalities beyond the core protocol. These extensions support specialized features tailored to specific needs, making it easier for agents to meet unique requirements. 📈 Getting started is user-friendly; developers can define and publish extensions through a simple &amp;ldquo;Agent Card.&amp;rdquo; This fosters an open, community-driven ecosystem. 🌐 Current use cases, like the Traceability Extension, highlight the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Genkit Go 1.0 and Enhanced AI-Assisted Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9510/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9510/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Go developers! We are thrilled to announce the stable release of &lt;strong&gt;Genkit Go 1.0&lt;/strong&gt;. This open-source framework enables the creation of production-ready AI applications seamlessly. Key features include: - Type-safe AI flows - Unified model interface - Support for multiple model providers Additionally, the new &lt;strong&gt;genkit init:ai-tools&lt;/strong&gt; command enhances your AI development experience. Check out the latest tools and get started today! #GenkitGo #AIDevelopment #OpenSource&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>August 2025 in Auth0: Non-Unique Emails, DPoP, and TLS Fingerprints</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9489/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9489/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Auth0 for August 2025! This month, they introduced flexibility with passwordless connection switching on Universal Login, allowing users to choose their login method easily. They also launched early access to Non-Unique Emails, enabling multiple accounts to share the same email, benefiting various business scenarios. Additionally, enhanced security features like DPoP and TLS Fingerprints have been added to protect users from token theft. #Auth0 #ProductUpdate&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Together, Earn Together: Introducing Railway Partnerships</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9475/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9475/</guid>
      <description>🚆 Exciting news for users! We are launching Railway Partnerships to enhance user acquisition through our template marketplace. This initiative aims to create collaborative opportunities for growth in the railway sector. Join us in exploring this new avenue for success! #RailwayPartnerships #UserAcquisition #GrowthOpportunities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ascend to the cloud: The next chapter for Atlassian and our customers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9454/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9454/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Atlassian is embracing a cloud-first future! With 99% of its 300,000+ customers already on the cloud, the company is sunsetting Data Center products over the next three years. This transition, part of the Atlassian Ascend initiative, aims to enhance teamwork and innovation. 🌟 Customers will gain access to AI tools, improved data connectivity, and robust analytics. Many organizations report faster results and reduced costs through the cloud. Atlassian is committed to supporting all customers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Data Center to Cloud: The Next Chapter for Marketplace Apps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9455/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9455/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian announces the end of life for Data Center products, shifting to a cloud-first approach over the next three years. This transition aims to enhance innovation and agility for customers. Marketplace apps will also gradually be phased out, with key dates set for app submissions and renewals. A new license option for Bitbucket Data Center apps will allow more flexibility during this change. Atlassian is committed to supporting customers and partners throughout this journey. #Atlassian&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Comply-to-Connect (C2C) Training Now Supports Third-Party Integrations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9443/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 20:53:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9443/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has updated its Comply-to-Connect (C2C) training to now support third-party integrations. This training is crucial for deploying C2C solutions in mixed-vendor environments. The program includes both instructor-led courses and e-learning options, featuring hands-on labs and instructional videos. 📚 Key integrations with Microsoft MECM, Tenable, and Trillex enhance endpoint compliance and access control. This update aligns with the Department of Defense&amp;rsquo;s Zero Trust initiatives. 🔒 For&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD FSR 4 now available in over 85 games</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9437/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9437/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Exciting news for gamers! AMD has launched FidelityFX™ Super Resolution 4 (FSR 4), now available in over 85 games. This advanced neural rendering technology enhances graphics quality using machine learning, resulting in clearer visuals without compromising performance. To experience FSR 4, simply update your AMD Software: Adrenalin Edition driver and enable it in supported games. Explore enhanced gaming today! 🌟 #AMD #FSR4 #GamingTech #Graphics #GameOn</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: VolumeAttributesClass for Volume Modification GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9451/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9451/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 introduces the VolumeAttributesClass API, now in General Availability (GA). This enhancement allows users to dynamically modify volume attributes within Kubernetes. It acts as a profile for storage, enabling scalability, cost optimization, and simplified operations. Key updates include: - Explicit cancel support for infeasible volume modifications. - Quota enforcement on PersistentVolumeClaims based on VolumeAttributesClass. Supported by AWS EBS and GCE Persistent Disk CSI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI SDK and AI Gateway now integrated in GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9448/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9448/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The new integration of the AI SDK and AI Gateway with GitHub Actions allows users to access the vercel/ai-action@v2. This feature enables the generation of text or structured JSON directly within workflows by specifying prompts, models, and API keys. This opens up various AI-powered use cases, such as summarizing release notes, conducting light PR code reviews, moderating comments, and identifying duplicate issues. Explore more in the GitHub Actions marketplace&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Node.js HTTP servers to Cloudflare Workers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9397/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9397/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare Workers now support Node.js HTTP client and server APIs, making it easier to run existing Node.js applications. Developers can deploy apps like Express.js and Koa with minimal code changes. 🌍✨ This enhancement allows for zero cold starts, automatic scaling, and lower latency, all while maintaining familiar development patterns. Key features include support for standard HTTP methods and streaming responses. #Cloudflare #NodeJS #Serverless #WebDevelopment #APIs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk enable on-demand concurrent builds across projects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9439/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9439/</guid>
      <description>Pro teams can now enhance efficiency by bulk enabling on-demand concurrent builds across all projects with a single click. 🔄 This feature allows builds to start immediately upon request, optimizing compute capacity, except when multiple builds target the same Git branch. To activate this, visit your Pro team&amp;rsquo;s billing settings to enable or disable it for existing projects or select specific projects. Learn more in the documentation! 📄💻 #BuildAutomation #DevOps #ProjectManagement #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Functions now support graceful shutdown</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9432/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9432/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel Functions now enhance Node.js and Python runtimes with graceful shutdown support! This feature allows up to 500 milliseconds for running cleanup tasks before termination. When a function is terminated, a SIGTERM signal can be used to manage essential tasks like closing database connections or flushing logs. Learn more about the benefits of this update! #Vercel #NodeJS #Python #WebDevelopment #Serverless</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Mellum Now Available on Amazon Bedrock Marketplace – For Free</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9396/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9396/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains Mellum is now available on the Amazon Bedrock Marketplace for free! This production-grade large language model (LLM) makes code completion easier and more accessible. With Mellum, you can deploy quickly, control costs, and enjoy zero extra model fees. It’s optimized for enterprise use, ensuring better performance and stability. Choose your GPU hardware, hit deploy, and integrate seamlessly into your engineering workflows. Explore Mellum today for instant access! 🌐💻 #JetBrains&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini Batch API now supports Embeddings and OpenAI Compatibility</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9518/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9518/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The Gemini Batch API now supports the new Gemini Embedding model and OpenAI SDK, allowing for efficient batch processing. This enhancement offers asynchronous processing at 50% lower rates, ideal for high-volume use cases. You can access the Gemini Embedding model at just $0.075 per 1M input tokens. Start integrating with just a few lines of code! #GeminiAPI #OpenAI #Developers #TechUpdates #Embeddings</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Unity Audience Hub helps marketers reach mobile gaming audiences and gains industry recognition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9431/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9431/</guid>
      <description>Unity Audience Hub is transforming how marketers engage with mobile gaming audiences while prioritizing privacy. 🎮✨ This innovative platform integrates insights from Unity&amp;rsquo;s ad ecosystem with third-party data, enabling custom audience building across mobile and CTV channels. Unity has recently been recognized as the &amp;ldquo;Best Mobile Games Marketing Platform&amp;rdquo; at the MarTech Breakthrough Awards, highlighting its commitment to effective and privacy-conscious marketing solutions. 🏆 Learn more about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Signal Secure Backups</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9434/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9434/</guid>
      <description>📱 Signal has introduced secure backups, addressing a long-standing user request. This new opt-in feature allows users to back up their message history, ensuring important conversations are not lost if a phone is damaged or lost. Currently available in beta for Android, it will soon roll out to iOS and Desktop. Secure backups are end-to-end encrypted and refresh daily for added security. #Signal #SecureBackups #Privacy #Messaging #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veo 3 and Veo 3 Fast – new pricing, new configurations and better resolution</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9456/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9456/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for Veo users! Veo 3 and Veo 3 Fast now support vertical format outputs (9:16 aspect ratio) and 1080p HD resolution. This is ideal for mobile and social media content. Additionally, pricing has been reduced: - Veo 3: $0.40/second (was $0.75) - Veo 3 Fast: $0.15/second (was $0.40) These changes enhance accessibility and video quality. #VeoUpdates #VideoProduction #TechNews #ContentCreation #HDVideo</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Pod Replacement Policy for Jobs Goes GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7797/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7797/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 introduces the Pod Replacement Policy feature, now generally available. This allows users to manage how Pods are replaced in Jobs, addressing issues with overlapping Pods that can occur during terminations. You can choose between two policies: 1. &lt;strong&gt;TerminatingOrFailed&lt;/strong&gt; (default) - Replaces Pods immediately upon termination. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Failed&lt;/strong&gt; - Replaces Pods only after the previous ones have fully terminated. This enhancement is particularly useful for workloads requiring strict&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Released: NVIDIA PhysicsNeMo 25.08</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7789/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 17:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7789/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from NVIDIA! The latest release of PhysicsNeMo 25.08 introduces powerful workflows and recipes specifically designed for CAE application developers. This update aims to enhance simulations and streamline development processes. Explore the new features and boost your CAE projects with NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s advanced tools! #NVIDIA #PhysicsNeMo #CAE #TechUpdates #Simulation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Released: NVIDIA PhysicsNeMo 25.08</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-8228/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 17:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-8228/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for CAE developers! NVIDIA has just launched PhysicsNeMo 25.08, introducing new workflows and recipes designed to enhance application development. This update aims to streamline processes and improve efficiency in computational physics. Stay tuned for more advancements in simulation technology! #NVIDIA #PhysicsNeMo #CAE #TechUpdate #Simulation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the New Nexus Dashboard for Simplifying Data Center Operations in the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7780/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7780/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data center operations! Nexus Dashboard 4.1 is now available, offering complete lifecycle management for multiple data center networks through a single interface. This solution simplifies provisioning and enhances visibility while providing diagnostics and automation. It supports various environments, including NX-OS, ACI, AI fabrics, and more. The dashboard also enables VXLAN EVPN automation on Cisco Catalyst switches. #DataCenter #NexusDashboard #AI #NetworkManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the New Nexus Dashboard for Simplifying Data Center Operations in the AI Era</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7817/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7817/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news in data center management! The Nexus Dashboard 4.1 is now available for unified lifecycle management of multiple data center networks. This single interface streamlines provisioning and enhances visibility, making it easier for teams to manage diverse environments. It supports various network fabrics, including NX-OS and ACI, while offering robust automation and diagnostics. This advancement aims to simplify operations in an increasingly AI-driven landscape. #DataCenter&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect MCP Servers to Junie in PhpStorm</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7783/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 14:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7783/</guid>
      <description>🔗 The Model Context Protocol (MCP) offers a standardized way to connect AI models with various tools and data sources. 💻 You can integrate Junie, JetBrains&amp;rsquo; AI coding agent, with multiple MCP servers or build your own using the new MCP PHP SDK. 🛠️ The MCP PHP SDK is a collaborative effort aimed at providing a reliable framework for PHP developers. For guidance on setup and configuration, refer to the MCP server documentation and the Junie MCP Settings in PhpStorm. #AI #MCP #PhpStorm #Junie&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect MCP Servers to Junie in PhpStorm</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7893/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 14:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7893/</guid>
      <description>🔗 The Model Context Protocol (MCP) is an open standard from Anthropic, designed to connect AI models seamlessly to various tools and data sources. 🛠️ JetBrains’ Junie AI coding agent can link with multiple MCP servers, either community-built or custom ones using the new MCP PHP SDK. This SDK, developed collaboratively, provides a framework for PHP developers. 📈 To integrate Junie with an MCP server in PhpStorm, ensure the server is accessible, configure Junie through the MCP Settings, and add&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Export traces, web analytics events, and speed insights datapoints to any destination</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7788/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7788/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Vercel users! You can now export OpenTelemetry traces, Web Analytics events, and Speed Insights data to any third-party tool. This enhancement allows streaming of more raw data through expanded Log Drains infrastructure. Pro and Enterprise teams can set custom HTTP endpoints and choose from various encodings like JSON, NDJSON, or Protobuf. Explore Vercel Drains today! #Vercel #DataExport #WebAnalytics #OpenTelemetry #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Export traces, web analytics events, and speed insights datapoints to any destination</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7809/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7809/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel now allows users to export OpenTelemetry traces, Web Analytics events, and Speed Insights data to any third-party tool. This enhancement expands the Log Drains infrastructure for seamless data streaming. Users can set up custom HTTP endpoints to receive data in various formats like JSON, NDJSON, or Protobuf. Pro and Enterprise teams can export data at a cost of $0.50 per GB. Learn more about Vercel Drains! #DataExport #WebAnalytics #Vercel #OpenTelemetry&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero-configuration Express backends</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7787/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7787/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Express, the minimalist web framework for Node.js, now offers zero-configuration support on Vercel. This means you can deploy Express applications without the hassle of setting up redirects in vercel.json or using the /api folder. For a seamless experience, check out the Express on Vercel documentation. #NodeJS #Express #Vercel #WebDevelopment #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s new in network observability 1.9</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7761/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 07:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7761/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in Network Observability 1.9! This version enhances insights into network traffic with features like IPsec tracking, flowlogs-pipeline filter queries, and UDN mapping. It is compatible with Red Hat OpenShift Container Platform 4.19 and older releases. Learn how to enable IPsec and explore the new CLI enhancements for capturing flows, metrics, and packets. For detailed installation instructions, refer to the OpenShift documentation. 📊🔍 #NetworkObservability #RedHat&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netlify pricing update: Introducing credit-based plans</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7729/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7729/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Netlify has introduced credit-based plans for new accounts, simplifying pricing for better transparency. Current users can remain on their legacy plans, with options to switch soon. The new system uses a single credit balance instead of multiple metrics. 🔍 Three plans are now available: - &lt;strong&gt;Free&lt;/strong&gt;: 300 credits, $0 - &lt;strong&gt;Personal&lt;/strong&gt;: 1,000 credits, $9/month - &lt;strong&gt;Pro&lt;/strong&gt;: 5,000 credits, $20/member/month Additional credits can be purchased as needed, and costs remain predictable. For more details on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: PSI Metrics for Kubernetes Graduates to Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7768/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7768/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Kubernetes users! As of v1.34, Pressure Stall Information (PSI) Metrics has graduated to Beta. PSI helps quantify resource pressure by measuring stalled tasks due to contention, providing a clearer view of CPU, memory, and I/O performance. Metrics are available via the Summary API and Prometheus endpoints. 📊 To enable PSI metrics, ensure your nodes run Linux kernel 4.20+ and enable the KubeletPSI feature gate. This allows for better resource management and performance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Set of Updates and Fixes for ReSharper and Rider 2025.2 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7742/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7742/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The first bug-fix update for ReSharper and Rider 2025.2 is now available! This release includes important fixes and quality improvements, along with performance optimizations. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t upgraded yet, check out the latest features in ReSharper and Rider. Key updates include Unity support in Command Line Tools and various fixes for C++ and IDE functionality. For the complete list of changes, visit our issue tracker. #ReSharper #Rider #SoftwareUpdate #DevTools #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Set of Updates and Fixes for ReSharper and Rider 2025.2 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7895/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7895/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The first bug-fix update for ReSharper and Rider 2025.2 is here! This update includes essential fixes, quality improvements, and performance optimizations. Key highlights include Unity support in Command Line Tools for ReSharper and enhanced functionality in Out-of-Process mode. For those yet to upgrade, check out the detailed blog posts on ReSharper and Rider 2025.2 for new features and improvements. 🔗 #ReSharper #Rider #SoftwareUpdate #DevTools #PerformanceBoost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover How Heroku’s AI PaaS Delivers Real-World Results at Dreamforce</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7911/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7911/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Heroku has transformed into an AI PaaS, addressing the challenge of moving AI from experimentation to production. This evolution includes features like AppLink and Managed Inference, designed to speed up the development of AI-powered applications. Join us at Dreamforce 2025 to see how businesses like Workday and AT&amp;amp;T; leverage Heroku for impactful results! #Heroku #AI #Dreamforce #CloudComputing #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB Engineering: Expanding Our Presence in Greater Toronto</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7732/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7732/</guid>
      <description>🚀 MongoDB is expanding its presence in Toronto, a key tech hub in North America! We are hiring for three main areas: Identity and Access Management, Atlas Stream Processing, and Atlas Search. This growth aims to foster innovation and create a collaborative environment for engineers. Join us to work on cutting-edge technology and enhance your career! 🌟 #MongoDB #TorontoTech #EngineeringJobs #CareerGrowth #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moonshot AI&#39;s Kimi K2 0905 model is now supported in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7775/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7775/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Moonshot AI&amp;rsquo;s Kimi K2 0905 model is now accessible through Vercel AI Gateway. This model supports agentic coding with a 256K context window and requires no additional provider accounts. AI Gateway offers a unified API for tracking usage, costs, and optimizing performance. It includes built-in observability and intelligent routing for enhanced reliability. To get started, install the AI SDK v5 and set the model to moonshotai/kimi-k2-0905. #AI #MoonshotAI #Vercel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcoming The Browser Company to Atlassian</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7733/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 12:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7733/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Atlassian! We are welcoming The Browser Company, creators of the Dia and Arc browsers, into the Atlassian family. This acquisition aims to develop a browser tailored for knowledge workers, enhancing productivity in the AI era. The new browser, Dia, will prioritize work-related tasks, integrating seamlessly with SaaS applications and leveraging AI for improved workflow. With an emphasis on security and usability, it aims to redefine how we work online. Looking forward to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games made with Unity: August 2025 in review</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7749/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7749/</guid>
      <description>🎮 August 2025 showcased a diverse range of games made with Unity, from the roguelite &lt;em&gt;Starlight Re:Volver&lt;/em&gt; to the cozy &lt;em&gt;Tiny Bookshop&lt;/em&gt;. 🏆 Congratulations to the IGF finalists and winners, especially &lt;em&gt;Consume Me&lt;/em&gt; for their three awards! 📅 Check out the latest Unity games on our Steam Curator page and share your projects with us! #UnityGames #IndieDev #GameAwards #GameDevelopment #Unity3D</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing EmbeddingGemma: The Best-in-Class Open Model for On-Device Embeddings</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7752/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7752/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing EmbeddingGemma, Google&amp;rsquo;s new open embedding model tailored for on-device AI applications. With 308 million parameters, it ranks highest among multilingual text models under 500M on the MTEB benchmark. This model supports advanced features like Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) and semantic search without needing an internet connection. EmbeddingGemma is optimized for efficiency, running on devices like smartphones and laptops. It offers customizable output dimensions and a 2K&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Tempo, the payments-first blockchain</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7751/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7751/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Tempo, a new Layer 1 blockchain focused on payments! Incubated by Stripe and Paradigm, Tempo is designed for scalable and low-cost stablecoin transactions. This initiative aims to enhance the efficiency of payments in the crypto space. Stay tuned for more updates on this innovative project! #Blockchain #Crypto #Stablecoins #Payments #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome EmbeddingGemma, Google&#39;s new efficient embedding model</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7747/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7747/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in AI! Google has introduced EmbeddingGemma, a new embedding model designed for efficiency. This model aims to enhance various applications by improving performance while reducing resource consumption. Developers can explore its capabilities on GitHub. Stay tuned for more updates on AI advancements! #Google #EmbeddingGemma #AI #MachineLearning #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Service Account Token Integration for Image Pulls Graduates to Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7712/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7712/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 has officially moved Service Account Token Integration for Kubelet Credential Providers to beta. This update enhances security by reducing reliance on long-lived image pull secrets. 🔒 Key changes include a required &lt;code&gt;cacheType&lt;/code&gt; field in the configuration and improved security isolation for image pulls. This ensures that only authorized pods can access specific container images. 🛡️ For more details, check out the Kubernetes documentation. #Kubernetes #DevOps #CloudSecurity #K8s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerate Autonomous Vehicle Development with the NVIDIA DRIVE AGX Thor Developer Kit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7682/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7682/</guid>
      <description>🚗🔍 The NVIDIA DRIVE AGX Thor Developer Kit is now available, enhancing the development of autonomous vehicle technology. This platform supports advanced AI models for better perception and decision-making, enabling a comprehensive in-vehicle experience. With powerful Blackwell GPUs and next-gen Arm CPUs, it meets high safety and security standards. The DRIVE AGX Thor is designed to empower automotive OEMs and developers in scaling performance and efficiency for future demands. #NVIDIA&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Reimagined Marketplace for App Developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7690/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7690/</guid>
      <description>🌐 The marketplace for app developers is evolving. With customer purchasing behavior shifting to quicker decisions, traditional models are no longer sufficient. At HubSpot, we’re addressing the visibility challenge for partners and customers. Our reimagined marketplace helps customers discover solutions faster by focusing on the problems they need to solve. With a unified infrastructure, we&amp;rsquo;ve reduced dead-end searches by 56%, increasing opportunities for app partners. This ensures that your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now GA: Share Materialized Views and Streaming Tables with Delta Sharing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7691/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7691/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in data sharing! Delta Sharing now supports Materialized Views and Streaming Tables, allowing seamless sharing of real-time and pre-aggregated data. This feature enhances security and accessibility across different clouds, regions, and platforms. Connect with your customers and partners more effectively! #DeltaSharing #DataManagement #CloudComputing #RealTimeData #DataSharing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building an Interactive Manhattan Guide with Chatbot Demo Builder</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7678/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7678/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited to share insights on the Chatbot Demo Builder, a no-code tool from MongoDB&amp;rsquo;s Atlas Search Playground! This tool allows users to create interactive Q&amp;amp;A bots using their own data or sample data. It simplifies the process by handling index creation and query generation directly in your browser, with no setup required. We built a chatbot to guide visitors exploring Manhattan, offering recommendations for pizza spots like Joe&amp;rsquo;s Pizza and Prince Street Pizza, as well as tips for day&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MongoDB and Hope AI: Craft Enterprise Code with AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7679/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7679/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in software development! MongoDB has partnered with Bit.dev to introduce Hope AI, an innovative tool for developers. Hope AI streamlines the coding process by generating customizable code architecture based on user input. Developers can easily approve plans before moving to code generation, enhancing collaboration and flexibility. 🤝 With a focus on privacy, all generated code remains secure and accessible only to project members. This integration promises to empower teams,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Databricks Assistant Data Science Agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7700/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7700/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Databricks! The Databricks Assistant has evolved into a powerful Data Science Agent. This tool streamlines the process from data exploration to actionable results in just minutes. Since its launch two years ago, it has become essential for data teams. Stay ahead in data science with the latest advancements! #Databricks #DataScience #Innovation #AI #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Vulnerable API Detection in JetBrains IDEs and Qodana</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7663/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7663/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains has partnered with Mend.io to enhance code security in its tools. This collaboration enables IDEs and Qodana to identify vulnerable and malicious packages effectively. 📊 The new Vulnerable API feature in the Package Checker plugin utilizes enriched data to analyze open-source libraries, improving detection capabilities across various programming languages. 🔍 Users can easily enable inspections for vulnerable APIs in their IDE settings, ensuring their code remains secure&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cycle is joining Atlassian</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7660/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 07:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7660/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Cycle is joining Atlassian to enhance Jira Product Discovery with AI-powered feedback capabilities. This integration will help product managers capture and process customer insights directly within Jira, streamlining decision-making and improving alignment across teams. Cycle will simplify feedback management by automatically gathering insights and highlighting key information, enabling more confident product development. Stay tuned for smarter features that elevate your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharks of DigitalOcean: Archana Kamath, Senior Director, IaaS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7654/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 04:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7654/</guid>
      <description>Archana Kamath, Senior Director of IaaS at DigitalOcean, shares insights from her six years at the company. She highlights the importance of simplifying complex cloud solutions and fostering a collaborative culture focused on customer needs. DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s mission is to disrupt cloud computing, especially in AI/ML, with a customer-first approach. Archana emphasizes an iterative innovation process driven by customer feedback. Learn more about Archana&amp;rsquo;s views and DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s journey! 🎥&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe coding with GitLab Duo Agent Platform: Issue to MR Flow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7686/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7686/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing the GitLab Duo Agent Platform! Available now in Beta, this tool enables AI agents to streamline complex tasks with GitLab resources like issues and merge requests. The &amp;ldquo;Issue to MR&amp;rdquo; Flow simplifies turning well-scoped issues into draft merge requests, saving developers time and effort. By automating the process, it reduces the overhead associated with common development tasks. To get started, ensure you have a clear issue with requirements and the necessary permissions. Then,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New on DigitalOcean App Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7636/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7636/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from DigitalOcean App Platform! This week, the platform has integrated AI-powered coding assistants like Claude Code and VS Code MCP plugins with the new DigitalOcean MCP Server. Now, you can deploy apps, manage databases, and check billing—all from your coding environment. 💻 Ready to streamline your workflow? DigitalOcean offers tutorials to help you quickly go from code to production using just a few prompts. Explore more with the Claude Code Tutorial and GitHub repo!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall Spotlight 2025: A Look at Tools for Developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7640/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:33:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7640/</guid>
      <description>🚀 HubSpot is enhancing the developer experience by providing powerful tools and seamless integrations. With direct links to Sentry and Honeycomb, developers can now monitor app health in real-time, ensuring better visibility and faster troubleshooting. 🔍 The new MCP server allows integration of popular IDE tools, simplifying project management with chat-based prompts. Plus, the Figma Design Kit enables quick prototyping of app cards without coding. #DeveloperTools #HubSpot #AppDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Faster, Deliver Smarter: Introducing the HubSpot Developer Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7641/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:30:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7641/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from HubSpot! The new HubSpot Developer Platform is here, offering a unified framework for building apps. This platform enhances developer productivity with AI-native documentation and a streamlined CLI setup. Developers can now create deeper integrations and rich user experiences, with expanded UI flexibility. Customize app spaces and empower HubSpot admins to utilize unique functionalities. #HubSpot #DeveloperPlatform #Innovation #SoftwareDevelopment #AppIntegration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing your newest study buddy: stackoverflow.ai</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7625/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7625/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing stackoverflow.ai, your new study buddy for coding! This AI tool offers instant answers and guides you through learning, making it easier for developers at any level to find solutions. It prioritizes community-verified knowledge, ensuring reliable information. Plus, you can connect with the Stack Overflow community for deeper discussions. Try it out this school year and share your feedback! 👩‍💻👨‍💻 #Coding #AI #StackOverflow #Learning #DeveloperCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s New in CUDA Toolkit 13.0 for Jetson Thor: Unified Arm Ecosystem and More</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7631/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7631/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements are on the horizon with CUDA Toolkit 13.0 for Jetson Thor! This release introduces a unified toolkit for Arm platforms, eliminating the need for separate installations. Developers can build applications once and deploy them seamlessly across various systems. Enhanced features like Unified Virtual Memory and improved developer tools streamline workflows and enhance performance for edge AI applications. #NVIDIA #CUDA #JetsonThor #EdgeComputing #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Sign-On is Now Available, Strengthening Security and Simplifying Authentication</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7637/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7637/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for DigitalOcean users! Single Sign-On (SSO) is now available via Okta OpenID Connect (OIDC). SSO simplifies user access, reduces IT workload, and strengthens security. Teams can log in securely with corporate credentials, eliminating multiple passwords. Key benefits include streamlined onboarding, enhanced security, and a seamless login experience. Get started today and empower your team! #SingleSignOn #DigitalOcean #Okta #Cybersecurity #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Django MongoDB Backend Now Generally Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7621/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7621/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news for Django developers! The Django MongoDB Backend is now generally available. This production-ready package allows seamless integration of MongoDB with familiar Django libraries and conventions. Enjoy the flexibility of MongoDB’s document model while maintaining Django’s structure. With features like ORM support and the full admin interface, you can build everything from prototypes to complex applications efficiently. 🌐 Deploy globally with MongoDB Atlas, scaling easily across&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RubyMine Is Now Free for Non-Commercial Use</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7616/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7616/</guid>
      <description>🚀 RubyMine is now available for free for non-commercial use! This change supports learners, open-source contributors, and developers working on personal projects. The goal is to make essential tools accessible for everyone in the Ruby community. Commercial use still requires the existing licensing model. 🎉 For full details on features and licensing, check the FAQ! #RubyMine #Ruby #Development #OpenSource #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab achieves ISO/IEC 42001 certification for AI governance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7617/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7617/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab has achieved the ISO/IEC 42001 certification for AI governance! This certification establishes a framework for responsible AI management within organizations. The certification covers GitLab Duo and the Duo Agent Platform, enhancing collaboration and efficiency in software development. Key features include code suggestions, vulnerability explanations, and automated test generation. This achievement promotes trust, transparency, and aligns with evolving AI regulations. GitLab is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Fab September Flash Sale is now on!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7619/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7619/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The Fab September Flash Sale is here! 🚨 Enjoy discounts of up to 70% on thousands of assets. 🛍️ The sale kicks off at 10 AM ET on September 2 and will continue until 5 PM ET on September 5. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on these amazing deals! #FabSeptemberSale #Discounts #FlashSale #Savings #ShopNow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why enterprise independence matters more than ever in DevSecOps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7635/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7635/</guid>
      <description>GitLab emphasizes the importance of enterprise independence in its latest release, GitLab 18.3. Key features include enhanced AI transparency and governance, ensuring that your code and data are not locked into vendor systems. The GitLab AI Transparency Center details data usage, providing clarity in an evolving landscape. 🛠️✨ Deployment options are flexible, allowing organizations to adapt to regulatory challenges without vendor constraints. Security and compliance are built-in, reducing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Open — AWS Asia Pacific (New Zealand) Region</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7601/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 22:06:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7601/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AWS has officially launched its first New Zealand Region with three Availability Zones! This new infrastructure allows local organizations to store data and run workloads securely within New Zealand, enhancing performance and reducing latency. The investment of NZD $7.5 billion is projected to boost the GDP by NZD $10.8 billion and create 1,000 jobs annually. Since establishing its presence in 2013, AWS has expanded its services to improve connectivity and support compliance with multiple&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: DRA has graduated to GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7599/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7599/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes 1.34 is now live, featuring significant advancements in Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA)! Key highlights include the core of DRA graduating to General Availability (GA), ensuring stability and confidence for users. Key features have also moved to beta, enhancing control and flexibility in resource management. Notable updates include improved admin access labeling and prioritized device lists for workloads. Explore new alpha features aimed at simplifying resource management for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Ben McCarthy is bringing Obscura’s vision to photo editing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7577/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7577/</guid>
      <description>📸 Ben McCarthy, creator of Obscura, has launched Obscura Studio, a new photo editing app focused on simplicity and efficiency. The app emerged from the need to adapt to Apple&amp;rsquo;s Lock Screen Camera extension, prompting a redesign of Obscura. This standalone editor allows for streamlined editing without launching the camera first. McCarthy emphasizes thoughtful design that prioritizes ease of use, aiming to create a product that meets user needs effectively. #PhotoEditing #AppDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The LSP API Is Now Available to All IntelliJ IDEA Users and Plugin Developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7587/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 09:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7587/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The LSP API is now available to all IntelliJ IDEA users and plugin developers. Starting with IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate 2025.2, users can access a limited set of LSP features even after their subscription expires. This change aims to remove barriers for plugin developers and smaller language communities. In 2025.3, the Community Edition will be phased out, consolidating the installation process for all users. This allows for broader plugin development without&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Finer-Grained Control Over Container Restarts</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7552/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7552/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes 1.34 introduces an alpha feature called Container Restart Policy and Rules. This feature allows developers to set individual restart policies for each container in a Pod, moving beyond the previous single policy for all containers. 🔧 Users can now define restart rules based on exit codes, offering more control for complex workloads. For instance, you can ensure that an ML training job restarts only on retriable errors without rescheduling the entire Pod. 📦 The new capability is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating threat analysis and response with Cloudy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7537/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7537/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloudflare has enhanced threat analysis with Cloudy, its AI agent, integrating advanced security analytics and a new conversational interface. This development aims to simplify investigations during traffic spikes, helping security teams quickly identify and address issues. Over 54,000 users have engaged with Cloudy since its launch, highlighting its effectiveness in rule creation and insightful log summaries. Now, users can ask questions and refine their inquiries, streamlining root cause&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare is the best place to build realtime voice agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7539/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7539/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news from Cloudflare! They have launched new tools to simplify the development of real-time, voice-enabled AI applications. With Cloudflare Realtime Agents, developers can now orchestrate voice AI pipelines efficiently on a global network. These advancements support features like direct WebRTC audio connections and real-time AI inference. Cloudflare aims to make voice AI deployment as easy as creating a static website, enhancing user experience with low latency. #VoiceAI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudy Summarizations of Email Detections: Beta Announcement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7538/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7538/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Cloudflare! We are enhancing our Email Security product with Cloudy, our internal AI, to provide automated summaries of detected threats. This aims to assist SOC teams in understanding flagged messages better. Given the rapid evolution of email attacks, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for security teams to know what threats are being blocked and why. However, current detection methods can leave analysts with unclear information. Cloudy Summaries will translate complex detection logic into&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2.1 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7535/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7535/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA has released its first minor update: version 2025.2.1! You can easily update through the IDE, Toolbox App, or download it from the website. This update resolves key issues, including improved EAR artifact management and better SVG exports. For a full list of improvements, check the release notes. Happy coding! #IntelliJIDEA #Update #SoftwareDevelopment #Coding #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New general-purpose Amazon EC2 M8i and M8i Flex instances are now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7497/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 19:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7497/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for cloud users! Amazon has launched the M8i and M8i-Flex EC2 instances powered by Intel Xeon processors. These new instances offer up to 15% better price performance and 20% higher performance than previous generations. They&amp;rsquo;re designed for general workloads like web applications, databases, and AI models. M8i instances also provide enhanced network and EBS bandwidth, improving performance across various applications. #AmazonEC2 #CloudComputing #TechUpdates #AWS #IntelXeon</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: User preferences (kuberc) are available for testing in kubectl 1.34</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7520/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7520/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Kubernetes users! The Kubernetes v1.34 release introduces user preferences in kubectl, now in beta. This feature allows you to set default options, like enabling interactive delete, and define custom aliases to streamline your workflow. To configure, place your preferences in a &lt;code&gt;kuberc&lt;/code&gt; file, located in your kubeconfig directory. Check out the official documentation for more details! #Kubernetes #kubectl #DevOps #CloudComputing #UserPreferences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.1.5 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7483/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7483/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA has released update v2025.1.5! You can easily update from the IDE, Toolbox App, or download it from the website. Key improvements include better performance during Google Meet screen sharing on macOS with a second monitor and enhancements to UrlClassLoader.getFiles. For details on resolved issues, check the release notes. Happy coding! 💻✨ #IntelliJIDEA #SoftwareUpdate #Programming #DeveloperTools #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating image segmentation models for background removal for Images</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7467/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7467/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This week, the Images team introduced background removal using dichotomous image segmentation models on Workers AI. We evaluated several models to efficiently isolate subjects from their backgrounds. Image segmentation involves dividing an image into meaningful parts, with salient object detection highlighting the most prominent areas. The focus was on creating a soft saliency mask, assigning pixel values to indicate foreground and background. This allows for accurate predictions across&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The age of agents: cryptographically recognizing agent traffic</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7468/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7468/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Cloudflare has introduced Web Bot Auth, allowing websites to differentiate between verified bots and agents. This new system supports the growing demand for granular control over bot traffic, helping to block malicious bots while enabling helpful ones. The classification includes agents that act on behalf of users, enhancing interactions like booking flights or ordering food. Stay updated on the evolving bot landscape! 🤖✨ #WebSecurity #BotTraffic #Cloudflare #VerifiedBots #AIagents</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The next step for content creators in working with AI bots: Introducing AI Crawl Control</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7470/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7470/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloudflare has launched AI Crawl Control, previously known as AI Audit, to empower content creators with smarter crawling controls. This tool allows creators to communicate their terms directly to AI crawlers, addressing the challenges of licensing and referral traffic. With customizable 402 HTTP responses, content owners can specify how crawlers can access their material while promoting potential revenue opportunities. This innovative approach aims to enhance content independence for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koog 0.4.0 Is Out: Observable, Predictable, and Deployable Anywhere You Build</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7458/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7458/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The release of Koog 0.4.0 introduces significant improvements for developers. Key features include support for Langfuse and W&amp;amp;B Weave, enhanced observability with OpenTelemetry, and seamless Ktor integration. This version focuses on making agents more predictable and easier to deploy, while also supporting new models and platforms. Explore how these updates can streamline your development process! #Koog #DevTools #OpenTelemetry #Ktor #AIIntegration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper’s New Out-of-Process Engine Cuts Visual Studio startup UI freezes by 61%</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7459/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7459/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Visual Studio users! ReSharper 2025.2 introduces an out-of-process engine that significantly reduces UI freezes during analysis. With this update, analysis runs in a separate 64-bit worker, improving workflow by allowing the UI to remain responsive. Testing showed a 61% decrease in UI freezes during startup compared to the previous version. Stay tuned for more optimizations! ⚙️ #ReSharper #VisualStudio #SoftwareDevelopment #Productivity #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Of Wind &amp; Will (O&#39; WaW)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7447/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7447/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 is here, featuring 58 enhancements! This release includes 23 stable, 22 beta, and 13 alpha features, showcasing the strength of its development cycle. 🌬 The theme &amp;ldquo;Of Wind &amp;amp; Will&amp;rdquo; highlights the community&amp;rsquo;s resilience in navigating challenges. Key updates include: - &lt;strong&gt;Stable&lt;/strong&gt;: Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA) now enables better device management. - &lt;strong&gt;Beta&lt;/strong&gt;: Short-lived ServiceAccount tokens enhance security for image pulls. - &lt;strong&gt;Alpha&lt;/strong&gt;: KYAML introduces a new, safer YAML&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform provider for Google Cloud 7.0 is now GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7288/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7288/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Terraform users! The Terraform provider for Google Cloud has reached general availability with version 7.0. This release introduces new ephemeral resources and write-only attributes to enhance security when managing sensitive data. The community&amp;rsquo;s feedback has played a crucial role in this improvement. With over 1.4 billion downloads, the provider now supports 800+ resources and 300+ data sources. #Terraform #GoogleCloud #CloudSecurity #DevOps #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s Next for CLion: The 2025.3 Roadmap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7275/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7275/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are on the horizon for CLion with the upcoming 2025.3 release, set for November! Key priorities include: - Transitioning to the CLion Nova language engine as the default. - Enhancements to project formats and build tools. - Improved features for embedded development. Stay tuned for more details on these updates! #CLion #SoftwareDevelopment #TechUpdates #EmbeddedDevelopment #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Gateway now gives you access to your favorite AI models, dynamic routing and more — through just one endpoint</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7233/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7233/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Cloudflare! The new AI Gateway allows users to access multiple AI models through a single endpoint. This update simplifies the management of AI applications with features like unified billing, secure key storage, and dynamic routing. Users can connect to providers like OpenAI and Google, managing everything from one dashboard. Experience improved performance and observability while controlling costs effortlessly. Learn more about these features on the AI Gateway landing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State-of-the-art image generation Leonardo models and text-to-speech Deepgram models now available in Workers AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7293/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7293/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in Workers AI! We&amp;rsquo;ve partnered with Leonardo.Ai and Deepgram to enhance our model catalog. Users can now access advanced image generation and real-time text-to-speech models, all hosted on Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s infrastructure. This integration allows developers to create applications with low-latency image generation and audio voice agents effectively. Discover more about our new models and how they can support your AI projects! #AI #WorkersAI #Leonardo #Deepgram #Cloudflare</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anomaly alerts now in limited beta for Enterprise customers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7270/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7270/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Enterprise customers can now access anomaly alerts in limited beta! These alerts help quickly identify unusual patterns in application metrics, allowing for prompt issue resolution. Users can integrate alerts via webhooks into existing monitoring systems and receive notifications directly in Slack channels. Explore this feature with Observability Plus and streamline your monitoring process! #AnomalyDetection #EnterpriseSolutions #MonitoringAlerts #TechUpdates #ObservabilityPlus</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Slack&#39;s Bolt.js to Vercel with @vercel/slack-bolt</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7271/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7271/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! @vercel has released @vercel/slack-bolt, an adapter that allows you to deploy Slack&amp;rsquo;s Bolt for JavaScript on Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Cloud. This tool helps manage Slack webhook events efficiently. It addresses the challenge of responding within three seconds to avoid timeouts, using Fluid compute’s streaming feature. Compatible with any function or framework like Hono, Nitro, or Next.js, you can start with the Slack Agent Template or explore the library on npm. #Slack&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop Accelerates Innovation with Faster Release Cadence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7231/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7231/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news from Docker! Starting with release 4.45.0 on August 28, Docker Desktop will shift to a new update schedule, moving from monthly to bi-weekly releases, aiming for weekly updates by 2025. This change is in response to user requests for quicker access to new features and urgent updates. 🚀 Enhancements include smarter component updates that occur silently without interrupting your workflow and clearer update information within the app. Enterprise users will retain control over&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the terminal: Gemini CLI comes to Zed</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7253/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7253/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Gemini CLI is now integrated into the Zed code editor. This partnership brings AI capabilities directly into your coding environment. With this integration, developers can generate and refactor code in real-time, and get instant answers to coding queries. The seamless workflow enhances productivity and efficiency. Explore the power of AI in your coding tasks with Gemini CLI in Zed! 💻✨ #GeminiCLI #Zed #AIinCoding #DeveloperTools #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring Back the Free Plan</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7294/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7294/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Great news for new Railway users! Railway has re-introduced its free plan, making it more accessible for everyone. This initiative aims to enhance user experience and encourage more individuals to explore its features. Check it out and start building your projects today! #Railway #FreePlan #TechUpdates #UserExperience #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike to Acquire Onum to Transform How Data Powers the Agentic SOC</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7436/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7436/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike has announced its agreement to acquire Onum, enhancing its Falcon® platform. This acquisition aims to transform how data powers the agentic SOC by leveraging real-time data architecture. 📊 Onum&amp;rsquo;s technology will enable faster, high-fidelity intelligence, addressing the data crisis security teams face today. Legacy SIEMs struggle with overwhelming volumes of data, often leading to costly decisions. 💡 With Onum, CrowdStrike promises to improve processing speed and reduce storage&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level Up Your Security Posture with the Auth0 Security Detection Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7228/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7228/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for security professionals! Auth0 has launched the &lt;strong&gt;Security Detection Catalog&lt;/strong&gt; on GitHub, an open-source resource aimed at enhancing your security posture. It offers actionable intelligence and proactive threat updates to help you stay ahead of emerging threats. Each detection includes threat descriptions and recommended prevention strategies, ensuring a swift response. The catalog is designed for compatibility with Sigma rules, allowing for quick deployment across various&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop “vibe testing” your LLMs. It&#39;s time for real evals.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7292/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7292/</guid>
      <description>Stop relying on &amp;ldquo;vibe testing&amp;rdquo; for LLMs! Stax, a new developer tool, aims to improve AI evaluations by streamlining the testing process. It allows users to conduct thorough assessments and make data-driven decisions using human labeling and LLM-as-a-judge auto-raters. General benchmarks may not fit your specific needs. With Stax, you can create tailored evaluations that offer clear metrics for performance. #AI #LLM #Stax #Evaluation #TechInnovation 🤖📈🔍</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Dedicated Cisco Wireless Certification Track Is on the Horizon</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7194/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7194/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for wireless professionals! Cisco is launching a dedicated Wireless Certification Track in March 2026. This includes the new CCNP Wireless and CCIE Wireless certifications, designed to align with modern wireless technologies. From foundational courses to expert levels, these certifications will equip you with essential skills for managing complex networks. Start your journey with the Understanding Cisco Wireless Foundations training to build the necessary knowledge for WLAN&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From contextual understanding to execution: AI that truly works as part of your team</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7247/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7247/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in Rovo Chat enhance team collaboration! New features allow teams to tackle complex tasks with ease. Rovo can now autonomously break down requests and gather insights from various Atlassian tools. Additionally, Rovo&amp;rsquo;s improved memory understands your organization&amp;rsquo;s context, making interactions more efficient. Explore how Rovo Chat can work as a true team member today! #AI #Teamwork #RovoChat #Atlassian #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Nova Models: Now Available on Heroku</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7214/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7214/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Nova models are now available on Heroku. Provisioning these advanced AI models is as easy as adding an add-on to your Heroku app. This allows businesses to access powerful, cost-effective AI with simplicity. The Nova family includes nova-pro, designed for accuracy and deep reasoning, and nova-lite, optimized for speed and high-throughput applications. Explore the capabilities of these models today! #AmazonNova #Heroku #AI #MachineLearning #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing the AI Revolution: Introducing Cloudflare MCP Server Portals</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7237/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7237/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in AI security! Cloudflare has launched MCP Server Portals in Open Beta. This new feature allows organizations to centralize, secure, and monitor every MCP connection. The Model Context Protocol (MCP) enables Large Language Models (LLMs) like ChatGPT to interact with various applications, enhancing their functionality. Discover how MCP transforms AI into collaborative teammates while addressing security concerns. 🔒 #AI #Cloudflare #Cybersecurity #MCP #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30-day runtime log retention, now available in Observability Plus</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7230/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7230/</guid>
      <description>📊 Exciting news for Observability Plus users! Teams can now access 30 days of runtime log retention, which includes valuable details on requests, Vercel Functions, and cache activity. This feature allows you to view, query, and share up to 14 consecutive days of log data at once. Best of all, this extended retention comes at no extra cost for Pro and Enterprise plans! Learn more about Runtime Logs and how to utilize this feature. #ObservabilityPlus #LogRetention #DataInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaHuman for Houdini Release</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7276/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7276/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for creators! A new version of MetaHuman for Houdini is now available for download from Fab. This update allows users to bring MetaHuman characters to life in SideFX Houdini. This release enhances the integration between Unreal Engine and Houdini, streamlining workflows for developers. #MetaHuman #Houdini #GameDevelopment #3DArt #UnrealEngine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DigitalOcean MCP Server is now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7176/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7176/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The new DigitalOcean MCP Server is here! This tool allows developers to manage cloud resources using natural language commands through AI tools like Cursor and Claude. It connects to 9 services, streamlining operations. 👨‍💻 With simple commands, you can deploy apps, manage databases, and optimize costs—all without extensive scripting. 🔗 Get started by following the configuration guidelines on GitHub. #DigitalOcean #CloudManagement #AI #MCP #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-grained permissions for job tokens is now GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7209/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7209/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab 18.3 has launched fine-grained permissions for job tokens, now in GA! This update enhances security by allowing maintainers to set specific permissions for job tokens, following the principle of least privilege. 🔒 Key resources include Repositories, Deployments, and Pipelines, with more API endpoints planned for future releases. This capability aims to reduce security risks in CI/CD pipelines. 👥 DevOps teams should assess this opt-in feature for projects with automated deployments&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Gemini 2.5 Flash Image, our state-of-the-art image model</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7255/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7255/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Gemini 2.5 Flash Image! This advanced image generation and editing model allows users to blend multiple images seamlessly. It maintains character consistency for storytelling and enables targeted transformations through natural language. Available via the Gemini API, Google AI Studio, and Vertex AI, it is priced at $30 per million output tokens. #Gemini2.5 #AI #ImageEditing #GoogleAI #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCS is now generally available: Increase engagement and ROI with zero code changes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7244/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7244/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for businesses! RCS is now generally available through Twilio. Engage your customers with rich content on a branded channel without any code changes to your existing messaging solutions. This update aims to enhance customer engagement and improve return on investment. #RCS #Twilio #CustomerEngagement #Messaging #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Coding Agent Experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7191/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 23:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7191/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian is enhancing the coding agent experience through machine learning. This aims to identify well-scoped Jira work items and provide relevant code context, leading to more efficient AI-powered development for software teams. Key indicators of effective task descriptions include detailed descriptions, presence of file paths, code snippets, and technical terms. These elements help coding agents understand and act on tasks more effectively. For implementation, Atlassian is considering both&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s Next for Kotlin Multiplatform and Compose Multiplatform – August 2025 Update</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7171/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7171/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates on Kotlin Multiplatform and Compose Multiplatform! In the next 6-12 months, key priorities include enhancing the iOS target for improved developer experience, enabling more web use cases, and refining IDE support. Compose Multiplatform is now in Beta for Web, with a focus on essential APIs and ecosystem components. Your feedback is crucial! 💻✨ #Kotlin #Multiplatform #Compose #WebDevelopment #DeveloperExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVFP4 Trains with Precision of 16-Bit and Speed and Efficiency of 4-Bit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6335/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6335/</guid>
      <description>🚀 NVIDIA has introduced NVFP4, a 4-bit format designed to enhance AI workloads during pretraining of large language models (LLMs). This innovation aims to improve training efficiency and throughput while maintaining accuracy. The shift from higher precision formats to 4-bit is set to redefine scalability in AI development. Collaboration with major organizations like Google Cloud and OpenAI is ongoing to explore this technology&amp;rsquo;s full potential. #AI #NVIDIA #MachineLearning #LLMs #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing NVIDIA Jetson Thor, the Ultimate Platform for Physical AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6336/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 17:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6336/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Robotics is evolving! The shift from specialist machines to adaptable robots marks a new era in generalist robotics. These robots are designed to learn and perform various tasks, enhancing efficiency across industries. With NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Jetson Thor platform, developers can create flexible robots that streamline operations without constant reprogramming. Key components include hardware integration, real-time control, perception, and high-level reasoning to facilitate complex interactions&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon Aurora 10th anniversary, Amazon EC2 R8 instances, Amazon Bedrock and more (August 25, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6537/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:30:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6537/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting week in AWS! Amazon Aurora celebrates 10 years of innovation, revolutionizing database technology with features like serverless capabilities and generative AI support. 🎉 New AWS launches include customizable dashboards in Billing and Cost Management, and enhanced access to OpenAI models through Amazon Bedrock. Check out the latest advancements! 🚀 #AWS #AmazonAurora #CloudComputing #DatabaseInnovation #OpenAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLM Compressor 0.7.0 release recap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6534/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:09:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6534/</guid>
      <description>🚀 LLM Compressor has released version 0.7.0, enhancing performance for quantizing large language models. Key updates include: 1️⃣ New QuIP and SpinQuant-style transforms for improved accuracy. 2️⃣ Mixed-precision support with FP4 enhancements for better layer quantization. 3️⃣ DeepSeek v3-style block quantization for efficient compression without calibration data. Explore more about these features! #LLMCompressor #AI #MachineLearning #Quantization #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Cloudflare’s AI to FedRAMP High</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6347/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6347/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloudflare is set to enhance AI capabilities for the US public sector by bringing its AI Developer suite, including Workers AI, AI Gateway, and Vectorize, into FedRAMP Moderate and High boundaries by 2026. This initiative aims to streamline generative AI use while ensuring compliance and security. Workers AI will provide serverless inference close to users, improving response times for agency services. With these tools, agencies can modernize their operations and improve efficiency in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devin, Raycast, Windsurf, and Goose now supported on Vercel MCP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6342/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6342/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! You can now integrate Devin, Raycast, Windsurf, and Goose with Vercel&amp;rsquo;s Model Context Protocol (MCP). This allows for secure access to AI clients approved by Vercel. To get started, follow the installation steps for each client. Discover how to enhance your projects with Vercel MCP! #Vercel #AIIntegration #WebDevelopment #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Bolsters Security for Government With New FedRAMP Authorizations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6333/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6333/</guid>
      <description>Cisco has announced three new FedRAMP-authorized cloud security solutions designed for federal, state, and local agencies. These solutions respond to the growing need for secure, adaptable systems in complex digital environments. The new offerings include Cisco Secure Access for Government, Cisco Security Cloud Control for Government, and Cisco Multicloud Defense for Government. These tools aim to enhance security while supporting compliance and zero trust initiatives. As government agencies&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom admin roles are now GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6337/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6337/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab has rolled out custom admin roles for Self-Managed and Dedicated instances! These roles enable organizations to apply granular permissions, ensuring the principle of least privilege is upheld while enhancing operational efficiency. Key features include centralized management, LDAP integration, and purpose-built roles for various teams. This aligns with GitLab&amp;rsquo;s mission to boost software supply chain security. For more details, check out the custom roles documentation. #GitLab&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tecton is Joining Databricks to Power Real-Time Data for Personalized AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6318/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 23:55:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6318/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news in the data world! Tecton is set to join forces with Databricks to enhance real-time data capabilities for personalized AI agents. This partnership aims to streamline data operations and improve AI performance across various applications. Stay tuned for advancements in AI technology! #DataScience #ArtificialIntelligence #TechNews #Databricks #Tecton</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian’s AI Gateway: Best in Class Model Garden</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6538/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:05:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6538/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Atlassian has launched its AI Gateway, a solution designed to streamline access to various LLMs from top providers like OpenAI and Google. This platform supports developers by offering a curated model garden with over 20 LLMs and integrates seamlessly with existing tools. It features a unified API for easy model switching and automated fallback options for reliability. All models maintain zero data retention, ensuring user privacy and security. #Atlassian #AI #MachineLearning #LLM&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reimagine Your Data Center With Cisco Nexus Hyperfabric on Black Belt Academy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6294/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:22:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6294/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data center professionals! Cisco Nexus HyperFabric, co-developed with NVIDIA, offers scalable AI data center solutions. This cloud-managed network fabric is designed to simplify the management of infrastructure and software. 🌐 Partners can now access enablement resources on Cisco Black Belt Academy, covering everything from solution overviews to deployment guidance. Learn how to leverage Nexus HyperFabric for diverse use cases and enhance your offerings in the evolving AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoQ: Refactoring the Internet&#39;s real-time media stack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6314/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6314/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Media over QUIC (MoQ) is a new IETF standard transforming real-time media streaming by unifying various protocols. For years, we relied on RTMP, HLS, and WebRTC, each addressing specific needs but creating complexity in the process. MoQ aims to streamline this by combining low latency with scalability and operational simplicity. Cloudflare has launched the first MoQ relay network, collaborating with industry leaders like Meta and Google to create a shared foundation for future applications&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy xmcp servers with zero-configuration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6307/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6307/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel now supports xmcp, a framework for building MCP servers using TypeScript with zero configuration. 📁 It utilizes file-based routing, making it easy to develop tools for your MCP server. You can create tools simply by adding a file with a default export. 🛠️ Learn more about deploying xmcp to Vercel in the documentation. #Vercel #xmcp #TypeScript #WebDevelopment #MCPServers</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Drive Integration, Python 3.11 in Conda Environments, and Security improvements in Datalore 2025.4</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6304/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6304/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Datalore 2025.4 is now live! Key updates include support for Google Drive folders as data connections, allowing seamless access to files like CSV and JSON without manual uploads. Python 3.11 is the new default in conda environments, enhancing performance and security. Users can also customize their Python versions as needed. Security improvements have been made to address CSRF and XSS vulnerabilities, ensuring safer usage. #Datalore #DataScience #Python #CloudStorage #SecurityUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Less Coding, More Science: Simplify Ocean Modeling on GPUs With OpenACC and Unified Memory</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5038/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5038/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in ocean modeling are here! NVIDIA HPC SDK v25.7 simplifies GPU programming for high-performance computing applications. This update automates data movement between CPU and GPU, reducing manual management and enhancing developer productivity. Notable systems like the NVIDIA GH200 Grace Hopper Superchip are leading the way. With unified memory programming, developers can focus more on science and less on coding complexities. This change is already benefiting projects,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Building SaaS from Scratch: Meet the SeaNotes Starter Kit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5049/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 14:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5049/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing SeaNotes, a SaaS Starter Kit by DigitalOcean! Designed for indie hackers and developers, it offers a ready-to-use framework for building SaaS applications quickly. With built-in features like user authentication, Stripe billing, and AI integrations, you can focus on your product instead of setup. 🔗 Check it out on GitHub and start building with best practices in mind! #SaaS #DigitalOcean #SeaNotes #OpenSource #DevTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tax and Price Updates for Apps, In-App Purchases, and Subscriptions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5171/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:00:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5171/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The App Store is adjusting prices for apps and in-app purchases due to recent tax and exchange rate changes. 📅 As of August 21, updates include new VAT rates in Estonia and Romania, along with a digital services tax removal in Canada. The Philippines and Vietnam have introduced new VAT and personal income tax rates for developers. 🔄 Starting September 8, pricing updates will occur for apps not using the Philippines or Vietnam as their base storefront. For further details on managing prices,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Gateway is now generally available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5777/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5777/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI Gateway is now available! This new tool offers a unified API to access hundreds of AI models with features like transparent pricing and built-in observability. Key benefits include sub-20ms latency, automatic failover, and detailed usage analytics. You can use the AI SDK or an OpenAI-compatible endpoint to get started quickly. Discover more about AI Gateway today! #AIGateway #AIModels #TechNews #Innovation #APIs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Gateway: Production-ready reliability for your AI apps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5776/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5776/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Building AI apps just got easier! With tools like the AI SDK, developers can create both frontends and backends in minutes. However, moving to production poses challenges, especially with reliability. Connecting to a single LLM provider can create risks if that provider faces downtime or rate limits. Introducing AI Gateway: it ensures consistent availability and stability for AI workloads, having already supported millions of users. #AIGateway #AIApps #TechInnovation #Reliability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Streamdown: Open source Markdown for AI streaming</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5778/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5778/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Streamdown: a new open-source Markdown renderer tailored for AI streaming! Streamdown enhances the AI Elements Response component and can also function as a standalone option for developers. It effectively manages unterminated chunks, interactive code blocks, and math expressions. Key features include: - Tailwind typography styles - GitHub Flavored Markdown support - Interactive code blocks with Shiki highlighting - LaTeX math support - Enhanced security for untrusted content&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedded views: The future of work tracking in GitLab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5775/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5775/</guid>
      <description>📊 Tired of switching tabs in GitLab to track your projects? Introducing &lt;strong&gt;Embedded Views&lt;/strong&gt;! This feature, available in version 18.3, allows you to access live, relevant data directly within your workflow. No more outdated reports or endless context switching. With &lt;strong&gt;GitLab Query Language (GLQL)&lt;/strong&gt;, you can pull real-time data right where you need it, enhancing collaboration and maintaining context. Learn how this can transform your team&amp;rsquo;s work tracking! 🚀 #GitLab #ProjectManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab 18.3: Expanding AI orchestration in software engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5063/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5063/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab 18.3 is here, enhancing AI orchestration in software engineering! The platform now integrates AI at three levels: a unified data repository, a control plane for software delivery, and a streamlined user experience. This aims to boost productivity and simplify workflows. Key updates include the introduction of AI agents, expanded integrations, and enhanced context awareness for improved collaboration. Explore the future of DevSecOps with GitLab! 🌟 #GitLab #DevSecOps #AIIntegration&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab 18.3: Expanding AI orchestration in software engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-6302/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-6302/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab 18.3 is here, enhancing software engineering with integrated AI capabilities! The platform now serves as a comprehensive system of record, control plane, and user experience hub. Key updates include a Knowledge Graph for better data context, an Orchestration Layer for multi-agent workflows, and first-class agent integration across the development lifecycle. This evolution promotes seamless human-AI collaboration, boosting productivity for over 50 million users. Explore the future of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s new in Gemini Code Assist</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5172/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5172/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Gemini Code Assist! Agent Mode is now available in VS Code (Preview) and IntelliJ (Stable), enhancing your coding experience. It offers a collaborative approach to complex tasks by proposing detailed plans for user review and approval. Key features include inline diffs for visual code modifications and persistent chat history to streamline workflows. This aims to boost developer productivity and efficiency significantly. #GeminiCodeAssist #DeveloperTools #Programming&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Public Preview of Request for Access in Unity Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5103/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5103/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Databricks! The public preview of the Request for Access feature in Unity Catalog has been announced. This tool aims to enhance self-service data discovery and simplify access provisioning for users in security-focused enterprises. Stay informed and empower your teams with better data access! 📊🔐 #DataAccess #UnityCatalog #Databricks #DataSecurity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing OpenAI gpt-oss Models on the DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5050/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5050/</guid>
      <description>🚀 OpenAI has launched its first open-source GPT models (20b and 120b) on the Gradient AI Platform! These models offer flexibility for developers to create AI applications, from prototypes to production agents. Users can access them through the Serverless Inference API or the Gradient dashboard. With integrated billing and monitoring features, building AI apps is now simpler than ever. Get started today! 🔗 #OpenAI #GradientAI #AIDevelopment #TechNews #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD FidelityFX SDK 2.0 launches our neural rendering technologies for developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5018/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AMD has launched the FidelityFX SDK 2.0, introducing new machine learning-based rendering technologies for developers. This update simplifies integration of FidelityFX features, starting with AMD FSR 4 upscaling. It allows for automatic upgrades in supported games without needing separate updates. Developers will need to use specific DLLs for the new technologies, ensuring compatibility with the latest AMD hardware. #AMDFidelityFX #GamingTech #GameDevelopment #FSR4 #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD FidelityFX Super Resolution 4 now available on GPUOpen</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5022/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for gamers! AMD has launched FidelityFX Super Resolution 4 (FSR 4), now available on GPUOpen. This new machine learning-based upscaler significantly enhances image quality compared to FSR 3.1. FSR 4 utilizes AMD Instinct GPUs and RDNA 4 architecture for optimal performance. It improves temporal stability, detail preservation, and reduces ghosting on moving objects. Upgrade your gaming experience today! 🎮✨ #AMD #FSR4 #GamingTechnology #GameDev #Graphics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heroku AI Expands Model Offering with OpenAI’s gpt-oss-120b</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5054/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5054/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s new model, gpt-oss-120b, is now available on Heroku Managed Inference and Agents. This open-weight model allows for easy integration into existing applications through an OpenAI-compatible API. With its Mixture-of-Experts architecture, gpt-oss-120b is efficient and designed for a variety of text generation tasks. Early benchmarks show it performs competitively with other models. Explore the future of AI application development on Heroku! 🌟 #AI #OpenAI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we built AI face cropping for Images</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5130/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5130/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Developer Week 2024! We launched AI face cropping, a feature that automatically crops images around detected faces. This marks a significant step in our AI image manipulation capabilities. Our transition from a CPU-based prototype to a GPU-based implementation allows for better performance and scalability, addressing previous technical challenges. This feature is aimed at enhancing image handling for social media platforms and e-commerce sites, making it easier to create&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powering Long-Term Memory for Agents With LangGraph and MongoDB</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-6477/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 13:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-6477/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! The MongoDB Store for LangGraph is now available, enhancing AI agents with long-term memory. This integration allows agents to remember past interactions across sessions, leading to more intelligent systems that learn over time. It complements existing short-term memory capabilities, creating a robust solution for memory-enabled agents. Key features include cross-thread persistence, JSON structure for easy storage, and vector search for efficient retrieval. Explore the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reverse ETL with Lakebase: Activate your lakehouse data for operational analytics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5105/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:41:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5105/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of your lakehouse data with Reverse ETL using Lakebase! 🌊 This approach allows you to serve data to applications efficiently and at scale, eliminating the need for custom pipelines. It bridges the gap between analytics and operations, enhancing decision-making processes. Explore how to activate your data for seamless operational analytics! 📊🔄 #DataAnalytics #Lakehouse #ReverseETL #OperationalExcellence #Lakebase</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway MCP - Stateful, Serverful, Pay-per-use Infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-6360/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-6360/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! A new Railway MCP server has been introduced, enabling AI coding agents to deploy applications and manage infrastructure directly from code editors. This innovative approach aims to streamline the development process. With this tool, developers can enhance their productivity by integrating deployment and infrastructure management seamlessly. #RailwayMCP #AICoding #AppDevelopment #TechInnovation #InfrastructureManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GitLab documentation site gets a major design overhaul</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5064/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5064/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The GitLab documentation site has undergone a major redesign! Key updates include: 🌙 Dark mode for improved readability. 🎨 Enhanced brand alignment with GitLab&amp;rsquo;s marketing site. 👍 Simplified feedback options with thumbs up/down directly on pages. 📚 Redesigned navigation for easier access to over 2,300 pages. 🔧 Addressed technical debt for a more polished experience. These changes stem from a recent platform migration, enhancing overall performance. #GitLab #Documentation #UXDesign&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Nemotron Nano 2 Open Reasoning Model Tops Leaderboard and Delivers 6x Higher Throughput</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5043/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5043/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in AI! The NVIDIA Nemotron Nano 2 model has topped the leaderboard with impressive accuracy. This open reasoning model offers up to 6x higher throughput compared to its closest competitors, enhancing edge AI capabilities. Stay updated on advancements in technology! 🔍📈 #AI #NVIDIA #Innovation #EdgeComputing #Nemotron</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Real-Time Mode in Apache Spark™ Structured Streaming</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5107/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5107/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data engineers! Apache Spark™ Structured Streaming now features a Real-Time Mode that processes events in milliseconds. This upgrade enhances the ability to manage mission-critical data pipelines efficiently. Stay updated with the latest in streaming technology! #ApacheSpark #StructuredStreaming #RealTimeData #DataEngineering #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best performance and fastest memory with the new Amazon EC2 R8i and R8i-flex instances</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5167/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5167/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amazon has launched the new R8i and R8i-flex instances, optimized for memory and powered by Intel Xeon processors. These instances offer 15% better price performance, 20% higher performance, and 2.5 times more memory throughput than previous generations. Ideal for memory-intensive workloads like SQL databases and real-time analytics, R8i instances scale up to 96xlarge with impressive capabilities for various applications. Check it out! 💻🔍 #AmazonEC2 #CloudComputing #IntelXeon&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing langchain-gradient: Seamless LangChain Integration with DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5051/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5051/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! We&amp;rsquo;ve launched &lt;strong&gt;langchain-gradient&lt;/strong&gt;, an open-source integration connecting LangChain to the DigitalOcean Gradient AI Platform. This innovative package simplifies the development of AI applications with tools for chaining prompts and managing data. Key features include: - Seamless integration for quick deployment. - Access to multiple AI models with GPU-accelerated performance. - Full open-source compatibility. Use cases range from chatbots to automated workflows, enhancing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthening the core: Stack Overflow for Teams 2025.6</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5126/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5126/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are here with Stack Overflow for Teams 2025.6! This release focuses on back-end improvements enhancing stability, data integrity, and identity management. Key upgrades include better SAML and SCIM integrations for smoother onboarding. Email address changes now sync automatically for improved reporting accuracy. Look forward to upcoming features like nested comments for richer discussions and an ingestion engine to convert content from various platforms into reusable&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood Launches Pro and College Football Prediction Markets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5033/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5033/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Robinhood has launched pro and college football prediction markets in its app! Since the introduction of prediction markets last year, over 2 billion contracts have been traded. Now, users can trade outcomes for popular football games, including all regular season pro matchups and college Power 4 schools. These markets will be available for eligible customers soon, with contracts for the first two weeks of the season. Unlike traditional sports betting, these contracts allow customers to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents can now access protected deployments via Vercel’s MCP server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5084/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5084/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel has introduced two new tools in its MCP server. The &lt;strong&gt;get_access_to_vercel_url&lt;/strong&gt; feature allows agents to generate a temporary shareable URL, enabling access to Vercel Auth-protected deployments without login credentials. Additionally, the &lt;strong&gt;web_fetch_vercel_url&lt;/strong&gt; tool lets agents fetch content directly from protected deployments, even when access would normally be denied. Explore these features to streamline your development process! #Vercel&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Node.js Vercel Functions now support fetch web handlers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5086/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5086/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel Functions on the Node.js runtime now support fetch web handlers. This enhancement boosts interoperability across various JavaScript frameworks and runtimes. You can still choose to export individual HTTP methods if that suits your project better. For further details, check out the documentation! 📚 #NodeJS #Vercel #WebDevelopment #JavaScript #APIs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Digests by Robinhood Cortex for customers in the UK</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5036/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5036/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for UK investors! Robinhood has launched Digests powered by Robinhood Cortex, an AI-driven feature that explains stock movements in clear language. This tool reviews news, analyst reports, and proprietary data to help users make informed decisions. Available for free on stock detail pages, Digests aims to support investors of all experience levels. For more details, visit the Help Centre. #InvestSmart #StockMarket #AI #Robinhood #UKInvestors</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MONGIL: STAR DIVE brings monster collection and solo party play to PC, console, and mobile</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5073/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5073/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the gaming world! Netmarble Monster&amp;rsquo;s CEO, Ken Kim, recently shared insights about their new game, MONGIL: STAR DIVE. This cross-platform collectible action-adventure game is set to launch on PC, console, and mobile, developed using Unreal Engine 5. Stay tuned for more updates on this innovative gaming experience! 🎮✨ #MONGIL #StarDive #GamingNews #Netmarble #ActionAdventure</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Device Trust Check makes browser extension enforcement easier</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5135/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5135/</guid>
      <description>🔒 1Password has launched the new Device Trust Check to enhance security in managing browser extensions. This feature allows admins to ensure the 1Password browser extension remains installed and active on user devices. If the extension is missing, users receive prompts to restore it before access to the desktop app is denied. The integration between the Extended Device Compliance feature and EPM strengthens security enforcement continuously, closing gaps for potential compliance issues&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Latest NVIDIA Gaming AI and Neural Rendering Technologies</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5044/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5044/</guid>
      <description>🚀 NVIDIA has made significant announcements at Gamescom 2025, introducing updates to its RTX neural rendering and ACE generative AI technologies. These advancements aim to enhance gaming experiences with expanded integration for DLSS 4, new AI models, and cloud solutions like GeForce NOW inside Discord. 🎮 Upcoming titles, including Resident Evil Requiem and Borderlands 4, will feature these technologies, helping developers optimize graphics even for players with older hardware. For Unreal&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Next Edit Suggestions in JetBrains AI Assistant</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5067/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5067/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains AI Assistant has launched a new feature: next edit suggestions, now available in Beta for Java, Kotlin, and Python. These intelligent recommendations offer edit suggestions across your entire file, enhancing your coding experience. With integration into IDE-native actions, users can benefit from smart edits while maintaining workflow. The feature triggers as you type, providing instant suggestions highlighted in light purple. Global support ensures fast responses from regions like&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identify Speakers in Meetings, Calls, and Voice Apps in Real-Time with NVIDIA Streaming Sortformer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5045/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5045/</guid>
      <description>Introducing NVIDIA Streaming Sortformer, a breakthrough in real-time speaker identification for meetings, calls, and voice-enabled apps. 🎤 This production-grade diarization model offers low-latency performance, making it ideal for multi-speaker environments. Key features include frame-level diarization, precision timestamps, and efficient GPU inference. 🌐 Optimized for English and tested with Mandarin and other languages, it promises robust tracking with minimal latency. #NVIDIA #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform now supports assigning agent pools at the project level</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5113/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5113/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for HCP Terraform and Terraform Enterprise users! You can now assign default agent pools at the project level. This update simplifies the management of self-hosted agents, enhancing security and scalability. With this feature, project owners can easily set a default agent pool for future workspaces, promoting consistency across projects. Existing workspaces maintain their current settings, ensuring a smooth transition. Get started today and streamline your infrastructure&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Single GPU P5 instances, Advanced Go Driver, Amazon SageMaker HyperPod and more (August 18, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5168/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5168/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from AWS this week! The upcoming BeSA (Become a Solutions Architect) cohort starts on September 6, offering free mentoring to enhance cloud careers. Learn more on the BeSA website. New launches include: - &lt;strong&gt;Amazon EC2 Single GPU P5 instances&lt;/strong&gt; for cost-effective ML and HPC. - &lt;strong&gt;AWS Advanced Go Driver&lt;/strong&gt; for improved database performance. - Enhanced &lt;strong&gt;Cilium support&lt;/strong&gt; for Amazon EKS Hybrid Nodes. For AI enthusiasts, &lt;strong&gt;Amazon SageMaker HyperPod&lt;/strong&gt; now supports advanced features&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading the Future of IoT Mobility: Cisco Wins Frost &amp; Sullivan Award Two Years Running</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5287/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5287/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Cisco has been awarded Frost &amp;amp; Sullivan’s 2025 Global Company of the Year for Mobile IoT Platforms, marking a second consecutive win. This honor reflects the trust of customers and partners in Cisco&amp;rsquo;s innovative solutions for IoT mobility. The Cisco Mobility Services Platform serves as a comprehensive resource for enterprise mobility, supporting advanced technologies like 5G and NB-IoT. Thank you to our partners and customers for your collaboration and trust! Together, we are&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing the Cloudflare Browser Developer Program</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5131/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5131/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news from Cloudflare! They have launched the Browser Developer Program, aimed at enhancing collaboration between Cloudflare and browser development teams. This initiative focuses on improving security measures while ensuring a seamless user experience. Browser developers can join to share feedback, access best practices, and engage in discussions with Cloudflare engineers. The program also offers insights into updates that may affect browser interactions with Cloudflare Challenges&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Native support for SvelteKit&#39;s new OpenTelemetry spans</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5089/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5089/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has added native support for SvelteKit&amp;rsquo;s new server-side OpenTelemetry spans. To begin, users can activate experimental tracing in SvelteKit and set up a tracing instrumentation file with the Vercel OpenTelemetry collector. Generated traces will now include built-in SvelteKit spans, and other collectors can also be configured. For further details, check the SvelteKit observability documentation. 📊 #SvelteKit #OpenTelemetry #Vercel #WebDevelopment #Observability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Sandbox increases concurrency and port limits</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5088/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5088/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has enhanced its Sandbox capabilities for Pro and Enterprise teams! Now, users can run up to 2,000 Sandboxes concurrently, a significant increase from the previous limit of 150. Each Sandbox can also expose up to 4 ports for external access. This improvement allows for better handling of traffic spikes, untrusted code execution, and more complex applications. For projects needing even higher limits, contacting the sales team is an option. Learn more in the Vercel Sandbox docs! 📊🔧&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>URL context tool for Gemini API now generally available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5173/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5173/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Gemini API&amp;rsquo;s URL Context tool is now generally available for developers! This tool allows users to enhance prompts using web content, making applications more contextually aware. Key features include support for PDFs and images, expanding the types of content that can be grounded. The tool is now ready for scaled production use, with updated limits based on the specific Gemini model. #GeminiAPI #AI #TechUpdate #Developers #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s new in Git 2.51.0?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5065/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5065/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Git has released version 2.51, with key updates aimed at improving performance and user experience. 🔧 Notable changes include enhanced git-push(1) and git-fetch(1) commands, which now use batched updates for reference synchronization, resulting in up to 22x speed improvements. 📦 The release also introduces the &amp;ldquo;reftable&amp;rdquo; format as the default reference backend, addressing limitations of the previous &amp;ldquo;files&amp;rdquo; backend. 🔑 Additionally, SHA-256 is now the default hash function, enhancing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celebrating 10 years of Amazon Aurora innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5170/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5170/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Celebrating 10 years of Amazon Aurora! Join us for a livestream event on August 21, 2025, marking a decade of innovation in database technology. Amazon Aurora revolutionized the industry with its unique architecture, offering high performance and 99.99% availability at a fraction of the cost. Key milestones include the launch in 2015, the introduction of serverless capabilities in 2018, and ongoing enhancements focused on security, scalability, and cost management. #AmazonAurora&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleash the Power of Storage Networking for Mainframe Environments with Cisco MDS 9000 Series</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5290/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5290/</guid>
      <description>🌐 As enterprises increasingly rely on mainframes, efficient storage networking solutions become crucial. The Cisco MDS 9000 Series, now z17 qualified, enhances FICON support and is designed for modern mainframe environments. This series promises exceptional reliability and performance, handling today&amp;rsquo;s growing data demands. 📊 With mainframes like IBM&amp;rsquo;s z17 at the forefront of AI integration, the need for robust SANs is more important than ever. #StorageNetworking #CiscoMDS9000 #Mainframe&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved fake hardware detection with Vercel BotID</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5091/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5091/</guid>
      <description>Vercel has enhanced its BotID Deep Analysis with an updated detection model. This improvement expands fingerprinting coverage for headless browsers and simulated device hardware, allowing for better identification of advanced bots. The upgraded model works in real-time without disrupting genuine users. Current users can benefit from these updates immediately by upgrading to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:botid@1.5.2&#34;&gt;botid@1.5.2&lt;/a&gt;. 🔍🤖🚀 #BotID #CyberSecurity #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking about trying or upgrading to Datalore Cloud? This August, you can save 30%.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5071/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5071/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Thinking about Datalore Cloud? This August, new users and trial teams can save 30% on their first payment! This offer is valid until August 31, 2025. Datalore provides tools for efficient data exploration and collaboration. Key features include smart code assistance, no-code automations, and interactive dashboards. Ready to upgrade? Visit the upgrade page and use code: DATALORE_CLOUD_25. #Datalore #DataScience #CloudComputing #Discount #UpgradeNow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Imagen 4 Fast and the general availability of the Imagen 4 family in the Gemini API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5174/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5174/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Google! Imagen 4, the advanced text-to-image model, is now generally available in the Gemini API and Google AI Studio. This update brings substantial improvements in text rendering, enhancing image generation quality. Introducing Imagen 4 Fast, designed for speed and efficiency, alongside Imagen 4 and Imagen 4 Ultra, which now support up to 2K resolution for detailed visuals. Explore the capabilities of the Imagen 4 family for your creative needs! 🎨✨ #GoogleAI #Imagen4&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI fields now available in ECS allowing parity and compatibility with OTel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5060/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5060/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Elastic! The Elastic Common Schema (ECS) now supports generative AI (GenAI) fields, enhancing compatibility with OpenTelemetry (OTel). This allows for better normalization of data from diverse GenAI vendors. Key use cases include observability, security, and log normalization for GenAI applications. Users can seamlessly integrate ECS and OTel for improved monitoring. Stay informed and explore how these advancements can benefit your workflows! #Elastic #GenerativeAI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming IT Help Desk: How Elastic’s Search AI Platform supercharges Salesforce Service Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5061/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5061/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Transforming IT support with Elastic&amp;rsquo;s Search AI Platform in Salesforce Service Cloud is a game-changer. The platform enhances internal IT operations by providing real-time, accurate assistance. It allows users to choose between instant AI support or traditional ticket submissions for complex issues. This dual approach improves ticket quality and accelerates resolution times. By integrating with tools like JIRA and Google Docs, it ensures responses are grounded in enterprise-specific&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Desktop 4.44: Smarter AI Modeling, Platform Stability, and Streamlined Kubernetes Workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5121/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 20:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5121/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker Desktop 4.44 introduces key updates for developers. The new Docker Model Runner allows users to inspect AI inference requests and responses directly, enhancing transparency and debugging. This feature aids in troubleshooting workflows, especially for AI/LLM applications. Real-time resource checks are now available to prevent system slowdowns when running multiple models. Additionally, Goose and Gemini CLI are supported as MCP clients, streamlining connections to over 140 MCP servers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Livestream: Building Cross-Framework Agent Ecosystems</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5047/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5047/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join us for an insightful livestream on August 21! Discover how the NVIDIA NeMo Agent Toolkit enhances multi-agent workflows through deep MCP integration. 📅 Time: 18:00 - 19:00 (CEST) 📍 Learn about building optimized agentic systems with NVIDIA NIM. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to expand your knowledge! #NVIDIA #Livestream #NeMoAgent #TechInnovation #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure and Modernize your Roadways with Cisco</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5291/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:19:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5291/</guid>
      <description>🚦 Modernizing roadways is essential for enhancing safety and efficiency. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s networking solutions are at the forefront of Intelligent Transportation Systems (ITS), enabling real-time data and connectivity. Join us at ITS World Congress 2025 in Atlanta (Aug 24-28) at Booth #1741 to explore our innovations in traffic management and public safety. Discover how our secure solutions can improve communication through digital signage and support a connected roadway network. #Cisco #ITS2025&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing SQL Stored Procedures in Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5109/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 15:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5109/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Databricks is enhancing its platform with SQL Stored Procedures! These procedures aim to simplify repetitive SQL tasks such as data cleaning and updating business rules. This feature will streamline workflows, making it easier for teams to manage their data. Explore how this advancement can benefit your operations! #Databricks #SQLStoredProcedures #DataManagement #TechUpdates #DataAnalytics</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build smarter AI agents: new tools now available for the DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4995/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 14:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4995/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are here for the Gradient AI Platform! The new tools enable faster and easier AI app development. Key features include: - &lt;strong&gt;Unified Gradient AI Python SDK:&lt;/strong&gt; Access all major services in one place. - &lt;strong&gt;Log Stream Insights:&lt;/strong&gt; Real-time analysis improves agent performance. - &lt;strong&gt;Dropbox Data Connector:&lt;/strong&gt; Ingest knowledge directly from Dropbox. These enhancements support building production-ready AI applications efficiently. #AI #GradientAI #PythonSDK #TechUpdates #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing GPU Droplets accelerated by NVIDIA HGX H200</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4996/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4996/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI developers! DigitalOcean has launched NVIDIA HGX H200 GPU Droplets, offering up to 2x faster inference speeds and double the memory capacity compared to the H100. These droplets are designed for simplicity and scalability, priced at just $3.44/GPU/hr. With 141 GB of memory and HBM3e technology, they enhance performance for demanding tasks in AI and HPC. All droplets are HIPAA-eligible and SOC 2 compliant, ensuring security. Start accelerating your AI projects today!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Quarter, New Qodana 2025.2 Release Highlights</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5072/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5072/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in the Qodana 2025.2 release! The latest features include a new Insights dashboard, expanded Native mode support for Go and Python linters, and enhanced SSO functionality. The redesigned Taint Trace Explorer improves security analysis, making navigation easier and providing clearer descriptions for each trace step. Explore these advancements that enhance code quality and security! #Qodana #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment #SecurityAnalysis #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeamCity 2025.07.1 Is Here</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4999/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4999/</guid>
      <description>🚀 TeamCity On-Premises 2025.07.1 is now available! This update addresses several issues, including authentication errors and display problems on the Project Overview page. It also brings performance and security enhancements. For seamless upgrades, you can use the automatic update feature or download directly from the JetBrains website. Stay updated for optimal performance and security! #TeamCity #SoftwareUpdate #DevOps #JetBrains #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next-Level Performance Improvements in ReSharper 2025.2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5000/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5000/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in ReSharper 2025.2! This release enhances performance with features like out-of-process support, improving solution startup speed and refactoring capabilities. Razor and Blazor handling has also been optimized, ensuring quicker responsiveness for developers. Check out the new Rename refactoring improvements for better progress reporting and reduced memory usage. #ReSharper #SoftwareDevelopment #PerformanceImprovements #VisualStudio #CodingEfficiency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper and the .NET Tools 2025.2 Are Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5001/</guid>
      <description>🚀 ReSharper and .NET tools 2025.2 are now available for download! This release features the public preview of ReSharper’s Out-of-Process mode, enhancing stability and performance. It supports the latest C# 14 and C++26 features, alongside numerous performance improvements. Key updates include faster refactoring, optimized Razor processing, and better logging with ILogger. Explore the new features and download the release candidate today! #ReSharper #DotNet #CSharp #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rider 2025.2 Is Here with Junie, In-IDE OpenTelemetry, Game Dev Upgrades, and More</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5002/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5002/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Rider 2025.2 has launched, enhancing development tools with new features. Meet Junie, the AI coding agent, now faster and more capable, offering high-level brainstorming and hands-on coding support. It also integrates with GitHub for efficient pull request management. The updated Monitoring tool window simplifies performance optimization, while the new OpenTelemetry plugin provides runtime metrics directly in your IDE. Explore the improvements and elevate your coding experience! 💻✨&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Databricks Assistant Edit Mode: The Fastest Way to Transform Your Notebooks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5110/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 08:05:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5110/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Databricks! They have launched the Assistant Edit Mode, which allows users to make AI-driven edits across notebooks with just one prompt. This feature aims to enhance efficiency and consistency in data processing. This innovation is designed to streamline workflows and improve productivity for users. #Databricks #AI #DataScience #Productivity #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing system resilience with Krkn chaos dashboard</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4993/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 07:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4993/</guid>
      <description>🔧 In today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape, system resilience is crucial for businesses. The Krkn chaos dashboard is an open-source tool designed to enhance Kubernetes environments by simulating failures to identify vulnerabilities. 📊 The dashboard allows teams to easily design and monitor chaos experiments, providing real-time updates on system health and generating detailed reports on failures. 💻 With user-friendly features, it encourages regular chaos testing, helping teams improve their system&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A look at our roadmap: shipping for resiliency, security, and performance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5652/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5652/</guid>
      <description>🚀 We&amp;rsquo;re committed to enhancing Webflow&amp;rsquo;s platform for our users. Following a recent incident, we&amp;rsquo;ve taken steps to improve resiliency, security, and performance. Key investments are underway to strengthen our systems and ensure reliability. 🌐 Our hosting now leverages Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s global network, enhancing speed and protection against threats. 🔧 Additionally, we&amp;rsquo;re re-architecting our CMS to better meet the growing needs of our users. Stay tuned for more updates! #Webflow #TechUpdates #CMS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Twilio Support for Meta’s WhatsApp Marketing Messages Lite API on Private Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5144/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5144/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for businesses! Twilio now supports Meta’s WhatsApp Marketing Messages Lite API, enhancing the delivery of high-volume marketing campaigns. 📈 The MM Lite API is designed to improve message deliverability and reduce errors, all managed through the Twilio platform. Key features include optimized delivery, TTL control, and ROI tracking. 🔗 With Twilio, businesses gain a reliable communication platform that simplifies the management of multiple channels while ensuring compliance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic joins AWS Zero Trust Accelerator for Government (ZTAG) program</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4998/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4998/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Elastic has joined the AWS Zero Trust Accelerator for Government (ZTAG) program. This partnership aims to enhance the security of US federal agencies by integrating Elastic’s data-centric approach with AWS’s Zero Trust framework. 🔐 The collaboration focuses on improving security information and event management (SIEM) tailored for the government&amp;rsquo;s Zero Trust architecture. This is crucial as cyber threats continue to evolve. 📈 Together, they aim to support federal agencies in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Next-Gen Identity Security Unifies Protection Across All Identities and Domains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7441/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7441/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in identity security! CrowdStrike has launched Falcon Next-Gen Identity Security, a comprehensive solution designed to protect all identities—human, non-human, and AI—across various environments. This new platform unifies critical capabilities, including initial access prevention, privileged access security, and identity threat detection. It addresses the evolving landscape of identity threats as organizations increasingly adopt SaaS applications and AI agents. With Falcon,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Gemma 3 270M: The compact model for hyper-efficient AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5175/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5175/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Google has unveiled the Gemma 3 270M, a compact AI model with 270 million parameters designed for efficiency and task-specific fine-tuning. This model excels in instruction-following and text structuring, making it ideal for on-device and research use. It sets a new performance standard for its size, enhancing accessibility to sophisticated AI capabilities. Explore the future of AI with Gemma! 🌟 #Gemma3 #AI #MachineLearning #Innovation #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling LLM Reinforcement Learning with Prolonged Training Using ProRL v2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4893/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 21:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4893/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in AI with NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s ProRL v2! This new framework explores whether large language models (LLMs) can enhance their capabilities through extended reinforcement learning (RL). ProRL v2 incorporates advanced algorithms and rigorous training methods across multiple domains. Key features include over 3,000 RL steps, stability improvements, and fully verifiable rewards. These innovations aim to help models discover new solutions rather than just refining existing ones. #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet our newest AWS Heroes — August 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4965/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4965/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! We proudly introduce the latest cohort of AWS Heroes for August 2025. These individuals are recognized for their outstanding contributions to the AWS community. 🌍 From AI and machine learning to serverless architectures, they bring diverse expertise and a strong commitment to knowledge sharing. Join us in welcoming Kristine Armiyants, Nadia Reyhani, and Raphael Manke, who are shaping the future of cloud computing and inspiring the next generation! 💡 #AWSHeroes #CloudComputing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamlining Quantum Error Correction and Application Development with CUDA-QX 0.4</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4894/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4894/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Quantum computing is advancing with the latest release of CUDA-QX 0.4, focusing on quantum error correction (QEC). This update streamlines QEC experiments, enabling researchers to define and simulate codes, configure decoders, and deploy them effectively. Key features include a comprehensive API for user-defined components and the introduction of a detector error model (DEM) for improved circuit simulations. 🔗 Check out the full release notes on GitHub for ongoing development and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamo 0.4 Delivers 4x Faster Performance, SLO-Based Autoscaling, and Real-Time Observability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4895/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4895/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in AI! Dynamo 0.4 has been released, offering 4x faster performance and SLO-based autoscaling. This update is designed for deploying new open-source models like OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s gpt-oss and Moonshot AI&amp;rsquo;s Kimi K2 efficiently. Key features include enhanced real-time observability and resiliency, making it easier to monitor performance and manage requests. #AI #OpenSource #Dynamo #Innovation #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simpler, More Transparent Model for AI Quotas</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4905/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4905/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting changes coming to JetBrains AI! Starting August 18, 2025, a new AI quota model will simplify subscriptions. Users can seamlessly extend usage beyond their quota with clear, real currency pricing. This update aims for transparency and better management of AI resources. Each subscription tier will align with its price, providing equivalent AI Credits. Additional credits can be purchased as needed. Stay tuned for more updates! #JetBrains #AI #TechUpdates #SubscriptionModel #Transparency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightning-Fast Python: Mastering the uv Package Manager</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4906/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4906/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover the future of Python development with uv, a new package manager that is 10-100x faster than pip! Join our livestream recap from August 7, featuring experts Michael Kennedy and William Vincent. They discussed uv&amp;rsquo;s advanced features and practical migration strategies. Learn why Python developers are making the switch to this efficient tool! 🔧🐍 #Python #PackageManager #uv #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTalks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Runtime Cache API</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4938/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4938/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel has launched the Runtime Cache API, allowing you to store and retrieve data seamlessly across Functions, Routing Middleware, and Builds within the same region. This ephemeral cache offers tag-based invalidation for better cache management. You can monitor performance metrics like hit rates and storage usage in the Observability dashboard. Keep in mind, reads and writes are billed regionally based on your runtime area. Learn more in the documentation! 📊&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kodee’s Kotlin Roundup: 2.2.20-Beta2, Kotlin LSP Update, Shipaton 2025, and a New Face on the Foundation Board</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4908/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 09:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4908/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting updates from Kotlin-land! Kotlin 2.2.20-Beta2 has launched, featuring enhancements in Multiplatform, including Swift export as default and new web development targets. Kotlin ranks 15th in the 2025 Stack Overflow Developer Survey, showing steady growth in popularity. The Kotlin Language Server Protocol is also improved, enhancing core functionality. Stay tuned for more updates! 🚀📈 #Kotlin #Programming #DevCommunity #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New features in Bunsen</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4886/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 07:01:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4886/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Bunsen has rolled out new features to enhance user experience! The updated web interface now includes a simplified project chooser, making it easier to select projects and modify search criteria. A cookie support feature allows users to save search settings for future use, streamlining the process. 🍪 Additionally, the testrun overview section is customizable, letting users sort results by various columns. The new &amp;ldquo;filter by testcase&amp;rdquo; feature helps identify regressions in test results more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic wins 2025 Google Cloud DORA Award for Architecting for the Future with AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4897/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4897/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Elastic has won the 2025 Google Cloud DORA Award for Architecting for the Future with AI. This recognition highlights our commitment to enhancing software delivery and operational performance using DORA principles. By adopting a data-driven approach, we&amp;rsquo;ve improved the velocity and reliability of our services for customers. AI is transforming software development, with 76% of technologists relying on it daily. Our focus remains on innovation and smart operations in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini CLI &#43; VS Code: Native diffing and context-aware workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4967/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4967/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The latest update to Gemini CLI enhances its integration with VS Code. This update offers context-aware suggestions by accessing your workspace and selected text. This means targeted help right when you need it. Additionally, you can now use native in-editor diffing. Review and modify proposed changes directly in a full-screen diff view for better control over your code. 🔧 Ready to enhance your workflow? Check your Gemini CLI version and get started! #GeminiCLI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Register now for the Mega Stack-O-Jam game jam</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4913/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4913/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Join the Mega Stack-O-Jam starting August 14! This week-long game jam invites participants to explore level design using the new Stack-O-Bot sample. Learn from industry professionals and compete for exciting prizes. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this chance to showcase your creativity! #GameJam #LevelDesign #StackOBot #CreativityUnleashed #GameDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updated Stack-O-Bot for Unreal Engine 5.6—available now</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4914/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4914/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for game developers! The updated Stack-O-Bot sample game is now available for Unreal Engine 5.6. This version includes numerous new features to enhance your experience. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re new to UE or seeking a strong base for your project, Stack-O-Bot offers valuable resources to boost your game development skills. #UnrealEngine #GameDevelopment #StackOBot #GameDesign #UE5</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Terraform embraces Arm: More choice, greater flexibility</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4955/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4955/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Terraform has expanded support for Arm architecture, giving customers more options for their IT investments. With the rise of Arm&amp;rsquo;s popularity for its cost savings and performance benefits, Terraform now allows running Terraform Enterprise and HCP Terraform agents on Arm-based platforms like AWS Graviton. This change enables customers to optimize their setups for both performance and cost. One user shared that they moved to 100% Graviton CPUs, enhancing efficiency in their operations. Learn&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judging with Confidence: Meet PGRM, the Promptable Reward Model</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4952/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4952/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the Prompt-Guided Reward Model (PGRM) from Databricks! This innovative tool enhances AI monitoring and evaluation, offering a flexible solution for businesses. PGRM adapts to new rules, flags uncertain cases, and provides confidence-backed scores for AI decisions. 📊✨ It combines the strengths of LLM judges and reward models, achieving high accuracy in judgment quality while facilitating scalable oversight. With PGRM, companies can ensure safety, accuracy, and alignment with brand&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataSpell Is Now an AI-First Tool for Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4909/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4909/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DataSpell 2025.2 is now an AI-first tool for data analysis! This release includes JetBrains AI Pro for free with every paid subscription, enhancing your data workflow. Users can access advanced AI tools and the latest models, including GPT-5. Key features include easier project creation and dedicated AI agents for tasks like managing files and connecting to databases. Explore these updates today! #DataAnalysis #JetBrains #AI #DataScience #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free JetBrains Student Pack – Your Toolkit for a Future in Tech</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4911/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4911/</guid>
      <description>Unlock your potential in tech with the JetBrains Student Pack! 🌟 This all-in-one toolkit provides professional-grade IDEs, programming courses, and AI tools, helping you build real-world projects and prepare for your career. Join over 3 million students using JetBrains tools trusted by top companies like Google and NASA. Apply by September 12, 2025, for a chance to win a MacBook Pro or iPad Pro! 🎉 #JetBrains #StudentPack #TechTools #FutureInTech #CodingEducation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Art and Science of Sizing Search Nodes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-6481/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-6481/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of your search deployment with optimal sizing! 🖥️ Understanding key factors like data and index size, data ingestion, and query performance is essential. With the introduction of storage-optimized search nodes, you can now scale efficiently without overprovisioning resources. These nodes cater to large indexes while keeping costs down, making them ideal for moderate query loads. Explore more about effective search deployment strategies! 📈💡 #MongoDB #SearchOptimization&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auto-recharge available in AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4940/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4940/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Great news for Vercel users! The AI Gateway now offers an auto-recharge feature. This allows for automatic credit top-ups, ensuring your apps run smoothly without interruptions. You can easily enable or adjust this feature in the AI Gateway dashboard. Set your preferred top-up amount, trigger balance, and even a monthly spend limit to manage your credits efficiently. Learn more about this update! #Vercel #AIGateway #AutoRecharge #WebDevelopment #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Sonnet 4 now supports 1M token context in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4941/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4941/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Claude Sonnet 4 now offers a 1 million-token context window through Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway. This enhancement allows for larger inputs, such as extensive codebases and document sets. With a unified API, users can easily manage performance optimizations and track usage. The AI Gateway also supports built-in observability and intelligent provider routing for reliability. For implementation, simply install the AI SDK v5 and set up the model. #AI #Vercel #ClaudeSonnet4&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cutting delivery times in half with v0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4939/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4939/</guid>
      <description>Ready.net is enhancing utility company operations with its new feature, v0. This platform streamlines the process for managing financing and compliance with state-level stakeholders. Faced with urgent and often unclear requirements, Ready.net needed a solution to accelerate ideation, validation, and delivery. v0 is designed to cut delivery times significantly, supporting three teams with limited design resources. Learn more about this innovative approach! 🚀⚡️ #UtilityManagement #Innovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>uReview: Scalable, Trustworthy GenAI for Code Review at Uber</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4963/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4963/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Uber has introduced uReview, a GenAI-powered tool designed to enhance code review efficiency. This innovative solution automates the review process, helping developers save thousands of hours while maintaining high-quality standards. uReview aims to improve trust in code reviews without compromising on quality for every commit. #CodeReview #GenAI #UberTech #DeveloperTools #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel BotID now leverages Vercel&#39;s verified bot directory</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4942/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4942/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! With the release of BotID 1.5.0, you can now access Vercel&amp;rsquo;s verified bot directory for deeper insights. This update enhances real-time detection of verified bots, allowing for secure programmatic decisions. The Deep Analysis mode provides key information like source IP range and user-agent validation, helping teams manage bot interactions effectively. Discover how BotID can improve your workflow! #BotID #Vercel #WebDevelopment #TechUpdates #Bots 🤖</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel&#39;s bot verification now supports Web Bot Auth</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4943/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4943/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has enhanced its bot verification system by supporting Web Bot Auth, developed through collaboration with industry partners. This new protocol uses HTTP Message Signatures for verifying traffic from various automated sources. It helps maintain a curated directory of verified bots, ensuring legitimate ones access your site while blocking spoofed bots. Web Bot Auth uses public-key cryptography to authenticate bots, including popular tools like SEO crawlers and AI bots. Notably,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains with its CLion IDE Is Now an Official ST Authorized Partner</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4912/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 09:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4912/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! JetBrains has officially joined the ST Partner Program, enhancing the CLion IDE for embedded developers. This collaboration focuses on optimizing development for STM32 and STM8 microcontrollers. Developers can expect seamless integration with ST toolchains, boosting productivity. STMicroelectronics is known for its semiconductor technologies, powering a variety of devices. Together, they aim to improve the development experience for embedded systems. Stay tuned for updates on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 Product Updates (July 2025): New Security Features, Global Regions, and Developer Previews</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4946/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4946/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Auth0 this July! We&amp;rsquo;re introducing enhanced security features like PII masking in logs, which helps protect sensitive data. Improvements in bot detection will ensure smoother experiences for genuine users. Additionally, new global cloud regions are now available, including Mexico 🇲🇽 and Hong Kong 🇭🇰, expanding our reach. Stay tuned for more features aimed at empowering developers! #Auth0 #Security #DeveloperUpdates #CloudExpansion #IdentityManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Named the Only Leader in GigaOm Radar for SaaS Security Posture Management</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7442/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7442/</guid>
      <description>🌟 CrowdStrike has been named the sole Leader in the 2025 GigaOm Radar Report for SaaS Security Posture Management (SSPM). The report highlights CrowdStrike as the most innovative platform in the field, excelling in protecting identities and SaaS environments. With the rise of SaaS applications, the need for robust security has never been greater. CrowdStrike’s Falcon® platform addresses challenges like identity-based threats and misconfigurations, offering real-time threat detection and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 8.17.10 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4898/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4898/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Elastic Stack 8.17.10 has officially been released! This new version comes with important updates and fixes compared to 8.17.9. Users are encouraged to upgrade to enhance their experience. For a complete list of changes and resolved issues, check out the release notes. #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews #VersionRelease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 8.18.5 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4899/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4899/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Elastic Stack users! Version 8.18.5 has been officially released today. Users are encouraged to upgrade from version 8.18.4 to benefit from the latest improvements. For a comprehensive list of issues fixed and changes made, check the release notes. #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews #Upgrade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 8.19.2 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4901/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4901/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Elastic Stack 8.19.2 has been released today. The new version offers improvements over 8.19.1, and users are encouraged to upgrade. For a detailed overview of fixed issues and changes, check the release notes. Stay updated! #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews #Upgrade #VersionRelease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 9.0.5 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4900/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4900/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Elastic Stack has officially launched version 9.0.5! This update is recommended over version 9.0.4 for improved performance and fixes. For a complete list of changes and resolved issues, check out the release notes. Stay updated and enhance your experience! 🔧📊 #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 9.1.2 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4902/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4902/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Elastic Stack version 9.1.2 has been officially released! This update brings several important fixes and improvements over version 9.1.1. For a complete list of changes and resolved issues, please check the release notes. Upgrade today to enhance your experience! #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews #VersionRelease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Jules’ sharpest critic and most valuable ally</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4968/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4968/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Jules&amp;rsquo; new critic functionality! 🛠️ This feature enhances AI-generated code by acting as a peer reviewer during the generation process. With &amp;ldquo;critic-augmented generation,&amp;rdquo; every code change undergoes adversarial review, aiming for higher quality output. It flags potential issues like subtle bugs and logic errors before you see the code. This integration helps ensure better code quality while you focus on other tasks. #AICoding #CodeQuality #Innovation #TechNews #GoogleLabs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now available on Pax8 Marketplace: 1Password Enterprise Password Manager - MSP Edition</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4961/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4961/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Managed Service Providers! 1Password Enterprise Password Manager - MSP Edition is now available on Pax8 Marketplace. This tool helps MSPs enhance client security, streamline operations, and boost profitability through a user-friendly interface and advanced features. Key benefits include: 🔒 End-to-end encryption for client data 📈 Customized security policies for each client 💼 Centralized management for operational efficiency Start your 14-day free trial today! #1Password&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aligning our prices and packaging with the problems we help customers solve</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4959/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 23:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4959/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Cloudflare is introducing Externa and Interna, two new packages designed to simplify how you connect and protect your infrastructure. These use-case bundles address the need for straightforward solutions and pricing, responding to customer feedback for simplicity. Externa focuses on connecting and protecting public-facing systems, while Interna secures internal resources. These packages aim to reduce complexity and enhance security. #Cloudflare #Cybersecurity #TechSolutions #Simplicity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Tableau Cloud Custom Domains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-7208/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 19:12:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-7208/</guid>
      <description>📊 Exciting news for Tableau Cloud users! Tableau has introduced Custom Domains, allowing site admins to set up a brand-specific subdomain, like analytics.example.com. This feature simplifies access to published content and enhances brand identity. 🔒 Key benefits include improved security and seamless embedding of analytics, even in browsers that block third-party cookies. To get started, admins can configure Custom Domains in site settings at no extra cost. #Tableau #BusinessIntelligence&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: OpenAI models, Automated Reasoning checks, Amazon EVS, and more (August 11, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4856/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:05:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4856/</guid>
      <description>🌍 AWS Summits in Mexico City and Jakarta brought together the community for learning and networking. 🚀 Key highlights include the availability of OpenAI models on AWS, which excel in coding and analysis. 🛠️ The new Amazon Elastic VMware Service allows running VMware environments in Amazon VPC. 🔍 Automated Reasoning checks are now available to validate content accuracy from AI models. 📈 Additional updates include expanded Amazon SQS message sizes and AWS Lambda support for GitHub Actions. #AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Renewing Chat on Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4853/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4853/</guid>
      <description>🔄 Stack Overflow is focusing on enhancing its chat features to foster better conversations among developers. 💬 The goal is to create a more collaborative environment where users can engage in meaningful discussions. 👥 These improvements aim to make the platform a valuable space for sharing knowledge and support. #StackOverflow #DeveloperCommunity #Collaboration #TechTalk #ChatImprovements</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing General Availability for NVIDIA Isaac Sim 5.0 and NVIDIA Isaac Lab 2.2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-302/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-302/</guid>
      <description>🚀 NVIDIA has announced the general availability of NVIDIA Isaac Sim 5.0 and NVIDIA Isaac Lab 2.2 at SIGGRAPH 2025. These frameworks are now accessible on GitHub, providing developers with tools for building, training, and testing AI-powered robots in physics-based simulations. Explore the cutting-edge capabilities that these releases bring to robotics development. #NVIDIA #IsaacSim #Robotics #AI #SIGGRAPH2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developers Build Fast and Reliable Robot Simulations with NVIDIA Omniverse Libraries</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4832/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4832/</guid>
      <description>NVIDIA recently unveiled updates to the Omniverse libraries and Cosmos world foundation models at SIGGRAPH. 🌐 These enhancements, driven by OpenUSD, provide developers with new tools and models to create accurate virtual environments. They focus on building AI agents and simulations that can interact effectively with the real world. 🤖 This advancement aims to improve the reliability and speed of robotic simulations. #NVIDIA #Omniverse #Robotics #AI #SIGGRAPH</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximize Robotics Performance by Post-Training NVIDIA Cosmos Reason</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4833/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4833/</guid>
      <description>Introducing NVIDIA Cosmos Reason, unveiled at GTC 2025! 🤖 This innovative reasoning vision language model (VLM) is designed for physical AI and robotics. It allows robots and vision AI agents to utilize prior knowledge, physics, and common sense to interpret and interact with the real world. By processing video and text prompts, Cosmos Reason transforms visual information into actionable insights. #NVIDIA #Robotics #AI #Innovation #GTC2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Add context when using Instant Rollback</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4944/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4944/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New feature alert! You can now add context when performing an Instant Rollback. This allows you to include a reason visible to your team in the project overview. You can even incorporate links or notes for clarity. Plus, updates can be made at any time! Learn more about enhancing your rollback process. #InstantRollback #ProjectManagement #TeamCollaboration #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>v0.dev -&gt; v0.app</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4838/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4838/</guid>
      <description>Transform your ideas into deployed apps with ease using v0.app! 🚀 With just one prompt, v0 streamlines the process by providing UI, content, backend, and logic. It also offers support for research, debugging, and planning. From product managers to recruiters, v0 is revolutionizing team operations. #AppDevelopment #TechInnovation #Teamwork #Productivity #v0app</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating creativity with Elasticsearch vector database and the Dell AI Data Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4836/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4836/</guid>
      <description>Unlock creativity in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced industries! 🚀 The collaboration between Dell and NVIDIA is enhancing the Dell AI Data Platform with Elasticsearch, streamlining access to unstructured data for teams in media, gaming, and design. This partnership enables natural language searches, global collaboration, and AI-generated insights, ensuring efficient workflows and quick decision-making. Discover how this innovative platform can transform your creative processes! 💡🌍 #AI #Elasticsearch #Dell&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Neki</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-6038/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-6038/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the database world! Today, the team behind Vitess announced Neki, a new sharded Postgres solution. Neki aims to bring the power of explicit sharding to Postgres users, leveraging insights from extensive experience with Vitess. This initiative is not a fork of Vitess but a fresh architecture designed to handle demanding workloads effectively. Stay updated on Neki&amp;rsquo;s development by signing up at neki.dev! #Neki #Postgres #Databases #OpenSource #Vitess</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with GitLab Duo Agentic Chat in the web UI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4837/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4837/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab has introduced the Duo Agentic Chat feature, enhancing user interaction with the GitLab API directly from the web UI. This tool allows users to manage issues, track statuses, and take actions based on conversations. Access is available for Duo Pro or Enterprise users, streamlining workflows across projects. To start, navigate to your Group or Project, open the chat panel, and toggle to Agentic mode. Explore how Agentic Chat can simplify your development tasks! #GitLab #DuoAgenticChat&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cursor now supported on Vercel MCP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-09-4791/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-09-4791/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Great news for developers! Cursor is now compatible with Vercel&amp;rsquo;s Model Context Protocol (MCP). With this integration, you can easily explore projects, inspect deployments, and fetch logs directly from Cursor. 🔍 To get started, simply follow the one-click setup or update your .cursor/mcp.json file. A Vercel account login will be required. Learn more about using Cursor with Vercel MCP! #Vercel #Cursor #DevTools #MCP #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Developer’s Guide to INBOUND25</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4757/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:43:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4757/</guid>
      <description>🚀 INBOUND 2025 is just around the corner, taking place in San Francisco from September 3rd-5th! This year&amp;rsquo;s event will focus on how HubSpot is evolving, bringing developers and builders closer together. AI will be a key topic, promising fresh insights and innovations. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss Partner Day on September 2nd for app and solutions partners, featuring valuable sessions and networking opportunities. #INBOUND25 #HubSpot #DeveloperCommunity #TechInnovation #Networking 🌟</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KotlinX RPC 0.9.1 Is Now Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4725/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4725/</guid>
      <description>🚀 KotlinX RPC 0.9.1 has been released with key improvements for stability and user experience. The library now decouples from KotlinX Serialization, allowing for more flexible gRPC setups. Resource management has been simplified, reducing potential errors in implementation. Strict mode is now the default, ensuring better API correctness. Ready to dive in? Start your project at start.ktor.io and explore samples on GitHub! #KotlinXRPC #Kotlin #Programming #SoftwareDevelopment #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk upgrade deprecated Node.js versions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4733/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4733/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Upgrade your Node.js projects easily! Team owners can now update all projects using Node.js 18 or earlier to Node.js 22 with just one click in the Vercel Dashboard. Remember, if your project specifies a version in package.json, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to update it manually. Existing deployments remain unaffected. Check out your deprecated Node.js projects today! #Nodejs #Vercel #TechUpdate #WebDevelopment #SoftwareEngineering</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Zapier scales product partnerships with v0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4730/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4730/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Zapier is enhancing product partnerships with its v0 tool, streamlining how SaaS and AI companies can integrate automation. This innovation allows partners to embed Zapier&amp;rsquo;s automation engine directly into their products without extensive in-house integration work. With v0, the Powered by Zapier team can now create high-fidelity demos in just hours, leading to quicker implementation and more integrations. #Automation #Partnerships #SaaS #Innovation #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved metrics search in Observability Plus</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4731/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4731/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in Vercel Observability! The metrics search and navigation experience has been enhanced. You can now quickly find metrics using partial names or abbreviations like TTFB (time to first byte). Additional features include a side-by-side view of all metrics for an event, keyboard shortcuts for faster navigation, and a mobile-optimized interface. These updates are available now for all teams using Observability Plus. #Vercel #Observability #TechUpdates #Metrics #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Redesigning Workers KV for increased availability and faster performance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4764/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4764/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare has redesigned its Workers KV service following a significant outage on June 12, 2025. This incident was caused by a failure in the underlying storage infrastructure. To enhance availability and performance, Cloudflare has transitioned to its own storage infrastructure. This change eliminates single points of failure and reduces reliance on third-party providers for redundancy. The updated design aims to provide high availability while improving response times for critical&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>vlt is now available in builds via zero configuration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4732/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4732/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel now supports the vlt package manager for builds without the need for configuration. 📂 Projects with a vlt-lock.json file will automatically execute vlt install as the default Install Command. 🔧 Note: vlt requires Node 20.x and is available only in the modern build image. Learn more about this new feature on Vercel! #Vercel #vlt #WebDevelopment #PackageManager #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Security: Announcing Agentic Query validation, Attack Discovery persistence, and automated scheduling and actions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4720/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4720/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Elastic Security has unveiled updates to Attack Discovery and the Elastic AI Assistant, enhancing security operations with AI support. 🔍 The new agentic query validation ensures reliable queries, reducing errors during investigations. Analysts can focus on critical tasks with functional queries provided right away. 📅 The AI Assistant is now time-aware, streamlining incident management by providing real-time on-call information. 📊 Additionally, Attack Discovery saves historical findings and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AI Sheets: a tool to work with datasets using open AI models!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4738/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4738/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data enthusiasts! Hugging Face has launched AI Sheets, an open-source tool designed to build, enrich, and transform datasets using AI models without any coding required. You can deploy it locally or access it directly on the Hub, utilizing thousands of models, including gpt-oss from OpenAI. Explore the tool for free here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://huggingface.co/spaces/aisheets/sheets&#34;&gt;AI Sheets&lt;/a&gt; or install it locally from GitHub! #AISheets #OpenSource #DataScience #MachineLearning&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Live: GPT-5 on the DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4719/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4719/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! GPT-5 is now live on the DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform. Developers can access this advanced model via serverless inference APIs or the Gradient AI Platform SDK. You can also use your own OpenAI API key for integration. GPT-5 enhances reasoning and performance, making it ideal for tasks like financial planning, medical analysis, and creative content generation. Get started today! 🌟 #GPT5 #DigitalOcean #AIPlatform #Developers #OpenAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Headlamp AI Assistant</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5780/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5780/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! The Headlamp AI Assistant is here to enhance Kubernetes management and troubleshooting. This new plugin allows users, regardless of experience, to ask questions like &amp;ldquo;Is my application healthy?&amp;rdquo; and receive actionable insights. 🛠️ With a conversational UI powered by Large Language Models, users can now get contextual help directly from their Headlamp interface. Try it out today and streamline your Kubernetes operations! #Kubernetes #AI #TechInnovation #Headlamp #DevOps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Assistant, Junie and Kineto Now Support GPT-5 by OpenAI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4727/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4727/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from JetBrains! The latest model from OpenAI, GPT-5, is now integrated into AI Assistant, Junie, and Kineto. This update enhances coding capabilities, improving code quality and handling complex tasks more effectively. Junie, now powered by GPT-5, shows significant performance gains, making it easier to create production-ready code. To experience GPT-5, update to JetBrains IDE version 2025.2 and install the latest AI Assistant and Junie plugins. #JetBrains #GPT5 #AI #Coding&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build with GPT-5 on Databricks with AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4760/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:42:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4760/</guid>
      <description>🚀 OpenAI has launched GPT-5, their latest and most advanced language model! This new model can be integrated with Databricks through the AI Gateway, allowing users to harness its capabilities securely and at scale. Developers can now leverage Mosaic AI Gateway to enhance their applications effectively. #OpenAI #GPT5 #Databricks #AIGateway #MosaicAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get ready for FSR Redstone with AMD FSR 3.1.4 and our new UE 5.6 plugin</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4713/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4713/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for game developers! AMD has released FidelityFX™ Super Resolution 3.1.4, enhancing framerates with improved upscaling and frame generation. This version also features a signed DLL for easy upgrades to future FSR technologies, including FSR Redstone. The updated Unreal Engine 5.6 plugin simplifies integration, allowing developers to prepare for upcoming ML-powered features like Neural Radiance Caching and ML Frame Generation. Get ready to elevate your game’s performance! 🎮✨&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robinhood Presents: HOOD Summit ‘25 – Enter the Mainframe</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4710/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 15:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4710/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Robinhood! Join us for the second annual HOOD Summit in Las Vegas on September 9-10. This event will showcase new technology and trading tools for active traders. 📅 Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the keynote by CEO Vlad Tenev on September 9 at 5:30 PM PT, available via livestream. 📈 On September 10, industry leaders will share insights on active trading. Celebrate with HOOD Month starting August 19, featuring special promotions! For more details, visit events.robinhood.com/presents-&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-5, GPT-5-mini, and GPT-5-nano are now available in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4736/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4736/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s GPT-5, GPT-5-mini, and GPT-5-nano are now accessible via Vercel AI Gateway. This platform allows seamless model integration without needing multiple provider accounts. Users can easily track usage, costs, and optimize performance. To get started, install the AI SDK v5 and select your preferred model. Explore more about the AI Gateway and its features! 🌐✨ #OpenAI #Vercel #AIGateway #GPT5 #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel collaborates with OpenAI for GPT-5 launch</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4734/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4734/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has partnered with OpenAI to launch the GPT-5 family of models! These models are now available through AI Gateway and in production on v0.dev. Vercel has been testing GPT-5 in various environments, and the results indicate improved frontend design capabilities. GPT-5 generates clean, composable code and enhances workflows, particularly with long-context reasoning and tool handling. Vercel is already integrating GPT-5 into its dashboard and other applications. #Vercel #OpenAI #GPT5&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel is the only vendor to be recognized as a Visionary in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud-Native Application Platforms</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4735/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4735/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Vercel has been recognized as a Visionary in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for Cloud-Native Application Platforms. With over 4M weekly active domains and 115B requests served, Vercel’s AI Cloud empowers teams to create fast and secure applications effortlessly. This acknowledgment underscores Vercel&amp;rsquo;s role in shaping the future of web development. #CloudComputing #Gartner #WebDevelopment #Vercel #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trials 2 – A New First-Person Puzzle Game</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4729/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:52:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4729/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Introducing &amp;ldquo;The Trials 2&amp;rdquo;! Ahmad Sultan, an independent game developer from Syria, has launched a new first-person puzzle game. The Trials 2 draws inspiration from well-known titles like The Talos Principle. Get ready to solve intricate puzzles and experience a unique gaming journey! #TheTrials2 #GameDevelopment #IndieGame #PuzzleGame #GamingCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 8.19.1 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4723/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4723/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New Release Alert! 🚨 Elastic Stack 8.19.1 has officially launched! This version includes important fixes and improvements over 8.19.0. For a detailed overview of the changes and resolved issues, check the release notes. Upgrade your systems for enhanced performance! 🔄 #ElasticStack #TechUpdate #SoftwareRelease #UpgradeNow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 9.1.1 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4722/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4722/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Elastic Stack has officially released version 9.1.1. This update includes important fixes and improvements compared to version 9.1.0. Users are encouraged to upgrade to benefit from these enhancements. For a complete list of changes and resolved issues, check the release notes. #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews #UpgradeNow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s New and Important in CUDA Toolkit 13.0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4134/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4134/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in CUDA Toolkit 13.0! This major release enhances computing on NVIDIA CPUs and GPUs, introducing new features like tile-based programming and improved support for Arm platforms. Key updates include: - Enhanced NVIDIA Nsight Developer Tools - Math libraries updates for linear algebra and FFT - Improved NVCC Compiler with better compression - Accelerated Python cuda.core release CUDA 13.0 continues to support Blackwell GPUs and introduces a new programming model to boost&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minimize AI hallucinations and deliver up to 99% verification accuracy with Automated Reasoning checks: Now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4149/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4149/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI developers! Amazon has launched Automated Reasoning checks, a new feature in Amazon Bedrock Guardrails. This tool offers up to 99% verification accuracy to minimize AI hallucinations and ensure data accuracy. Key features include support for large documents, simplified policy validation, and automated scenario generation. This will enhance the reliability of AI-generated content. Learn how to create policies using this tool to maintain strict adherence to rules in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Next Evolution of Docker Hardened Images: Customizable, FedRAMP Ready, AI Migration Agent, and Deeper Integrations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4148/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4148/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker Hardened Images (DHI) have seen rapid adoption since their launch in May, helping organizations achieve near-zero CVEs and secure their software supply chains. 🔒 The latest enhancements include a broader image catalog, customizable options, and an AI migration agent. These updates will be showcased at Black Hat 2025. 🛠️ DHI now supports full-stack systems with trusted, production-ready images, ensuring security without hindering developer speed. #Docker #Cybersecurity #DevOps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AI Elements: build AI interfaces faster</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4693/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4693/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for frontend engineers! Vercel has launched AI Elements, a tool designed to simplify the process of building AI interfaces. With this new product, developers can create ChatGPT or v0-like interfaces in just minutes. This innovation aims to streamline the app-building process, allowing teams to focus on functionality over design complexity. #AIElements #Vercel #FrontendDevelopment #TechInnovation #AIInterfaces</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AI Elements: Prebuilt, composable AI SDK components</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4171/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4171/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing AI Elements, a new open-source library designed for customizable React components! Built on shadcn/ui, it allows developers to create interfaces using the Vercel AI SDK. Key features include control over UI elements like message threads and input boxes. To get started, simply initialize with our CLI, choose your components, and begin building. For detailed guidance, check out the documentation. #AI #OpenSource #React #Vercel #Development</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Vercel MCP: Connect Vercel to your AI tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4161/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4161/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Vercel has launched its MCP server, now in Public Beta. This secure interface allows AI tools to connect with your Vercel projects seamlessly. With Vercel MCP, tools like Cursor and Claude can access project logs, documents, and metadata directly, enhancing your workflow. Discover more about this innovative development! #Vercel #AIDevelopment #MCP #TechNews #DeveloperTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microfrontends support is now in Public Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4162/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4162/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Microfrontends support is now in Public Beta! This feature allows developers to split large applications into smaller, manageable parts, enabling faster development and independent testing. Vercel simplifies the assembly and routing of these microfrontends into a cohesive user experience. To get started, users can clone examples from the Vercel dashboard, create microfrontend groups, and configure their projects with ease. For more details, check the documentation or contact Vercel support&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s Fixed in IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4119/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4119/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2! This release introduces a standalone &amp;ldquo;What’s Fixed&amp;rdquo; overview, highlighting stability and quality improvements. Key areas of focus include enhanced Spring and Kotlin support, better remote development features, and performance upgrades. For the complete list of fixes, check the release notes. #IntelliJIDEA #SoftwareUpdates #Kotlin #SpringFramework #DevelopmentTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MetaHuman for Maya Release</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4122/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:24:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4122/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for creators! The latest version of MetaHuman for Maya has been launched, featuring the new Pose Editor. This tool allows rigging artists to assemble and customize MetaHuman characters directly in Autodesk Maya. Explore the enhanced capabilities and improve your character creation process! #MetaHuman #Maya #3DAnimation #CharacterDesign #GameDev</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify access management for Red Hat Insights for Red Hat Enterprise Linux with new system roles</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4103/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 07:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4103/</guid>
      <description>Managing user access for Red Hat Enterprise Linux (RHEL) just became simpler! 🚀 Red Hat has introduced three new system roles in the User Access service of the Hybrid Cloud Console: 1️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;RHEL Administrator&lt;/strong&gt;: Full privileges for managing configurations and vulnerabilities. 2️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;RHEL Operator&lt;/strong&gt;: Broad capabilities for editing configurations, but with some restrictions. 3️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;RHEL Viewer&lt;/strong&gt;: Read-only access for viewing system data. These roles enhance security and streamline user management&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI open weight models now available on AWS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4102/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4102/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s open weight models are now available on AWS through Amazon Bedrock and Amazon SageMaker JumpStart. These models, gpt-oss-120b and gpt-oss-20b, are designed for text generation and reasoning tasks, providing flexibility and control over your projects. With a 128K context window and adjustable reasoning levels, they offer enhanced capabilities for coding, scientific analysis, and more. Explore and innovate with ease in a seamless environment! #OpenAI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the transition to IBM means for HashiCorp customers: Greater value, same commitment</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4052/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4052/</guid>
      <description>🚀 HashiCorp is transitioning to IBM starting September 1, 2025. This move aims to enhance customer value while maintaining the trust you&amp;rsquo;ve built with HashiCorp. 🔧 Key updates include changes to product naming conventions, aligning with IBM’s portfolio, but no alterations to features. Customers using legacy products will benefit from upgrades at current pricing. 💼 Billing operations will also shift to IBM, with new customer numbers issued. PAYG customers will see no changes. For more details,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expose hidden threats with EASE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4115/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4115/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the Elastic AI SOC Engine (EASE)! 🚀 EASE is designed to enhance security operations by integrating AI capabilities into existing SIEM and EDR systems. It helps analysts detect complex threats faster and reduces investigation time. With features like centralized alert summaries and automated attack discovery, EASE enables better prioritization and response to high-risk alerts. 🛡️ This solution is especially beneficial for organizations looking to improve their threat detection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partnering with OpenAI to bring their new open models onto Cloudflare Workers AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2075/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 21:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2075/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s latest open-source models are now live on Cloudflare Workers AI. Developers can access two new models: a 120 billion parameter and a 20 billion parameter version. These models feature a Mixture-of-Experts architecture for efficient performance and are designed for transparency and flexibility. 🛠️ In addition, Cloudflare supports the new Responses API, enhancing interaction capabilities. The Code Interpreter and Web Search features are also on the way! #OpenAI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD releases Vulkan support for Dense Geometry Format</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4091/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4091/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AMD has announced a provisional Vulkan® extension for its Dense Geometry Format (DGF), a block-based geometry compression technology. This extension, VK_AMDX_dense_geometry_format, allows DGF data to be directly used in building acceleration structures, enhancing performance and reducing memory costs. With native DGF support, developers can expect improved build times and lower memory usage for BLAS. #AMD #Vulkan #GameDev #Graphics #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA vGPU 19.0 Enables Graphics and AI Virtualization on NVIDIA Blackwell GPUs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-210/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-210/</guid>
      <description>NVIDIA has released vGPU 19.0, enhancing virtualization for graphics and AI workloads. 🌐 The update leverages the NVIDIA RTX PRO 6000 Blackwell GPUs, which support advanced features like Multi-Instance GPU (MIG) for improved scalability and user density in data centers. With 96 GB of GDDR7 memory, these GPUs excel in demanding enterprise tasks, from AI inference to scientific computing. This release aims to significantly boost performance for virtualized workloads. #NVIDIA #Virtualization #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP UI: Breaking the text wall with interactive components</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2203/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2203/</guid>
      <description>🚀 MCP UI is transforming AI interactions in commerce by enabling agents to deliver interactive UI components. This open-source protocol enhances the shopping experience with features like product selectors and image galleries, addressing the limitations of text-only communication. MCP UI uses an intent-based messaging system to maintain agent control while providing dynamic user experiences. Explore the Shopify Storefront MCP UI Server prototype for a firsthand look! 🛒✨ #ECommerce #AI #MCPUI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA Accelerates OpenAI gpt-oss Models Delivering 1.5 M TPS Inference on NVIDIA GB200 NVL72</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-211/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-211/</guid>
      <description>🚀 NVIDIA and OpenAI are advancing AI technologies with the launch of the gpt-oss-20b and gpt-oss-120b models. These models, designed for high-performance inference, can achieve 1.5 million tokens per second on the NVIDIA GB200 NVL72 system. 🧠 The gpt-oss models utilize a mixture of experts architecture and are optimized for NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s Blackwell system. They support advanced text reasoning capabilities and are trained on NVIDIA H100 Tensor Core GPUs. 🔧 Developers can access optimized kernels and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Amazon Elastic VMware Service for running VMware Cloud Foundation on AWS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2486/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:08:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2486/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for organizations looking to migrate VMware workloads to the cloud! AWS has launched the Amazon Elastic VMware Service (Amazon EVS), which allows users to run VMware Cloud Foundation environments directly within Amazon VPCs. This service simplifies migration while maintaining existing tools and practices. With Amazon EVS, you can deploy fully functional environments in just a few hours, ensuring minimal disruption and full control over your cloud resources. 🌥️ Key features&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing OpenAI’s New Open Models on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-3180/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 17:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-3180/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from OpenAI! They&amp;rsquo;ve partnered with Databricks to launch new open weight models, gpt-oss 20B and gpt-oss 120B. These models will help developers build intelligent, domain-specific AI agents securely. Stay tuned for updates on how these advancements can transform AI applications! #OpenAI #Databricks #AI #MachineLearning #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RustRover 2025.2 Is Now Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-540/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-540/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! RustRover 2025.2 is now available, featuring significant debugger enhancements. New functionalities include remote and on-chip support, improved borrow checker assistance, and additional Rust learning resources. Junie, the in-IDE coding agent, is now 30% faster and offers smarter code completion, enhancing your coding experience. Check out the updated features and improvements today! #RustRover #DevelopmentTools #Coding #RustLang #JetBrains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin DSL: What’s New?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-541/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-541/</guid>
      <description>🚀 TeamCity has introduced significant enhancements to the Kotlin DSL in recent releases! 📁 Users can now store Kotlin DSL files outside the .teamcity directory, improving visibility and convenience when working with IntelliJ IDEA. 🔄 Additionally, code reuse is simplified with the introduction of DSL libraries, allowing developers to share code across projects more efficiently. 📊 For those managing multiple branches, changes in DSL files can now better align with build configurations. Learn&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhpStorm 2025.2 Is Now Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-542/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-542/</guid>
      <description>🚀 PhpStorm 2025.2 is here! This release introduces several key features, including making Laravel Idea free for users and enhancing the remote development experience. Junie coding agent now supports the Model Context Protocol (MCP), allowing connections to databases and APIs. Additionally, enjoy a 30% speed increase in prompt processing and improved JetBrains AI tools. Explore the new features today! #PhpStorm #WebDevelopment #JetBrains #AI #SoftwareUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Opus 4.1 is now supported in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4163/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4163/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Claude Opus 4.1 is now accessible via Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI Gateway without the need for additional provider accounts. This new model enhances task execution, coding, and reasoning compared to its predecessor. AI Gateway offers a unified API, usage tracking, and performance optimizations for improved reliability. Start using it with the AI SDK v5 by installing the package and setting the model to anthropic/claude-4.1-opus. Learn more about the AI Gateway and explore the new model&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>gpt-oss-20b and gpt-oss-120b are now supported in Vercel AI Gateway</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4164/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4164/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Vercel AI Gateway now supports OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s gpt-oss-20b and gpt-oss-120b models. These open-weight reasoning models enhance access with a unified API, simplifying usage tracking and performance optimizations. 💻 Developers can easily integrate them using AI SDK v5, with built-in observability and support for multiple model providers. Discover more about AI Gateway and check out the new model leaderboard! 📊 #Vercel #OpenAI #AIModels #TechNews #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoLand 2025.2 Is Now Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-543/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-543/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GoLand 2025.2 is here with exciting updates! Key features include enhanced support for HTTP servers, smarter inspections using data flow analysis (DFA), and a new non-blocking Welcome screen for faster access to tools. The update also improves golangci-lint integration for real-time code analysis. 🛠️ Explore the new capabilities and streamline your development process! #GoLand #SoftwareUpdate #CodingTools #Golang #DevCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Ideas Clickable With Kineto by JetBrains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-544/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-544/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Kineto by JetBrains! This new platform addresses the technical challenges faced when creating websites and apps. Kineto allows anyone to build their own app in just 20 minutes, without needing coding skills. It&amp;rsquo;s designed for small applications like personal blogs, fitness trackers, and more. With Kineto, your ideas can become reality effortlessly! Join the waitlist today! 📱✨ #Kineto #NoCode #AppDevelopment #JetBrains #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello Developer: August 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2278/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2278/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Exciting news for developers! Apple is launching new workshops globally, offering opportunities to enhance your skills. Also, you can now download Apple UI design kits for Figma and Sketch. Don’t miss the chance to connect with the Italy-based team behind Sunlitt. #AppleDeveloper #UIDesign #Figma #Sketch #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLion 2025.2 Is Here: Better CLion Nova, Smarter Embedded Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-545/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 11:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-545/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CLion 2025.2 has been released! This update enhances the JetBrains IDE for C and C++ with several new features. Key improvements include an upgraded code formatter in CLion Nova, faster remote development, and live watches in the debugger for real-time variable monitoring. 🛠️ Additionally, the ESP32 debug server is now available for ESP-IDF projects. You can download CLion 2025.2 via the Toolbox App, as a snap package for Ubuntu, or as a patch update from version 2025.1. #CLion #JetBrains&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyCharm 2025.2: AI Toolkit for AI Engineers and More!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-546/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 11:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-546/</guid>
      <description>Discover the new features in PyCharm 2025.2! 🚀 This release introduces the AI Toolkit, designed to support AI engineers with tools for experimentation, debugging, and deployment all within the IDE. Additionally, it marks the last version of PyCharm Community, paving the way for a unified PyCharm experience. Notable updates include enhancements to AI Assistant, Junie, and notebooks. Download the latest version today! 💻✨ #PyCharm #AIToolkit #SoftwareUpdate #Programming #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains is a Platinum Sponsor of the Godot Foundation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-547/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-547/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from JetBrains! We are proud to announce our Platinum Sponsorship of the Godot Foundation. Godot is an open-source game engine, driven by a community-focused approach and dedicated to supporting developers. The Godot Foundation plays a vital role in ensuring financial backing for the Godot Project. Our support enhances JetBrains Rider, which offers robust features for Godot development, including improved GDScript support in upcoming releases. Together, we&amp;rsquo;re committed to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing incident detection in Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management for Kubernetes 2.14</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-92/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 07:01:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-92/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management for Kubernetes 2.14 introduces incident detection, helping teams manage alert storms more effectively. This feature groups related alerts into manageable incidents, allowing for better root cause analysis and prioritization. To utilize this, install the Cluster Observability Operator on each cluster. It simplifies navigation between incidents within managed clusters. For installation details and to explore this feature, check the latest documentation&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome GPT OSS, the new open-source model family from OpenAI!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-577/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-577/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from OpenAI! They have launched GPT OSS, a new open-source model family featuring two versions: gpt-oss-120b with 117B parameters and gpt-oss-20b with 21B parameters. Both models utilize a mixture-of-experts design for efficient performance. These models are licensed under Apache 2.0, promoting safe and responsible use. OpenAI aims to enhance accessibility in AI through this release. #OpenAI #GPTOSS #MachineLearning #AICommunity #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NVIDIA CUDA-Q 0.12 Expands Toolset for Developing Hardware-Performant Quantum Applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-214/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-214/</guid>
      <description>🚀 NVIDIA CUDA-Q 0.12 has been released, bringing new simulation tools for quantum application development. The update allows researchers to access detailed statistics on individual simulation runs, aiding in areas like noise correlation and circuit benchmarking. New features also enhance the CUDA-Q dynamics backend, improving support for multidiagonal sparse matrices and generic super-operators. This open-source project includes community contributions and Python 3.13 support. For more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2 Is Here!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-548/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 17:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-548/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2 has officially launched! This version offers updates aimed at enhancing productivity and code quality. Users can download it from the website, update through the IDE, or use the Toolbox App. Key highlights include smarter AI workflows, support for Java 25 Early Access, and improvements for Spring developers. For more details, visit the newly redesigned What’s New page. Check it out and explore the features today! 🔍💻 #IntelliJIDEA #SoftwareUpdates #Coding #Java&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Weekly Roundup: Amazon DocumentDB, AWS Lambda, Amazon EC2, and more (August 4, 2025)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2487/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2487/</guid>
      <description>🚀 This week, AWS announced several key updates across its services. 🔹 Amazon DocumentDB Serverless is now live, providing a fully managed MongoDB API-compatible database. 🔹 The Amazon Q Developer CLI allows for custom agent creation to streamline specialized tasks. 🔹 Amazon Bedrock now supports DOC/DOCX files and H.265 video files for enhanced data processing. 🔹 AWS Lambda increases response streaming payload size to 200 MB, improving performance. For the full details, check the article! #AWS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AMD TressFX 5.0 for Unreal Engine 5 is now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-200/</guid>
      <description>🌟 AMD has launched TressFX 5.0 for Unreal Engine 5.4, enhancing realistic hair and fur simulation. Key updates include support for Lumen ray tracing, deep shadow approximation, and continuous LOD. This version is designed for seamless integration into your Unreal projects. To install, ensure you are a registered Unreal developer and follow the simple integration steps. #AMD #UnrealEngine #TressFX #GameDev #Simulation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains AI Assistant Update: Better Context, Greater Offline Flexibility, Deeper IDE Integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-549/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-549/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains AI Assistant has received a significant update! Key features include smarter code completion with support for more languages and file types like SQL and Markdown. The improved Mellum model enhances context-awareness for better results. Project rules now allow for consistent instructions, making it easier to maintain coding standards across teams. Additionally, users can connect local models for offline flexibility and attach images in chats for quicker analysis. #JetBrains #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataGrip and Database tools UX Survey #2 Results</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-550/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-550/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from the DataGrip community! The second UX Survey results are in, highlighting key improvements made from your feedback. Significant changes include faster introspection, editable results for SELECT queries, and new AI-powered features. The survey also expanded to gather insights on user experiences and team collaboration with database tools. Discover more about the findings and upcoming enhancements in DataGrip! #DataGrip #UXSurvey #DatabaseTools #AI #UserExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimize workloads with right-sizing recommendations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-94/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-94/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing the Right-Sizing Recommendations in Red Hat Advanced Cluster Management for Kubernetes! This new capability helps users identify over-provisioned and under-utilized resources across clusters, promoting efficient infrastructure use and cost savings. By analyzing real-time CPU and memory consumption, it offers actionable recommendations for workload optimization. Key features include a Grafana dashboard for resource metrics, customizable data filtering, and policy-driven&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RubyMine 2025.2: Junie and AI Assistant Upgrades, Faster Rails Project Startup, Enhanced Bundler Management, and More</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-551/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-551/</guid>
      <description>🚀 RubyMine 2025.2 is here with exciting updates! The JetBrains AI Assistant has been enhanced, providing smarter code completion and project-specific context. Key features include improved ERB code support and project rules for consistency. You can now connect local AI models for offline use, plus enjoy expanded code suggestions and image attachments in chat. Explore the full details on our website! #RubyMine #AI #Coding #SoftwareDevelopment #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New custom visualization in Vercel Observability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4167/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4167/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Observability Plus users! You can now customize your data visualizations with options like line charts, volume charts, tables, or big numbers. 📊 Both queries and visualization settings can be saved in shareable notebooks, enhancing teamwork. This update is available at no extra cost for Observability Plus teams. Explore the new features today! #DataVisualization #Observability #TechUpdate #Vercel #Collaboration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel MCP now in Public Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4166/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4166/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel&amp;rsquo;s Model Control Protocol (MCP) server is now in Public Beta! The server, accessible at mcp.vercel.com, offers a remote interface with OAuth-based authorization, allowing secure interactions with AI tools and Vercel projects. It supports AI assistants like Claude.ai and integrates with tools such as VS Code to help manage projects, analyze deployment logs, and navigate documentation. This update aims to enhance collaboration between AI workflows and the Vercel ecosystem. For more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check out the winners of the Unreal Engine Dance Animation Challenge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4082/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4082/</guid>
      <description>Discover the remarkable winners of the Unreal Engine Dance Animation Challenge! 🎉 These entries showcase impressive dance animations that highlight creativity and skill. Check out the fantastic moves that have taken the spotlight! 💃🕺 #UnrealEngine #DanceAnimation #AnimationChallenge #Winners #Creativity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Amazon Application Recovery Controller Region switch: A multi-Region application recovery service</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2488/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 15:10:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2488/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing the Amazon Application Recovery Controller (ARC) Region switch! This feature allows organizations to efficiently plan and execute failover operations between AWS Regions. It automates workflows and continuously validates recovery processes, enhancing confidence in your Region failover strategy. With ARC Region switch, you can create detailed recovery plans for seamless transitions, ensuring your critical applications remain resilient during operational events. Learn more about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new wave of software, shipped on Vercel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-4168/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-4168/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A new initiative, &amp;ldquo;Shipped on Vercel,&amp;rdquo; highlights innovative apps currently in production on the Vercel platform. This platform showcases teams that are reimagining web development, offering insights into their creative processes and technologies used. Discover how these real-world applications are shaping the future of the web! 🌐 #Vercel #WebDevelopment #Innovation #TechTrends #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Hono backends with zero configuration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-4169/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-4169/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel now offers native support for Hono, a lightweight backend framework, with zero configuration required. This integration allows Vercel to optimize Hono applications for builds and deployments, enhancing performance. New deployments benefit from features like Fluid compute, Active CPU pricing, and automatic cold start optimizations. For more details, check out Hono&amp;rsquo;s Vercel documentation. #Hono #Vercel #BackendDevelopment #WebStandards #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Google Developer Program is evolving</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-20/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are here for the Google Developer Program! 🔹 A new flexible monthly subscription is now available for $24.99. This plan includes access to AI tools, Google Cloud credits, and more. 🔹 The launch of the Google Developer Program forums simplifies collaboration among developers, allowing for easy sharing of knowledge and support. Explore these enhancements to elevate your coding experience! #GoogleDeveloper #AI #TechUpdates #DeveloperCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlashList v2: A Ground-Up Rewrite for React Native&#39;s New Architecture</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2204/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2204/</guid>
      <description>🚀 FlashList v2 has arrived, offering a complete rewrite for improved performance in React Native applications. This new version eliminates the need for item size estimates, allowing for faster load times and smoother scrolling. It is now production-ready and powers thousands of lists in the Shopify mobile app. Key improvements include precise rendering and support for complex lists without the hassle of manual estimates. The transition to React Native&amp;rsquo;s New Architecture has enhanced layout&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Released: NVIDIA HPC SDK v25.7</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-218/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:09:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-218/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Just announced: NVIDIA HPC SDK v25.7 is now available! This update includes support for CUDA 12.9U1, along with updated library components, bug fixes, and performance improvements. For installation, users can download the SDK for Linux x86_64 and follow the provided instructions for setup. Check it out to enhance your high-performance computing projects! #NVIDIA #HPCSDK #CUDA #TechUpdate #HighPerformanceComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Released: NVIDIA cuPQC v0.4</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-219/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:07:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-219/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Just in: NVIDIA has launched cuPQC v0.4! This update brings Poseidon2 to cuHash and introduces a Merkle Tree API compatible with all cuHash hash functions. For those interested, you can download the SDK for GPU-accelerated Post-Quantum Cryptography. Check the documentation for system requirements and installation instructions. 🔗 Download cuPQC: &lt;a href=&#34;https://developer.download.nvidia.com/compute/cupqc/redist/cupqc/cupqc-sdk-0.4.0-x86_64.tar.gz&#34;&gt;x86_64&lt;/a&gt; |&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HCP Terraform introduces Hold Your Own Key (HYOK)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-1996/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-1996/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for HCP Terraform customers! The new Hold Your Own Key (HYOK) feature is now available, providing enhanced control over sensitive data in Terraform artifacts. HYOK allows organizations to manage their encryption keys, ensuring that secrets in state and plan files are securely handled. This is crucial for those migrating to the cloud and needing compliance with strict security standards. 🔒 With HYOK, customers can encrypt their Terraform artifacts before uploading them,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Databricks Vancouver Development Center</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3182/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3182/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news! Databricks is expanding its R&amp;amp;D efforts with a new development center in Vancouver. This initiative aims to enhance capabilities in data and AI, fostering innovation in the tech community. Stay tuned for updates on projects and opportunities coming from this new location! #Databricks #Vancouver #DataInnovation #AI #TechExpansion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon DocumentDB Serverless is now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2489/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2489/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Amazon DocumentDB Serverless is now available. This new configuration automatically adjusts compute and memory based on your application&amp;rsquo;s needs, leading to potential cost savings of up to 90% compared to peak provisioning. It supports the same MongoDB compatible APIs and offers seamless scaling without data migration. Key benefits include handling variable workloads, managing multi-tenant environments, and balancing mixed-use workloads efficiently. For steady&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI SDK 5</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4170/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4170/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The AI SDK 5 is making waves with over 2 million weekly downloads! This open-source toolkit for TypeScript and JavaScript offers a unified provider API, allowing developers to utilize any language model easily. It also supports powerful integrations with popular web frameworks. Explore the potential of AI SDK 5 for your projects! #AISDK #OpenSource #WebDevelopment #JavaScript #TypeScript</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel Open Source Program: Summer cohort</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4737/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4737/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Vercel! The Vercel Open Source Program has announced its summer 2025 cohort. This initiative supports developers by providing resources, credits, and assistance to enhance their projects. This season features 28 innovative projects, including AI-powered calendars and stylish React Native components. Learn more about these amazing contributions! #Vercel #OpenSource #DeveloperCommunity #Innovation #TechForGood</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating by direct transfer is generally available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3191/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3191/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab 18.3 introduces direct transfer for migrating groups and projects, making it easier for users to copy resources between instances. This feature simplifies the migration process, allowing you to move entire top-level groups with sub-groups and projects without manual file exports. It supports user contribution mapping and works reliably with large projects. For those using GitLab.com, the feature is enabled by default. Self-managed users should check their application settings. 🌐&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Veo 3 Fast and new image-to-video capabilities</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-21/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Google has launched Veo 3 Fast, a new model designed for speed and cost-effectiveness. It allows developers to create high-quality videos quickly, supporting both text-to-video and image-to-video capabilities. This functionality is available through the Gemini API. With prices starting at $0.40/second for videos with audio, Veo 3 Fast is ideal for programmatic advertising and content creation at scale. #Google #Veo3 #VideoContent #TechNews #Developers</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
