<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pinterest-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/pinterest-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pinterest-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:02:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/pinterest-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How Pinterest Built a Real‑Time Radar for Violative Content using AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13564/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13564/</guid>
      <description>Pinterest has developed an AI-driven system to monitor violative content in real-time. This approach, known as prevalence measurement, assesses the percentage of views on policy-violating content daily. Historically, user reports were the main metric, but this method left gaps. Under-reported issues, such as self-harm, and rare content types can go unnoticed. The new system samples user impressions, allowing for a broader, more stable view of content violations. This provides quicker insights&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving Quality of Recommended Content through Pinner Surveys</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13521/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 20:02:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13521/</guid>
      <description>Pinterest is enhancing content quality by utilizing user feedback through surveys. 📊 In partnership with the Inspired Internet Pledge, the platform collects ratings on visual appeal to understand what users value. This data is then used to train machine learning models to improve recommendations across Homefeed, Related Pins, and Search. The initiative aims to reduce low-quality content and elevate user experience. 📈✨ Learn more about how Pinterest is putting Pinners first! #Pinterest&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On the (re)-prioritization of open-source AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13458/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 17:02:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13458/</guid>
      <description>The AI landscape is shifting, highlighting the importance of open-source models. Pinterest’s team reports significant cost savings, achieving similar performance to proprietary models for under 10% of the cost. The focus is on tailored models that excel in specific tasks, leveraging Pinterest&amp;rsquo;s unique data. This trend reflects a broader industry move towards domain-specific data and personalization. As Pinterest continues to invest in open-source AI, the goal remains to enhance user&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous Observability at Pinterest (Part 1 of 2)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13403/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13403/</guid>
      <description>At Pinterest, we are enhancing our observability tools to create a unified experience. Traditionally, our systems operated in silos, making it hard to connect logs, metrics, and traces. To address this, we are implementing the Model Context Protocol (MCP) to streamline our observability data. This will enable faster root-cause analysis and empower our teams to build context-aware tools. We are excited to embrace AI in this journey, aiming for a more intelligent observability future! 🚀🔍&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slashing CI Wait Times: How Pinterest Cut Android Testing Build Times by 36%&#43;</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12128/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 23:02:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12128/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Pinterest Engineering! To address slow and flaky Android testing builds, the team implemented a runtime-aware sharding mechanism. This new approach reduces build times by 36%, cutting down the slowest shard&amp;rsquo;s runtime by 55%. The solution optimizes test distribution based on historical data, ensuring balanced runtimes across shards. 📉 This advancement enhances developer velocity and streamlines the CI process. #PinterestEngineering #CIPipeline #AndroidDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Decade of AI Platform at Pinterest</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11824/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 18:01:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11824/</guid>
      <description>Over the past decade, Pinterest has transformed its AI Platform from fragmented machine learning stacks to a unified system that supports all major operations. Key lessons include the importance of organizational alignment for adoption, the need for layered foundations, and the interplay of enablement, efficiency, and velocity. The evolution is divided into five eras, highlighting the journey from initial fragmentation to broader alignment and advanced capabilities. For more insights, check&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identify User Journeys at Pinterest</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11135/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 21:42:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11135/</guid>
      <description>📌 Pinterest is enhancing its platform by introducing user journeys, focusing on understanding users&amp;rsquo; long-term goals beyond immediate interests. A user journey combines interests, intent, and context, enabling personalized recommendations for projects like wedding planning or home renovations. To implement this, Pinterest is using a dynamic keyword extraction approach for greater adaptability and personalization. This shift aims to help users achieve their aspirations effectively. #Pinterest&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tracking Down Mysterious ML Training Stalls</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11036/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:01:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11036/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Pinterest recently tackled a significant challenge during a PyTorch upgrade, experiencing a 50% drop in ML training throughput. The team meticulously traced the issue, identifying low-level Linux kernels and a monitoring process as major culprits. Their systematic debugging provided insights into optimizing performance and enhancing training efficiency. This journey highlights the importance of thorough analysis and innovative solutions in tackling complex tech issues. 💻✨ #MachineLearning&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Gen Data Processing at Massive Scale At Pinterest With Moka (Part 2 of 2)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9530/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:01:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9530/</guid>
      <description>Pinterest is evolving its data processing capabilities with Moka, a next-gen platform built on AWS EKS. 🌐 The new infrastructure includes standardized cluster environments like test, dev, staging, and production, allowing for effective resource management and security. Key features include enhanced logging using Fluent Bit and observability metrics via OTEL, improving insights into performance and stability. 📊 Learn more about Moka&amp;rsquo;s architecture and its future developments. #DataProcessing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Experience at Pinterest: The Journey to PinConsole</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6316/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:12:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6316/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Pinterest has introduced PinConsole, an Internal Developer Platform (IDP) aimed at simplifying the developer experience. This initiative addresses increasing complexity and improves engineering velocity for over 550 million users. 🔍 The team identified challenges such as tool fragmentation and inconsistent workflows, which were hindering productivity. By leveraging Backstage, PinConsole creates a unified interface, allowing engineers to focus on business logic. 📈 Early adoption shows&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
