<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dropbox-Tech-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/dropbox-tech-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dropbox-Tech-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/dropbox-tech-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Engineering VP Josh Clemm on how we use knowledge graphs, MCP, and DSPy in Dash</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-28-14981/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-28-14981/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Engineering VP Josh Clemm recently shared insights on Dropbox&amp;rsquo;s use of knowledge graphs, MCP, and DSPy during a session in Jason Liu’s RAG course on Maven. He discussed how Dropbox Dash integrates with third-party apps, allowing users to easily search and manage their content. For a deeper understanding, check out the full video on Maven! #DropboxDash #KnowledgeGraphs #TechInnovation #MavenCourse #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the feature store powering real-time AI in Dropbox Dash</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14032/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14032/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dropbox Dash is leveraging AI to enhance how we search and organize our work. By using a feature store, Dash ranks and retrieves relevant files quickly, adapting to user behavior across various content types. This system is essential for effective collaboration and improves access to important documents and conversations. The development of this feature store was tailored specifically for Dash, addressing unique infrastructure challenges and ensuring speed and efficiency. #DropboxDash #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building the future: highlights from Dropbox’s 2025 summer intern class</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13081/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13081/</guid>
      <description>This summer, Dropbox welcomed 43 interns as part of the 2025 Camp Dropbox Intern Program. 🌍 They came from 27 colleges, including six international institutions. Over 12 weeks, interns worked on impactful projects, especially related to Dropbox Dash, our AI-powered search tool. They received over 6,000 hours of mentorship and participated in various community-building events. 🤝 Interns shared their experiences, highlighting technical achievements and personal growth throughout their time at&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Dash uses context engineering for smarter AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12726/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12726/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in AI are here with Dash! Initially a traditional search system, Dash has evolved into an agentic AI that interprets and acts on user requests. This shift emphasizes the importance of context engineering—delivering the right information at the right time. As Dash incorporates new tools, the focus remains on providing relevant context to enhance decision-making. With these developments, teams can streamline their workflows and improve project management. #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>With Mobius Labs&#39; Aana models, we&#39;re bringing deeper multimodal understanding to Dropbox Dash</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11198/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11198/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Dropbox! They&amp;rsquo;ve partnered with Mobius Labs to enhance Dropbox Dash’s AI capabilities. With the integration of Aana models, Dash will improve its understanding of photos and videos, making it easier for teams to access and analyze their multimedia content. This multimodal processing will help users get answers faster without sifting through multiple tools. Stay organized and efficient with Dropbox Dash! #Dropbox #AI #MobiusLabs #Multimodal #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Half-Quadratic Quantization of large machine learning models</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11199/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11199/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Explore Half-Quadratic Quantization (HQQ), a new method for compressing large AI models without needing calibration data. This technique significantly speeds up quantization, processing models like Llama-2-70B in under 5 minutes—over 50x faster than traditional methods. HQQ maintains competitive compression quality, enabling efficient deployment of large language models. #MachineLearning #AI #Quantization #HQQ #Llama2</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A practical blueprint for evaluating conversational AI at scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10388/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10388/</guid>
      <description>Building effective conversational AI involves more than just training models. At Dropbox, we discovered that structured evaluation is crucial for accuracy. 🛠️ Initially, our evaluations were ad-hoc, but as we refined our processes, we developed a standardized approach to assess every change rigorously. This evaluation-first mindset is now part of our workflow. 📊 We created a playbook detailing datasets, metrics, and tools to help others implement this method across various media types,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hack Week 2025: How these engineers liquid-cooled a GPU server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7290/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7290/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Hack Week 2025 at Dropbox focused on the theme “Keep It Simple,” encouraging innovation and collaboration. One highlight was the &amp;ldquo;Liquid Cooling CPU/GPU Hardware&amp;rdquo; project, which won the Learn Fast award. The team developed a custom liquid cooling system for GPU servers to address the thermal demands of AI workloads. This system demonstrated significant benefits, including lower operating temperatures and quieter performance. Future plans include expanding testing across multiple data&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving AI adoption at Dropbox: a conversation with CTO Ali Dasdan</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5166/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5166/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI is transforming how Dropbox operates, enhancing productivity for engineers. In early 2025, a shift occurred, leading to over 90% AI adoption among engineering teams. This change was driven by leadership alignment and a culture of knowledge-sharing. CTO Ali Dasdan emphasizes AI&amp;rsquo;s role in automating tasks and allowing deeper focus on coding and innovation. #AI #Dropbox #Productivity #Innovation #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
