<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pragmatic-Engineer on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/pragmatic-engineer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pragmatic-Engineer on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:44:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/pragmatic-engineer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Pulse: Cloudflare’s latest outage proves dangers of global configuration changes (again)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14008/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14008/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare experienced another significant outage on December 5, just two weeks after a similar incident. This recent disruption lasted 25 minutes and affected 28% of its HTTP traffic. The outage was caused by a global configuration change intended to fix a React vulnerability, which inadvertently triggered errors across the network. Cloudflare is now prioritizing staged rollouts for configuration changes to avoid future issues. However, repeated outages may lead customers to consider backup&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pulse: Could a 5-day RTO be around the corner for Big Tech?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-13-13574/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 15:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-13-13574/</guid>
      <description>Meta&amp;rsquo;s Instagram division will require employees to return to the office five days a week starting February 2. This marks Meta as the second tech giant, after Amazon, to enforce a full RTO policy. CEO Adam Mosseri highlighted that in-person collaboration boosts creativity and efficiency. Key changes include reduced meetings and a focus on product prototypes over slides. This decision impacts about 25% of Meta&amp;rsquo;s workforce, raising questions about whether other divisions will follow suit&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Downdetector and the real cost of no upstream dependencies</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13483/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 09:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13483/</guid>
      <description>During the recent Cloudflare outage, Downdetector also faced downtime, highlighting its reliance on Cloudflare. Dhruv Arora from Ookla explained that although Downdetector is multi-cloud, it uses Cloudflare for essential services like DNS and CDN. This dependency allows for lower costs, faster load times, and robust DDoS protection. Removing this dependency could significantly increase costs without improving revenue. Downdetector is exploring ways to enhance its infrastructure while managing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A startup in Mongolia translated my book</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12934/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 13:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12934/</guid>
      <description>A small startup in Mongolia, Nasha Tech, translated my book, &lt;em&gt;The Software Engineer&amp;rsquo;s Guidebook&lt;/em&gt;, to support their company and the local tech community. 📚🇲🇳 The translation project began over a year ago, and despite my initial skepticism, they successfully printed 500 copies. The team invited me to a book signing in Ulaanbaatar, where I saw their unique office culture. Nasha Tech focuses on agency work, primarily for Japanese companies, leveraging connections from their co-founders&amp;rsquo;&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pulse: Cloudflare takes down half the internet – but shares a great postmortem</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12913/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12913/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare recently experienced a significant outage, impacting thousands of websites, including major platforms like ChatGPT, Dropbox, and Reddit. The outage lasted six hours, highlighting the reliance many services have on Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s content delivery network. In response, Cloudflare released a detailed postmortem to explain the root cause, which stemmed from a database permissions change. Additionally, The Pragmatic Engineer is launching The Pragmatic Summit, aimed at connecting engineers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four years on writing a tech book: pitching to a publisher</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-11972/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 10:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-11972/</guid>
      <description>In 2019, the journey to write &amp;ldquo;The Software Engineer’s Guidebook&amp;rdquo; began, initially expected to take only 6-12 months. 📅 However, it took 4 years to complete. The book has received positive feedback, becoming a #1 bestseller in two Amazon markets and selling around 40,000 copies in 24 months. 🌍📚 Originally aiming for traditional publishing, the author’s experience taught valuable lessons about the publishing landscape and pitching. The article shares insights on the tech book publishing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pulse: Amazon layoffs – AI or economy to blame?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11855/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 16:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11855/</guid>
      <description>Amazon has announced 14,000 job cuts, citing the need for a more agile structure. This follows previous layoffs of 18,000 in January and 9,000 in March 2023. The recent cuts heavily impact software engineers, with 25% of laid-off employees in Washington State falling into this category. Despite strong business results, the company emphasizes the impact of AI on operations, leading to the decision for a leaner workforce. 📉🤖 #AmazonLayoffs #TechNews #JobMarket #AI #BusinessTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comparing interviews at 8 large tech companies</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11566/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11566/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Puneet Patwari recently shared insights from his interview experiences with 8 major tech companies, having received 6 job offers. He accepted a position at Atlassian and highlighted that behavioral interviews played a crucial role in securing offers at the Staff and Principal levels. Notably, the Amazon interview extended to 160 minutes due to engaging discussions, while Atlassian emphasized leadership and values in their evaluation process. Puneet’s experience underscores the importance of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New trend: programming by kicking off parallel AI agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11567/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11567/</guid>
      <description>A new trend is emerging in software development: using multiple AI coding agents simultaneously. 🖥️🤖 Engineers like Sid Bidasaria from Anthropic and Simon Willison are finding that running several agents, such as Claude Code and OpenAI Codex, boosts productivity. They report managing tasks in parallel, despite initial skepticism about the review process. This shift could challenge long-standing software engineering practices and enhance efficiency in coding. #AI #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
