<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pragmatic-Engineer on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/pragmatic-engineer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pragmatic-Engineer on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:00:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/pragmatic-engineer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Comparing interviews at 8 large tech companies</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11566/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:00:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11566/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Puneet Patwari recently shared insights from his interview experiences with 8 major tech companies, having received 6 job offers. He accepted a position at Atlassian and highlighted that behavioral interviews played a crucial role in securing offers at the Staff and Principal levels. Notably, the Amazon interview extended to 160 minutes due to engaging discussions, while Atlassian emphasized leadership and values in their evaluation process. Puneet’s experience underscores the importance of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New trend: programming by kicking off parallel AI agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11567/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11567/</guid>
      <description>A new trend is emerging in software development: using multiple AI coding agents simultaneously. 🖥️🤖 Engineers like Sid Bidasaria from Anthropic and Simon Willison are finding that running several agents, such as Claude Code and OpenAI Codex, boosts productivity. They report managing tasks in parallel, despite initial skepticism about the review process. This shift could challenge long-standing software engineering practices and enhance efficiency in coding. #AI #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
