<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JetBrains-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/jetbrains-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JetBrains-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:08:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/jetbrains-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How We Made Variable Inspections 87 Times Faster for Unreal Engine in Rider</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-26-14859/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-26-14859/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for Unreal Engine users! Rider&amp;rsquo;s debugger has seen a major upgrade with the expression evaluator being rewritten. Variable inspection is now up to 87 times faster on warm runs and 16 times faster on cold runs. Memory usage has also decreased significantly. These improvements are available in Rider 2026.1 EAP 1. Check it out today! #UnrealEngine #Rider #Debugging #GameDevelopment #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the First Speakers Heading to KotlinConf 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-26-14848/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:58:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-26-14848/</guid>
      <description>🌍 KotlinConf&#39;26 is approaching, bringing together developers from around the globe! The first speakers have been announced, showcasing leaders who are shaping the Kotlin ecosystem. The conference will feature inspiring talks, workshops, and networking opportunities. Secure your ticket now and stay tuned for more updates! 🎟️ #KotlinConf #Kotlin #DeveloperCommunity #TechEvents #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Livestream – From Detection to Remediation: Wiz in Your JetBrains IDE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-26-14849/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 09:39:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-26-14849/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join us for an insightful IntelliJ IDEA livestream featuring Daniel Velikanski from Wiz! 🗓️ Date: February 5, 2026 🕒 Time: 3:00–4:00 pm UTC Discover how Wiz&amp;rsquo;s cloud security insights integrate into your JetBrains IDE, enabling you to detect and address security risks as you code. Learn about the Wiz plugin&amp;rsquo;s capabilities, enhancing your coding workflow by surfacing vulnerabilities and misconfigurations directly in the IDE. 🔗 Register now to secure your spot! #CloudSecurity #JetBrains&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Boot Debugging – Now Remote</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-23-14815/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 16:17:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-23-14815/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Spring Debugger, released in May 2025, has surpassed 300,000 downloads. This tool enhances visibility into Spring Boot applications. Now, remote debugging is possible without using debug agents. You can access Spring context information depending on your servlet container—Tomcat provides immediate access, while Jetty and Undertow may introduce a slight delay. To set up remote debugging, simply use an open debug port with standard JVM configurations. #SpringBoot&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ktor 3.4.0 Is Now Available!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-23-14803/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 14:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-23-14803/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ktor 3.4.0 is here! This release focuses on improved stability and performance, addressing various outstanding issues. Key highlights include: - OpenAPI document generation for dynamic endpoint documentation. - Duplex streaming support for OkHttp clients. - Zstd compression support via the new compression module. Explore the full list of updates and consider joining the Ktor Early Access Program to contribute! #Ktor #OpenAPI #SoftwareDevelopment #TechUpdate #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exposed 1.0 Is Now Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-23-14804/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 13:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-23-14804/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Exposed 1.0 is now available, marking a significant milestone for the project and its team. This major release introduces highly requested R2DBC support, performance enhancements, and a stable API with no breaking changes until the next major version. Check out examples with Ktor or Spring, and feel free to join the #exposed channel on Kotlin Slack for questions or feedback. For existing users, a Migration Guide is available to help transition from version 0.61.0 to 1.0&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Codex Is Now Integrated Into JetBrains IDEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14777/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 18:14:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14777/</guid>
      <description>🚀 OpenAI Codex is now integrated into JetBrains IDEs, enhancing your development experience directly within your workspace. You can access Codex using a JetBrains AI subscription, a ChatGPT account, or your OpenAI API key. It&amp;rsquo;s available in the AI chat interface starting from version 2025.3. A limited-time free access promotion begins on January 22. After the promotional period, usage will require AI Credits. #OpenAI #JetBrains #AI #Coding #Development</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3.2 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14762/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:42:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14762/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3.2 is now available! You can easily update from within the IDE, via the Toolbox App, or download it from our website. This update includes fixes for terminal flickering, credential storage issues, and improvements in the Services tool window. Check the full list of enhancements on our site! #IntelliJ #SoftwareUpdate #DevelopmentTools #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper 2026.1 Early Access Program Has Begun</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14763/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:42:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14763/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The ReSharper 2026.1 Early Access Program is now live! This initial build includes updates for C# productivity, new inspections, and enhanced C++ support. Users can experience new features early and contribute to their refinement. Key updates: - Improved code generation for partial types. - New context action for cleaner extension member declarations. - Enhanced inspections for ImmutableArray initialization. Check it out! 🌟 #ReSharper #EarlyAccess #CSharp #Coding #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rider 2026.1 Early Access Program Is Now Open!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14764/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14764/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Early Access Program (EAP) for Rider 2026.1 is now live! You can download the first preview build from the website, the Toolbox App, or via SnapCraft for Linux users. The EAP allows users to preview new features and provide feedback. This version includes enhanced C# support and Azure DevOps integration for cloning repositories directly from Rider. Additionally, a new Package Manager Console supports NuGet&amp;rsquo;s PowerShell commands. Explore the latest features and get involved! #Rider2026&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ROI of Developer Experience: How a Better CI/CD Tool Pays for Itself</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14765/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 13:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-22-14765/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Developer experience (DevEx) is key to engineering performance and business growth. Many teams still rely on outdated CI/CD tools, which can hinder productivity and create inefficiencies. Modern CI/CD platforms enable faster deployment and reduced lead times, driving competitive advantage. Organizations that upgrade their tools see substantial ROI and improved developer satisfaction. Don&amp;rsquo;t let legacy systems hold your team back! #DeveloperExperience #CICD #SoftwareEngineering #Productivity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA Conf 2026: Learn From the People Building the JVM Ecosystem</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-21-14728/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-21-14728/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join us for IntelliJ IDEA Conf 2026, a free online conference for JVM developers! 🗓️ Taking place on March 26–27, this event features live sessions from experts at JetBrains, Oracle, AWS, and more. Topics include Java and Kotlin development, AI in programming, and troubleshooting with IntelliJ IDEA. 💬 Engage directly with speakers through live Q&amp;amp;A and connect with fellow developers. Register now to secure your spot! 🎟️ #IntelliJConf2026 #Java #Kotlin #JVM #DevCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Avoid Common Pitfalls With JPA and Kotlin</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-20-14683/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 17:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-20-14683/</guid>
      <description>Kotlin and Jakarta Persistence (JPA) are powerful for server-side development, but they come with challenges. 📊 Thorben Janssen shares best practices to avoid common pitfalls, focusing on entity class design. Key points include the necessity of no-argument constructors and non-final attributes for effective persistence. ⚙️ Additionally, implementing equals, hashCode, and toString correctly is crucial to prevent unexpected behavior. IntelliJ IDEA 2026.1 will help by detecting issues and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeamCity 2025.11.2 Is Now Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-19-14658/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:32:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-19-14658/</guid>
      <description>🚀 TeamCity 2025.11.2 is now available! This second bug-fix update addresses several issues, including UID changes in Linux agent images and dark theme inconsistencies. 🛠️ All updates enhance performance and security, making it essential not to overlook minor releases. For details on resolved issues and upgrade options, check the TeamCity release notes. #TeamCity #SoftwareUpdate #DevOps #JetBrains #PerformanceImprovement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Platform Debugger Architecture Redesign for Remote Development in 2026.1</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-19-14654/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:15:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-19-14654/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for IntelliJ Platform users! The debugger architecture has been redesigned to enhance remote development. Now, the Debugger tool window operates on the frontend, while the backend manages the active session. This results in improved responsiveness and stability. For plugin developers, be aware that these changes may impact existing plugins. The guide provides essential migration steps for both Local and Remote Development modes. Stay informed and adapt your plugins&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Update your Kotlin projects for Android Gradle Plugin 9.0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14611/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-16-14611/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Android Gradle Plugin 9.0 is here! This update brings two significant changes for Kotlin projects: 1️⃣ Built-in Kotlin support for Android apps, eliminating the need for the Kotlin Android plugin. 2️⃣ A new Android KMP library plugin for Kotlin Multiplatform projects, requiring migration from previous plugins. Ensure you update all related tools and plugins to maintain compatibility. For full details and migration steps, refer to the official documentation. #AndroidDevelopment #Kotlin&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TransformConf: a New Conference on AI in Software Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14558/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:43:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14558/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news for software developers! TransformConf, a new conference on AI in software development, will take place on September 15–16, 2026, in London, UK. AI is increasingly central to development, with 85% of developers using it daily. This event aims to foster practical discussions and insights on integrating AI into workflows. Expect educational talks, peer discussions, and networking opportunities across various topics. Early bird tickets are available now! 🎟️ #TransformConf #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scala 3.8 Support in the Scala Plugin</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14559/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 12:08:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-15-14559/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Scala 3.8 is nearing its release, marking the last major update before the feature freeze. This version introduces new features, while Scala 3.9 will serve as the Long-Term Support release. One highlight is the new &amp;ldquo;into&amp;rdquo; modifier, enhancing type conversion without needing implicit imports. Additionally, Scala 3.8 now requires JDK 17 or higher, with IntelliJ IDEA providing warnings for incompatible versions. Stay tuned for more updates! 📅✨ #Scala #Programming #SoftwareDevelopment #Java #JDK17</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Global Project Configuration: One Place to Manage All Your Qodana Rules</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14506/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 09:06:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-14-14506/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Introducing Global Project Configuration for Qodana users! This new feature simplifies managing linter settings across entire organizations from a single location, eliminating the need for manual updates in every repository. Key benefits include: ✅ Establishing organization-wide standards ✅ Enforcing best practices with project-specific adjustments ✅ Reducing manual overhead for large teams With a dedicated repository for configuration files, teams can easily customize their coding&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insights Into China’s Developer Landscape: Key Trends From the JetBrains Developer Ecosystem Survey 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14450/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 16:11:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14450/</guid>
      <description>🌐 The JetBrains Developer Ecosystem Survey 2025 reveals insights into China&amp;rsquo;s developer landscape. Java remains the dominant language, used by 58.17% of developers, driven by the e-commerce and fintech sectors. In contrast, global usage averages around 27.76%. Emerging languages like Go and TypeScript show a shift towards modern web architectures and improved developer experiences. This survey highlights the unique traits of China&amp;rsquo;s software development scene in a global context&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compose Multiplatform 1.10.0: Unified @Preview, Navigation 3, and Stable Compose Hot Reload</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14451/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14451/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Compose Multiplatform 1.10.0 is now available with key updates. This release includes a unified @Preview annotation, simplifying UI previews across platforms. Additionally, Navigation 3 is now supported on non-Android targets, enhancing navigation management. The stable Compose Hot Reload feature allows for instant UI updates without restarting the app. Explore the full details in the release notes on GitHub! #ComposeMultiplatform #Jetpack #Navigation3&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Journey to Compose Hot Reload 1.0.0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14452/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 14:47:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14452/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Compose Hot Reload has reached stable status with its 1.0.0 release. This tool is designed for ease of use, requiring no configuration from users. It&amp;rsquo;s included with Compose Multiplatform starting from version 1.10. Developers can now make extensive code changes during development with real-time updates while preserving application state. The floating toolbar enhances user experience, providing access to logs and error notifications. #ComposeHotReload #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s Next for CLion: The 2026.1 Roadmap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14437/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 09:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14437/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are on the way for CLion users! The team is currently focused on the upcoming release, v2026.1, set for March. This release will prioritize maintenance and bug fixes rather than new features, focusing on areas like language support, build tools, and debugging improvements. Key enhancements include better coding experiences, support for Clang blocks, and GCC nested functions, along with improved code folding and popup functionalities. Stay tuned for more details! #CLion #IDE&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI Agents in Kotlin – Part 4: Delegation and Sub-Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14438/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 08:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-13-14438/</guid>
      <description>🔍 In the latest installment of &amp;ldquo;Building AI Agents in Kotlin,&amp;rdquo; the focus is on delegation and sub-agents. The article explores how to leverage tracing data to enhance agent performance. It suggests experimenting with a &amp;ldquo;find sub-agent&amp;rdquo; to potentially reduce costs and improve efficiency by limiting context growth. By narrowing the context early in the agent&amp;rsquo;s operation, unnecessary distractions can be minimized. This sub-agent utilizes a simpler model, GPT4.1 Mini, to perform its task&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2025 in Kotlin: Puzzles, Prizes, and Community</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-12-14432/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:33:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-12-14432/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Thank you to all who participated in Advent of Code 2025 in Kotlin! Your enthusiasm and collaboration made this event special. This year featured five days of livestreams, where Sebastian Aigner and guests tackled puzzles and shared Kotlin strategies. If you missed it, recordings are available for viewing. The #advent-of-code channel in Kotlinlang Slack thrived with creative snippets, hints, and encouragement. Congratulations to our nine winners across categories: Fastest to Solve, Random,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Troubleshoot Builds With TeamCity Dashboards</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-12-14420/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 17:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-12-14420/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Struggling with CI/CD issues? You&amp;rsquo;re not alone. Many engineers face challenges with legacy systems like Jenkins. TeamCity offers built-in health signals to help identify root causes of pipeline problems quickly. This reduces time spent debugging and allows for faster fixes. Learn how TeamCity’s monitoring tools can enhance pipeline stability, ensuring high-quality software delivery. 📊🔧 #TeamCity #CICD #SoftwareDevelopment #DevOps #Monitoring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dancing Backwards With Go</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-12-14412/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 12:07:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-12-14412/</guid>
      <description>Explore the unique approach of programming backwards with Go, as shared by John Arundel. He suggests starting with testing a function before writing it, using the example of checking if a slice is sorted. This method emphasizes the importance of test-driven development. Learn more about this technique and the insights from his book, &lt;em&gt;The Power of Go: Tests&lt;/em&gt;. 📚✨ #GoProgramming #TestDrivenDevelopment #CodingTips #Programming #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bringing Real Users Into a Product Team Gathering – A JetBrains Research Story</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-09-14374/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-09-14374/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Last spring, JetBrains introduced a new approach to product development by involving real users in their Junie team gathering. They conducted hands-on workshops, both online and in-person, to bridge the gap between user assumptions and practical realities. This direct interaction allowed team members to gain valuable insights and foster empathy. Challenges included participant recruitment and training team members for live interviews, but the results were promising. Key takeaways&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – January 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14254/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 12:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14254/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Happy New Year! Welcome to the January 2026 edition of Java Annotated Monthly! This month features Neha Sardana, a VP at Morgan Stanley, sharing her insights on Java technology and open-source software. She discusses Project Valhalla, highlighting its potential to enhance Java&amp;rsquo;s performance by treating data more efficiently. This could significantly benefit frameworks and libraries we use daily. For more details, check out the full article! #Java #ProjectValhalla #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotInsights | January 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14226/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 15:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14226/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Did you know? C# now supports default interface methods, allowing method implementation directly in interfaces. Welcome to dotInsights by JetBrains, your source for the latest in .NET and software development! Check out recent articles including updates on .NET MAUI, C# 14 features, and practical guides for developers. Stay informed and keep coding! 💻✨ #DotNet #CSharp #SoftwareDevelopment #JetBrains #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Bug-Fix Releases Are Available for MPS – 2025.2.2, 2025.1.2, 2024.3.5, and 2024.1.6</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-02-14205/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 12:53:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-02-14205/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New updates are here for several MPS versions! The releases include bug-fixes for: - MPS 2025.2.2 - MPS 2025.1.2 - MPS 2024.3.5 - MPS 2024.1.6 You can download the updates and see the full list of fixed issues for each version through the provided links. Stay up to date! 🛠️ #MPSUpdates #JetBrains #SoftwareRelease #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeamCity Pipelines Is Now Part of TeamCity Enterprise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-26-14162/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:19:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-26-14162/</guid>
      <description>🚀 TeamCity Pipelines has officially joined TeamCity Enterprise! After a successful launch in March 2024, the new Pipelines workflow simplifies CI/CD setup with a visual editor and YAML support. Feedback from users has been positive, leading to its integration into TeamCity Enterprise. 📅 In December 2025, TeamCity announced a unified platform, enhancing user experience by combining Pipelines with existing build configurations. Existing Pipelines users have successfully transitioned to TeamCity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ruby Turns 30: A Celebration of Code, Community, and Creativity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-25-14151/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:11:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-25-14151/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Ruby celebrates 30 years of making coding more human and enjoyable! Created by Yukihiro “Matz” Matsumoto, Ruby&amp;rsquo;s design emphasizes intuitive syntax and object-oriented principles. As part of the anniversary, RubyMine is now free for non-commercial use, supporting new developers. Over the years, Ruby has introduced key tools like Bundler, RSpec, and RuboCop, shaping a vibrant community focused on craftsmanship. #Ruby30 #Programming #DeveloperCommunity #RubyMine #CodeCraftsmanship</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Wanted to Ask About Rust – Answered by Herbert Wolverson</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14137/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:36:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14137/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Curious about Rust? Check out insights from the recent JetBrains livestream with expert Herbert Wolverson! He discussed key topics for developers at all levels, including memory management, ownership, and the latest in Rust programming. Wolverson also introduced his new book, &lt;em&gt;Advanced Hands-On Rust&lt;/em&gt;, which dives deeper into concepts like generics and macros. Catch the full livestream replay on JetBrains TV! 📺 #RustLang #Programming #JetBrains #SoftwareDevelopment #Coding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thread Dumps and Project Loom (Virtual Threads)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14128/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 14:14:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14128/</guid>
      <description>Java&amp;rsquo;s virtual threads enhance hardware utilization for parallel I/O-bound operations by mapping multiple concurrent I/O tasks to a single OS thread without blocking. This approach requires minimal code changes, offering a lightweight concurrency model compatible with existing APIs. While this feature benefits developers, it presents challenges for Java tooling. Tools that analyze thread dumps may struggle with the increased volume of data, complicating debugging processes. Thread dumps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code in Rust: Winners and Highlights</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14114/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:29:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14114/</guid>
      <description>🎉 A big thank you to all who participated in Advent of Code 2025 in Rust! It was great to see the community come together to solve puzzles during the holiday season. Before the event, Vitaly Bragilevsky shared tips on using AI effectively in the challenges. Over 12 days, daily features in the RustRover Advent Calendar highlighted useful tools for Rust developers. 🏆 Congratulations to our top winners: 1. Duro 2. JohnX4321 3. MaRcR11 4. Giacomo Stevanato 5. Agnibha Chakraborty Additionally,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Mobile Development Teams Use Kotlin in 2025: Insights From a Certified Trainer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14053/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:44:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14053/</guid>
      <description>🔍 In his latest guest post, José Luis González shares insights on mobile development teams using Kotlin in 2025. He emphasizes the importance of effective error handling, particularly regarding CancellationException, to maintain structured concurrency. 📊 For teams pressed for time, he recommends prioritizing crash-free metrics, ANR rates, and UI performance monitoring using tools like Firebase Crashlytics and JankStats. 🛠️ Performance insights can be gained through Sentry, which helps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top 3 Qodana 2025.3 Release Highlights</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14054/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 14:34:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14054/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in Qodana 2025.3! This release introduces Global Project Configuration, allowing teams to manage linter settings centrally. This simplifies policy enforcement across projects while respecting individual needs. Improvements also include enhanced license auditing for .NET and better monorepository support for Java and Kotlin, streamlining compliance and code quality. For more details, check out the documentation! 📚 #Qodana #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment #TechUpdates&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>First-Class Docker Support: Building and Deploying Containers With TeamCity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14055/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 12:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14055/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker has transformed software development by allowing the packaging of applications into portable containers. However, building and deploying these containers at scale requires a reliable CI/CD system. This article discusses how TeamCity offers built-in Docker support for a seamless pipeline experience. Key features include dedicated Docker build runners, native registry integration, and Kotlin DSL support, making it easier to set up and maintain pipelines compared to Jenkins. #Docker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper and Rider 2025.3.1 Released: Next Edit Suggestions and Other Important Updates</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14016/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14016/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are here! The 2025.3.1 release of ReSharper and Rider consolidates previous fixes and introduces new enhancements. 🔧 Rider now features Next Edit Suggestions (NES), which provide intelligent recommendations as you code, improving efficiency. These suggestions analyze your edits and propose related updates throughout your file. 💡 To enable NES, update JetBrains AI Assistant and check the settings. This feature is available in AI Pro and AI Ultimate plans. #JetBrains #Rider&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Edit Suggestions: Now Generally Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14017/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for JetBrains users! The next edit suggestions feature is now available in all JetBrains IDEs for AI Pro, AI Ultimate, and AI Enterprise subscribers. This tool offers native diff suggestions directly in your editor, optimizing latency and ensuring reliability without consuming your AI quota. Next edit suggestions appear as you code, modifying existing code and enhancing your workflow. Users can review changes in a small diff view, allowing for a smooth coding experience&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring Your Own Key (BYOK) Is Now Live in JetBrains IDEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:59:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14018/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! JetBrains IDEs now support Bring Your Own Key (BYOK) for AI chat and agents like Junie and Claude. This feature allows you to integrate your own API keys from providers such as Anthropic and OpenAI, offering flexibility and transparency without vendor lock-in. Getting started is easy: install the JetBrains AI Assistant plugin, select your provider, and enter your API key. JetBrains is also expanding BYOK to include more providers like Google Gemini and Azure&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3.1 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14019/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3.1 is now available! This update includes several important fixes. You can update directly in the IDE, through the Toolbox App, or download it from the website. Key improvements include: - Enhanced support for Maven projects. - New option to disable force-push warnings in Version Control settings. - Fixed issues with query result tabs and debugging in WSL. For a full list of fixes, check the release notes. #IntelliJIDEA #SoftwareUpdate #Coding #DeveloperTools #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Query Consoles Are Coming Back</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:35:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14020/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for DataGrip Users! 🚨 Following feedback on the 2025.3 release, we will revert the changes to query consoles and files. The upcoming 2025.3.1 release will restore query consoles as the default workflow. If you updated to 2025.3, we recommend upgrading to 2025.3.1 to minimize disruption. For those who haven’t updated, your workflow remains unchanged. We appreciate your patience and are committed to improving the experience moving forward. #DataGrip #DatabaseTools&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Successfully Adopting Kotlin in a Java-Dominated Environment</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14000/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 15:04:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14000/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Adopting Kotlin in a Java-centric environment is a gradual process, focusing on people, timing, and trust. Over four weeks, a series of articles by Urs Peter explored key aspects of this migration. The ultimate guide ties these insights together, offering practical steps for tech teams. 📁 It covers a five-part journey, from starting with Kotlin in existing projects to evaluating its use in production and encouraging team buy-in. For detailed guidance, check out the full Kotlin Adoption&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Programming Courses in 2025: New and Favorite Picks on JetBrains Academy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-13994/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-13994/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from JetBrains Academy! Their annual roundup highlights both popular courses and new offerings for 2025. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to enhance your programming skills, this overview is a great place to start. Key courses include: ❤️ &lt;strong&gt;100 Days of Code – The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp&lt;/strong&gt;: Perfect for motivated learners wanting hands-on experience with real projects. ❤️ &lt;strong&gt;Introduction to Python&lt;/strong&gt;: Ideal for beginners to start coding with essential concepts. ❤️ &lt;strong&gt;AtomicKotlin&lt;/strong&gt;: Aimed&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When AI Amplifies Your Bad (and Good) Habits</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13938/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13938/</guid>
      <description>AI acts as a megaphone, amplifying existing habits in workflows. Good practices will enhance productivity, while poor habits will lead to confusion. 🛠️ A study shows firms with disciplined management practices see better long-term returns with AI adoption. 📈 Clear structure and documentation are essential for AI to function effectively. Discipline in coding and project management helps AI contribute positively, while lack of structure may amplify weaknesses. #AI #Productivity #BestPractices&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPS 2025.3 Has Been Released!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13928/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 11:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13928/</guid>
      <description>🚀 MPS 2025.3 has been released with significant updates! Key changes include a complete overhaul of the JavaDoc language, which now uses jetbrains.mps.lang.text for improved editing. This enhances consistency with other MPS languages and supports features like text styling and multi-line descriptions. New functionalities also allow for keyboard actions in the Logical view and visually distinct TextIcon variants for light and dark themes. Explore all updates and improvements in generator plans&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Industry Leaders on the KotlinConf’25 Stage: What Global Brands Built With Kotlin</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13929/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 10:24:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13929/</guid>
      <description>🌍 KotlinConf 2025 showcased how global brands like Meta, AWS, Duolingo, and Uber utilize Kotlin for real-world engineering challenges. Developers shared insights on navigation, performance, and cross-platform architecture. Key talks included AWS&amp;rsquo;s massive multiplatform project, Duolingo&amp;rsquo;s productivity with Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP), and Google Workspace&amp;rsquo;s deployment experiences. Join KotlinConf 2026 to connect with industry leaders! #KotlinConf #Kotlin #SoftwareEngineering #TechCommunity #KMP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataGrip turns 10. Hidden gems of DataGrip.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13663/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 18:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13663/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Celebrating 10 years of DataGrip! On December 16, 2016, the first version of DataGrip was released, marking a significant milestone in database IDE development. Originally codenamed 0xdbe, the tool has evolved considerably since then. To celebrate, the team shared 10 hidden features of DataGrip that many may not know about, including word completion from open files and a Recent Locations feature for quick access to edits. Thank you to our users for your support throughout the years!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin 2.3.0 Released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13664/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 16:10:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13664/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kotlin 2.3.0 has been released! This version introduces new language features, stable defaults, and improved tooling, alongside performance enhancements across various platforms. Key updates include better Java 25 support, faster build times for Kotlin/Native, and new features in Kotlin/JS. For installation, update your build scripts or download the command-line compiler from GitHub. Stay informed about Kotlin updates! #Kotlin #Programming #SoftwareDevelopment #TechUpdate #Kotlin2.3</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust vs C&#43;&#43;: competition or evolution in systems programming for 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13665/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 12:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13665/</guid>
      <description>C and C++ have long been foundational in software development, providing low-level control over memory and performance. However, the rise of Rust presents a new option for systems programming. Rust emphasizes memory safety and modern tooling, addressing challenges found in C++. Its design enforces safety through ownership and borrowing, reducing runtime bugs. While both languages show comparable performance in benchmarks, the choice between C++ and Rust ultimately depends on project needs and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agents, Protocols, and Why We’re Not Playing Favorites</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13666/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 10:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13666/</guid>
      <description>JetBrains clarifies its stance on AI agents amid recent developments. 🤖 With the introduction of AgentHQ by GitHub, some users wondered if support for ACP (Agent Client Protocol) would diminish. JetBrains confirms it will not favor any specific protocol. ACP is an open standard for various IDEs to interact with AI agents, while AgentHQ is a GitHub-centric management system. JetBrains remains committed to supporting multiple protocols and ensuring agent portability. For agent builders, the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeamCity 2025.11.1 Is Now Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13667/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 15:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13667/</guid>
      <description>🚀 TeamCity 2025.11.1 is now available! This update addresses several bugs, including issues with pull request builds, branch selections, accessibility for color vision impairments, and missing Visual Studio tools in .NET pipeline runners. Performance and security enhancements are also included, making prompt installation advisable. For upgrade options, you can use the automatic update, download from the JetBrains website, or pull the updated Docker image. For more details, refer to the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Tame Your Flaky Tests in TeamCity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13668/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 12:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13668/</guid>
      <description>Flaky tests can disrupt your CI pipeline, leading to confusion and wasted time. 🕒 This article by Satish Subrahmanya explains how TeamCity helps identify and manage flaky tests. It highlights common causes like race conditions, test dependencies, external services, and resource contention. Learn to streamline your testing process and improve team efficiency! 🚀 #SoftwareDevelopment #ContinuousIntegration #TeamCity #FlakyTests #DevOps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyCharm 2025.3 – Unified IDE, Jupyter notebooks in remote development, uv as default, and more</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13559/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 16:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13559/</guid>
      <description>🚀 PyCharm 2025.3 is now available! This release brings together Community users into a unified IDE. 📚 Jupyter notebooks are fully supported for remote development, allowing you to edit and run them directly on remote machines. 🔧 The new version also features uv as the default environment manager and proactive data exploration for pandas DataFrames to enhance your workflow. Learn more about these updates! #PyCharm #PythonIDE #JupyterNotebooks #DataScience #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Fleet</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13547/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 14:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13547/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains has announced significant changes regarding Fleet, its experimental IDE. Starting December 22, 2025, Fleet will no longer be available for download. Despite initial goals, it became clear that having two overlapping IDE families caused confusion among users. Instead of competing with existing IntelliJ-based IDEs, JetBrains is pivoting to focus on agentic development workflows. This new direction aims to enhance productivity by streamlining task management through AI. Stay tuned&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhpStorm 2025.3 Is Now Out</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13560/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 13:35:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13560/</guid>
      <description>🚀 PhpStorm 2025.3 has launched! This update features native Claude Agent integration, enhanced Laravel support, and compatibility with PHP 8.5. Key improvements include better generics and a new Islands theme. You can explore new features by adjusting your project language level to PHP 8.5. For more details, download PhpStorm 2025.3 today! #PhpStorm #PHP8 #WebDevelopment #SoftwareUpdate #Coding 🖥️✨</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Made Simple: A Guide for JVM Developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13548/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 13:28:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13548/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of Kubernetes for JVM developers! 🚀 This guide simplifies the deployment of Kotlin and Java Spring Boot apps on Kubernetes. It covers essential concepts like Pods, Deployments, and Services, making it easier to manage microservices. Prerequisites include Docker and Minikube for a smooth setup. Dive into best practices and enhance your application management skills! #Kubernetes #JVM #Microservices #SpringBoot #TechGuide</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junie Now Integrated Into the AI Chat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13535/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13535/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from JetBrains! Junie, the coding agent, is now integrated into the AI chat, simplifying user experience by merging two separate interfaces. Starting today, users can select Junie directly within the AI chat in Beta. The goal is to unify the experience, ensuring a seamless transition without losing functionality. 🔍 Your feedback is crucial during this phase! Try out the new setup and share your thoughts to help improve the tool further. For those who prefer a gradual change,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoLand 2025.3 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13536/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13536/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GoLand 2025.3 has been released with powerful upgrades for cleaner coding! Key features include on-the-fly resource leak detection, bundled Terraform support, and improvements to single-file editing. The IDE also sees performance boosts for a smoother experience. Claude Agent is now integrated, enhancing your development workflow. Explore the new features and improve your coding efficiency! #GoLand #SoftwareDevelopment #Coding #Terraform #IDE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLion 2025.3 Is Here, and It’s Epic: Faster Language Engine, Unique Constexpr Debugger, DAP Support, and Much More</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13537/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:25:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13537/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! CLion 2025.3 has launched with significant updates. This version introduces the CLion Nova language engine, prioritizing speed and precision for C and C++ support. It offers enhanced performance, making coding faster and more efficient. Key features include a unique Constexpr Debugger for compile-time evaluations and expanded debugger options with DAP support. For a fresh look, the new Islands theme is now the default. Download CLion 2025.3 via the Toolbox App&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RubyMine 2025.3: Multi-Agent AI Chat, Rails-Aware MCP Server, Faster Multi-Module Projects Startup, and More</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13538/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13538/</guid>
      <description>🚀 RubyMine 2025.3 has been released with exciting new features! The update introduces multi-agent AI support with Junie and the new Claude Agent, enhancing your coding workflow. You can now switch between agents for tailored assistance in tasks like code generation and debugging. 💻 Additionally, RubyMine offers improved AI quota tracking, smarter autocomplete for constants, accurate type navigation for global variables, and full Unicode regex support. Get the latest build from our website or&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 Is Out Now!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13539/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:17:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13539/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 is now live! This update focuses on enhancing productivity with new features like command completion and improvements to the Spring Debugger. It also introduces support for the latest technologies, including Java 25 and Spring Boot 4. For more details, check the What’s New page or watch the roundtable discussion. Your feedback is important to us! #IntelliJIDEA #JavaDevelopment #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ Scala Plugin 2025.3 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13540/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 10:59:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13540/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in the IntelliJ Scala Plugin 2025.3! Scala 3.8 introduces key changes like a new &amp;lsquo;into&amp;rsquo; modifier, a compiled standard library, and an updated minimum JDK requirement of 17. These updates pave the way for upcoming Scala 3.9 LTS. Additionally, the plugin now supports Structural Search and Replace, enhancing code pattern management. Build tool improvements and various bug fixes enhance performance and navigation. #Scala #IntelliJ #SoftwareDevelopment #Coding #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unified IntelliJ IDEA: More Free Features, a Better Experience, Smoother Flow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13541/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 10:45:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13541/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news for developers! IntelliJ IDEA has unified its offerings into a single product starting with version 2025.3. Now, users can access all core and extended features without choosing between editions. The Community Edition remains free for both commercial and non-commercial use, with additional free features like enhanced syntax highlighting and database support. Existing Ultimate users will transition to a subscription model automatically, ensuring continued access to all tools&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet the Islands Theme – The New Default Look for JetBrains IDEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13542/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 09:53:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13542/</guid>
      <description>🌊✨ The Islands theme is now the default look for JetBrains IDEs starting with version 2025.3. This update enhances the user experience with a focus on comfort and clarity. The theme features a clean layout with rounded corners, making the interface easier on the eyes. Improvements in tab recognition allow for quicker navigation between files. Additionally, organized visual spaces help maintain focus while working. Explore the new look and adjust settings for an even clearer experience!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s Fixed in IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13543/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 09:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13543/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3! This release addresses over 800 bug reports and usability issues, enhancing the developer experience, Spring support, build tools, and version control. Key highlights include a unified distribution for better quality, a smaller installation size, and improved workflows with indexing. Accessibility improvements have also been implemented to enhance usability. For the complete list of updates, check the release notes! 📚 #IntelliJIDEA #SoftwareUpdate&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebStorm 2025.3: Enhanced Monorepo Support, Framework Improvements, Vitest 4 Support, Multiple Agents in AI Assistant, Remote Debugging, and More</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13533/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 08:28:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13533/</guid>
      <description>🌟 WebStorm 2025.3 is out now! This update features enhanced TypeScript support with a service-powered type engine for better performance. It also offers improved module resolution and monorepo support, along with upgraded AI Assistant capabilities. Remote debugging is now available for JavaScript projects in WSL, Docker, and dev containers. This release supports Vitest 4, ensuring smooth test execution. To update, use the Toolbox App or download directly from the website. Happy coding! 💻✨&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring your own AI agent to JetBrains IDEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13485/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 12:40:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13485/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from JetBrains! We’re introducing the Agent Client Protocol (ACP) to enhance integration between IDEs and AI agents. This new standard streamlines communication, allowing users to select any compatible agent easily. The beta version is now available in our latest IDE release. Join us in exploring this innovative feature! For more details, check out the documentation. #JetBrains #AI #SoftwareDevelopment #IDE #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPS 2025.3 Release Candidate Is Ready!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13486/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 12:37:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13486/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Release Candidate for MPS 2025.3 is now available for download! You can explore the new features by checking the updates from the previous EAP 1 and EAP 2 builds. For details on fixed issues, refer to the provided link. Download now to stay ahead! #MPS2025 #JetBrains #SoftwareRelease #DownloadNow #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Manage Configuration Drift in Your Jenkins Environment</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13487/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 12:31:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13487/</guid>
      <description>Managing configuration drift in Jenkins is crucial for maintaining a reliable CI/CD environment. 🛠️ Configuration drift occurs when changes made through the Jenkins UI aren&amp;rsquo;t reflected in the code, leading to inconsistencies across environments. This can create issues with builds, compliance, and disaster recovery. 📉 To address this, the article outlines steps like establishing a baseline, codifying configurations, enforcing access controls, and continuous monitoring. By following these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – December 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13488/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 10:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13488/</guid>
      <description>📅 December 2025 brings key updates in the Java ecosystem! Java has started announcing JEPs for the upcoming release. Meanwhile, Spring has launched Spring Framework 7 and Spring Boot 4, offering new features like API versioning and modularization. Guest author Siva Katamreddy shares valuable resources from the developer community. Explore the latest articles, videos, and podcasts on Java, Kotlin, Spring, and AI! #Java #SpringFramework #SoftwareDevelopment #TechNews #DeveloperCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Deprecation of K1 Mode</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13425/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 09:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13425/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for IntelliJ IDEA users! With the 2025.3 release, K1 mode is officially deprecated as we focus on K2 mode. This transition improves performance, stability, and future Kotlin support. Adoption rates are high, with 98.6% of Ultimate and 99.5% of Community Edition users already using K2 mode. For those still on K1, options remain available for re-enabling. Read more about K2 mode&amp;rsquo;s development and performance improvements in our latest blog. #IntelliJ #Kotlin #K2Mode&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ask Us Anything During JetBrains AMA Week</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13372/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 11:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13372/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join JetBrains for AMA Week on Reddit from December 9–12! Our product teams will engage directly with developers to discuss your experiences with our tools. This is a great opportunity to share your feedback and influence future developments. Check the schedule for session times and participate! 💬 #JetBrains #AMAWeek #DeveloperCommunity #FeedbackMatters</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Stories Of Developers Using JetBrains Rider to Create, Collaborate, and Have Fun</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13373/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 09:33:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13373/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains Rider has introduced a free non-commercial license, encouraging developers to explore coding without financial constraints. Recently, they shared inspiring stories from users who embraced this opportunity. From a cloud architect creating a digital board game to a self-taught programmer developing a productivity app, curiosity drives innovation. These narratives highlight the joy of coding beyond commerce. #JetBrains #CodingCommunity #CuriosityDriven #DeveloperStories&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok Models Come to the AI Chat in JetBrains IDEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13267/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 15:30:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13267/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for JetBrains users! The AI chat feature now includes xAI’s Grok family of LLMs: Grok 4, Grok 4.1 Fast, Grok 4.1 Fast (Non-Reasoning), and Grok Code Fast 1. This expansion offers more flexibility in choosing the model that suits your workflow. To try the Grok models, ensure you have an active JetBrains AI subscription. Start a free trial from your IDE, select a Grok model in the AI chat, and interact with it to enhance your coding experience. #JetBrains #AI #GrokModels #Coding&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataGrip 2025.3: Migration From Consoles to Query Files, Connection to Cloud Providers, Introspection Levels for Amazon Redshift, and More!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13224/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 14:47:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13224/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DataGrip 2025.3 is now available! This update introduces several key features aimed at enhancing user experience. 🔄 The transition from query consoles to query files is a significant change. Users can now migrate SQL files easily into their IDE projects, with options for customization. 🌐 Connectivity improvements allow users to link their AWS, Google Cloud, or Azure accounts, facilitating database browsing and source creation. 📂 Additionally, Amazon Redshift users benefit from new&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotInsights | December 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13225/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 13:38:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13225/</guid>
      <description>Did you know that calling GC.Collect() explicitly can force the garbage collector to reclaim memory? While it may seem useful, it&amp;rsquo;s generally discouraged in most applications. The garbage collector is optimized to run automatically, and forcing it can lead to performance issues. Welcome to dotInsights by JetBrains! This newsletter shares the latest in .NET and software development. Check out the latest articles, including updates on .NET 10 and new C# 14 features! 🔗 #DotNet&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Achieve Significant Build Performance Gains With TeamCity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13215/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 10:34:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13215/</guid>
      <description>Long build times can hinder developer productivity and increase release cycle times. The article by Mdu Sibisi highlights the importance of optimizing CI/CD pipelines for better performance. 🚀 It outlines a three-phase approach: 1️⃣ Identify performance bottlenecks. 2️⃣ Optimize with effective solutions. 3️⃣ Continuously improve to prevent future issues. Using data-driven strategies ensures teams adopt the right tools effectively. 📊 #DevOps #CICD #Productivity #TeamCity #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Livestream: Engineers Talk About Spring Boot 4, Life, and Other Stuff</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13159/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 14:22:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13159/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join us for an insightful livestream featuring the Spring team and Evgeny Borisov! 🗓️ Date: December 11, 2025 🕓 Time: 4:00–5:00 pm UTC We&amp;rsquo;ll dive into the latest updates in Spring Boot 4, explore how they enhance developer productivity, and discuss migration considerations. The session will also cover community insights and more. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss this opportunity to learn from the experts! #SpringBoot #JavaDevelopment #IntelliJIDEA #Livestream #TechTalks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cutting Through the Noise: Smarter Context Management for LLM-Powered Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13160/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 13:31:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13160/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The article discusses the challenges of managing context in software engineering (SE) agents powered by LLMs. As agents generate outputs, their context grows, leading to excessive and costly memory logs. 📉 Large contexts can hinder performance and increase expenses without delivering better results. Current research mainly focuses on enhancing planning capabilities but lacks efficiency-based context management. 📊 Researchers have proposed two main approaches: observation masking and LLM&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advent of Code 2025: A Kotlin Playground</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13123/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 15:18:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13123/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Join us for Advent of Code 2025 from December 1–5! Participate in five days of Kotlin livestreams featuring experts and special guests. Solve puzzles, learn tips, and engage with the Kotlin community in Slack. 🛠️ Climb the leaderboards for a chance to win prizes and share your solutions on GitHub. Happy coding! 🚀 #AdventOfCode #Kotlin #CodingCommunity #Programming #LiveStream</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Advent of Code in Rust, With Just Enough AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13124/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 14:23:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13124/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited about solving Advent of Code puzzles using Rust? A recent blog post revisits the importance of limiting AI use during problem-solving. The creator of Advent of Code, Eric Wastl, suggests that relying on AI may hinder personal growth in coding skills. However, the article argues for using AI as a tool to enhance learning, not as a replacement for solving puzzles. Join the Advent of Code 2025 contest and ensure your GitHub profile is updated for prize eligibility! 🎁 #AdventOfCode&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 Release Candidate Is Here</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13125/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 14:04:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-28-13125/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Release Candidate for IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 is now available! The Early Access Program has officially closed. A big thank you to all who provided feedback during this cycle—it has greatly influenced the final release. Key highlights include productivity enhancements, expanded support for new technologies, and AI upgrades. Stay tuned for more details on features and improvements in the upcoming full release! #IntelliJ #IDE #SoftwareDevelopment #ReleaseCandidate #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I Went to BazelCon 2025 – Here’s Everything You Need to Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13089/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 14:54:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13089/</guid>
      <description>🎉 BazelCon 2025 took place at the Omni Atlanta Hotel, celebrating Bazel&amp;rsquo;s tenth anniversary. The event coincided with KubeCon, creating a vibrant atmosphere filled with tech discussions. JetBrains participated, providing insights on the Bazel for CLion plugin, gathering valuable user feedback. Key announcements included the deprecation of the WORKSPACE file and the introduction of Bzlmod as the default. Bazel 9 will disable autoloads, requiring explicit load statements in BUILD files for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s New in TeamCity 2025.11: AI Assistant, New Pipeline Features, Enhanced Server Encryption Settings, and More.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13090/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 14:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13090/</guid>
      <description>🚀 TeamCity 2025.11 is here with exciting new features! The release introduces an AI Assistant for Enterprise users, providing context-aware support to enhance CI/CD workflows. New build steps streamline pipeline configuration, and project-level Docker and NPM connections simplify resource management. Enhanced actions for builds and tests improve collaboration. #TeamCity #CICD #SoftwareDevelopment #AI #DevOps</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper and Rider 2025.3.0.3: A Fresh Set of Updates Released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13091/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 13:40:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13091/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for ReSharper and Rider 2025.3.0.3 are here! ReSharper now recognizes extension methods from source-only NuGet packages, enhancing editor functionality. 🛠️ Rider includes several fixes, such as restored automatic package restore, improved .NET MAUI project support, and faster Solution-Wide Analysis. 🔍 Check out the complete list of updates in the issue tracker. #ReSharper #Rider #SoftwareUpdates #DevTools #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One Could Simply Add Nullability Check Support… Without Even Noticing It</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13092/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13092/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JSpecify adoption is on the rise! With automatic nullability support in popular frameworks like Spring Boot and JUnit, developers can upgrade their projects without hassle. IntelliJ IDEA will analyze your code using JSpecify, enhancing data-flow analysis and nullability checks. However, migrating your own code can be challenging. The new typed annotation model requires comprehensive re-annotations, which may lead to inconsistencies if not handled carefully. Learn more about JSpecify and its&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Master Spring Data AOT in IntelliJ IDEA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13069/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 14:50:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13069/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Spring Data now supports Ahead-of-Time (AOT) processing, enhancing repository infrastructure. This update allows method queries to be pre-generated during the build process, reducing runtime delays. 🔍 With IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3, developers can easily inspect and debug AOT-generated classes, improving the overall development experience. 📚 For detailed guidance, refer to the official documentation for Gradle and Maven setup. #SpringData #IntelliJ #AOT #SoftwareDevelopment #ProgrammingTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kodee’s Kotlin Roundup: Too Many News to Keep Quiet About</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13065/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 11:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13065/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting Kotlin updates are here! Kotlin 2.3.0-RC has been released, showcasing new features and improvements as we approach the stable version. The Kotlin Multiplatform documentation has a fresh look and is now hosted on kotlinlang.org, making navigation easier. Don’t miss the Reddit AMA with the Kotlin team, where you can ask your burning questions! 🔥 #Kotlin #Programming #TechNews #GoogleSummerOfCode #AMA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI Agents in Kotlin – Part 2: A Deeper Dive Into Tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13063/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 08:23:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13063/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of AI agents with Kotlin! 🚀 In the latest article, we explore extending the capabilities of a basic coding agent using the Koog framework. This includes building an ExecuteShellCommandTool, allowing the agent to run code and learn from real-time feedback. We also discuss the anatomy of a Koog tool and essential safety considerations when enabling command-line execution. Understanding these components is crucial for creating effective tools. #Kotlin #AI #KoogFramework&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open-source IntelliJ IDEA: A Simpler Way to Build and Contribute to the Community</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13033/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 12:07:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13033/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for the IntelliJ IDEA community! The source code of IntelliJ IDEA has been open for over 15 years, making it a valuable resource for developers. Now, the process of exploring and contributing has been simplified. 🔧 With new CI/CD pipelines using GitHub Actions, you can build your own version effortlessly. Plus, open-source builds are now available directly on GitHub, eliminating the need for complex setups. Join the community, contribute, and collaborate to enhance your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate KMP Watchlist: Level Up Your Skills in 10 Talks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12999/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 16:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12999/</guid>
      <description>Unlock your potential with the Top 10 KotlinConf talks! 🚀 Week 3 of KMP Level Up features key insights from industry leaders. Learn from real-world case studies, including how Duolingo boosts productivity and McDonald&amp;rsquo;s innovates navigation with KMP. Gain practical skills and inspiration for your projects. 🛠️ Explore the latest in Kotlin Multiplatform and elevate your development journey! #KotlinConf #KMP #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTalks #Learning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amper Update, November 2025 – Extensibility Preview</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12985/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:47:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12985/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amper 0.9.0 has launched, introducing the first version of the extensibility prototype! This release supports custom tasks via local plugins, enhancing user experience for unique project needs. Use IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 Beta or newer for the latest features. 📄 Check out the revamped Amper website for improved documentation and navigation at &lt;a href=&#34;https://amper.org&#34;&gt;https://amper.org&lt;/a&gt;. Explore the extensibility preview and start building your own plugins today! #AmperUpdate #SoftwareDevelopment #Extensibility&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Kotlin Adoption Across Your Organization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12980/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 11:42:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12980/</guid>
      <description>📈 Scaling Kotlin adoption in your organization involves strategic planning. In the latest post by Urs Peter, key strategies are outlined for managing Java and Kotlin cohabitation. 1️⃣ End-of-life applications: No migration needed. 2️⃣ New systems: Start with Kotlin. 3️⃣ Active applications: Migrate alongside new features for added value. Learn how to navigate these challenges effectively. #Kotlin #SoftwareDevelopment #TechStrategy #Java #CodeMigration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Boot 4: Leaner, Safer Apps and a New Kotlin Baseline</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12916/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 20:11:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12916/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Spring Boot 4.0 has officially launched, enhancing the development experience with cleaner modularization and improved observability through Micrometer. This release integrates Kotlin 2.2 as the official baseline, supporting native nullability checks with JSpecify annotations. This ensures safer code practices for developers. Additionally, the new API versioning mechanism simplifies the process for Kotlin users. #SpringBoot #Kotlin #JavaDevelopment #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2.5 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12917/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12917/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2.5 has been released! You can update directly from the IDE, the Toolbox App, or download it from the website. Ubuntu users can also use snaps for the update. Key updates include: - Improved processing of API calls with Docker Engine v29. - Enhanced Gradle 9.x support for Spring Boot projects. - Fixed an issue causing hangs with specific JSON structures. - GitLab plugin now supports large pipeline IDs. For more details, check the release notes. Happy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Updates and Fixes for ReSharper and Rider 2025.3</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12896/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 16:04:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12896/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Updates for ReSharper and Rider 2025.3 are here! The latest versions, ReSharper 2025.3.0.2 and Rider 2025.3.0.2, include important fixes. Key improvements for ReSharper include resolving issues with MSTest v4, false positive warnings, and correct functioning of external services in multiple Visual Studio instances. Rider updates ensure proper authentication for Azure DevOps NuGet feeds and correct usage of the user’s installed .NET SDK. For more details, check the issue tracker. #ReSharper&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn AI-Assisted Programming With Junie: Free Courses From JetBrains Academy and Nebius</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12888/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 12:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12888/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Unlock your potential in AI-assisted programming with JetBrains Academy! JetBrains, a leader in developer tools, has partnered with Nebius to offer free courses featuring Junie, their AI coding agent. Learn to build real projects and understand how AI can enhance your workflow in two courses: &amp;ldquo;Coding With Junie&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;AI Agents as Your Team.&amp;rdquo; Start your journey into the future of software development today! 🌟 #JetBrains #AIProgramming #LearnCoding #TechEducation #Nebius</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini 3 Pro Is Now Available in JetBrains IDEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12762/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12762/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The Gemini 3 Pro AI model from Google is now integrated into JetBrains IDEs. It enhances AI Chat and Junie, offering improved reasoning, instruction-following, and seamless workflow integration. Key features include: - Adapting to your codebase and style 🖥️ - Precise understanding of complex prompts 📄 - Major advancements in frontend development 🎨 To experience Gemini 3 Pro, activate it through your JetBrains AI subscription. #JetBrains #Gemini3Pro #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Second Release of MPS 2025.3 Early Access Program</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12763/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12763/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The second Early Access Program release for MPS 2025.3 is now available for download. This update features significant improvements, including a complete overhaul of the JavaDoc language. 🔧 Key enhancements include: - Migration to jetbrains.mps.lang.text for better consistency - Enhanced copy/paste functionality across various languages - New styling options for text, now generating HTML tags Additionally, a new &amp;ldquo;Paste as JavaDoc&amp;rdquo; action allows seamless&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helping Decision‑Makers Say Yes to Kotlin</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12752/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:11:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12752/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Discover how to effectively advocate for Kotlin adoption in your organization! Urs Peter, a Senior Software Engineer and Kotlin Trainer, shares insights on building a strong business case for Kotlin. With 2.5 million developers using Kotlin and a strategic partnership with Spring Boot, its market momentum is undeniable. Key benefits include reduced code complexity, improved maintainability, and fewer bugs, leading to greater productivity and faster time-to-market. #Kotlin&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Source in Focus: Projects We’re Proud to Support</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12753/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 12:07:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12753/</guid>
      <description>At JetBrains, we celebrate the growth of the developer community by supporting impactful open-source projects. 🚀 We highlight five key projects that enhance developer experiences across various ecosystems, including Ratatui and Django. Each project is designed to improve productivity and make software development more enjoyable. 🛠️ Ratatui elevates terminal UIs, while Django streamlines web development with built-in solutions. Both frameworks focus on efficiency and community-driven&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Database Features in Rider</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12208/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 14:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12208/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Rider enhances your development experience with strong database support, powered by DataGrip! You can now create Database Projects (.sqlproj) easily, targeting various database environments like PostgreSQL, MySQL, and even NoSQL options like MongoDB. Manage your database objects visually or through SQL scripts, benefiting from features like code completion and syntax highlighting. #DatabaseDevelopment #Rider #DataGrip #SQL #NoSQL</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Prepare for the Future of Programming</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12199/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 11:17:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12199/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The future of programming is uncertain, with many voices suggesting varying paths. Should you start a startup, return to school, or focus on coding? The article emphasizes a healthy skepticism towards current trends, including prompt engineering. It stresses the importance of understanding your educational context and adapting to change. Key questions remain about what skills will truly matter in the evolving landscape of AI and programming. For those navigating this shift, self-awareness&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mark Your Calendars! Qodana Events in November</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 10:29:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12200/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Mark your calendars for November! The JetBrains Qodana team is hosting events focused on secure workflows and high-quality code. 📅 On November 18, Grigorii Liullin will discuss integrating security into IDEs in JRush Episode 6. 📅 Join the Qodana livestream on November 19 to explore modern enterprise practices for building secure code. 📅 Lastly, don’t miss the meetup in Utrecht on November 26, centered around AI applications. #JetBrains #Qodana #SoftwareDevelopment #SecureCode #AIApplications</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Diffusion Models Could Change Developer Workflows in 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12198/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 07:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12198/</guid>
      <description>Developers often spend more time editing and debugging than writing new code. This non-linear process involves revisiting and refining code multiple times. Diffusion models, especially diffusion large language models (d-LLMs), are changing this workflow. Unlike traditional models, d-LLMs can consider both past and future context, reflecting how developers think and work. This design enhances reasoning, allowing for better handling of complex code structures and dependencies. The flexibility&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Is Heading to VSLive! Orlando</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-15-12190/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 01:33:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-15-12190/</guid>
      <description>📢 JetBrains is heading to Visual Studio Live! in Orlando next week! 🎉 Join us at booth #118 in the expo area to explore our .NET tools, including live demos of ReSharper and Rider. Learn about our support for .NET 10 and Visual Studio 2026. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the chance to ask questions, discuss product roadmaps, and grab some JetBrains swag! We will also have special offers for booth visitors. #JetBrains #VSLive #dotNET #OrlandoEvents #TechCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 💚 Spring 7</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12167/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 15:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12167/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Spring Framework 7 has been released, simplifying application building and addressing long-term development challenges. IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 offers seamless integration with this release, making it easier to implement new features, including a built-in API versioning mechanism. This versioning allows for smoother handling of API changes directly in your code. IntelliJ IDEA even checks for proper configuration and adherence to SemVer rules. Explore how these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Summer of Code 2025: What Our Contributors Built</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12037/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 20:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12037/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Congratulations to the contributors and mentors of Google Summer of Code 2025! This year&amp;rsquo;s projects have significantly impacted the Kotlin ecosystem. 🔍 Highlights include the IntelliJ Platform Gradle Plugin, which improved reporting and build speeds, and enhancements to Configuration Cache for faster Gradle builds. Many contributors shared their experiences, emphasizing the value of mentorship and collaboration in their growth. 🌟 Thank you for your dedication and hard work! #GSoC2025&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Developers Really Mean by “Bad Code”</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12038/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:43:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12038/</guid>
      <description>Understanding &amp;ldquo;bad code&amp;rdquo; is essential for developers and project managers. 🖥️ This term encompasses various coding issues like bugs, security vulnerabilities, and low readability, which can hinder maintenance and scalability. Factors like confusing variable names and lack of documentation contribute to a codebase being labeled as &amp;ldquo;bad.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s important to recognize that the definition of bad code can vary based on context. Key indicators include difficulty in understanding, maintenance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf 2025 Recordings Are Now Live</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12039/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 17:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12039/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf 2025 took place on November 5, focusing on plugin development for JetBrains IDEs. 🎥 If you missed it, recordings of all sessions are now available on YouTube. The event gathered over 1,000 viewers and featured 10 speakers sharing insights on various topics, including plugin creation and AI-powered tools. 🙏 A huge thank you to all participants and speakers for making this event successful! #JetBrains #PluginDevelopment #TechConference #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# 14 Language Features in ReSharper and Rider 2025.3</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12040/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12040/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for C# developers! The 2025.3 release of ReSharper and Rider has arrived alongside .NET 10 and C# 14. Both tools are ready to support the latest language features right from the start. Explore the new extension members, user-defined compound assignment operators, and the field keyword for code cleanup. With enhanced inspections, quick-fixes, and refactorings, your coding experience just got better! 🔗 Download now: Rider 2025.3 | ReSharper 2025.3 #CSharp #ReSharper #Rider&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s Been Fixed in Rider 2025.3</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12041/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:49:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12041/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains Rider 2025.3 is here with over 300 fixes and refinements! This release enhances IDE stability and speeds up startup times, making code completion and navigation more accessible from the start. Key fixes include addressing working directory issues and unexpected file openings. Unit testing and debugging also see improvements, with resolved disruptions in the test runner UI and better handling of remote processes. Explore the advancements in project reliability, especially for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper C&#43;&#43; 2025.3: C&#43;&#43;26 Language Support, Faster Unreal Engine Startup, and Visual Studio 2026 Compatibility</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12042/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:48:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12042/</guid>
      <description>🚀 ReSharper C++ 2025.3 has been released, featuring significant updates for C++26 support and improved performance for Unreal Engine developers. Key highlights include: - Enhanced support for C++26 language features like pack indexing and contracts. - Upgraded constexpr evaluation for better diagnostics. - Up to 30% faster warm startup for Unreal Engine projects. This version also brings UI refinements and compatibility with Visual Studio 2026. #ReSharper #CPlusPlus #UnrealEngine&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper 2025.3: Day-One C# 14 Support, Visual Studio 2026 Compatibility, and Major Performance Gains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12043/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:48:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12043/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! ReSharper 2025.3 has been released alongside .NET 10, offering full support for C# 14 features. This version includes extension members, operators, and user-defined compound assignment operators. It makes refactoring easier with new inspections and quick-fixes. Notably, performance has improved significantly. Expect faster startup times, reduced UI unresponsiveness, and enhanced solution-wide analysis. Explore all the details on C# 14 support in ReSharper and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rider 2025.3: Day-One Support for .NET 10 and C# 14, a New Default UI, and Faster Startup</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12044/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 15:48:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12044/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Rider 2025.3 is here, supporting .NET 10 and C# 14 from day one! This release features full compatibility with .NET 10, alongside enhancements like extension members, operators, and user-defined compound assignment operators. Additionally, the new Islands theme offers a fresh UI, with improved startup speed and expanded game development tools for Unity, Unreal Engine, and Godot. #Rider2025 #DotNet10 #CSharp14 #GameDev #SoftwareUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building AI Agents in Kotlin – Part 1: A Minimal Coding Agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12045/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 08:35:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12045/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Building AI Agents in Kotlin has begun! This article introduces the concept of agents as LLMs that autonomously call functions until completing a task. It emphasizes the balance between granting too many or too few capabilities to the agent. The series will guide readers on creating a coding agent step by step, using the Koog framework to navigate codebases and make changes. Stay tuned for more insights! 🌟 #AI #Kotlin #CodingAgents #Koog #LLM</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains and DMCC AI Centre Announce Strategic Partnership to Accelerate AI Innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12046/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12046/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains and the DMCC AI Centre have formed a strategic partnership to boost AI innovation in Dubai. This collaboration aims to support startups and developers by providing access to JetBrains&amp;rsquo; tools and expertise. DMCC members will receive six months of free subscriptions to various JetBrains services, fostering growth in the tech community. The initiative includes AI challenges, hackathons, and events to promote knowledge sharing and policy development. Together, they aim to strengthen&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rust vs. Python: Finding the right balance between speed and simplicity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12047/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 12:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12047/</guid>
      <description>Deciding between Python and Rust is more than just syntax; it’s a career choice. 📊 According to the StackOverflow Developer Survey, Python is the go-to for 66.4% of new coders, showing a significant rise in usage. Meanwhile, Rust has also gained traction, especially among developers who admire its performance and safety features. 🔍 This article dives into their differences in syntax, performance, and ecosystems. Python is ideal for rapid development, while Rust excels in performance and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Go Ecosystem in 2025: Key Trends in Frameworks, Tools, and Developer Practices</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12048/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 09:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-10-12048/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Go celebrates 16 years with significant growth! Recent data shows that 2.2 million developers now use Go as their primary language, doubling in five years. Over 5 million use it as a secondary language. 11% of developers plan to adopt Go in the next year, maintaining its position in the JetBrains Language Promise Index. The Go ecosystem thrives with a strong standard library and popular frameworks like chi. #GoLang #Programming #DeveloperTrends #TechNews #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growing Kotlin Adoption in Your Company</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-05-11849/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 11:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-05-11849/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Growing Kotlin Adoption in Your Company! In a recent guest post by Urs Peter, insights on expanding Kotlin use in Java-dominated environments are shared. After gaining initial support from a core team, the focus shifts to winning over skeptical Java developers. Key strategies include showcasing Kotlin&amp;rsquo;s advantages through code comparisons and building an in-house community for support. Emphasis is placed on practical onboarding and providing self-study resources. Learn more about Kotlin&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 Smart Performance Hacks For Faster Python Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-05-11850/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 10:50:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-05-11850/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of Python with 10 smart performance hacks! 🚀 This article by Dido Grigorov highlights strategies to enhance your code&amp;rsquo;s speed without losing clarity. Key techniques include using sets for faster membership testing and avoiding unnecessary copies of large objects. 🐍 These tips empower developers to optimize their performance and tackle complex tasks efficiently. #Python #CodingTips #PerformanceOptimization #SoftwareDevelopment #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhpStorm Plugins You Might Not Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11717/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:15:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11717/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your PhpStorm experience with powerful plugins! 🛠️ Plugins add new languages and tools, improving your coding workflow. Notably, Dmitrii Derepko has developed several useful tools for web projects and PHP. Check out the .gitattributes Support plugin for better editing, the Git CODEOWNERS plugin for easier management, and the Cron Support plugin for simplified task scheduling. Interested in plugin development? Don’t miss the free JetBrains Plugin Developer Conference 2025! 🎤 #PhpStorm&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Universal Entry Point: A Single Entry Point for Context-Aware Coding Assistance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11718/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 15:21:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11718/</guid>
      <description>Unlock your IDE&amp;rsquo;s potential with the new &lt;strong&gt;Command Completion&lt;/strong&gt; feature! 🚀 This tool provides a universal entry point for context-aware actions, allowing developers to discover IDE features without interrupting their workflow. Just type &lt;code&gt;..&lt;/code&gt; to get action suggestions tailored to your current context. Explore a more efficient coding experience and enhance productivity in 2025.2 Beta! #IDE #DeveloperTools #CodingEfficiency #TechInnovation #CommandCompletion</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming the Billion Dollar Mistake: Maarten Balliauw’s Guide to C# Nullable Reference Types</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11707/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 13:39:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11707/</guid>
      <description>Maarten Balliauw recently presented at JetBrains.NET Days Online 2025 on migrating to C# nullable reference types, a feature that enhances null safety in codebases. He emphasized that while this feature helps at design and compile time, it does not provide runtime safety. Developers should approach migration pragmatically, especially in larger projects, using the Boy Scout Rule to gradually enable nullability. Maarten also warned against the misuse of the null-forgiving operator, advocating&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Busy Plugin Developers Newsletter – Q3 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11665/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 16:18:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11665/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting updates for plugin developers from JetBrains! 📅 Mark your calendars for the JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf on November 5, 2025. This free online event will cover essential topics like plugin creation and the Language Server Protocol. 🧩 New features include resolved reviews that maintain visibility without affecting ratings, and updated requirements for plugin names and descriptions. 🔧 Check out the new IntelliJ Platform Compose Plugin Template for building modern UIs, along with&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bring Your Own Key (BYOK) Is Coming Soon to JetBrains AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11666/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 15:15:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11666/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! JetBrains is introducing Bring Your Own Key (BYOK) support for JetBrains AI Assistant and Junie. This feature allows you to connect your own AI provider accounts, like OpenAI and Anthropic, directly to your JetBrains IDE. 🔍 With BYOK, you&amp;rsquo;ll enjoy: - Freedom to choose your preferred AI model - Full transparency on usage and costs - Enhanced privacy and security for your API keys JetBrains aims to create an open ecosystem, supporting various AI providers and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ Platform 2025.3: What Plugin Developers Should Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11641/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11641/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for plugin developers as IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 approaches! Key points include: 🔹 No urgent upgrade needed for plugins built on versions 2025.2 or earlier. Compatibility checks can be done locally using the verifyPlugin Gradle task. 🔹 A major change: IntelliJ IDEA Community and Ultimate will now be unified, simplifying plugin development and distribution. 🔹 All plugins targeting 2025.3 must use the intellijIdea() platform artifact moving forward. Stay informed and adapt your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Trust Leads and Speed Follows in Agentic Design</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11642/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 08:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11642/</guid>
      <description>In the world of development, there&amp;rsquo;s a crucial trade-off: speed versus trust. With AI agents becoming more integrated into workflows, the focus shifts from how fast they act to how trustworthy they are. AI agents can enhance productivity when trust is prioritized alongside speed. They transform goals into actions, adapting to context and collaborating effectively in multi-agent systems. However, while agents show promise in routine tasks, their contributions require supervision to avoid&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pourquoi Python est-il si populaire en 2025 ?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11621/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 17:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11621/</guid>
      <description>Python continue de dominer le paysage de la programmation en 2025. 🐍 D&amp;rsquo;après l&amp;rsquo;Enquête sur l’Écosystème des Développeurs, 57 % des développeurs l&amp;rsquo;utilisent, et 34 % en font leur langage principal. Il est particulièrement prisé dans le domaine de l&amp;rsquo;IA et du machine learning, avec 41 % des utilisateurs l&amp;rsquo;employant pour ces applications. Sa syntaxe lisible et son écosystème riche avec des frameworks comme PyTorch et TensorFlow le rendent essentiel pour les projets modernes. 🚀📊 #Python&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Academy 插件迎来 AI 驱动的学习功能</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11622/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 08:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11622/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains Academy has introduced two new AI-driven features to enhance your coding journey: Machine Translation and Theory Lookup. 🌐 &lt;strong&gt;Machine Translation&lt;/strong&gt; allows you to translate task titles and descriptions into 10 languages, helping you focus on coding instead of language barriers. 📚 &lt;strong&gt;Theory Lookup&lt;/strong&gt; provides quick definitions of key programming terms directly in the IDE, reducing interruptions during learning. 💻 Update your JetBrains Academy plugin to experience these improvements in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koog × A2A: KI-Agents in Kotlin vernetzen</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11623/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 03:24:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11623/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Koog × A2A: KI-Agents effektiv vernetzen! Entwickler, die mit mehreren KI-Agents arbeiten, kennen die Herausforderungen der Kommunikation. Jeder Agent hat seine eigene API und Authentifizierung, was Integrationen komplex macht. Hier kommt das Agent2Agent-Protokoll (A2A) ins Spiel. A2A bietet eine standardisierte Kommunikationsschicht, die den Austausch zwischen Agents vereinfacht. Plug-and-play-Konnektivität und integrierte Orchestrierung reduzieren den Aufwand für die Integration. Koog ist&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Livestream recording] Maximizing TeamCity: New Features in Action and a Look Ahead</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11508/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11508/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In our recent livestream, TeamCity Solutions Engineers shared exciting updates on new features designed to enhance the CI/CD experience. Key highlights include an improved user interface, pipelines, and Kubernetes executor mode. These updates aim to simplify workflow management for teams. Looking ahead, the 2026 roadmap focuses on performance enhancements, UX improvements, AI features, and tighter integration with JetBrains IDEs. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the chance to explore the future of TeamCity! 🌐&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Livestream recording] Maximizing TeamCity: New Features in Action and a Look Ahead</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11624/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:37:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11624/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In a recent livestream, TeamCity Solutions Engineers Ricardo Leite and Daniel Gallo shared exciting updates on TeamCity&amp;rsquo;s new features and a glimpse into the 2026 roadmap. Key highlights include an improved user interface, pipelines, Kubernetes executor mode, and conditional dependencies for better CI/CD workflows. Looking ahead, 2026 will focus on performance, user experience, AI features, and closer integration with JetBrains IDEs. Stay tuned for more updates! 🌟 #TeamCity #CICD&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grazie’s Next Step: Built-In Language Intelligence for Your IDE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11492/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 12:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11492/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Grazie is evolving! Starting with the 2025.3 IDE versions, Grazie transitions from an external plugin to a built-in feature in IntelliJ-based IDEs via the Natural Languages plugin. This integration enhances proofreading and writing support across various contexts, including code comments and documentation. While most Grazie Pro features will be included, some will not be available in the integrated version. Feedback is being collected to determine the future of these features. With this&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grazie’s Next Step: Built-In Language Intelligence for Your IDE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11625/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 12:43:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11625/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates for developers! Grazie is evolving from a proofreading tool to a built-in writing assistant in IntelliJ-based IDEs with the upcoming 2025.3 release. It will now support code comments, documentation, and more through the Natural Languages plugin. This integration enhances performance and offers localized proofreading with customizable writing styles. Grazie Pro features will transition, but some may not be available in the integrated version yet. Your feedback is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Les Frameworks et Bibliothèques Python les plus populaires en 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11626/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 11:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11626/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Découvrez les frameworks Python les plus populaires en 2025 ! Chaque année, des milliers de développeurs partagent leurs préférences en matière de frameworks. Selon les résultats de l’enquête, FastAPI se distingue avec une adoption de 38% en 2024, en hausse de 9% par rapport à 2023. FastAPI est apprécié pour sa rapidité et sa simplicité, facilitant la création d&amp;rsquo;APIs modernes. Il excelle dans l&amp;rsquo;intégration avec des outils d&amp;rsquo;IA et de machine learning, tout en offrant une documentation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Becomes Cloud9’s Official AI-Powered Coding Partner</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11470/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11470/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! JetBrains has partnered with Cloud9 Esports as their official AI-Powered Coding Partner. This collaboration aims to enhance productivity in gaming and coding. JetBrains will equip Cloud9 with advanced AI tools to improve internal solutions and fan experiences. Expect a large-scale hackathon and events focused on applying AI in esports, fostering creativity and innovation. 🕹️✨ #JetBrains #Cloud9 #Esports #AICoding #GamingCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Becomes Cloud9’s Official AI-Powered Coding Partner</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11627/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:09:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11627/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! JetBrains has partnered with Cloud9 Esports as their official AI-Powered Coding Partner. This collaboration aims to integrate AI coding tools into the esports environment, enhancing team performance and developer creativity. Together, they will host a large-scale hackathon and share insights through online sessions. Fans can look forward to innovative solutions and special events throughout the esports season! 🎮🤖 #JetBrains #Cloud9 #Esports #AICoding #GameDev</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Distributed Systems: Jason Taylor Shows How .NET Aspire Makes the Complex Feel Effortless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11455/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 14:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11455/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025, Jason Taylor showcased how .NET Aspire simplifies building distributed systems. He emphasized that &amp;ldquo;effortless&amp;rdquo; means reducing friction while focusing on delivering user-centric features. With just a few clicks, developers can enhance ASP.NET Core apps with automatic resilience and health checks. The local development experience is notably improved, allowing new team members to onboard quickly with one press of F5. Discover more in the full presentation!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying Distributed Systems: Jason Taylor Shows How .NET Aspire Makes the Complex Feel Effortless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11628/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 14:28:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11628/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025, Jason Taylor, Microsoft MVP, introduced .NET Aspire, a tool aimed at simplifying distributed systems development. He emphasized that “effortless” means focusing effort where it counts, reducing unnecessary complexity. With just a few clicks, developers can enhance applications with features like automatic retry policies and service discovery. Taylor showcased how .NET Aspire improves local development, making onboarding new team members easier and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The MPS 2025.3 Early Access Program Has Started</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11441/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11441/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The MPS 2025.3 Early Access Program (EAP) has officially launched! You can now download the first release and explore its features. This version includes several bug fixes and three key improvements: 1️⃣ Light and dark TextIcon options for better customization. 2️⃣ Highlighting of only visible usages to enhance clarity. 3️⃣ An updated reflective editor for a streamlined user experience. Check out the full list of fixes! 🔧 #MPS2025 #EarlyAccess #JetBrains #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The MPS 2025.3 Early Access Program Has Started</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11629/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:28:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11629/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! The MPS 2025.3 Early Access Program (EAP) has launched today! You can now download the first release and explore new features. Key improvements include: - Light and dark TextIcon options for better customization. - Highlighting of only visible usages in the editor for clarity. - A refreshed look for the reflective editor, merging it with the read-only default. Check out the full list of fixes and enhancements! #MPS2025 #EarlyAccess #JetBrains #SoftwareUpdate #ProgrammingTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Order in the Mayhem: A Novel Concurrency Testing Tool that Improved the Kotlin Compiler</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11442/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11442/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in concurrent programming! JetBrains Research introduces LitmusKt, a novel testing tool for Kotlin&amp;rsquo;s multiplatform concurrency. This tool is designed to identify complex, platform-specific concurrency bugs that traditional methods miss. LitmusKt enhances the Kotlin compiler by systematically uncovering hidden issues, improving reliability in concurrent applications. Learn more about the challenges of concurrent programming and how LitmusKt is transforming Kotlin&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding Order in the Mayhem: A Novel Concurrency Testing Tool that Improved the Kotlin Compiler</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11630/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 12:12:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11630/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in concurrency testing! JetBrains Research has developed LitmusKt, a novel tool for Kotlin&amp;rsquo;s multiplatform concurrency. This tool aims to identify subtle concurrency errors that traditional testing often misses. LitmusKt is designed for Kotlin&amp;rsquo;s diverse backends, enhancing automated testing for the Kotlin compiler and runtime. Learn more about its features, history, and the complexities of concurrent programming. #Kotlin #Concurrency #JetBrains #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin AI 技术栈：使用 Koog 构建 AI 智能体，使用 Junie 更智能地编码，等等</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11631/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 08:37:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11631/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming software development, and Kotlin is at the forefront of this change. 🚀 This article discusses tools from JetBrains and the community for building AI-powered applications and how Kotlin integrates AI tools to enhance development efficiency. Key highlights include Koog—a native Kotlin framework for creating AI agents—and Junie, an AI coding assistant integrated into JetBrains IDE. 🛠️ Kotlin is already being used in large-scale AI systems, such as a major chatbot by Deutsche&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DroidKaigi 2025 – Koog で広がる Kotlin とAI の可能性</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11632/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 07:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11632/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Recently, I attended the DroidKaigi After Party hosted by KINTO Technologies and JetBrains. The focus was on the session “AI Utilization in Development with Kotlin,” particularly on the Koog framework. 📹 For those interested, you can watch the session video featuring Sebastian Aigner discussing Koog, an OSS Kotlin agent framework. 📚 I also shared insights on how to construct AI workflows using Koog and provided additional resources for further learning. For more details, check out the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Launch of Developer Productivity AI Arena: An Open Platform for Benchmarking AI Coding Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11382/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 21:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11382/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains has launched the Developer Productivity AI Arena (DPAI Arena), an open platform aimed at benchmarking AI coding agents. This initiative addresses the need for transparent metrics in measuring AI&amp;rsquo;s impact on developer productivity. The DPAI Arena will provide a framework that supports various programming languages and workflows, ensuring fair comparisons across tasks like bug fixing and test generation. JetBrains emphasizes the importance of collaboration among coding agent&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Developer Productivity AI Arena: An Open Platform for AI Coding Agents Benchmarks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11383/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 21:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11383/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in software development! The Developer Productivity AI Arena (DPAI Arena) has been launched as an open benchmarking platform for AI coding agents. This platform aims to evaluate developer productivity across various languages and workflows. Current benchmarks are outdated and limited, failing to reflect modern development practices. DPAI Arena introduces a multi-track architecture to assess real-world engineering activities, including pull request reviews and code coverage&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>YouTrack Introduces a Remote MCP Server and New Apps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11379/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 17:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11379/</guid>
      <description>🚀 YouTrack 2025.3 has launched with remote MCP (Model Context Protocol) support, enhancing integration with AI tools! This update allows teams to manage tasks directly from LLMs, IDEs, or agent platforms, streamlining project management. New apps in JetBrains Marketplace further extend YouTrack’s capabilities for planning and release management. Additionally, AI features improve search and provide text completion assistance for faster writing. #YouTrack #AIIntegration #ProjectManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Kotlin in Real Projects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11361/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 14:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11361/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exploring Kotlin in Real Projects! In the latest post by Urs Peter, a Senior Software Engineer, he discusses evaluating Kotlin in practical scenarios. This is part of a series focused on adopting Kotlin in Java-heavy environments. Two main approaches for evaluation are highlighted: 1️⃣ Build a new microservice/application in Kotlin. 2️⃣ Extend or convert an existing Java application. Starting fresh allows for a better learning experience, but expert guidance is recommended to avoid common&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper and Rider 2025.2.4: Another Set of Updates Released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11335/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 09:13:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11335/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New updates for ReSharper and Rider 2025.2.4 are here! The latest release includes crucial bug fixes and feature enhancements. Notably, the TeamCity extension has been restored, addressing user feedback on CI workflows. Key improvements include: - Correct display of tool windows in in-process mode. - Enhanced code completion and stability. - Resolved Visual Studio crashes on exit. Rider also sees updates like improved code analysis and debugging in Unity projects. For full details, check&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Modern Enterprise Toolkit for Secure, High-Quality Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11311/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11311/</guid>
      <description>Join JetBrains Qodana on November 19, 2025, for a live session focused on embedding quality, security, and compliance into development workflows. Hosted by Kai Schmithuesen, learn about Qodana&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and how it integrates with DevOps. Key topics include secure code practices, enhanced access control, and insights for managing project health. Mark your calendars and register! 🗓️🔒 #JetBrains #DevOps #Qodana #SecureCoding #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kodee’s Kotlin Roundup: Finally Back with News</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11312/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 13:19:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11312/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting updates from Kodee’s Kotlin Roundup! In September and October, significant developments include Kotlin 2.2.20 and 2.2.21, featuring new dataflow checks and an overhaul of contracts. Kotlin Multiplatform now promotes WebAssembly to Beta, plus Swift Export is available in KMP projects. Kotlin is also making waves in AI development with the Kotlin AI Stack, enhancing app creation and developer workflows. Lastly, a piece by Marcin Moskała discusses transitioning from Python to Kotlin&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State of Django 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11297/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11297/</guid>
      <description>📊 The Django Developers Survey 2025 reveals insights from over 4,600 developers globally. This annual collaboration highlights the growth and stability of Django, now celebrating its 20th anniversary. ✨ With new features released regularly, the community continues to thrive, supported by the ongoing efforts of Django’s maintainers and the Annual Django Fundraiser. 🛠️ You can also support the Django Software Foundation by purchasing PyCharm Professional with a 30% discount until November 9,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use a Spec-Driven Approach for Coding with AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11291/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 11:07:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11291/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of AI coding with a spec-driven approach! 🤖✨ Using Junie, JetBrains&amp;rsquo; AI agent, developers can tackle complex software features with clarity. Start by defining high-level requirements to guide the agent effectively. This step ensures a shared understanding and sets clear priorities. Next, generate a detailed development plan. Ask Junie to create a plan based on your requirements, allowing for deeper thinking before implementation. This process helps outline the approach&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2.4 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11243/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 00:26:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11243/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2.4 has been released, featuring key fixes and improvements. You can update directly from the IDE, via the Toolbox App, or download it from the website. Notable updates include: - Functional uninstaller - No more freezing during code completion - Enhanced cURL command conversion - Correct line endings when shelving changes For a full list of improvements, check out the release notes. Happy coding! 💻✨ #IntelliJIDEA #SoftwareUpdate #Coding #Development #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How BoldSign Modernized Development at Scale With JetBrains dotUltimate</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11231/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 19:47:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11231/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements at BoldSign! The Syncfusion engineering team revamped their modern e-signature platform to support over 40,000 organizations. They faced performance challenges as adoption grew, but the integration of JetBrains dotUltimate transformed their development process. With tools like Rider, dotTrace, and dotMemory, build times are now just 15–20 seconds, and issues are identified earlier. This shift has enhanced code quality and reduced debugging cycles significantly&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Performance Matters in Python Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11195/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:31:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11195/</guid>
      <description>Python&amp;rsquo;s popularity stems from its flexibility and ease of use, but challenges exist. 🚧 Performance bottlenecks arise due to its interpreted nature and the global interpreter lock (GIL). These can hinder large-scale applications, affecting speed and user experience. The article discusses practical strategies to optimize Python code, addressing issues like the GIL&amp;rsquo;s impact on CPU-bound tasks. #Python #Programming #Performance #Coding #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Kotlin for Java Developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11189/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 10:51:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11189/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exploring Kotlin? 🖥️ Urs Peter, a Senior Software Engineer and Kotlin Trainer, introduces a guide for Java developers transitioning to Kotlin. The series covers essential stages, from initial curiosity to large-scale adoption, emphasizing strategic planning and gaining support from peers. Key topics include starting small, building a business case, and factors for success in Kotlin adoption. #Kotlin #JavaDevelopers #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTransition #ProgrammingLanguages</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Matter: The AI Development Companion for Product Teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11159/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11159/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains introduces Matter, an AI development companion designed for product teams! This tool enhances collaboration by allowing teams to prototype and test ideas directly in their codebase without writing code. It connects to GitHub, enabling safe experimentation with real-time previews. Matter is currently available for web-based projects and is tailored for teams, emphasizing the importance of collaboration among product managers, designers, and engineers. Join the Early Access Program&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Python to Kotlin: A Transition Worth Making</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11148/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 11:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11148/</guid>
      <description>Transitioning from Python to Kotlin can be beneficial for certain projects. While Python excels in scripting and data analysis, it can struggle with large codebases due to dynamic typing and performance issues. In contrast, Kotlin, running on the JVM, offers improved efficiency and modern language features. Many teams, like Wolt, have successfully made this switch for better performance and safety. Kotlin shares similarities with Python, making it an intuitive choice for developers. #Python&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coming to Rider 2025.3: ASP.NET and Database Issue Detection In The Monitoring Tool Window</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11067/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 13:01:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11067/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Rider 2025.3 introduces enhanced Monitoring tool capabilities! Now, users can detect database and ASP.NET issues in real time, including slow queries and inefficient request handling. This information is displayed alongside CPU, memory, and GC activity for comprehensive performance tracking. With a dotUltimate subscription, you can delve deeper into specific methods causing issues. Explore these features in the Rider 2025.3 EAP 6 build today! #Rider2025 #MonitoringTool #ASPNet #Database&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Science Learning Curve: Insights from 18k Learners Worldwide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11060/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 06:52:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11060/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The landscape of computer science education is evolving rapidly, driven by AI tools and online learning. Our research team surveyed 18,032 learners from 173 countries to gain insights into who is learning CS and how. This study fills a critical gap in understanding global trends in CS education. 📊 Key findings will be shared at ACM CompEd on October 23rd. Explore the dataset and learn how these insights can impact real-world applications. #ComputerScience #EducationResearch #LearningTrends&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koog 0.5.0 Is Out: Smarter Tools, Persistent Agents, and Simplified Strategy Design</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 07:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11019/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Koog 0.5.0 is here! This update features full Agent2Agent (A2A) protocol support, making it easier to build interconnected AI agents in Kotlin. Key highlights include a non-graph API for simpler strategy design, improved agent persistence with rollback tools, and refined Tool API for smoother integration. Additionally, the new AIAgentService simplifies managing multiple agents. Explore the advancements for more efficient AI workflows! #Koog #AI #Kotlin #TechUpdate #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf 2025 Is Coming Up Soon!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11010/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 21:38:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11010/</guid>
      <description>📢 Exciting news for plugin developers! The JetBrains Plugin Developer Conf is set for November 5. This event features a full day of talks, live Q&amp;amp;A, and in-depth sessions on plugin development. Key topics include creating your first plugin, language plugins, AI-powered testing, and more. Join us live on YouTube or catch up later! #JetBrains #PluginDevelopment #DevConference #SoftwareDevelopment #TechEvent</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The “10x” Commandments of Highly Effective Go</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10988/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:13:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10988/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the secrets to writing effective Go code with John Arundel&amp;rsquo;s “10x” Commandments! 🚀 1️⃣ Focus on creating packages, not just programs. This enhances usability for others. 2️⃣ Test everything to refine your code and catch issues early. 3️⃣ Write for readability. Simplifying code improves collaboration and maintenance. Dive into these insightful tips for better coding practices! 💻✨ #GoLang #CodingTips #SoftwareDevelopment #Programming #TechAdvice</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Is Sunsetting CodeCanvas</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10980/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 07:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10980/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update from JetBrains! 🚨 JetBrains has announced the discontinuation of CodeCanvas, originally launched in 2024. The decision stems from the evolving needs of developers in a rapidly AI-driven landscape. New CodeCanvas licenses will be unavailable after October 16, 2025, with support continuing for existing users until January 1, 2026. Users can access CodeCanvas until March 31, 2026, after which the service will cease. JetBrains is shifting focus to develop a new AI-first, cloud-&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State of PHP 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10939/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10939/</guid>
      <description>The State of PHP 2025 report highlights the ongoing evolution of PHP, showcasing its modern frameworks, enhanced tools, and AI-driven workflows. In the Developer Ecosystem Survey, 1,720 PHP developers shared insights, with most having over three years of experience. Notably, 88% have extensive backgrounds, and 56% work in small teams. While 58% plan to stick with PHP, interest in languages like Go and Python is growing. The report reflects the stability and maturity of the PHP community. 📊💻🌍&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State of Developer Ecosystem 2025: Coding in the Age of AI, New Productivity Metrics, and Changing Realities</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10940/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:01:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10940/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The JetBrains Developer Ecosystem Survey 2025 reveals insights from 24,534 developers across 194 countries. 📈 AI tools are now integral to development, with 85% of developers using them regularly. While many save significant time, 15% remain hesitant about adoption. 🔍 Developers express mixed feelings about AI&amp;rsquo;s role, favoring it for repetitive tasks while wanting to retain control over complex work. 💻 Programming languages like TypeScript, Rust, Go, and Kotlin are gaining traction&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[Livestream] Maximizing TeamCity: New Features in Action and a Look Ahead</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10941/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10941/</guid>
      <description>📅 Join us on October 22, 2025, for a livestream on maximizing TeamCity! TeamCity Solutions Engineers Ricardo Leite and Daniel Gallo will showcase new features and provide a sneak peek at future updates. This session is designed for those looking to enhance their TeamCity experience. Expect hands-on demos, configuration walkthroughs, and insights into licensing changes. 🕓 Don&amp;rsquo;t miss it! #TeamCity #DevOps #Webinar #CI/CD #JetBrains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Bug-Fix Releases Are Available for MPS – 2025.2.1, 2025.1.1, 2024.3.4, and 2024.1.5</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10904/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10904/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New updates are here for MPS! The latest releases, including versions 2025.2.1, 2025.1.1, 2024.3.4, and 2024.1.5, address various issues. Key improvements include: 🔹 Exclusion of invisible references from usage highlighting (MPS-38681) 🔹 Ant task now supports additional project properties for log file configuration (MPS-36481) For more details, check out the full list of fixes. #JetBrains #MPS #SoftwareUpdates #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper Is Now on the Open VSX Registry</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10893/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 14:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10893/</guid>
      <description>🚀 ReSharper for Visual Studio Code is now available on the Open VSX Registry! Previously, users of VS Code-compatible editors faced challenges in accessing ReSharper, needing to manually update from the Visual Studio Marketplace. Now, installation is simple—just search for ReSharper in the Extensions view. This change aims to enhance the C# development experience for Cursor, Windsurf, and VSCodium users. Note: The extension&amp;rsquo;s initial startup may take longer due to new architecture, but future&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build a Kotlin Multiplatform Project and Win a Trip to KotlinConf 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10587/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 13:29:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10587/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for students and recent grads! The Kotlin Multiplatform Contest is now open. Build a project using Kotlin Multiplatform (KMP) for a chance to win a trip to KotlinConf 2026 in Munich, Germany! 🏆 Join the dedicated Slack channel for support, share progress, and connect with other participants. Prizes include travel, accommodation, and community recognition. Contest details: - Opens: September 15, 2025 - Deadline: January 12, 2026 - Winners announced: January 22, 2026 For more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Qodana’s Public API Is Now Available!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10588/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 12:46:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10588/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Qodana Public API is now live! This launch provides Qodana Cloud users with full documentation, examples, and OpenAPI specifications. Users can integrate Qodana into their systems, automate workflows, and manage teams and projects directly via the API. Explore the complete reference and stay tuned for new updates throughout the year! 🔗 #Qodana #API #DevOps #Automation #CodeQuality</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeamCity 2025.07.3 Is Here</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10578/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 10:32:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10578/</guid>
      <description>🚀 TeamCity 2025.07.3 has been released! This minor update focuses on fixing several issues, including: - “Tests” tab issues during long tests - Display inconsistencies in the “Reuse jobs” setting - Trigger failures for new pull request pipelines - Incorrect assignments for new cloud instances Regular updates not only fix bugs but also enhance performance and security. It&amp;rsquo;s recommended to update your On-Premises servers for optimal functionality. For more details, check the TeamCity 2025.07.3&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crafting Your KotlinConf Proposal: Expert Tips to  Help You Stand Out</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10557/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 16:26:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10557/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to share your Kotlin expertise at KotlinConf? Here are some expert tips to craft a standout proposal! 1️⃣ Start with a clear and compelling title. First impressions matter! Make sure your title conveys your topic and its benefits to the audience. 2️⃣ Use storytelling in your abstract. Engage your audience by promising a valuable learning experience through a narrative. These insights can boost your chances of acceptance and help you shine at the event! 🌟 #KotlinConf #Kotlin&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling All Non-Commercial JetBrains Rider Users: Tell Us Your Stories!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10533/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 12:19:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10533/</guid>
      <description>📣 Attention non-commercial JetBrains Rider users! It’s been nearly a year since Rider became free for non-commercial use. To celebrate, JetBrains is inviting users to share their stories about projects developed with Rider. They are seeking participants for interviews to discuss your experiences, whether it’s for side projects, open-source contributions, or educational endeavors. If interested, contact &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sasha.ivanova@jetbrains.com&#34;&gt;sasha.ivanova@jetbrains.com&lt;/a&gt; for more details. Participants will gain visibility for their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet JetBrains at Azure Dev Summit 2025 (Lisbon, Oct 13–16)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10513/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10513/</guid>
      <description>🌍 JetBrains is excited to attend the Azure Dev Summit 2025 in Lisbon from October 13–16! Join Max Solovyev, Head of Growth for .NET and GameDev Tools, at our booth to explore how Rider and the dotUltimate suite can enhance your .NET on Azure projects. We will showcase practical demos, discuss Azure App Service, and share insights on performance diagnostics and JetBrains AI features. 📅 Book a brief chat with Max to discuss your goals. #JetBrains #AzureDevSummit #DotNet #Lisbon2025&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLion Now Supports DAP Debuggers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10497/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 13:22:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10497/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for CLion users! The latest EAP build of CLion 2025.3 now supports the Debug Adapter Protocol (DAP). This allows for communication with various third-party debuggers in addition to the bundled LLDB and GDB. 🛠 Setting up your DAP debugger is simple, requiring just five steps. Check the documentation for guidance on configuration. 📚 Additionally, CLion now supports the Visual Studio 2026 Insiders toolchain, featuring new MSVC build tools and C++23 enhancements. 🔧 Your feedback&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLion Nova Will Become the Default Engine for All Users in v2025.3 – Here’s What You Need to Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10464/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:41:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10464/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CLion Nova will be the default engine for all users in the upcoming v2025.3 release, following its success since becoming the default for new users in v2024.2. Feedback from users has been positive, confirming its stability and performance improvements over CLion Classic. The legacy engine will remain available, but no further updates are planned for it. Key features of CLion Nova include enhanced speed, better memory management, and new functionalities like improved refactoring options and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains × Zed: Open Interoperability for AI Coding Agents in Your IDE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10465/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 15:57:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10465/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from JetBrains! We are collaborating with Zed on the Agent Client Protocol (ACP), an open protocol for integrating AI coding agents into IDEs. This collaboration focuses on eliminating vendor lock-in, giving developers confidence and control over their coding environments. With ACP, you can choose your preferred agent while maintaining familiar workflows. Stay tuned for updates on ACP-powered experiences in JetBrains IDEs! #JetBrains #AIcoding #DeveloperTools #OpenSource&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 ReSharper Features Every .NET Developer Should Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10454/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 14:35:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10454/</guid>
      <description>Unlock your productivity with ReSharper! 🚀 This essential Visual Studio extension offers features every .NET developer should know. From Initial Letter Search to Contextual Navigation, it streamlines your coding experience. Navigate quickly and efficiently with Recent Locations and Changes, making it easier to read and implement features. Explore the top nine features that can enhance your workflow! #ReSharper #DotNet #VisualStudio #Coding #DeveloperTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State of CI/CD in 2025: Key Insights from the Latest JetBrains Survey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10455/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 12:45:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10455/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The JetBrains survey on CI/CD tools for 2025 reveals key insights into the evolving landscape. GitHub Actions leads in popularity for personal projects, used by 62% of respondents. However, organizations still rely on Jenkins and GitLab for enterprise needs. 🔄 Many companies adopt a multi-tool strategy, often due to legacy systems or practical trade-offs. Switching CI/CD tools is complex, with many teams managing both old and new pipelines simultaneously. #CICD #DevOps #JetBrains&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotInsights | October 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10444/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 10:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10444/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Did you know? The yield return keyword in C# allows pausing and resuming method execution, which supports lazy evaluation without needing intermediate collections. This simplifies creating custom iterators. 📆 Just two days until JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025! Check out the latest insights from the developer community, covering topics from .NET MAUI to optimization techniques. #DotNet #SoftwareDevelopment #JetBrains #CSharp #ProgrammingInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper and Rider 2025.2.3: The Third Set of Updates Released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10445/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 09:55:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10445/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A new update is here! The third set of updates for ReSharper and Rider 2025.2 has been released. 🔧 ReSharper 2025.2.3 includes bug fixes, such as resolving a regression in License Vault authentication and fixing InspectCode issues. 💻 Rider 2025.2.3 introduces the new Islands theme and notable fixes for F# projects and .uproject file loading. For detailed changes, check the issue tracker! #ReSharper #Rider #SoftwareUpdate #DevelopmentTools #IDE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – October 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10438/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 08:15:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10438/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Ready to catch up on the latest in Java? This month&amp;rsquo;s Java Annotated Monthly highlights exciting updates in Java 25, along with tech tips, tutorials, and AI news. A special feature includes Marco Behler from JetBrains, who shares insights through his new podcast, The Marco Show, covering coding and developer tools. 🎙️ Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the first two episodes focusing on LLMs and software performance! 🎧 #Java #DeveloperCommunity #TechUpdates #Podcast #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amper Update, October 2025 – Compose Hot Reload and UX Improvements</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10422/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 16:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-03-10422/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Amper 0.8.0 is here! This update introduces key features like Compose Hot Reload, allowing automatic code loading without app restarts. You can now customize your Kotlin compiler version and benefit from simplified single-platform experiences. Additionally, Amper supports new JavaScript and Wasm platforms for multiplatform library modules. For full details, check the release notes. #AmperUpdate #Kotlin #JavaScript #Wasm #CodingTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2.3 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10395/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 18:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10395/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2.3 has been released! You can update directly via the IDE, Toolbox App, or download it from the website. This update includes: - Restored Jira Task Server integration. - Fixed breakpoints in the Services view with ClassicUI. - Multiple file access improved in the Find Usages dialog. For detailed resolved issues, check the release notes. Happy coding! 💻✨ #IntelliJIDEA #SoftwareUpdate #DeveloperTools #Coding</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koog × A2A: Building Connected AI Agents in Kotlin</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10369/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10369/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Building connected AI agents just got easier! The Koog framework in Kotlin simplifies the creation and management of AI agents. It allows for complex workflows and integrates seamlessly with the A2A Protocol, enabling efficient communication between agents. With A2A, agents can connect and collaborate effortlessly, eliminating the need for custom integrations and allowing developers to focus on enhancing agent capabilities. Together, Koog and A2A streamline the AI agent ecosystem. #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper and Visual Studio 2026: Day-One Compatibility, Migration Steps, and Performance Gains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10370/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:41:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10370/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Microsoft Visual Studio 2026 Insiders is now available, and developers can breathe easy—ReSharper is compatible from day one! Microsoft and JetBrains collaborated to ensure a smooth transition. ReSharper 2025.2.1 has been validated to work seamlessly with the new version. Visual Studio 2026 also brings a new migration strategy, allowing extensions from VS 2022 to work without additional setups. For ReSharper users, a new Migration Assistant will bridge compatibility, addressing the unique&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving PHP open source forward</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10371/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 09:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10371/</guid>
      <description>JetBrains is committed to advancing the PHP community through various initiatives. We create PhpStorm, support the PHP Foundation, and recently organized PHPverse for global access. Additionally, the Laravel Idea plugin is now available for free. 🌍💻 In our new sponsorship plan for 2025-2026, we aim to support five open-source projects annually, starting with notable contributors like Saif Eddin Gmati and Markus Staab. We also encourage suggestions for projects to sponsor. Contact us if you&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataGrip Is Now Free for Non-Commercial Use</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10323/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 14:43:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10323/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! DataGrip is now free for non-commercial use! This change makes it easier for students, hobbyists, and open-source contributors to access professional database tools. DataGrip joins other JetBrains IDEs like RustRover and WebStorm that are already free. Commercial users will see no changes to their licensing. This initiative aims to support learning and creativity in SQL projects. For more details, check the FAQ. #DataGrip #JetBrains #SQL #Developers #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Recognized in the 2025 Magic Quadrant™ for AI Code Assistants</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10278/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 19:03:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10278/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains’s AI, including AI Assistant and Junie, has been recognized in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for AI Code Assistants. AI is becoming essential in software development, helping automate tasks like code generation and documentation. Gartner predicts a 30% productivity gain in this sector by 2028. 📈 JetBrains is committed to enhancing productivity while maintaining code quality and developer experience. Key focuses include privacy, security, and transparency in AI solutions. Stay&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better AI Depends on Better Data: We Need Your Help</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10252/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:52:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10252/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI has advanced, but it still struggles to meet the needs of professional developers due to limited real-world data. JetBrains invites users to help improve AI tools by sharing relevant data. Companies can enable data sharing at a corporate level, while individual users can choose to opt in or out easily. Your feedback is crucial for refining AI models to better handle complex scenarios. Participation is voluntary, and privacy is respected. #AI #DataSharing #JetBrains #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Updates to TeamCity On-Premises Renewal Pricing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10242/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 08:17:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10242/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for TeamCity Users 🚨 TeamCity will update its on-premises renewal pricing and grace period policies effective November 3, 2025. Existing licenses purchased before this date will retain current renewal discounts. 🔍 Changes include: - The 50% renewal discount will end for new licenses. - Licenses must be renewed within one month of expiry to benefit from the discount. Review your licenses and consider purchasing before the deadline to secure discounted rates. Stay tuned for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Claude Agent in JetBrains IDEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10223/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 17:04:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10223/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The Claude Agent is now integrated into JetBrains IDEs as part of the AI subscription. No extra plugins or subscriptions are needed. This advanced AI coding assistant uses Anthropic’s technology to enhance your coding experience directly within your IDE. Key benefits include: - Native integration for seamless workflow - Instant setup without additional tools - Ability to analyze projects and manage tasks effectively Explore the potential of AI in your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“I tried out JetBrains’ code analysis tool Qodana”</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10202/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 12:59:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10202/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Explore JetBrains&amp;rsquo; Qodana, a powerful code analysis tool designed to enhance code quality and security! Qodana supports various languages and frameworks, allowing integration via command line, JetBrains IDEs, VS Code, and CI/CD environments like GitHub Actions. It also features Qodana Cloud for team collaboration on code issues. This tool helps bridge gaps in AI-assisted coding by ensuring that IDE warnings align with CI checks, preventing unnoticed issues during code reviews. For more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Java Open-Source Projects Use IntelliJ IDEA: Real-World Examples – Part 2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10121/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:08:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10121/</guid>
      <description>Discover the latest highlights from the Java open-source community! In Part 2 of this series, we explore standout projects that enhance builds, improve testing, and streamline modern web stacks, all while leveraging IntelliJ IDEA. 🌐 🔍 &lt;strong&gt;jsoup&lt;/strong&gt;: A Java library for parsing HTML, designed for simplicity and efficiency. Recent updates include HTTP/2 support and a new StreamParser. 🚀 &lt;strong&gt;http4k&lt;/strong&gt;: A lightweight toolkit for building HTTP services in Kotlin, focusing on testability and performance&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Continuing Positive Impact: This Year’s AI4SE Interns in their New Roles at JetBrains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10082/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:37:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10082/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news from JetBrains! This year’s AI4SE interns from TU Delft have transitioned to full-time roles on our tech team. During their internships, they worked on innovative projects, enhancing their technical skills and driving impactful changes in software development. Their contributions have already improved team performance and sparked collaboration across product teams. One intern even developed an AI tool that&amp;rsquo;s still in use today! We look forward to their continued growth and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rider Roadmap: What to Expect From the Upcoming Updates and Releases</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10051/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:22:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10051/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are coming to Rider! Rider 2025.2 is out now, and the 2025.3 release cycle is underway. Key highlights include a same-day launch with .NET 10, ensuring you get the latest SDK and C# features right away. We&amp;rsquo;re focusing on performance, aiming to enhance startup times and improve Roslyn analyzer speeds by up to 20%. Additionally, look forward to the new Islands UI theme, designed for better clarity and a modern feel. Stay tuned for more updates! #RiderUpdates #DotNet10&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Is Python So Popular in 2025?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9974/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 11:19:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9974/</guid>
      <description>Python continues to be a top choice for developers in 2025, ranking as the second most-used programming language. 🌍 With 57% of developers using it and 34% identifying it as their primary language, Python outperforms competitors like JavaScript and Java. Its versatility makes it relevant for both beginners and seasoned professionals. A significant factor in its popularity is its strong presence in AI and machine learning, where 41% of users focus on these areas. Python&amp;rsquo;s readable syntax and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Kotlin AI Stack: Build AI Agents With Koog, Code Smarter With Junie, and More</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9967/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 08:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9967/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI is transforming software development, and Kotlin is leading the way. This article highlights tools like Koog, a Kotlin-native framework for AI agents, and Junie, an AI coding assistant in JetBrains IDEs. Kotlin supports large-scale AI systems, demonstrated by its use in building Europe&amp;rsquo;s largest LLM chatbot. Explore how Kotlin streamlines AI integration with SDKs and libraries. #Kotlin #AI #SoftwareDevelopment #JetBrains #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ktor roadmap and previews</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9938/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 19:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9938/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from the Ktor team! The Ktor roadmap is evolving thanks to community feedback. OpenAPI and WebRTC support are now in preview following the Ktor 3.3.0 release. Check the What’s New section for a comprehensive overview. Your contributions are always valued! 🔗 Start building your projects with the interactive generator at start.ktor.io. #Ktor #OpenAPI #WebRTC #SoftwareDevelopment #CommunityFeedback</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From AI-Generated to Production-Ready Code: WebStorm Refactorings for the Modern Workflow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9939/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 14:15:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9939/</guid>
      <description>Transforming AI-generated code into production-ready components is crucial for developers. 🖥️ WebStorm&amp;rsquo;s refactoring tools play a key role in this process, enhancing maintainability and efficiency. The article illustrates how to refine an AI-generated analytics dashboard step by step, showcasing the synergy between AI and WebStorm. Take your coding workflow to the next level! 🚀 #WebDevelopment #AI #WebStorm #CodeRefactoring #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercharging Unit Test Generation with in-IDE TestSpark</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9912/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 11:13:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9912/</guid>
      <description>Introducing TestSpark, a new framework developed by our Software Testing Research team in collaboration with TU Delft. 🚀 TestSpark enhances automated unit test generation for Java and Kotlin, integrating well with IntelliJ. It offers user-friendly access to LLM-based and automated testing techniques. This tool aims to streamline the testing process, improving efficiency and software quality. Discover how it compares to traditional methods and other LLM approaches. #SoftwareTesting&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Islands Theme: The New Look Coming to JetBrains IDEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9887/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 16:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9887/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains IDEs are introducing the new Islands theme with version 2025.2.3! This update offers both dark and light modes, providing a visual refresh while keeping all functionality intact. You can easily switch themes in the Appearance settings. The Islands theme aims for a modern look, better navigation, and consistent design across all JetBrains products. Your feedback played a crucial role in its development, making it user-friendly and visually clear. Users can now try the Islands theme&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compose Multiplatform 1.9.0 Released: Compose Multiplatform for Web Goes Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9866/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 10:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9866/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Compose Multiplatform for Web is now in Beta! This marks a significant shift from experimental to real-world use, aided by early adopters&amp;rsquo; feedback. 🌐 Developers can now leverage existing Compose skills for web apps, with features like Material 3 components, adaptive layouts, and browser navigation integration. 🔧 Version 1.9.0 also enhances Android, iOS, and desktop experiences, ensuring a unified UI framework. Explore the growing ecosystem of multiplatform libraries that support this new&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Academy – September Digest</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9818/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 11:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9818/</guid>
      <description>🎉 This September, JetBrains Academy is offering free IDEs and tools for students! Take advantage of the JetBrains Student Pack, which includes popular IDEs like IntelliJ IDEA and PyCharm Pro, along with AI Assistant and essential plugins. Share your coding story for a chance to win prizes like a MacBook Air! Explore new courses and start your learning journey today. 🚀 #JetBrains #StudentPack #CodingJourney #TechEducation #FreeTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2.2 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9812/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 09:53:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9812/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2.2 is now available! This latest update includes important fixes like the return of the Run Maven Build icon and improved Remote SSH tools. Windows users will also notice enhancements in the Find in Files dialog and terminal functionality. You can update via the IDE, Toolbox App, or download directly from the website. For more details, check the release notes! #IntelliJ #Update #SoftwareDevelopment #IDE #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing: JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9796/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9796/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited to announce JetBrains .NET Days Online 2025! Join us on October 8-9 for a free, online event featuring practical talks, live demos, and expert tips from community speakers and the JetBrains .NET team. 🔗 Register here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://lp.jetbrains.com/dotnet-days-2025&#34;&gt;https://lp.jetbrains.com/dotnet-days-2025&lt;/a&gt; Don’t miss sessions on topics like Clean Architecture, Test Driven Development, and more! #DotNetDays #JetBrains #Programming #TechEvents #CommunityEngagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More Updates and Fixes for ReSharper and Rider 2025.2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9785/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 14:49:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9785/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! ReSharper and Rider have released their second set of updates for version 2025.2. Key improvements include a lightweight migration extension for a smooth transition to Visual Studio 2026. 🔧 Notable fixes include support for xUnit v3, enhanced Search Everywhere functionality, and automatic license application at startup. Rider&amp;rsquo;s AI coding agent, Junie, is now stable and supports all languages! For the full list of changes, check the issue tracker. #ReSharper&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Common DevOps Problems And How to Solve Them With GoLand</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9749/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:15:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9749/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DevOps can be challenging, as highlighted by a popular post on the /devops subreddit expressing frustration with debugging YAML files. However, many issues can be simplified with the right tools. GoLand, the JetBrains IDE for Go, offers solutions to eight common DevOps problems. It centralizes tools like Kubernetes and Docker, helping engineers debug and manage infrastructure efficiently. For example, fixing broken Kubernetes deployments can be streamlined in GoLand, allowing for quicker&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Debugger: ApplicationContext at Your Fingertips</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9723/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 11:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9723/</guid>
      <description>Discover the Spring Debugger plugin for IntelliJ IDEA! 🛠️ This tool enhances your debugging experience for Spring Boot applications by allowing you to explore the entire Spring ApplicationContext. You can access Spring components and their metadata directly from your debugger. For example, when debugging a BookmarkService, you can interact with beans not directly injected, making it easier to manage data during development. Enhance your workflow with Spring Debugger today! 🚀 #SpringBoot&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Early Access Program for Rider 2025.3 Is Now Open!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9717/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9717/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Early Access Program (EAP) for Rider 2025.3 is officially open! Explore the first preview build and test out new features. Your feedback is crucial for refining the final release. Join the EAP for free via our website, Toolbox App, or Snapcraft store. Key updates include improvements for Unity, Unreal Engine, and Godot. 🔗 Learn more and get involved! #Rider2025 #EarlyAccess #GameDevelopment #Unity #UnrealEngine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Early Access Program for ReSharper and .NET Tools 2025.3 Is Here!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9718/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 09:01:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9718/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Early Access Program (EAP) for ReSharper and .NET Tools 2025.3 has officially launched! The initial preview build is now available for users to explore upcoming features. Your feedback is vital for enhancing these updates. Key highlights include faster startup with Out-of-Process mode on .NET Core and support for new C++26 features in ReSharper C++. Join the EAP and share your experiences! #ReSharper #NetTools #EarlyAccess #SoftwareDevelopment #CSharp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Farewell to Consoles</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9704/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:46:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9704/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Big changes are coming to JetBrains IDEs! Starting with the 2025.3 release, the term &amp;ldquo;query console&amp;rdquo; will be replaced with &amp;ldquo;query file.&amp;rdquo; This update aims to simplify the workflow and enhance discoverability for users. Historically, consoles were temporary areas for SQL writing, but they lacked integration within project structures, making them hard to find. The new query files will be part of your project, making them easier to manage and locate. Now, creating a query file is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQ: New AI Quotas</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9693/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9693/</guid>
      <description>📢 New AI quotas have been introduced, reducing previous limits based on early data. This change aligns usage with actual provider costs to ensure sustainability. 💡 Expect updates on pricing transparency and usage stats soon, helping users manage their AI credits better. 🔍 Remember, AI costs vary based on model type and input length. Tools and guides will be provided to improve usage efficiency. #AI #TechUpdates #Transparency #BusinessInsights #Sustainability</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 Early Access Program Is Open!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9681/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:46:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9681/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Early Access Program (EAP) for IntelliJ IDEA 2025.3 is now open! This program allows users to preview new features and improvements while providing feedback. EAP builds are free and can coexist with your stable version. Notable upcoming changes include a unified distribution, expanded free features, and enhanced support for Java 25, Spring Boot 4, and Kotlin. Explore the improvements in Kubernetes YAML file handling as well. #IntelliJIDEA #EAP #SoftwareDevelopment #Programming #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java 25 LTS and IntelliJ IDEA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9682/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 11:15:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9682/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Java developers! Java 25 LTS was released on September 16, 2025. This new version brings user-friendly features like compact source files, instance main methods, and flexible constructor bodies. IntelliJ IDEA is ready to support these changes, enhancing both stable and preview features. Key improvements also include better performance and memory efficiency. For those migrating from earlier versions like Java 21 or 17, be sure to check out the relevant updates. Learn how to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Constexpr Debugger</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9639/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 07:33:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9639/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing the Constexpr Debugger in CLion 2025.3 EAP! This tool allows developers to step through compile-time evaluations, inspect values, and understand why a constexpr expression fails. No more guessing from compiler notes! Key features include: 🔍 Step-by-step debugging 🔄 Compile-time reverse stepping 📊 Access to call stacks and variable values With the upcoming reflection support in C++26, this debugger lays the groundwork for future metacode debugging. #Cplusplus #Debugging #CLion&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GameDev Day 2025 Is Back in October!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9646/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9646/</guid>
      <description>🎮 Exciting news for game developers! JetBrains GameDev Day returns on October 21, 2025! This free, one-day online event focuses on creativity, storytelling, and community in game development. Join industry professionals as they share valuable insights on various topics, from improving workflows to designing accessible games. New this year: local watch parties! Connect with fellow developers in your city while participating in this global event. All sessions will be streamed live on YouTube&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your Voice Belongs Here: Creating Compelling KotlinConf Proposals [Livestream]</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9621/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:57:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9621/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Ready to elevate your speaking skills? Join the webinar &amp;ldquo;Your Voice Belongs Here&amp;rdquo; on October 14! This session is tailored for individuals from underrepresented groups in tech who have some speaking experience and want to present at KotlinConf. Learn what makes a compelling CFP, how to craft your proposal, and what reviewers seek. Connect, build confidence, and prepare to share your Kotlin journey! #KotlinConf #PublicSpeaking #TechInclusion #CFP #DiversityInTech</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieve Effortless GitHub Releases With a New Plugin for TeamCity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9606/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 10:55:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9606/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers using TeamCity! A new GitHub Releases Support plugin simplifies the process of publishing releases for open-source projects. No more custom scripts or authentication hassles—just a few clicks to publish builds as GitHub releases. To get started, download the plugin from the Marketplace and add it to your build configurations. Key features include setting release tags, titles, and asset paths easily. #GitHub #TeamCity #DevTools #OpenSource #Automation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains at the ICPC World Finals 2025 Baku</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9554/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 14:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9554/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The ICPC World Finals 2025 in Baku was a significant event, showcasing top student talent from around the globe. JetBrains was proud to support the competition and the community it fosters. 🎓 The Neapolis University Pafos team, Sigma++, participated and earned an Honors distinction. Andrey Ivanov from JetBrains emphasized the camaraderie and appreciation for those who organized the event. 🛠️ Attendees enjoyed activities at the JetBrains booth, including the Kotlin Challenge and interactions&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testing AI Coding Agents With TeamCity and SWE-bench</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9546/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 08:35:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9546/</guid>
      <description>AI coding agents are evolving into practical tools for developers. To assess their effectiveness, systematic testing is essential. At JetBrains, we developed an evaluation pipeline using TeamCity and SWE-bench to test our coding agent, Junie. This method enables us to measure performance across real-world tasks. Key metrics include solved-task percentage and performance stability, ensuring development decisions are data-driven. For more insights, explore our GitHub project! 🔗💻 #AICoding&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeamCity 2025.07.2 Is Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9532/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9532/</guid>
      <description>🚀 TeamCity has released version 2025.07.2, the second bug-fix update for the major release. This update addresses multiple issues, including problems with pipelines, pull request builds, and JDBC driver downloads. Alongside bug fixes, it also enhances performance and security. 🔒 Stay updated to ensure better compatibility and faster builds. You can upgrade easily through the automatic update feature or download it directly from the JetBrains website. For more details, check the release notes!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin 2.2.20 Released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9511/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 09:54:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9511/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kotlin 2.2.20 is here with key updates for web development! Kotlin/Wasm is now in Beta, featuring enhanced exception handling, improved npm dependency management, and built-in browser debugging support. Highlights include: - Swift export for Kotlin Multiplatform - Improved overload resolution for lambdas - Smaller binary sizes in Kotlin/Native - Long values as JavaScript BigInt in Kotlin/JS For detailed changes, check the release notes on GitHub. #Kotlin #WebDevelopment #Programming&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Junie Is Now Available in CLion: Supercharge Your C and C&#43;&#43; Development Today</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9509/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 07:26:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9509/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for C and C++ developers! With CLion version 2025.2.1, Junie, the AI coding agent by JetBrains, is now integrated in Beta. This integration provides enhanced project insights and tooling directly within the IDE. Developers can benefit from improved visibility, automatic task completion, and easy access to project details without leaving CLion. Explore features like Ask mode for Q&amp;amp;A and Code mode for generating tests and README files. #CLion #AI #CProgramming #CPlusPlus #JetBrains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPS 2025.2 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9472/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 14:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9472/</guid>
      <description>🚀 MPS 2025.2 has officially launched! This update enhances quality and stability while introducing key features. Users can now start MPS with OS-native launchers for easier access. The Show Node Info dialog has been modernized, and resolve-info updates during copy-paste have improved. 🔧 Notable changes include: - New binary launchers for Windows and Linux - FactoryMethodIcon support - Compatibility with Java 21 For more details, visit the What’s New page! #MPS2025 #SoftwareUpdate #Java21&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Investigating IntelliJ Platform UI Freezes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9473/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 12:26:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9473/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever experienced UI freezes in JetBrains IDEs? 🤔 This article delves into the reasons behind these freezes, primarily caused by the single-threaded nature of the Java AWT framework. When the event dispatch thread (EDT) is blocked, user interactions become unresponsive. To investigate, start by examining the thread dump, focusing on the AWT-EventQueue thread. Look for signs of lock acquisition issues, particularly the read-write lock, which can indicate background threads causing the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“GoLand Can Do That?” Ten Secret Superpowers You Might Not Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9438/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:05:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9438/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of GoLand! 🚀 In a recent article by John Arundel, he highlights ten powerful features of GoLand that many developers might not know about. From efficient searching and easy navigation to inline hints and error detection, these tools can enhance your productivity as a Go developer. 🛠️ Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on maximizing your coding efficiency! #GoLang #DeveloperTools #Productivity #CodingTips #GoLand</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Mellum Now Available on Amazon Bedrock Marketplace – For Free</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9396/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:56:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9396/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains Mellum is now available on the Amazon Bedrock Marketplace for free! This production-grade large language model (LLM) makes code completion easier and more accessible. With Mellum, you can deploy quickly, control costs, and enjoy zero extra model fees. It’s optimized for enterprise use, ensuring better performance and stability. Choose your GPU hardware, hit deploy, and integrate seamlessly into your engineering workflows. Explore Mellum today for instant access! 🌐💻 #JetBrains&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect MCP Servers to Junie in PhpStorm</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7783/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 14:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7783/</guid>
      <description>🔗 The Model Context Protocol (MCP) offers a standardized way to connect AI models with various tools and data sources. 💻 You can integrate Junie, JetBrains&amp;rsquo; AI coding agent, with multiple MCP servers or build your own using the new MCP PHP SDK. 🛠️ The MCP PHP SDK is a collaborative effort aimed at providing a reliable framework for PHP developers. For guidance on setup and configuration, refer to the MCP server documentation and the Junie MCP Settings in PhpStorm. #AI #MCP #PhpStorm #Junie&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Connect MCP Servers to Junie in PhpStorm</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7893/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 14:47:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7893/</guid>
      <description>🔗 The Model Context Protocol (MCP) is an open standard from Anthropic, designed to connect AI models seamlessly to various tools and data sources. 🛠️ JetBrains’ Junie AI coding agent can link with multiple MCP servers, either community-built or custom ones using the new MCP PHP SDK. This SDK, developed collaboratively, provides a framework for PHP developers. 📈 To integrate Junie with an MCP server in PhpStorm, ensure the server is accessible, configure Junie through the MCP Settings, and add&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7762/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 08:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7762/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Excited for September&amp;rsquo;s Java Annotated Monthly! This edition features updates on Java 25, set to release on September 16, 2025. Key enhancements include Compact Source Files, Flexible Constructor Bodies, and Scoped Values for better thread management. Additionally, IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2 supports these updates, including new debugging tools. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on the upcoming events and insights from Marit van Dijk! #Java25 #IntelliJIDEA #TechNews #SoftwareDevelopment #JavaCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7894/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 08:24:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7894/</guid>
      <description>🚀 September brings exciting updates in the latest Java Annotated Monthly! This edition features the much-anticipated Java 25 release on September 16, 2025, highlighting new features like Compact Source Files and improvements in performance. Marit van Dijk shares insights on these updates and the support in IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2. Don’t miss this month’s tech news and upcoming events! #Java25 #IntelliJ #TechNews #Kotlin #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Ways Static Code Analysis Can Improve Developer Experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7758/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7758/</guid>
      <description>Enhance developer experience with static code analysis! 🛠️ This tool examines code before execution, identifying issues early and enabling teams to deliver quality software efficiently. Key benefits include: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Faster feedback loops&lt;/strong&gt; - Immediate insights reduce waiting time. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Reduced cognitive load&lt;/strong&gt; - Helps developers focus on problem-solving. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Improved code quality&lt;/strong&gt; - Enforces standards for consistency. Discover how static analysis can streamline your workflow! 💻✨&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Set of Updates and Fixes for ReSharper and Rider 2025.2 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7742/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7742/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The first bug-fix update for ReSharper and Rider 2025.2 is now available! This release includes important fixes and quality improvements, along with performance optimizations. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t upgraded yet, check out the latest features in ReSharper and Rider. Key updates include Unity support in Command Line Tools and various fixes for C++ and IDE functionality. For the complete list of changes, visit our issue tracker. #ReSharper #Rider #SoftwareUpdate #DevTools #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The First Set of Updates and Fixes for ReSharper and Rider 2025.2 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7895/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7895/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The first bug-fix update for ReSharper and Rider 2025.2 is here! This update includes essential fixes, quality improvements, and performance optimizations. Key highlights include Unity support in Command Line Tools for ReSharper and enhanced functionality in Out-of-Process mode. For those yet to upgrade, check out the detailed blog posts on ReSharper and Rider 2025.2 for new features and improvements. 🔗 #ReSharper #Rider #SoftwareUpdate #DevTools #PerformanceBoost</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains JavaScript Day 2025 Registration Is Now Open</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7727/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 14:39:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7727/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for JavaScript enthusiasts! Registration is now open for the fifth edition of JetBrains JavaScript Day, a free online event set for October 2 at 9:00 am EDT / 3:00 pm CEST. Join us for insightful talks from industry leaders, covering topics from modern JavaScript tooling to open source project management. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on this opportunity to learn and engage! 📅 Register now and be part of the conversation! #JavaScriptDay #JetBrains #JavaScript #TechEvent #WebDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Annotation Handling in Kotlin 2.2: Less Boilerplate, Fewer Surprises</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7728/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7728/</guid>
      <description>Kotlin 2.2 introduces improved annotation handling, addressing common issues developers faced with annotations in frameworks like Spring and JPA. Previously, annotations applied to constructor parameters often did not validate properties during updates, leading to unexpected behavior. The new default rule ensures that annotations are applied to both constructor parameters and properties, streamlining code and reducing boilerplate. This update enhances validation consistency, allowing for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Annotation Handling in Kotlin 2.2: Less Boilerplate, Fewer Surprises</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7896/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 11:56:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7896/</guid>
      <description>Kotlin 2.2 introduces improved annotation handling, addressing common issues developers faced with frameworks like Spring and JPA. Previously, annotations could only validate object construction, leading to unexpected bugs. Now, with the new default rule, annotations will apply to both constructor parameters and properties, ensuring they function as intended during updates. This change reduces boilerplate code and aligns better with framework expectations. 🔗 Kotlin 2.2 is required to enable&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhanced Vulnerable API Detection in JetBrains IDEs and Qodana</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7663/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:20:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7663/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains has partnered with Mend.io to enhance code security in its tools. This collaboration enables IDEs and Qodana to identify vulnerable and malicious packages effectively. 📊 The new Vulnerable API feature in the Package Checker plugin utilizes enriched data to analyze open-source libraries, improving detection capabilities across various programming languages. 🔍 Users can easily enable inspections for vulnerable APIs in their IDE settings, ensuring their code remains secure&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Popular Python Frameworks and Libraries in 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7638/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:11:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7638/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exploring the evolving landscape of Python in 2025! This year&amp;rsquo;s survey highlights the most popular frameworks and libraries among Python developers. FastAPI stands out with a 38% usage rate, showcasing its strengths in building APIs and supporting AI/ML integrations. Django and Flask continue to be popular, but FastAPI&amp;rsquo;s modern approach and active community are making waves. Stay informed on the latest trends! #Python #FastAPI #WebDevelopment #MachineLearning #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotInsights | September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7615/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:39:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7615/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Did you know C# has a GOTO statement? While it exists, its use is debated. Welcome to dotInsights by JetBrains, your source for .NET updates! 🌟 This month&amp;rsquo;s spotlight is on Chris Woodruff, a Microsoft MVP and mentor in software development. He emphasizes API design and scalable architectures. Discover essential tips on using EF Core, the leading ORM for .NET developers. Learn about DbContext, modeling relationships, and querying efficiently. For more insights, check out the full newsletter!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RubyMine Is Now Free for Non-Commercial Use</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7616/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7616/</guid>
      <description>🚀 RubyMine is now available for free for non-commercial use! This change supports learners, open-source contributors, and developers working on personal projects. The goal is to make essential tools accessible for everyone in the Ruby community. Commercial use still requires the existing licensing model. 🎉 For full details on features and licensing, check the FAQ! #RubyMine #Ruby #Development #OpenSource #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meet Our Newest Innovators: Welcoming AI4SE Interns as JetBrains Employees!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7592/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 15:17:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7592/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting times at JetBrains as we welcome our new AI4SE interns! These recent graduates from TU Delft have transitioned from academic projects to full-time roles, applying their MSc thesis work in real-world settings. Meet Milan, Nadine, Saga, and Sergey, who gained hands-on experience during their internships and contributed to significant research. Their work will soon lead to journal publications! 📚 The AI4SE program, launched in 2023, combines academic research with industry&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The LSP API Is Now Available to All IntelliJ IDEA Users and Plugin Developers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7587/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 09:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7587/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The LSP API is now available to all IntelliJ IDEA users and plugin developers. Starting with IntelliJ IDEA Ultimate 2025.2, users can access a limited set of LSP features even after their subscription expires. This change aims to remove barriers for plugin developers and smaller language communities. In 2025.3, the Community Edition will be phased out, consolidating the installation process for all users. This allows for broader plugin development without&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICPC World Finals Livestream: ecnerwala and SecondThread Speed-Solving Kotlin Challenge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7550/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 19:29:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7550/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Join us live from the ICPC World Finals in Baku, Azerbaijan, on September 2, 2025, at 9:30 am UTC! Watch top programmers Andrew ‘ecnerwala’ He and David ‘SecondThread’ Harmeyer compete in a real-time Kotlin speed-solving challenge. Hosted by Sebastian Aigner from JetBrains, this event showcases coding mastery under time pressure. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the chance to see Kotlin&amp;rsquo;s strengths and get inspired to join the upcoming Kotlin Heroes contest! #ICPC #KotlinHeroes #CompetitiveProgramming #LiveEvent&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2.1 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7535/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 09:34:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7535/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA has released its first minor update: version 2025.2.1! You can easily update through the IDE, Toolbox App, or download it from the website. This update resolves key issues, including improved EAR artifact management and better SVG exports. For a full list of improvements, check the release notes. Happy coding! #IntelliJIDEA #Update #SoftwareDevelopment #Coding #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.1.5 Is Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7483/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 16:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7483/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA has released update v2025.1.5! You can easily update from the IDE, Toolbox App, or download it from the website. Key improvements include better performance during Google Meet screen sharing on macOS with a second monitor and enhancements to UrlClassLoader.getFiles. For details on resolved issues, check the release notes. Happy coding! 💻✨ #IntelliJIDEA #SoftwareUpdate #Programming #DeveloperTools #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koog 0.4.0 Is Out: Observable, Predictable, and Deployable Anywhere You Build</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7458/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 09:26:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7458/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The release of Koog 0.4.0 introduces significant improvements for developers. Key features include support for Langfuse and W&amp;amp;B Weave, enhanced observability with OpenTelemetry, and seamless Ktor integration. This version focuses on making agents more predictable and easier to deploy, while also supporting new models and platforms. Explore how these updates can streamline your development process! #Koog #DevTools #OpenTelemetry #Ktor #AIIntegration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper’s New Out-of-Process Engine Cuts Visual Studio startup UI freezes by 61%</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7459/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7459/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Visual Studio users! ReSharper 2025.2 introduces an out-of-process engine that significantly reduces UI freezes during analysis. With this update, analysis runs in a separate 64-bit worker, improving workflow by allowing the UI to remain responsive. Testing showed a 61% decrease in UI freezes during startup compared to the previous version. Stay tuned for more optimizations! ⚙️ #ReSharper #VisualStudio #SoftwareDevelopment #Productivity #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s Next for CLion: The 2025.3 Roadmap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7275/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 14:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7275/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are on the horizon for CLion with the upcoming 2025.3 release, set for November! Key priorities include: - Transitioning to the CLion Nova language engine as the default. - Enhancements to project formats and build tools. - Improved features for embedded development. Stay tuned for more details on these updates! #CLion #SoftwareDevelopment #TechUpdates #EmbeddedDevelopment #Programming</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Data Science With Kotlin: A Powerlifting Case Study</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7210/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:18:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7210/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of data science with Kotlin! 📊 In her latest article, Adele Carpenter shares insights on using Kotlin Notebooks to analyze a 3.3 million-row dataset from powerlifting competitions. Learn how to connect to a PostgreSQL data source, manipulate data with DataFrame, and visualize results using the Kandy library. Perfect for those who prefer a familiar environment over Python! #DataScience #Kotlin #Powerlifting #KotlinNotebooks #DataAnalysis</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ready for the Best School Year Ever? Join Our STEM Clubs, Camps, and Competitions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7211/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 07:45:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7211/</guid>
      <description>🎉 A new school year is here, bringing fresh opportunities in STEM! Join our free online Youth Clubs to enhance your skills in math, coding, and AI. Weekly sessions with expert instructors and a global community await you. 🔍 Explore the Math Club, AI Club, and Coding Club for tailored learning experiences. 🌐 Engage in competitions and prepare for olympiads with peers worldwide! #STEMEducation #YouthClubs #Math #Coding #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Kotlin Notebook Helps You Teach Programming</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7212/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 19:21:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7212/</guid>
      <description>Kotlin Notebook is transforming programming education by enabling a hands-on approach. 📚 This tool combines runnable code, Markdown explanations, and visualizations in one interactive environment, eliminating the need to switch between multiple platforms during lectures. Anastasiia Birillo, a former Kotlin lecturer, highlights how structured notebooks enhance learning by providing immediate outputs alongside explanations. This method supports interactive lectures effectively. Explore the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a CI/CD Pipeline for iOS Projects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7213/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:52:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7213/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Building an iOS CI/CD Pipeline? Kumar Harsh&amp;rsquo;s article outlines the importance of automating continuous integration and delivery for iOS apps. Without a CI/CD pipeline, developers face challenges like slower release cycles and increased errors. TeamCity Cloud is highlighted as a solution, supporting Swift, Objective-C, and Xcode integration. The article guides readers through setting up a pipeline, from version control integration to deploying apps on TestFlight. Learn how to streamline your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling Ruby Debuggers: byebug, debug gem, and the Power of RubyMine</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7177/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 07:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7177/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Attention Ruby developers! In the latest blog post from RubyMine, the focus is on the importance of mastering debuggers like byebug and the debug gem. These tools are essential for tracking down bugs effectively. The article also explores RubyMine&amp;rsquo;s debugging architecture and provides insights from Dmitry Pogrebnoy&amp;rsquo;s talk, &amp;ldquo;Demystifying Debugger&amp;rdquo;. An interesting experiment on the performance of these debuggers is included as well. Learn how often Ruby developers rely on debuggers, with data&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s Next for Kotlin Multiplatform and Compose Multiplatform – August 2025 Update</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7171/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:47:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7171/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates on Kotlin Multiplatform and Compose Multiplatform! In the next 6-12 months, key priorities include enhancing the iOS target for improved developer experience, enabling more web use cases, and refining IDE support. Compose Multiplatform is now in Beta for Web, with a focus on essential APIs and ecosystem components. Your feedback is crucial! 💻✨ #Kotlin #Multiplatform #Compose #WebDevelopment #DeveloperExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Tuning and Deploying GPT Models Using Hugging Face Transformers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6334/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 11:01:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6334/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of AI with Hugging Face Transformers! 🤖 Hugging Face has become essential for machine learning, offering a framework for models in text, vision, audio, and video. Fine-tuning models is key for improving performance on specific tasks, saving time and resources. ⏳ In the latest blog, learn how to fine-tune GPT models for better mathematical reasoning, and leverage the vast model repository on Hugging Face. Discover how to integrate and deploy these models effortlessly! 🌟&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin on the Backend – What’s New From KotlinConf 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6303/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 15:02:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6303/</guid>
      <description>KotlinConf 2025 showcased significant advancements in server-side Kotlin. 🌐 Key highlights include a strategic partnership with Spring for enhanced null-safety and Kotlin-centric tutorials. 📚 Developers are increasingly adopting Kotlin for backend, with notable insights shared by leaders from major tech companies. Ktor continues to evolve, offering support for modern scalable applications, including new features for dependency injection and server-driven UI development. For in-depth insights,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Drive Integration, Python 3.11 in Conda Environments, and Security improvements in Datalore 2025.4</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6304/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:12:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6304/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Datalore 2025.4 is now live! Key updates include support for Google Drive folders as data connections, allowing seamless access to files like CSV and JSON without manual uploads. Python 3.11 is the new default in conda environments, enhancing performance and security. Users can also customize their Python versions as needed. Security improvements have been made to address CSRF and XSS vulnerabilities, ensuring safer usage. #Datalore #DataScience #Python #CloudStorage #SecurityUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Next Edit Suggestions in JetBrains AI Assistant</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5067/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 16:14:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5067/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains AI Assistant has launched a new feature: next edit suggestions, now available in Beta for Java, Kotlin, and Python. These intelligent recommendations offer edit suggestions across your entire file, enhancing your coding experience. With integration into IDE-native actions, users can benefit from smart edits while maintaining workflow. The feature triggers as you type, providing instant suggestions highlighted in light purple. Global support ensures fast responses from regions like&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using SQL and databases in JetBrains IDEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5068/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 14:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5068/</guid>
      <description>📅 Check out our recent livestream on August 14, where we discussed working with SQL and databases in JetBrains IDEs. 💻 The session featured a demo on writing SQL queries and utilizing embedded database functionality, covering both simple and advanced tasks. 👤 Speaker Maxim Sobolevskiy, a PMM at JetBrains, shared his expertise gained from years of experience as an SQL developer. For updates on product news and future livestreams, follow DataGrip on X or visit our Blog! #JetBrains #SQL&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The State of Python 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5069/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 11:42:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5069/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting insights from the eighth annual Python Developers Survey, conducted by the Python Software Foundation and JetBrains! Michael Kennedy shares key trends and actions that can enhance your Python career. Notably, 86% of respondents use Python as their main programming language. The survey reveals that many Python developers are relatively new to programming, highlighting a shift in the community. For those relying on Python for their projects, this article offers valuable perspectives&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps for Startups: CI/CD from the Ground Up</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5070/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 10:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5070/</guid>
      <description>Startups can greatly benefit from adopting DevOps practices. This approach enhances agility, allowing quicker responses to market demands while maintaining software quality. 🚀 DevOps fosters collaboration between development and operations teams, streamlining processes and automating tasks. This leads to improved productivity and faster delivery times. 📈 With continuous feedback and automated testing, startups can refine their products efficiently, ensuring a better user experience. 💻 #DevOps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thinking about trying or upgrading to Datalore Cloud? This August, you can save 30%.</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5071/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 10:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5071/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Thinking about Datalore Cloud? This August, new users and trial teams can save 30% on their first payment! This offer is valid until August 31, 2025. Datalore provides tools for efficient data exploration and collaboration. Key features include smart code assistance, no-code automations, and interactive dashboards. Ready to upgrade? Visit the upgrade page and use code: DATALORE_CLOUD_25. #Datalore #DataScience #CloudComputing #Discount #UpgradeNow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Quarter, New Qodana 2025.2 Release Highlights</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5072/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:32:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5072/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in the Qodana 2025.2 release! The latest features include a new Insights dashboard, expanded Native mode support for Go and Python linters, and enhanced SSO functionality. The redesigned Taint Trace Explorer improves security analysis, making navigation easier and providing clearer descriptions for each trace step. Explore these advancements that enhance code quality and security! #Qodana #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment #SecurityAnalysis #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TeamCity 2025.07.1 Is Here</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4999/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4999/</guid>
      <description>🚀 TeamCity On-Premises 2025.07.1 is now available! This update addresses several issues, including authentication errors and display problems on the Project Overview page. It also brings performance and security enhancements. For seamless upgrades, you can use the automatic update feature or download directly from the JetBrains website. Stay updated for optimal performance and security! #TeamCity #SoftwareUpdate #DevOps #JetBrains #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next-Level Performance Improvements in ReSharper 2025.2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5000/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5000/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in ReSharper 2025.2! This release enhances performance with features like out-of-process support, improving solution startup speed and refactoring capabilities. Razor and Blazor handling has also been optimized, ensuring quicker responsiveness for developers. Check out the new Rename refactoring improvements for better progress reporting and reduced memory usage. #ReSharper #SoftwareDevelopment #PerformanceImprovements #VisualStudio #CodingEfficiency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ReSharper and the .NET Tools 2025.2 Are Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5001/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:40:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5001/</guid>
      <description>🚀 ReSharper and .NET tools 2025.2 are now available for download! This release features the public preview of ReSharper’s Out-of-Process mode, enhancing stability and performance. It supports the latest C# 14 and C++26 features, alongside numerous performance improvements. Key updates include faster refactoring, optimized Razor processing, and better logging with ILogger. Explore the new features and download the release candidate today! #ReSharper #DotNet #CSharp #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rider 2025.2 Is Here with Junie, In-IDE OpenTelemetry, Game Dev Upgrades, and More</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5002/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:39:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5002/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Rider 2025.2 has launched, enhancing development tools with new features. Meet Junie, the AI coding agent, now faster and more capable, offering high-level brainstorming and hands-on coding support. It also integrates with GitHub for efficient pull request management. The updated Monitoring tool window simplifies performance optimization, while the new OpenTelemetry plugin provides runtime metrics directly in your IDE. Explore the improvements and elevate your coding experience! 💻✨&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Fuzz Testing in CLion</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 09:17:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5003/</guid>
      <description>Discover the essentials of fuzz testing in CLion! 🧪✨ This article explains how fuzz testing helps identify hidden bugs that traditional methods might miss. It highlights the use of CI Fuzz, a tool by Code Intelligence, to execute fuzz tests, analyze results, and debug functions. Learn how to set up CI Fuzz in CLion and run tests effectively. This approach enhances code reliability by feeding unexpected data to your programs. #FuzzTesting #CLion #SoftwareTesting #CodeQuality #CI_Fuzz</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains Academy – August Digest</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4904/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4904/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Boost your learning this August with JetBrains Academy! Explore free tools and career-launching courses. Students can access the JetBrains Student Pack, used by top universities and companies like NASA and Google. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss your chance to win a MacBook Pro! Apply by September 12. New courses include mastering AI agents and tackling 100 Rust exercises. #JetBrainsAcademy #Learning #CareerDevelopment #Rust #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Simpler, More Transparent Model for AI Quotas</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4905/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 15:10:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4905/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting changes coming to JetBrains AI! Starting August 18, 2025, a new AI quota model will simplify subscriptions. Users can seamlessly extend usage beyond their quota with clear, real currency pricing. This update aims for transparency and better management of AI resources. Each subscription tier will align with its price, providing equivalent AI Credits. Additional credits can be purchased as needed. Stay tuned for more updates! #JetBrains #AI #TechUpdates #SubscriptionModel #Transparency</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightning-Fast Python: Mastering the uv Package Manager</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4906/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 13:13:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4906/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover the future of Python development with uv, a new package manager that is 10-100x faster than pip! Join our livestream recap from August 7, featuring experts Michael Kennedy and William Vincent. They discussed uv&amp;rsquo;s advanced features and practical migration strategies. Learn why Python developers are making the switch to this efficient tool! 🔧🐍 #Python #PackageManager #uv #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTalks</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debugging Transactions? Let Spring Debugger Do the Heavy Lifting</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4907/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:08:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4907/</guid>
      <description>Debugging transaction issues in Spring Framework can be challenging due to potential misconfigurations. The @Transactional annotation simplifies transaction management but can lead to complications. The Spring Debugger plugin aids in identifying and resolving these issues, streamlining the debugging process. A practical example illustrates how to manage bookmarks and categories, ensuring proper transaction handling. Watch the demonstration to see the Spring Debugger in action! 🎥🔧&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kodee’s Kotlin Roundup: 2.2.20-Beta2, Kotlin LSP Update, Shipaton 2025, and a New Face on the Foundation Board</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4908/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 09:07:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4908/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting updates from Kotlin-land! Kotlin 2.2.20-Beta2 has launched, featuring enhancements in Multiplatform, including Swift export as default and new web development targets. Kotlin ranks 15th in the 2025 Stack Overflow Developer Survey, showing steady growth in popularity. The Kotlin Language Server Protocol is also improved, enhancing core functionality. Stay tuned for more updates! 🚀📈 #Kotlin #Programming #DevCommunity #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataSpell Is Now an AI-First Tool for Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4909/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4909/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DataSpell 2025.2 is now an AI-first tool for data analysis! This release includes JetBrains AI Pro for free with every paid subscription, enhancing your data workflow. Users can access advanced AI tools and the latest models, including GPT-5. Key features include easier project creation and dedicated AI agents for tasks like managing files and connecting to databases. Explore these updates today! #DataAnalysis #JetBrains #AI #DataScience #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>dotInsights | August 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4910/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:09:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4910/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Did you know about C# null-coalescing operators? The ?? operator returns the left operand if it&amp;rsquo;s not null; otherwise, it returns the right operand. The ??= operator assigns the right operand’s value only if the left is null. Stay updated with .NET insights from JetBrains in their latest dotInsights newsletter! 📢 Catch talks on refactoring, testing, and more from industry experts! #CSharp #dotNet #SoftwareDevelopment #JetBrains #ProgrammingTips</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free JetBrains Student Pack – Your Toolkit for a Future in Tech</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4911/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 14:02:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4911/</guid>
      <description>Unlock your potential in tech with the JetBrains Student Pack! 🌟 This all-in-one toolkit provides professional-grade IDEs, programming courses, and AI tools, helping you build real-world projects and prepare for your career. Join over 3 million students using JetBrains tools trusted by top companies like Google and NASA. Apply by September 12, 2025, for a chance to win a MacBook Pro or iPad Pro! 🎉 #JetBrains #StudentPack #TechTools #FutureInTech #CodingEducation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains with its CLion IDE Is Now an Official ST Authorized Partner</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4912/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 09:06:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4912/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! JetBrains has officially joined the ST Partner Program, enhancing the CLion IDE for embedded developers. This collaboration focuses on optimizing development for STM32 and STM8 microcontrollers. Developers can expect seamless integration with ST toolchains, boosting productivity. STMicroelectronics is known for its semiconductor technologies, powering a variety of devices. Together, they aim to improve the development experience for embedded systems. Stay tuned for updates on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KotlinX RPC 0.9.1 Is Now Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4725/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:40:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4725/</guid>
      <description>🚀 KotlinX RPC 0.9.1 has been released with key improvements for stability and user experience. The library now decouples from KotlinX Serialization, allowing for more flexible gRPC setups. Resource management has been simplified, reducing potential errors in implementation. Strict mode is now the default, ensuring better API correctness. Ready to dive in? Start your project at start.ktor.io and explore samples on GitHub! #KotlinXRPC #Kotlin #Programming #SoftwareDevelopment #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Integrate Qodana Into TeamCity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4726/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 20:33:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4726/</guid>
      <description>Integrating Qodana with TeamCity can enhance your CI/CD pipeline by improving code quality and compliance. TeamCity’s features make it a reliable CI server, while Qodana’s static code analysis helps enforce coding standards. You can easily embed quality checks in your workflow with a dedicated build runner. Explore how to set up Qodana in your TeamCity environment for better software quality. 📊🛠️💻 #TeamCity #Qodana #CICD #CodeQuality #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Assistant, Junie and Kineto Now Support GPT-5 by OpenAI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4727/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4727/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from JetBrains! The latest model from OpenAI, GPT-5, is now integrated into AI Assistant, Junie, and Kineto. This update enhances coding capabilities, improving code quality and handling complex tasks more effectively. Junie, now powered by GPT-5, shows significant performance gains, making it easier to create production-ready code. To experience GPT-5, update to JetBrains IDE version 2025.2 and install the latest AI Assistant and Junie plugins. #JetBrains #GPT5 #AI #Coding&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Configuration Drift: The Pitfall of Local Machines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4117/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 12:51:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4117/</guid>
      <description>Configuration drift can disrupt project development when environments deviate from intended setups. This often leads to issues like inconsistent test results, broken CI/CD pipelines, and wasted debugging time. Common causes include differing package versions and unshared configuration changes. While teams try to maintain consistency through version pinning and environment files, lapses can still occur. Addressing configuration drift is essential for smoother collaboration. 🔍💻🔧 #DevOps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Java Annotated Monthly – August 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4118/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 11:17:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4118/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into the latest edition of Java Annotated Monthly for August 2025! This month covers Java, Kotlin, frameworks, and the evolving tech landscape. 📚 Explore insightful articles tailored for developers and teams, along with a special feature by A N M Bazlur Rahman, who shares his reflections on the future of development. 🤖 Don&amp;rsquo;t miss the AI corner, highlighting the readiness of AI integration in Java, especially with the upcoming JDK 25 release. #Java #Kotlin #TechTrends #AI #JavaDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s Fixed in IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4119/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:39:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4119/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2! This release introduces a standalone &amp;ldquo;What’s Fixed&amp;rdquo; overview, highlighting stability and quality improvements. Key areas of focus include enhanced Spring and Kotlin support, better remote development features, and performance upgrades. For the complete list of fixes, check the release notes. #IntelliJIDEA #SoftwareUpdates #Kotlin #SpringFramework #DevelopmentTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin Notebook Meets IntelliJ Platform: Advancing IDE Plugin Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4120/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 10:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4120/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting news for developers! JetBrains has introduced Kotlin Notebook, an interactive platform that enhances plugin development within IntelliJ IDEs. This tool allows users to write, run, and visualize Kotlin code in a dynamic environment, streamlining data analysis and prototyping. The integration with IntelliJ enables faster brainstorming and testing of plugin features. Ready to get started? Simply create a new Kotlin notebook and use the command &lt;code&gt;%use intellij-platform&lt;/code&gt; to load&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RustRover 2025.2 Is Now Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-540/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:19:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-540/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! RustRover 2025.2 is now available, featuring significant debugger enhancements. New functionalities include remote and on-chip support, improved borrow checker assistance, and additional Rust learning resources. Junie, the in-IDE coding agent, is now 30% faster and offers smarter code completion, enhancing your coding experience. Check out the updated features and improvements today! #RustRover #DevelopmentTools #Coding #RustLang #JetBrains</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kotlin DSL: What’s New?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-541/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-541/</guid>
      <description>🚀 TeamCity has introduced significant enhancements to the Kotlin DSL in recent releases! 📁 Users can now store Kotlin DSL files outside the .teamcity directory, improving visibility and convenience when working with IntelliJ IDEA. 🔄 Additionally, code reuse is simplified with the introduction of DSL libraries, allowing developers to share code across projects more efficiently. 📊 For those managing multiple branches, changes in DSL files can now better align with build configurations. Learn&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join the Livestream: How to work with SQL and Databases in JetBrains IDEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4121/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-4121/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Join our livestream, &amp;ldquo;How to Work With SQL and Databases in JetBrains IDEs,&amp;rdquo; on August 14, 2025, at 4:00 pm UTC (6:00 pm CET / 12:00 pm ET). Learn about SQL queries, database navigation, and data import/export. We&amp;rsquo;ll showcase features like text-to-SQL and user parameters. Don’t miss the chance to ask questions! A recording will be available on our YouTube channel afterward. 🔗 Register now to stay updated! #JetBrains #SQL #Databases #Livestream #DataGrip</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PhpStorm 2025.2 Is Now Available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-542/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 13:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-542/</guid>
      <description>🚀 PhpStorm 2025.2 is here! This release introduces several key features, including making Laravel Idea free for users and enhancing the remote development experience. Junie coding agent now supports the Model Context Protocol (MCP), allowing connections to databases and APIs. Additionally, enjoy a 30% speed increase in prompt processing and improved JetBrains AI tools. Explore the new features today! #PhpStorm #WebDevelopment #JetBrains #AI #SoftwareUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GoLand 2025.2 Is Now Out!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-543/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-543/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GoLand 2025.2 is here with exciting updates! Key features include enhanced support for HTTP servers, smarter inspections using data flow analysis (DFA), and a new non-blocking Welcome screen for faster access to tools. The update also improves golangci-lint integration for real-time code analysis. 🛠️ Explore the new capabilities and streamline your development process! #GoLand #SoftwareUpdate #CodingTools #Golang #DevCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Ideas Clickable With Kineto by JetBrains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-544/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 12:02:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-544/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Kineto by JetBrains! This new platform addresses the technical challenges faced when creating websites and apps. Kineto allows anyone to build their own app in just 20 minutes, without needing coding skills. It&amp;rsquo;s designed for small applications like personal blogs, fitness trackers, and more. With Kineto, your ideas can become reality effortlessly! Join the waitlist today! 📱✨ #Kineto #NoCode #AppDevelopment #JetBrains #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CLion 2025.2 Is Here: Better CLion Nova, Smarter Embedded Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-545/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 11:24:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-545/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CLion 2025.2 has been released! This update enhances the JetBrains IDE for C and C++ with several new features. Key improvements include an upgraded code formatter in CLion Nova, faster remote development, and live watches in the debugger for real-time variable monitoring. 🛠️ Additionally, the ESP32 debug server is now available for ESP-IDF projects. You can download CLion 2025.2 via the Toolbox App, as a snap package for Ubuntu, or as a patch update from version 2025.1. #CLion #JetBrains&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PyCharm 2025.2: AI Toolkit for AI Engineers and More!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-546/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 11:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-546/</guid>
      <description>Discover the new features in PyCharm 2025.2! 🚀 This release introduces the AI Toolkit, designed to support AI engineers with tools for experimentation, debugging, and deployment all within the IDE. Additionally, it marks the last version of PyCharm Community, paving the way for a unified PyCharm experience. Notable updates include enhancements to AI Assistant, Junie, and notebooks. Download the latest version today! 💻✨ #PyCharm #AIToolkit #SoftwareUpdate #Programming #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains is a Platinum Sponsor of the Godot Foundation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-547/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:11:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-547/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from JetBrains! We are proud to announce our Platinum Sponsorship of the Godot Foundation. Godot is an open-source game engine, driven by a community-focused approach and dedicated to supporting developers. The Godot Foundation plays a vital role in ensuring financial backing for the Godot Project. Our support enhances JetBrains Rider, which offers robust features for Godot development, including improved GDScript support in upcoming releases. Together, we&amp;rsquo;re committed to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2 Is Here!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-548/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 17:08:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-548/</guid>
      <description>🚀 IntelliJ IDEA 2025.2 has officially launched! This version offers updates aimed at enhancing productivity and code quality. Users can download it from the website, update through the IDE, or use the Toolbox App. Key highlights include smarter AI workflows, support for Java 25 Early Access, and improvements for Spring developers. For more details, visit the newly redesigned What’s New page. Check it out and explore the features today! 🔍💻 #IntelliJIDEA #SoftwareUpdates #Coding #Java&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JetBrains AI Assistant Update: Better Context, Greater Offline Flexibility, Deeper IDE Integration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-549/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 15:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-549/</guid>
      <description>🚀 JetBrains AI Assistant has received a significant update! Key features include smarter code completion with support for more languages and file types like SQL and Markdown. The improved Mellum model enhances context-awareness for better results. Project rules now allow for consistent instructions, making it easier to maintain coding standards across teams. Additionally, users can connect local models for offline flexibility and attach images in chats for quicker analysis. #JetBrains #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DataGrip and Database tools UX Survey #2 Results</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-550/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 14:01:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-550/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from the DataGrip community! The second UX Survey results are in, highlighting key improvements made from your feedback. Significant changes include faster introspection, editable results for SELECT queries, and new AI-powered features. The survey also expanded to gather insights on user experiences and team collaboration with database tools. Discover more about the findings and upcoming enhancements in DataGrip! #DataGrip #UXSurvey #DatabaseTools #AI #UserExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RubyMine 2025.2: Junie and AI Assistant Upgrades, Faster Rails Project Startup, Enhanced Bundler Management, and More</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-551/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:06:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-551/</guid>
      <description>🚀 RubyMine 2025.2 is here with exciting updates! The JetBrains AI Assistant has been enhanced, providing smarter code completion and project-specific context. Key features include improved ERB code support and project rules for consistency. You can now connect local AI models for offline use, plus enjoy expanded code suggestions and image attachments in chat. Explore the full details on our website! #RubyMine #AI #Coding #SoftwareDevelopment #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
