<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PlanetScale-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/planetscale-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PlanetScale-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/planetscale-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automating our changelog with Cursor commands</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14319/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14319/</guid>
      <description>🌟 PlanetScale is enhancing its workflow with Cursor commands to automate changelog entries. Each time they ship a feature, a markdown file is created and merged into their GitHub repository, ensuring updates are published promptly. Cursor simplifies this process by generating changelog entries from existing documentation, making it efficient and repeatable. Additionally, these commands can be launched directly from Slack, streamlining the pull request process. #Automation #Changelog&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postgres 18 is now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13939/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13939/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Postgres 18 is now available on PlanetScale! When creating a new database, version 18.1 is the default, with options to select earlier versions. Recent offerings include $5 single-node databases and $50 Metal databases. Key updates in Postgres 18 include: - Improved query performance with a new asynchronous I/O system. - Built-in support for UUIDv7. - Enhanced multi-column index usage with Skip Scan optimization. To upgrade from Postgres 17, create a new database and follow the online&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using MotherDuck with PlanetScale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13687/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13687/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for data professionals! PlanetScale now supports the pg_duckdb extension for Postgres, enhancing analytics capabilities with DuckDB. 🔗 This integration allows seamless OLTP and OLAP queries, simplifying data movement between formats. Users can offload heavy analytics queries to MotherDuck’s cloud, ensuring optimal application performance. 📈 For setup, enable pg_duckdb in your database, grant necessary permissions, and add your MotherDuck token. Check the documentation for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$50 PlanetScale Metal is GA for Postgres</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13688/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13688/</guid>
      <description>🚀 PlanetScale Metal for Postgres is now available at a new starting price of $50/month! This update introduces smaller sizes, starting from 1GiB of RAM, and offers eight storage options ranging from 10GB to 1.2TB. With improved flexibility, customers can decouple CPU and RAM from storage, allowing for optimized database performance tailored to specific workloads. Support for GCP is coming soon! #PlanetScale #Postgres #Database #CloudComputing #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered Postgres index suggestions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12951/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12951/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for PostgreSQL users! PlanetScale Insights now offers AI-powered index suggestions to enhance database performance. This feature analyzes your database workload and recommends new indexes to optimize query execution speed. By leveraging large language models (LLMs), the system identifies the best indexes while ensuring suggestions are validated for effectiveness. The process involves filtering query patterns and validating suggestions to guarantee substantial performance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$5 PlanetScale is live</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12182/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12182/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from PlanetScale! You can now create single node Postgres databases for just $5/month. These databases are production-ready and ideal for startups, side projects, and development. PlanetScale offers features like Query Insights and schema recommendations, enhancing your development experience. Additionally, the price for development branches has dropped to $5/month. As your needs grow, you can easily scale your database or switch to high availability mode. Start your journey&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Vitess 23</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11719/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11719/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Announcing Vitess 23! The latest version, 23.0.0, is now available, enhancing deployment and observability for MySQL workloads. Key updates include moving to MySQL 8.4 as the default version, improved metrics for better insights, and simplified monitoring through deprecations. Important upgrade notes for operators: ensure to follow specific steps when transitioning from MySQL 8.0 to 8.4. Explore the improvements and continue scaling with confidence! #Vitess23 #MySQL #DatabaseManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$50 PlanetScale Metal</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11675/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11675/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from PlanetScale! They are introducing a new entry point for Metal&amp;rsquo;s performance at just $50/month. This will make high-quality database performance more accessible to startups. Customers can soon allocate CPU and Memory independently from storage size, enhancing flexibility. The new M-class clusters will be available in AWS and GCP, offering impressive performance with unlimited I/O. Sign up to be notified about the upcoming smaller sizes! #PlanetScale #DatabasePerformance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Report on our investigation of the 2025-10-20 incident in AWS us-east-1</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11678/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11678/</guid>
      <description>On October 20, 2025, PlanetScale experienced a significant incident due to a DNS misconfiguration from a service provider. This led to two phases of disruptions affecting their control plane and some database branches in AWS us-east-1. During Phase 1, engineers noticed control plane issues, but customer databases remained operational. Phase 2 saw resource exhaustion, preventing new EC2 instance launches, impacting autoscaling for key customers. PlanetScale implemented measures to mitigate the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>$5 PlanetScale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11493/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11493/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from PlanetScale! They are introducing a new $5 plan, making their quality database services more accessible. The new PS-5 option offers a single node, non-HA mode, ideal for development and testing, without the cost of a multi-node setup. This change allows builders to scale efficiently as their needs grow, reducing migration stress during rapid growth. 🔗 Sign up for notifications on the single node release! #PlanetScale #Database #TechUpdates #Startup #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Postgres 17 vs 18</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10905/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10905/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Postgres 18 has arrived, showcasing major enhancements in read performance with async I/O and new I/O worker threads. The new io_method option allows users to control disk I/O behavior, introducing worker and io_uring modes. These aim to optimize performance, particularly for read operations. Benchmark tests using sysbench focused on read-only scenarios across various EC2 configurations. Results show that Postgres 18 in sync and worker modes outperformed version 17 on network-attached&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larger than RAM Vector Indexes for Relational Databases</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10325/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10325/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A new hybrid design for scalable vector indexes is making waves in relational databases like MySQL. This innovative approach addresses the challenges of indexing multi-dimensional vectors for real-world applications. Existing research often overlooks the practical needs of relational databases, particularly in terms of storage and transactional requirements. The solution incorporates a well-known data structure, Hierarchical Navigable Small Worlds (HNSW), that enhances approximate nearest&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partnering with Cloudflare to bring you the fastest globally distributed applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10052/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10052/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! PlanetScale has partnered with Cloudflare to simplify the setup of full-stack applications using Postgres and MySQL. With our new native integration, you can quickly connect PlanetScale databases to Cloudflare Workers, enhancing performance and reliability. Key benefits include: - Faster setup with just a few clicks - Optimized performance through connection pooling and caching - Reduced latency via intelligent edge caching This integration is available for both Postgres and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Processes and Threads</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10026/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Understanding Processes and Threads is vital for grasping how operating systems function. This interactive article breaks down these key concepts and their role in database performance. 🖥️ Processes serve as the foundation for software execution, allowing multitasking on your computer. CPU and RAM are the primary components that work together to execute code and manage data. 📊 The article also explores instruction sets, explaining how CPUs process commands. Furthermore, it highlights the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlanetScale for Postgres is now GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9883/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9883/</guid>
      <description>🚀 PlanetScale for Postgres is now generally available! To create a Postgres database, simply log into your PlanetScale account and select Postgres. If you&amp;rsquo;re migrating from another provider, check out the available migration guides or contact the sales team for assistance. Hundreds of companies are already using PlanetScale for their production workloads, with success stories highlighting their experiences. Learn more about our Postgres sharding solution, Neki, which is designed to handle&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postgres High Availability with CDC</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9622/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9622/</guid>
      <description>Postgres High Availability can face challenges with Change Data Capture (CDC). The design of Postgres’ replication introduces complexities that may stall failover. The primary system emits Write Ahead Logs (WAL) to standbys. However, if a CDC client lags, it can prevent effective failover, as the logical replication slot on the primary depends on the client&amp;rsquo;s progress. Postgres 17 introduced logical replication failover, but eligibility for promotion has specific requirements. If the CDC&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Neki</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-6038/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-6038/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the database world! Today, the team behind Vitess announced Neki, a new sharded Postgres solution. Neki aims to bring the power of explicit sharding to Postgres users, leveraging insights from extensive experience with Vitess. This initiative is not a fork of Vitess but a fresh architecture designed to handle demanding workloads effectively. Stay updated on Neki&amp;rsquo;s development by signing up at neki.dev! #Neki #Postgres #Databases #OpenSource #Vitess</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
