<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PlanetScale-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/planetscale-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PlanetScale-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/planetscale-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Benchmarking Postgres 17 vs 18</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10905/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10905/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Postgres 18 has arrived, showcasing major enhancements in read performance with async I/O and new I/O worker threads. The new io_method option allows users to control disk I/O behavior, introducing worker and io_uring modes. These aim to optimize performance, particularly for read operations. Benchmark tests using sysbench focused on read-only scenarios across various EC2 configurations. Results show that Postgres 18 in sync and worker modes outperformed version 17 on network-attached&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larger than RAM Vector Indexes for Relational Databases</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10325/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10325/</guid>
      <description>🚀 A new hybrid design for scalable vector indexes is making waves in relational databases like MySQL. This innovative approach addresses the challenges of indexing multi-dimensional vectors for real-world applications. Existing research often overlooks the practical needs of relational databases, particularly in terms of storage and transactional requirements. The solution incorporates a well-known data structure, Hierarchical Navigable Small Worlds (HNSW), that enhances approximate nearest&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Partnering with Cloudflare to bring you the fastest globally distributed applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10052/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10052/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! PlanetScale has partnered with Cloudflare to simplify the setup of full-stack applications using Postgres and MySQL. With our new native integration, you can quickly connect PlanetScale databases to Cloudflare Workers, enhancing performance and reliability. Key benefits include: - Faster setup with just a few clicks - Optimized performance through connection pooling and caching - Reduced latency via intelligent edge caching This integration is available for both Postgres and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Processes and Threads</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10026/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Understanding Processes and Threads is vital for grasping how operating systems function. This interactive article breaks down these key concepts and their role in database performance. 🖥️ Processes serve as the foundation for software execution, allowing multitasking on your computer. CPU and RAM are the primary components that work together to execute code and manage data. 📊 The article also explores instruction sets, explaining how CPUs process commands. Furthermore, it highlights the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PlanetScale for Postgres is now GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9883/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9883/</guid>
      <description>🚀 PlanetScale for Postgres is now generally available! To create a Postgres database, simply log into your PlanetScale account and select Postgres. If you&amp;rsquo;re migrating from another provider, check out the available migration guides or contact the sales team for assistance. Hundreds of companies are already using PlanetScale for their production workloads, with success stories highlighting their experiences. Learn more about our Postgres sharding solution, Neki, which is designed to handle&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Postgres High Availability with CDC</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9622/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9622/</guid>
      <description>Postgres High Availability can face challenges with Change Data Capture (CDC). The design of Postgres’ replication introduces complexities that may stall failover. The primary system emits Write Ahead Logs (WAL) to standbys. However, if a CDC client lags, it can prevent effective failover, as the logical replication slot on the primary depends on the client&amp;rsquo;s progress. Postgres 17 introduced logical replication failover, but eligibility for promotion has specific requirements. If the CDC&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Neki</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-6038/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-6038/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the database world! Today, the team behind Vitess announced Neki, a new sharded Postgres solution. Neki aims to bring the power of explicit sharding to Postgres users, leveraging insights from extensive experience with Vitess. This initiative is not a fork of Vitess but a fresh architecture designed to handle demanding workloads effectively. Stay updated on Neki&amp;rsquo;s development by signing up at neki.dev! #Neki #Postgres #Databases #OpenSource #Vitess</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
