<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kubernetes-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/kubernetes-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kubernetes-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/kubernetes-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Uniform API server access using clientcmd</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-19-14662/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-19-14662/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/feed.xml&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/blog/2026/01/19/clientcmd-apiserver-access/&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35: Restricting executables invoked by kubeconfigs via exec plugin allowList added to kuberc</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-09-14399/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-09-14399/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.35 introduces a new feature: the credential plugin policy and allowlist. This enhancement allows users to control what executables kubeconfigs can invoke, improving security against potential supply-chain attacks. Users can manage this by editing the kuberc configuration file without writing code. For more details, check the official documentation! 🔍 #Kubernetes #DevOps #CloudSecurity #kubeconfig #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35: Mutable PersistentVolume Node Affinity (alpha)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-08-14361/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-08-14361/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.35 introduces mutable PersistentVolume node affinity in alpha, allowing more flexible online volume management. Previously immutable, this change lets administrators adapt to evolving storage needs without data loss. With features like live migration to regional disks, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for Pods to access the right nodes. However, caution is advised: race conditions may arise when updating node affinity. Future integration with CSI aims to streamline this process. 🔧 Feedback is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35: A Better Way to Pass Service Account Tokens to CSI Drivers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14330/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-07-14330/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.35 introduces a significant update for CSI drivers using service account tokens. Previously, tokens were passed via the volume_context field, which is not ideal for sensitive data. With the new beta feature, tokens can now be sent through the secrets field in NodePublishVolumeRequest, enhancing security. 🔒 This opt-in mechanism allows existing drivers to continue functioning while enabling a smoother transition to safer practices for those ready to adopt it. 🛠️ #Kubernetes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35: Extended Toleration Operators to Support Numeric Comparisons (Alpha)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14247/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-05-14247/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.35 introduces Extended Toleration Operators, allowing numeric comparisons for tolerations. With new Gt (Greater Than) and Lt (Less Than) operators, users can make smarter scheduling decisions based on specific thresholds, enhancing SLA-based placements and cost efficiency. This alpha feature aims to optimize workload distribution while maintaining the safety model of taints. For more info, check the Kubernetes community! 🔗 #Kubernetes #CloudComputing #DevOps #TechNews #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35: New level of efficiency with in-place Pod restart</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-02-14211/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-02-14211/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes 1.35 introduces the Restart All Containers feature, enabling efficient in-place restarts of Pods. This is crucial for AI/ML workloads, reducing overhead and enhancing recovery processes. By allowing full resets without recreating Pods, developers can focus more on training logic while Kubernetes handles failures effectively. Enable this feature by activating the RestartAllContainersOnContainerExits gate. #Kubernetes #AI #MachineLearning #DevOps #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes 1.35: Enhanced Debugging with Versioned z-pages APIs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-31-14196/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-31-14196/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes 1.35 enhances z-pages with structured, machine-parseable responses. This update improves debugging for control plane components like kube-apiserver and kube-controller-manager. Now, endpoints /statusz and /flagz support JSON responses while maintaining backward compatibility with plain text. This makes it easier to automate monitoring and troubleshoot issues. For more insights and how to use these features, check the documentation! 📊🔍 #Kubernetes #DevOps #CloudNative #Debugging&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35: Watch Based Route Reconciliation in the Cloud Controller Manager</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-30-14190/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-30-14190/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.35 introduces a new feature for the Cloud Controller Manager (CCM) that enhances route reconciliation. The feature gate, CloudControllerManagerWatchBasedRoutesReconciliation, allows the route controller to use watch-based informers, reducing unnecessary API requests when no changes occur. This feature can be enabled with the command: &lt;code&gt;--feature-gate=CloudControllerManagerWatchBasedRoutesReconciliation=true&lt;/code&gt;. For more details, check out KEP-5237. #Kubernetes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35: Introducing Workload Aware Scheduling</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-29-14179/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-29-14179/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.35 introduces significant advancements in workload scheduling, addressing the complexities of managing large workloads. The new Workload API allows users to define scheduling requirements for multi-Pod applications, including gang scheduling for all-or-nothing placements. This ensures efficiency for tasks like machine learning jobs. Additionally, the release includes opportunistic batching, which speeds up the scheduling process for identical Pods without user intervention&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35: Fine-grained Supplemental Groups Control Graduates to GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14139/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14139/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.35 has officially launched fine-grained supplemental groups control as a General Availability feature! This new field, supplementalGroupsPolicy, enhances control over supplemental groups in Linux containers, improving security and transparency of UID/GID details. If upgrading from v1.32 or earlier, note that there are behavioral changes since the beta version. Learn more about how this impacts your pods and security practices! #Kubernetes #DevOps #CloudComputing #Security&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35: Kubelet Configuration Drop-in Directory Graduates to GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14118/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-22-14118/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in Kubernetes v1.35! The kubelet configuration drop-in directory is now generally available, simplifying configuration management across diverse clusters. This feature allows administrators to specify a directory for kubelet configuration files, which are automatically merged with the main config. As clusters grow, managing various settings becomes crucial. This stable release provides a solution for configuration drift, customization needs, and operational overhead. For&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avoiding Zombie Cluster Members When Upgrading to etcd v3.6</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-21-14095/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-21-14095/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for etcd Users! 🚨 When upgrading to etcd v3.6, always start with v3.5.26 or later. This step ensures automatic repair of your cluster and prevents the issue of &amp;ldquo;zombie members,&amp;rdquo; which can disrupt operations. To upgrade safely: 1️⃣ Update to v3.5.26+ 2️⃣ Confirm all members are healthy 3️⃣ Proceed to v3.6 If you can&amp;rsquo;t access v3.5.26, delay your upgrade. Stay informed! 🔍 #etcd #UpgradeGuide #ClusterManagement #TechTips #DatabaseManagement</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes 1.35: In-Place Pod Resize Graduates to Stable</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14068/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-19-14068/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes 1.35 has officially made the In-Place Pod Resize feature stable! This marks a significant advancement after over 6 years of development. 🔧 With this feature, CPU and memory resources can now be modified within a running Pod without disruption, enhancing resource efficiency for workloads. 📈 It enables seamless vertical autoscaling and allows workloads to adjust resources dynamically, catering to transient needs without downtime. For detailed usage instructions, check the official&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35: Job Managed By Goes GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14036/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-14036/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in Kubernetes v1.35! The .spec.managedBy feature is now generally available, enabling external Job controllers to manage Job reconciliation. This update supports multi-cluster batch scheduling, allowing a Management Cluster to dispatch Jobs while Worker Clusters execute them. Users can track Job progress in real-time without accessing Worker Clusters. The .spec.managedBy field allows for delegation, with two operational modes: standard and delegation. This flexibility supports&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35: Timbernetes (The World Tree Release)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13974/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13974/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.35 has arrived, introducing 60 enhancements, including 17 stable, 19 beta, and 22 alpha features! 🔧 Key updates: - &lt;strong&gt;Stable&lt;/strong&gt;: In-place updates for Pod resources allow CPU and memory adjustments without restarts. - &lt;strong&gt;Beta&lt;/strong&gt;: Native workload identity simplifies certificate management with automated rotation. 📅 Note: The release also includes deprecations and removals, so be sure to check the details. #Kubernetes #OpenSource #DevOps #K8sRelease #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.35 Sneak Peek</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13055/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13055/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.35 is on the horizon! Key updates include: 🔹 Removal of cgroup v1 support, urging migration to cgroup v2 for improved resource control. 🔹 Deprecation of kube-proxy&amp;rsquo;s ipvs mode to streamline the codebase. 🔹 Final support for containerd v1.X, requiring upgrades to version 2.0 or later. Stay informed about feature enhancements like in-place updates for Pod resources and native workload identity with Pod certificates. #Kubernetes #CloudComputing #DevOps #K8s #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes Configuration Good Practices</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13030/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13030/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes configuration is crucial for successful deployments. Key practices include using the latest stable API version and storing configurations in version control systems like Git for easy rollback. YAML is preferred over JSON for readability, and keeping manifests minimal helps with debugging. Group related objects together and use annotations for clarity. Avoid creating Pods directly; instead, utilize Deployments and Jobs for better management. Learn more about these best practices for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingress NGINX Retirement: What You Need to Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12099/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12099/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for Kubernetes Users 🚨 Kubernetes SIG Network and the Security Response Committee have announced the retirement of Ingress NGINX, effective March 2026. After this date, there will be no more releases, bug fixes, or security updates. Existing deployments will remain functional, and installation artifacts will still be accessible. Users are encouraged to migrate to the Gateway API or other alternative Ingress controllers listed in the Kubernetes documentation. For further&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gateway API 1.4: New Features</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11942/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11942/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/feed.xml&#34;&gt;Kubernetes Blog&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kubernetes.io/blog/2025/11/06/gateway-api-v1-4/&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7 Common Kubernetes Pitfalls (and How I Learned to Avoid Them)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11079/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11079/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Navigating Kubernetes can be challenging. Here are 7 common pitfalls to avoid: 1️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Resource Requests &amp;amp; Limits&lt;/strong&gt;: Always specify CPU and memory needs to prevent performance issues. 2️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Liveness &amp;amp; Readiness Probes&lt;/strong&gt;: Set these up to ensure your containers are healthy and ready to serve traffic. 3️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Log Reliance&lt;/strong&gt;: Don’t depend solely on container logs; centralize them for better visibility. 4️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Environment Consistency&lt;/strong&gt;: Customize settings for dev, staging, and production to avoid&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spotlight on Policy Working Group</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-18-11048/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-18-11048/</guid>
      <description>The Policy Working Group has successfully completed its mission in the Kubernetes ecosystem. 🌐 Focused on developing a universal policy architecture, the group aimed to standardize policies for better management and security of Kubernetes clusters. Their work included creating the Policy Reports API and producing several important whitepapers. 📄 Insights from co-chairs Jim Bugwadia, Poonam Lamba, and Andy Suderman highlight the group&amp;rsquo;s collaborative approach and its involvement with other&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Headlamp Plugin for Karpenter - Scaling and Visibility</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10467/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10467/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The new Headlamp Karpenter Plugin enhances Kubernetes management by providing real-time visibility into Karpenter’s activities. With this plugin, users can explore how Karpenter resources connect to Kubernetes objects, view live metrics, and track scaling events as they occur. Key features include a map view of resources, insights on scaling decisions, and a configuration editor with validation support. The plugin aims to simplify the understanding and debugging of autoscaling behavior in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Changed Block Tracking API support (alpha)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10057/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10057/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Kubernetes users! The alpha support for the Changed Block Tracking API is here. This enhancement allows CSI storage drivers to identify modified blocks in PersistentVolume snapshots, leading to faster and more efficient backup operations. 🔍 Changed block tracking eliminates the need to scan entire volumes, focusing only on changed data. Currently, it supports block volumes only, which streamlines backup processes for large datasets. 📈 This API addresses challenges like&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Pod Level Resources Graduated to Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9893/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9893/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from the Kubernetes community! The Pod Level Resources feature has graduated to Beta in v1.34 and is now enabled by default. This update allows users to define CPU and memory resources for the entire Pod, streamlining resource management and reducing the need for per-container specifications. Pod-level resources enhance efficiency by enabling containers within a Pod to share unused resources, preventing bottlenecks during peak times. For those ready to explore, ensure your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Recovery From Volume Expansion Failure (GA)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9840/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9840/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 has introduced a significant update for PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs). Now, if you make a mistake while expanding your volumes, you can easily correct it without requiring admin access. Simply reduce the requested size before the expansion completes, and Kubernetes will handle the rest. 💻 This version also enhances error handling and observability during volume expansions. New API fields allow you to monitor progress and errors effectively. Explore these features and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: DRA Consumable Capacity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9799/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9799/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 introduces DRA Consumable Capacity, enhancing Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA) for better resource management. This feature allows multiple Pods to share devices more efficiently, accommodating specific workload needs. 🔑 Key benefits include: - Device sharing across multiple ResourceClaims. - Improved resource allocation for portions of devices. - New DistinctAttribute constraint to prevent duplicate allocations. To explore more about enabling this feature and its&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Pods Report DRA Resource Health</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9762/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9762/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 introduces a new alpha feature that enhances visibility into the health of specialized hardware in clusters, crucial for AI/ML workloads. This update allows Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA) drivers to report device health directly in a Pod’s status field, aiding quick diagnosis of issues. With the new gRPC health service and integration with Kubelet, operators can now identify hardware failures more efficiently, saving valuable time in troubleshooting. Explore this feature&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Moving Volume Group Snapshots to v1beta2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9705/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9705/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 has moved volume group snapshots to a second beta. 📦✨ This feature allows users to take crash consistent snapshots of multiple volumes using extension APIs. It relies on a label selector to group PersistentVolumeClaims for better snapshot management. Currently, it is supported only for CSI volume drivers. In this beta, a new VolumeSnapshotInfo struct has been introduced, enhancing snapshot identification and management. The project aims for general availability in future&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Decoupled Taint Manager Is Now Stable</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9667/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9667/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 introduces a stable Decoupled Taint Manager! This update separates the node lifecycle management from pod eviction. A new taint eviction controller now handles pod evictions, while the node lifecycle controller focuses on applying taints. The feature gate SeparateTaintEvictionController is now GA, and users can disable taint-based eviction if needed. For more details, check the KEP and previous announcements. A big thank you to all contributors for their efforts! 🙌&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Autoconfiguration for Node Cgroup Driver Goes GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9627/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9627/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 introduces a significant improvement in cgroup driver configuration. The new feature, KubeletCgroupDriverFromCRI, allows the kubelet to automatically detect the cgroup driver from the CRI implementation. This aims to reduce configuration issues for cluster admins. It&amp;rsquo;s important to ensure your CRI is updated: - containerd: Needs v2.0.0 or later - CRI-O: Needs v1.28.0 or later Kubernetes is also deprecating containerd v1.y support, with the last supported version being v1.35&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Mutable CSI Node Allocatable Graduates to Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9601/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9601/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Kubernetes users! The Mutable CSI Node Allocatable feature has officially graduated to Beta in the v1.34 release. This update allows CSI drivers to dynamically adjust attachable volume counts, improving the accuracy of stateful pod scheduling and reducing issues with outdated capacity information. 🔧 With two update mechanisms—periodic and reactive—Kubernetes enhances pod placement reliability. To enable this feature, activate the MutableCSINodeAllocatableCount gate on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Use An Init Container To Define App Environment Variables</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9536/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9536/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 introduces an alpha feature that simplifies how environment variables are set for containers. You can now define environment variables directly from a file in an emptyDir volume, without the need for mounting it into the main container. This approach streamlines app configuration and reduces API calls. Keep in mind, while it can handle sensitive data, security measures should be in place to protect node access. #Kubernetes #DevOps #CloudComputing #Containers #K8s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Snapshottable API server cache</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9504/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9504/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 introduces the snapshottable API server cache, now in Beta. This feature enhances the API server&amp;rsquo;s performance and stability by allowing most read requests to be served from cache. Key improvements include consistent reads and efficient handling of large responses. The new cache generates lightweight snapshots, ensuring predictable memory usage and reducing load on etcd. This marks a significant step towards a more resilient Kubernetes environment. 🌐✨ #Kubernetes #API&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: VolumeAttributesClass for Volume Modification GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9451/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9451/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 introduces the VolumeAttributesClass API, now in General Availability (GA). This enhancement allows users to dynamically modify volume attributes within Kubernetes. It acts as a profile for storage, enabling scalability, cost optimization, and simplified operations. Key updates include: - Explicit cancel support for infeasible volume modifications. - Quota enforcement on PersistentVolumeClaims based on VolumeAttributesClass. Supported by AWS EBS and GCE Persistent Disk CSI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Pod Replacement Policy for Jobs Goes GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7797/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7797/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 introduces the Pod Replacement Policy feature, now generally available. This allows users to manage how Pods are replaced in Jobs, addressing issues with overlapping Pods that can occur during terminations. You can choose between two policies: 1. &lt;strong&gt;TerminatingOrFailed&lt;/strong&gt; (default) - Replaces Pods immediately upon termination. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Failed&lt;/strong&gt; - Replaces Pods only after the previous ones have fully terminated. This enhancement is particularly useful for workloads requiring strict&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: PSI Metrics for Kubernetes Graduates to Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7768/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7768/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Kubernetes users! As of v1.34, Pressure Stall Information (PSI) Metrics has graduated to Beta. PSI helps quantify resource pressure by measuring stalled tasks due to contention, providing a clearer view of CPU, memory, and I/O performance. Metrics are available via the Summary API and Prometheus endpoints. 📊 To enable PSI metrics, ensure your nodes run Linux kernel 4.20+ and enable the KubeletPSI feature gate. This allows for better resource management and performance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Service Account Token Integration for Image Pulls Graduates to Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7712/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7712/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 has officially moved Service Account Token Integration for Kubelet Credential Providers to beta. This update enhances security by reducing reliance on long-lived image pull secrets. 🔒 Key changes include a required &lt;code&gt;cacheType&lt;/code&gt; field in the configuration and improved security isolation for image pulls. This ensures that only authorized pods can access specific container images. 🛡️ For more details, check out the Kubernetes documentation. #Kubernetes #DevOps #CloudSecurity #K8s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Introducing CPU Manager Static Policy Option for Uncore Cache Alignment</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7647/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7647/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 has introduced a new feature: the CPU Manager Static Policy Option, prefer-align-cpus-by-uncorecache, now in beta. This option optimizes performance for workloads on processors with a split uncore cache architecture, enhancing efficiency by reducing latency between CPU cores. To enable it, update your kubelet configuration. This feature is particularly beneficial for applications like telco systems but may vary based on workload types. #Kubernetes #CloudComputing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: DRA has graduated to GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7599/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7599/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes 1.34 is now live, featuring significant advancements in Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA)! Key highlights include the core of DRA graduating to General Availability (GA), ensuring stability and confidence for users. Key features have also moved to beta, enhancing control and flexibility in resource management. Notable updates include improved admin access labeling and prioritized device lists for workloads. Explore new alpha features aimed at simplifying resource management for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Finer-Grained Control Over Container Restarts</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7552/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7552/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes 1.34 introduces an alpha feature called Container Restart Policy and Rules. This feature allows developers to set individual restart policies for each container in a Pod, moving beyond the previous single policy for all containers. 🔧 Users can now define restart rules based on exit codes, offering more control for complex workloads. For instance, you can ensure that an ML training job restarts only on retriable errors without rescheduling the entire Pod. 📦 The new capability is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: User preferences (kuberc) are available for testing in kubectl 1.34</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7520/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7520/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Kubernetes users! The Kubernetes v1.34 release introduces user preferences in kubectl, now in beta. This feature allows you to set default options, like enabling interactive delete, and define custom aliases to streamline your workflow. To configure, place your preferences in a &lt;code&gt;kuberc&lt;/code&gt; file, located in your kubeconfig directory. Check out the official documentation for more details! #Kubernetes #kubectl #DevOps #CloudComputing #UserPreferences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Of Wind &amp; Will (O&#39; WaW)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7447/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7447/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 is here, featuring 58 enhancements! This release includes 23 stable, 22 beta, and 13 alpha features, showcasing the strength of its development cycle. 🌬 The theme &amp;ldquo;Of Wind &amp;amp; Will&amp;rdquo; highlights the community&amp;rsquo;s resilience in navigating challenges. Key updates include: - &lt;strong&gt;Stable&lt;/strong&gt;: Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA) now enables better device management. - &lt;strong&gt;Beta&lt;/strong&gt;: Short-lived ServiceAccount tokens enhance security for image pulls. - &lt;strong&gt;Alpha&lt;/strong&gt;: KYAML introduces a new, safer YAML&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuning Linux Swap for Kubernetes: A Deep Dive</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5779/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5779/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes is set to introduce the NodeSwap feature in version 1.34, allowing Linux nodes to utilize swap for improved resource management. This marks a shift from the traditional approach of disabling swap for performance. However, enabling swap requires careful tuning of Linux kernel parameters to avoid performance issues and manage memory pressure effectively. Key parameters include &lt;code&gt;vm.swappiness&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;vm.min_free_kbytes&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;vm.watermark_scale_factor&lt;/code&gt;. Testing various configurations can&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Headlamp AI Assistant</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5780/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5780/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! The Headlamp AI Assistant is here to enhance Kubernetes management and troubleshooting. This new plugin allows users, regardless of experience, to ask questions like &amp;ldquo;Is my application healthy?&amp;rdquo; and receive actionable insights. 🛠️ With a conversational UI powered by Large Language Models, users can now get contextual help directly from their Headlamp interface. Try it out today and streamline your Kubernetes operations! #Kubernetes #AI #TechInnovation #Headlamp #DevOps</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
