<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kubernetes-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/kubernetes-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kubernetes-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/kubernetes-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Recovery From Volume Expansion Failure (GA)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9840/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9840/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 has introduced a significant update for PersistentVolumeClaims (PVCs). Now, if you make a mistake while expanding your volumes, you can easily correct it without requiring admin access. Simply reduce the requested size before the expansion completes, and Kubernetes will handle the rest. 💻 This version also enhances error handling and observability during volume expansions. New API fields allow you to monitor progress and errors effectively. Explore these features and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: DRA Consumable Capacity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9799/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9799/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 introduces DRA Consumable Capacity, enhancing Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA) for better resource management. This feature allows multiple Pods to share devices more efficiently, accommodating specific workload needs. 🔑 Key benefits include: - Device sharing across multiple ResourceClaims. - Improved resource allocation for portions of devices. - New DistinctAttribute constraint to prevent duplicate allocations. To explore more about enabling this feature and its&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Pods Report DRA Resource Health</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9762/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9762/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 introduces a new alpha feature that enhances visibility into the health of specialized hardware in clusters, crucial for AI/ML workloads. This update allows Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA) drivers to report device health directly in a Pod’s status field, aiding quick diagnosis of issues. With the new gRPC health service and integration with Kubelet, operators can now identify hardware failures more efficiently, saving valuable time in troubleshooting. Explore this feature&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Moving Volume Group Snapshots to v1beta2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9705/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9705/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 has moved volume group snapshots to a second beta. 📦✨ This feature allows users to take crash consistent snapshots of multiple volumes using extension APIs. It relies on a label selector to group PersistentVolumeClaims for better snapshot management. Currently, it is supported only for CSI volume drivers. In this beta, a new VolumeSnapshotInfo struct has been introduced, enhancing snapshot identification and management. The project aims for general availability in future&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Decoupled Taint Manager Is Now Stable</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9667/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9667/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 introduces a stable Decoupled Taint Manager! This update separates the node lifecycle management from pod eviction. A new taint eviction controller now handles pod evictions, while the node lifecycle controller focuses on applying taints. The feature gate SeparateTaintEvictionController is now GA, and users can disable taint-based eviction if needed. For more details, check the KEP and previous announcements. A big thank you to all contributors for their efforts! 🙌&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Autoconfiguration for Node Cgroup Driver Goes GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9627/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9627/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 introduces a significant improvement in cgroup driver configuration. The new feature, KubeletCgroupDriverFromCRI, allows the kubelet to automatically detect the cgroup driver from the CRI implementation. This aims to reduce configuration issues for cluster admins. It&amp;rsquo;s important to ensure your CRI is updated: - containerd: Needs v2.0.0 or later - CRI-O: Needs v1.28.0 or later Kubernetes is also deprecating containerd v1.y support, with the last supported version being v1.35&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Mutable CSI Node Allocatable Graduates to Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9601/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9601/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Kubernetes users! The Mutable CSI Node Allocatable feature has officially graduated to Beta in the v1.34 release. This update allows CSI drivers to dynamically adjust attachable volume counts, improving the accuracy of stateful pod scheduling and reducing issues with outdated capacity information. 🔧 With two update mechanisms—periodic and reactive—Kubernetes enhances pod placement reliability. To enable this feature, activate the MutableCSINodeAllocatableCount gate on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Use An Init Container To Define App Environment Variables</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9536/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9536/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 introduces an alpha feature that simplifies how environment variables are set for containers. You can now define environment variables directly from a file in an emptyDir volume, without the need for mounting it into the main container. This approach streamlines app configuration and reduces API calls. Keep in mind, while it can handle sensitive data, security measures should be in place to protect node access. #Kubernetes #DevOps #CloudComputing #Containers #K8s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Snapshottable API server cache</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9504/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9504/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 introduces the snapshottable API server cache, now in Beta. This feature enhances the API server&amp;rsquo;s performance and stability by allowing most read requests to be served from cache. Key improvements include consistent reads and efficient handling of large responses. The new cache generates lightweight snapshots, ensuring predictable memory usage and reducing load on etcd. This marks a significant step towards a more resilient Kubernetes environment. 🌐✨ #Kubernetes #API&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: VolumeAttributesClass for Volume Modification GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9451/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9451/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 introduces the VolumeAttributesClass API, now in General Availability (GA). This enhancement allows users to dynamically modify volume attributes within Kubernetes. It acts as a profile for storage, enabling scalability, cost optimization, and simplified operations. Key updates include: - Explicit cancel support for infeasible volume modifications. - Quota enforcement on PersistentVolumeClaims based on VolumeAttributesClass. Supported by AWS EBS and GCE Persistent Disk CSI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Pod Replacement Policy for Jobs Goes GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7797/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7797/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 introduces the Pod Replacement Policy feature, now generally available. This allows users to manage how Pods are replaced in Jobs, addressing issues with overlapping Pods that can occur during terminations. You can choose between two policies: 1. &lt;strong&gt;TerminatingOrFailed&lt;/strong&gt; (default) - Replaces Pods immediately upon termination. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Failed&lt;/strong&gt; - Replaces Pods only after the previous ones have fully terminated. This enhancement is particularly useful for workloads requiring strict&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: PSI Metrics for Kubernetes Graduates to Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7768/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7768/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Kubernetes users! As of v1.34, Pressure Stall Information (PSI) Metrics has graduated to Beta. PSI helps quantify resource pressure by measuring stalled tasks due to contention, providing a clearer view of CPU, memory, and I/O performance. Metrics are available via the Summary API and Prometheus endpoints. 📊 To enable PSI metrics, ensure your nodes run Linux kernel 4.20+ and enable the KubeletPSI feature gate. This allows for better resource management and performance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Service Account Token Integration for Image Pulls Graduates to Beta</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7712/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7712/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes v1.34 has officially moved Service Account Token Integration for Kubelet Credential Providers to beta. This update enhances security by reducing reliance on long-lived image pull secrets. 🔒 Key changes include a required &lt;code&gt;cacheType&lt;/code&gt; field in the configuration and improved security isolation for image pulls. This ensures that only authorized pods can access specific container images. 🛡️ For more details, check out the Kubernetes documentation. #Kubernetes #DevOps #CloudSecurity #K8s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Introducing CPU Manager Static Policy Option for Uncore Cache Alignment</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7647/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7647/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 has introduced a new feature: the CPU Manager Static Policy Option, prefer-align-cpus-by-uncorecache, now in beta. This option optimizes performance for workloads on processors with a split uncore cache architecture, enhancing efficiency by reducing latency between CPU cores. To enable it, update your kubelet configuration. This feature is particularly beneficial for applications like telco systems but may vary based on workload types. #Kubernetes #CloudComputing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: DRA has graduated to GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7599/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7599/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes 1.34 is now live, featuring significant advancements in Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA)! Key highlights include the core of DRA graduating to General Availability (GA), ensuring stability and confidence for users. Key features have also moved to beta, enhancing control and flexibility in resource management. Notable updates include improved admin access labeling and prioritized device lists for workloads. Explore new alpha features aimed at simplifying resource management for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Finer-Grained Control Over Container Restarts</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7552/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7552/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes 1.34 introduces an alpha feature called Container Restart Policy and Rules. This feature allows developers to set individual restart policies for each container in a Pod, moving beyond the previous single policy for all containers. 🔧 Users can now define restart rules based on exit codes, offering more control for complex workloads. For instance, you can ensure that an ML training job restarts only on retriable errors without rescheduling the entire Pod. 📦 The new capability is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: User preferences (kuberc) are available for testing in kubectl 1.34</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7520/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7520/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Kubernetes users! The Kubernetes v1.34 release introduces user preferences in kubectl, now in beta. This feature allows you to set default options, like enabling interactive delete, and define custom aliases to streamline your workflow. To configure, place your preferences in a &lt;code&gt;kuberc&lt;/code&gt; file, located in your kubeconfig directory. Check out the official documentation for more details! #Kubernetes #kubectl #DevOps #CloudComputing #UserPreferences</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes v1.34: Of Wind &amp; Will (O&#39; WaW)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7447/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7447/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Kubernetes v1.34 is here, featuring 58 enhancements! This release includes 23 stable, 22 beta, and 13 alpha features, showcasing the strength of its development cycle. 🌬 The theme &amp;ldquo;Of Wind &amp;amp; Will&amp;rdquo; highlights the community&amp;rsquo;s resilience in navigating challenges. Key updates include: - &lt;strong&gt;Stable&lt;/strong&gt;: Dynamic Resource Allocation (DRA) now enables better device management. - &lt;strong&gt;Beta&lt;/strong&gt;: Short-lived ServiceAccount tokens enhance security for image pulls. - &lt;strong&gt;Alpha&lt;/strong&gt;: KYAML introduces a new, safer YAML&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tuning Linux Swap for Kubernetes: A Deep Dive</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5779/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5779/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes is set to introduce the NodeSwap feature in version 1.34, allowing Linux nodes to utilize swap for improved resource management. This marks a shift from the traditional approach of disabling swap for performance. However, enabling swap requires careful tuning of Linux kernel parameters to avoid performance issues and manage memory pressure effectively. Key parameters include &lt;code&gt;vm.swappiness&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;vm.min_free_kbytes&lt;/code&gt;, and &lt;code&gt;vm.watermark_scale_factor&lt;/code&gt;. Testing various configurations can&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Headlamp AI Assistant</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5780/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5780/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! The Headlamp AI Assistant is here to enhance Kubernetes management and troubleshooting. This new plugin allows users, regardless of experience, to ask questions like &amp;ldquo;Is my application healthy?&amp;rdquo; and receive actionable insights. 🛠️ With a conversational UI powered by Large Language Models, users can now get contextual help directly from their Headlamp interface. Try it out today and streamline your Kubernetes operations! #Kubernetes #AI #TechInnovation #Headlamp #DevOps</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
