<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Grab-Tech on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/grab-tech/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grab-Tech on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:23:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/grab-tech/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kinabalu AI SRE - Leveraging AI for scalable diagnostics and alert management (Part 1)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14249/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 00:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-06-14249/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Kinabalu AI SRE! 🚀 This innovative tool aims to enhance the on-call experience by consolidating alerts and context into one accessible platform. It utilizes AI to analyze data and facilitate quicker responses during incidents. Key features include automated triage, static diagnostics, and dynamic conversations through Slack and a Web UI. This streamlines incident management, reduces cognitive load, and supports collaboration. Stay tuned for insights on challenges and design&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying user journeys: Revolutionizing troubleshooting with auto tracking</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14121/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 00:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-23-14121/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Troubleshooting user journeys on the Grab app can be complex, akin to finding a needle in a haystack. Developers face challenges in accurately tracking user interactions due to numerous UI components. 📊 The traditional approach often led to incomplete data, hindering effective issue resolution and increasing operational costs. 💡 The introduction of the AutoTrack SDK marks a significant advancement. This system tracks application states, user interactions, and UI screens in real-time,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Grab is accelerating growth with real-time personalization using Customer Data Platform scenarios</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-18-13975/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-18-13975/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Grab is enhancing user experiences through real-time personalization with its Customer Data Platform (CDP). The CDP enables targeted campaigns, including mall offers and travel recommendations, by utilizing user data and event triggers. This innovative approach overcomes previous engineering limitations and promotes agility in marketing efforts. Key features include event-driven personalization, predictive modeling, and an easy-to-use interface for marketers. Early implementations show&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Decade of Defense: Celebrating Grab&#39;s 10th Year Bug Bounty Program</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13140/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13140/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Celebrating 10 years of Grab&amp;rsquo;s Bug Bounty Program with HackerOne! From a small group of 23 researchers, we&amp;rsquo;ve grown into a global community of over 850 security experts. Together, we protect 187 million users across Southeast Asia. Our program adapts to new threats and includes initiatives like mobile security and exclusive global campaigns to enhance collaboration. Here’s to continued partnerships and a secure digital future! 🌏🔐 #Cybersecurity #BugBounty #Collaboration #Grab #HackerOne</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time data quality monitoring: Kafka stream contracts with syntactic and semantic test</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13059/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13059/</guid>
      <description>Monitoring data quality is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s data-driven world. The article discusses the challenges in ensuring reliable data within Kafka streams, which are essential for real-time processing. The Coban platform introduces a solution that allows users to define data contracts, enabling automated quality checks. This helps identify issues in real-time and notifies stakeholders promptly. Key components include data contract definitions, automated test execution, and result observability. 📊📈&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SpellVault’s evolution: Beyond LLM apps, towards the agentic future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12924/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12924/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting developments at Grab with SpellVault! Originally a no-code platform for building LLM apps, SpellVault has evolved into a powerful tool for creating intelligent AI agents. Its journey highlights a focus on accessibility, allowing users to integrate external data sources easily. Key features now include dynamic plugins and a unified tools framework, enabling apps to reason and act intelligently. This evolution positions SpellVault as a leader in the agentic future of AI. 🤖💡&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grab&#39;s Mac Cloud Exit supercharges macOS CI/CD</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11924/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11924/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Grab has successfully relocated its macOS CI/CD infrastructure from a US cloud vendor to a colocation cluster in Southeast Asia. This move has significantly improved build performance and reduced operational costs. With a transition from 1 Mac Pro to over 250 Mac minis, Grab is now better equipped to meet growing demands. The new setup has led to estimated savings of $2.4 million over three years. Explore how this strategic decision enhances efficiency and supports Grab&amp;rsquo;s mission in the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How We Built a Custom Vision LLM to Improve Document Processing at Grab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11680/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11680/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in document processing at Grab! We&amp;rsquo;ve developed a specialized Vision LLM to tackle the challenges of extracting information from diverse documents in Southeast Asia. Traditional OCR systems faced limitations, especially with local languages. Our journey included fine-tuning the Qwen2-VL 2B model and creating a lightweight Vision LLM from scratch, resulting in significant accuracy improvements for various document types. This custom model outperforms existing solutions&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine-learning predictive autoscaling for Flink</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11473/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11473/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Grab is enhancing its Flink applications to meet growing demands for stream processing. With a 2.5x increase in Flink applications, the internal team is focusing on efficient, self-service CPU provisioning. Current reactive autoscaling methods face challenges like restart spikes and resource waste, leading to a need for a predictive solution. The new Predictive Resource Advisor optimizes CPU usage by forecasting workload and adjusting resources proactively, resulting in significant cost&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modernising Grab’s model serving platform with NVIDIA Triton Inference Server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11093/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11093/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Grab is enhancing its machine learning model serving platform, Catwalk, by integrating NVIDIA Triton Inference Server. This upgrade addresses performance issues caused by maintaining multiple legacy inference engines. Key benefits of Triton include multi-framework support, a unified API, and optimized hardware performance. Early results show over 50% of online deployments successfully migrated with improved latency and cost savings. Stay tuned for more updates on this transformation! 🌟&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly concurrent in-memory counter in GoLang</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10433/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10433/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Facing high database CPU utilization during heavy traffic? This article explores a scenario where migrating from SQL to NoSQL seemed easy but tackling the problem through optimization proved more effective. The focus was on real-time usage count tracking for marketing campaigns, utilizing highly concurrent in-memory caching to reduce database load. By periodically flushing data, the team achieved significant efficiency improvements. The implementation of GoLang&amp;rsquo;s Sync.Map led to a 68%&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>User foundation models for Grab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10119/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Grab is enhancing user experiences through a custom AI foundation model designed to understand individual preferences across Southeast Asia. This model combines both tabular and time-series data to create user embeddings, leading to improved personalization and performance in various applications like ad targeting and fraud detection. By leveraging diverse data types, Grab aims for a unified understanding of user behavior, ultimately driving better services. #AI #MachineLearning #Grab&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powering Partner Gateway metrics with Apache Pinot</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9900/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9900/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Grab is enhancing its Partner Gateway with Apache Pinot to provide real-time analytics and insights for its partners. 🔍 The integration supports API management, offering advanced metrics tracking through time-series charts. This allows partners like Alpha, a perishable goods distributor, to optimize operations by monitoring API performance and response times. 📊 Key features include a dashboard for real-time insights and Star-tree indexing for improved query performance. This ensures&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Taming the monorepo beast: Our journey to a leaner, faster GitLab repo</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9675/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9675/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At Grab, our engineering team tackled the challenges of a massive Go monorepo that had become a bottleneck over the years. We discovered that replication delays and a hefty repository size were crippling our developer workflows. With 12.7 million commits and 22.1 million Git trees, performance suffered significantly. To address this, we implemented a custom migration strategy that reduced commits by 99.9%, improving replication time from minutes to seconds! This transformation not only&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data mesh at Grab part I: Building trust through certification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5076/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 00:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5076/</guid>
      <description>At Grab, we are evolving our data ecosystem to better serve our diverse operations, including ride-hailing, food delivery, and financial services. 🚀 In 2024, we initiated the Signals Marketplace, a data mesh journey aimed at enhancing data quality and accessibility. This decentralized approach allows domain-specific teams to take ownership of their data, fostering reliability and trust. 📊 Key challenges included high data volume, unclear ownership, and communication gaps. We introduced data&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
