<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google-Research on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/google-research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google-Research on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:37:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/google-research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gemini provides automated feedback for theoretical computer scientists at STOC 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13905/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13905/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in theoretical computer science! A new tool using Gemini AI was tested at the STOC 2026 conference to help authors verify their submissions. It provided automated feedback within 24 hours, identifying calculation and logic errors. The feedback included structured insights on contributions, potential mistakes, and minor corrections, enhancing the quality of research before peer review. #TheoreticalComputerScience #STOC2026 #AI #ResearchInnovation #GeminiAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Titans &#43; MIRAS: Helping AI have long-term memory</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13459/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:26:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13459/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in AI! The Titans architecture and MIRAS framework are introduced to enhance AI&amp;rsquo;s long-term memory while it operates. These innovations allow models to process extensive contexts efficiently, updating their memory in real-time. Unlike traditional methods, Titans combines the speed of RNNs with the accuracy of transformers, enabling AI to adapt dynamically to new information without requiring offline retraining. #AI #MachineLearning #TechInnovation #LongTermMemory&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Waveforms to Wisdom: The New Benchmark for Auditory Intelligence</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13409/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 22:47:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13409/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the Massive Sound Embedding Benchmark (MSEB) — a new open-source platform designed to measure machine sound intelligence. 🎶 MSEB unifies eight essential capabilities such as transcription, classification, and reconstruction to enhance auditory performance in AI systems. It aims to address key questions about sound-based AI, including the potential for universal sound embeddings. This benchmark provides a structured evaluation framework and sets clear performance goals,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reducing EV range anxiety: How a simple AI model predicts port availability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12945/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12945/</guid>
      <description>🚗🔌 A new AI model predicts EV charging port availability, helping drivers minimize wait times and plan trips effectively. This solution targets &amp;ldquo;range anxiety&amp;rdquo; by integrating charging stations into routes based on battery levels. The model, based on simple linear regression, balances predictive power with efficiency. By using real-time data, it enhances user experience and supports the growing need for reliable EV infrastructure. #ElectricVehicles #AI #ChargingStations #RangeAnxiety&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real-time speech-to-speech translation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12855/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 09:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12855/</guid>
      <description>Introducing a groundbreaking speech-to-speech translation (S2ST) model that enables real-time communication with just a 2-second delay! 🌍🎤 This innovative system allows for direct audio translation in the original speaker&amp;rsquo;s voice, enhancing connection across language barriers. It overcomes previous delays and errors associated with traditional methods. The model utilizes a streaming framework and a scalable data acquisition pipeline to support multiple languages, making it suitable for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative UI: A rich, custom, visual interactive user experience for any prompt</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12769/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12769/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the world of AI! A new implementation of generative UI is now available in the Gemini app and Google Search. This technology allows AI to create immersive and interactive user experiences on the fly, tailored to any prompt. Generative UI can generate web pages, games, and applications based on simple or detailed instructions. Research shows these dynamic interfaces are preferred over traditional static designs. Explore the future of personalized interactions with this&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Separating natural forests from other tree cover with AI for deforestation-free supply chains</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12131/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:04:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12131/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The &amp;ldquo;Natural Forests of the World 2020&amp;rdquo; map uses AI to distinguish natural forests from other types of tree cover. This tool is essential for achieving deforestation-free supply chains and protecting ecosystems. Forests play a key role in regulating rainfall, storing carbon, and supporting biodiversity. However, deforestation remains a significant challenge. Current mapping often confuses natural forests with plantations, complicating conservation efforts. New regulations, such as the EU&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A new quantum toolkit for optimization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12132/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 07:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12132/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New insights from Google Quantum AI reveal that large-scale quantum computers may solve complex optimization problems beyond the reach of classical computers. 🔍 This potential spans various applications, from airline route planning to clinical trials. A new algorithm, Decoded Quantum Interferometry (DQI), uses quantum mechanics to find near-optimal solutions efficiently. 🧩 However, it also requires solving a challenging decoding problem, which has been studied extensively due to its&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Differentially private machine learning at scale with JAX-Privacy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12133/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12133/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in AI! JAX-Privacy 1.0 has been released, a library designed for differentially private machine learning on the JAX platform. This toolkit allows researchers to train deep learning models while ensuring data privacy. JAX, known for its high-performance capabilities, supports seamless scaling and efficient model training. JAX-Privacy enhances these features by providing tools for implementing and auditing private algorithms. This release marks a significant step for researchers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Nested Learning: A new ML paradigm for continual learning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11964/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 17:37:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11964/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://research.google/blog/rss/&#34;&gt;Google Research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://research.google/blog/introducing-nested-learning-a-new-ml-paradigm-for-continual-learning/&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DS-STAR: A state-of-the-art versatile data science agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11965/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 17:50:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11965/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://research.google/blog/rss/&#34;&gt;Google Research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://research.google/blog/ds-star-a-state-of-the-art-versatile-data-science-agent/&#34;&gt;Read full article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring a space-based, scalable AI infrastructure system design</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11825/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11825/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Project Suncatcher is a new initiative exploring AI infrastructure in space. The project aims to utilize solar-powered satellite constellations equipped with TPUs and optical links to enhance machine learning capabilities in orbit. Solar energy in space can be significantly more productive than on Earth, potentially revolutionizing AI compute. The early research paper outlines challenges like satellite communication and radiation effects. #SpaceTech #AI #Innovation #ProjectSuncatcher&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating the magic cycle of research breakthroughs and real-world applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11558/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11558/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements were shared at the recent Research@ event by Google Research, showcasing breakthroughs in earth science, genomics, and quantum computing. These innovations are part of a “magic cycle” where research and real-world applications drive each other forward. Enhanced AI tools and open platforms are accelerating this process, leading to new opportunities in various fields. 🌍🔬 Stay tuned for more updates on how technology is shaping our future! #GoogleResearch #Innovation #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward provably private insights into AI use</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11514/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11514/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking the potential of generative AI while ensuring user privacy is crucial. A new system called Provably Private Insights (PPI) uses federated analytics to analyze on-device generative AI data without exposing personal information. It combines large language models and differential privacy to provide insights into user interactions. This approach is already being implemented in Google’s Recorder app, allowing developers to improve AI tools while maintaining transparency in data handling&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>StreetReaderAI: Towards making street view accessible via context-aware multimodal AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11464/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 16:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11464/</guid>
      <description>Introducing StreetReaderAI, a groundbreaking prototype aimed at making street view experiences accessible for everyone. 🌍✨ This innovative tool utilizes context-aware, real-time AI to provide blind and low-vision users with descriptive information about their surroundings. Key features include real-time descriptions of streets and locations, dynamic conversations with a multimodal AI agent, and accessible navigation controls. StreetReaderAI represents a significant step towards inclusivity in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we are building the personal health coach</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11327/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 22:36:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11327/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in health tech! A new personal health coach powered by Gemini models is set to provide tailored coaching based on individual health data. This initiative aims to bridge gaps in health and fitness support, offering insights on sleep, fitness, and well-being. Starting tomorrow, eligible Fitbit Premium users in the US can access a public preview. The coach will use behavioral science and personal metrics to help users set goals and build lasting habits. Stay tuned for more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google Earth AI: Unlocking geospatial insights with foundation models and cross-modal reasoning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11201/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 08:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11201/</guid>
      <description>🌍 Google Earth AI is enhancing our understanding of the planet with advanced geospatial AI models and reasoning agents. These innovations provide actionable insights on environmental issues and natural disasters. By integrating various data sources, users can address complex queries like hurricane landfalls and community preparedness. New features include updated imagery models and a geospatial reasoning agent for intricate problem-solving. Explore the potential of these tools today!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A verifiable quantum advantage</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11153/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:07:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11153/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Exciting developments in quantum computing! A recent study in Nature introduces a new computational task measuring Out-of-Time-Order Correlators (OTOCs), showcasing a verifiable quantum advantage. This breakthrough could help tackle real-world challenges, such as Hamiltonian learning in Nuclear Magnetic Resonance (NMR). The research highlights chaos in both macroscopic and quantum systems, emphasizing how quantum computers can effectively simulate these complex, chaotic behaviors. 🔍&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A picture&#39;s worth a thousand (private) words: Hierarchical generation of coherent synthetic photo albums</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11090/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 21:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11090/</guid>
      <description>Introducing a new method for generating differentially private synthetic photo albums! 📷✨ This approach uses an intermediate text representation to create albums hierarchically, ensuring individual data privacy while maintaining thematic coherence across images. By leveraging generative AI models, organizations can simplify their data analysis workflows, safeguarding sensitive information without compromising quality. Explore the potential of this innovative technique! #DifferentialPrivacy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Gemini to spot exploding stars with just a few examples</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11085/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11085/</guid>
      <description>🌌 In a recent study published in Nature Astronomy, researchers demonstrate how Google’s Gemini model can effectively classify cosmic events, achieving 93% accuracy with just 15 examples per survey. 🔭 This innovative approach transforms Gemini into an astronomy assistant capable of explaining its reasoning in simple terms, addressing the challenges posed by the increasing volume of data from telescopes. 👨‍🔬 This advancement could significantly aid astronomers in distinguishing real events from&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solving virtual machine puzzles: How AI is optimizing cloud computing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11037/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:56:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11037/</guid>
      <description>Introducing LAVA, a new AI-driven scheduling algorithm designed to enhance resource efficiency in cloud data centers. ☁️💻 LAVA adapts to the lifetimes of virtual machines (VMs) by continuously updating predictions, addressing the challenges of VM allocation. This system helps prevent resource stranding and optimizes server usage for both economic and environmental benefits. 🌱📈 The approach includes three algorithms: NILAS, LAVA, and LARS, which work together to improve VM fitting on physical&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using AI to identify genetic variants in tumors with DeepSomatic</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11003/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11003/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DeepSomatic is an AI tool designed to identify cancer-related mutations in tumor genetic sequences. This innovation assists in understanding the genetic factors driving different types of cancer, which is crucial for developing targeted treatment plans. Developed in collaboration with the University of California, Santa Cruz Genomics Institute, DeepSomatic uses machine learning to enhance the accuracy of variant discovery across various sequencing technologies. Both the tool and its&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coral NPU: A full-stack platform for Edge AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10949/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10949/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Introducing Coral NPU, a new open-source platform designed to enhance Edge AI on low-power devices and wearables. This full-stack solution addresses key challenges such as performance gaps, fragmentation, and user privacy. By embedding AI directly into personal devices, it aims to deliver assistive experiences while maintaining data security. Developers can now access documentation and tools to start creating efficient, always-on AI applications. #EdgeAI #CoralNPU #GenerativeAI #Privacy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XR Blocks: Accelerating AI &#43; XR innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10609/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 09:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10609/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in the world of AI and XR! XR Blocks is an open-source framework aimed at developing immersive web experiences. It combines AI and extended reality to enhance intelligent computing. While AI has established frameworks, bridging the gap with XR has been challenging. XR Blocks offers a modular architecture for rapid prototyping of AI + XR applications. Discover more with live demos and templates available on GitHub! #AI #XR #Innovation #OpenSource #Technology</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>​​Speech-to-Retrieval (S2R): A new approach to voice search</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10515/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10515/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the Speech-to-Retrieval (S2R) engine, a new advancement in voice search technology! 🎤🔍 This innovative approach allows users to get answers directly from their spoken queries, eliminating the need for text conversion. This results in faster and more reliable search results. Traditional voice search relies on automatic speech recognition (ASR), which can misinterpret queries and lead to irrelevant results. S2R aims to improve this by addressing those challenges. #VoiceSearch&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A collaborative approach to image generation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10390/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10390/</guid>
      <description>Introducing PASTA, a new reinforcement learning agent designed to enhance text-to-image generation by learning user preferences through interactive refinement. 🎨🤖 This innovative approach transforms the process from trial-and-error to a collaborative conversation, making it easier for users to achieve their ideal images. PASTA outperformed traditional models in user satisfaction during evaluations. A dataset of over 7,000 interactions has been released to support this research. 📊✨&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing interactive on-device segmentation in Snapseed</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10329/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10329/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Snapseed users! The app now features a new Object Brush tool for iOS, enabling real-time image segmentation. This allows for easier and more intuitive selective edits, such as brightening a subject or enhancing the sky. Simply draw on the object you want to adjust without affecting the rest of the image. Try it out as this feature rolls out in the coming week! 📸✨ #Snapseed #PhotoEditing #MobilePhotography #TechUpdate #UserExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI as a research partner: Advancing theoretical computer science with AlphaEvolve</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10274/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10274/</guid>
      <description>Discover how AlphaEvolve, a coding agent powered by LLMs, is advancing theoretical computer science. This innovative tool helps find and verify combinatorial structures that enhance our understanding of optimization problems. The study highlights AlphaEvolve&amp;rsquo;s iterative process to improve code snippets, resulting in significant findings in complexity theory. Learn more about the potential of AI in mathematical discovery! 🤖📊 #TheoreticalComputerScience #AI #AlphaEvolve #Mathematics #Research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The anatomy of a personal health agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10288/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10288/</guid>
      <description>Discover the potential of a new research prototype: the Personal Health Agent (PHA). This LLM-powered tool analyzes data from wearable devices and health metrics to provide tailored health insights and coaching. The PHA uses a multi-agent system to address diverse health inquiries, ensuring personalized support. Extensive evaluations involved data from over 1,200 users, marking a significant advancement in health technology. This framework is intended for research and not a market-ready&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards better health conversations: Research insights on a “wayfinding” AI agent based on Gemini</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10112/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10112/</guid>
      <description>A new research article explores a “Wayfinding AI” agent that enhances health conversations. This AI helps users navigate health information by asking clarifying questions, understanding individual goals, and providing tailored responses. User studies revealed challenges in articulating health concerns, indicating a need for more personalized guidance. The findings suggest that proactive engagement from AI can lead to a better user experience. 🤖💬 #HealthTech #AI #UserExperience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AfriMed-QA: Benchmarking large language models for global health</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10039/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10039/</guid>
      <description>Introducing AfriMed-QA! 🌍 This new initiative focuses on evaluating large language models (LLMs) for health-related questions in Africa. It aims to bridge the gap in medical knowledge and support across diverse contexts. Developed with multiple partners, the dataset includes questions from medical schools in 16 African countries. This effort addresses the need for localized benchmarks in healthcare AI. Find out more about how this could enhance clinical decision support in low-resource&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time series foundation models can be few-shot learners</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9951/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 18:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9951/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in time-series forecasting! A new approach allows time-series foundation models to learn from just a few examples, enhancing prediction accuracy without the need for extensive training. This builds on the existing TimesFM model, which previously functioned as a zero-shot learner. The method, highlighted in &amp;ldquo;In-Context Fine-Tuning for Time-Series Foundation Models,&amp;rdquo; simplifies the forecasting process, making it more efficient for businesses to adapt to various needs&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep researcher with test-time diffusion</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9847/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9847/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Test-Time Diffusion Deep Researcher (TTD-DR), a groundbreaking framework in machine intelligence. 🤖📚 TTD-DR utilizes a Deep Research agent to draft and refine research reports using high-quality information. This method leads to state-of-the-art results in long-form writing and complex reasoning tasks. Unlike traditional DR agents, TTD-DR emulates the iterative human research process, enhancing drafts through research and revision. This innovative approach mirrors the retrieval-&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensible Agent: A framework for unobtrusive interaction with proactive AR agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9800/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 20:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9800/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Sensible Agent, a pioneering framework for proactive AR interaction. 🌟 This research prototype adapts its suggestions based on real-time context like gaze and hand availability, addressing limitations of current AR agents that rely on verbal commands. Sensible Agent aims to provide seamless, unobtrusive assistance in everyday situations, enhancing user experience. Learn more about this innovative approach at UIST 2025! #AugmentedReality #HumanComputerInteraction #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making LLMs more accurate by using all of their layers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9743/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9743/</guid>
      <description>Introducing SLED, a new decoding strategy aimed at improving the accuracy of large language models (LLMs) by utilizing all model layers. This method aligns outputs with intrinsic knowledge, tackling the issue of &amp;ldquo;hallucination,&amp;rdquo; where models generate incorrect information. SLED enhances factuality without requiring external data or additional fine-tuning. Learn more about this innovative approach presented at NeurIPS 2024! 📊💡✨ #AI #MachineLearning #LLMs #SLED #NeurIPS2024</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Your Way: Reimagining textbooks with generative AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9699/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9699/</guid>
      <description>📚 Exciting developments in education are here! New research on generative AI (GenAI) reveals innovative ways to transform textbooks into personalized learning experiences. Google&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Learn Your Way,&amp;rdquo; now in Google Labs, aims to enhance engagement by allowing students to tailor their learning paths with diverse formats. Early studies show that students using this approach scored 11 percentage points higher on retention tests compared to traditional methods. Explore how GenAI can reshape&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VaultGemma: The world&#39;s most capable differentially private LLM</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9617/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9617/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing VaultGemma, the largest differentially private language model trained from scratch! As AI becomes more integrated into daily life, ensuring privacy is essential. VaultGemma uses differential privacy (DP) to protect user data by adding calibrated noise that prevents memorization. Our research with Google DeepMind highlights the trade-offs of applying DP in large language models, including increased computation costs and altered training dynamics. We are excited to release&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speculative cascades — A hybrid approach for smarter, faster LLM inference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9597/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9597/</guid>
      <description>Introducing &amp;ldquo;speculative cascades,&amp;rdquo; a new method enhancing the efficiency of LLMs by merging speculative decoding with standard cascades. This approach aims to reduce inference costs while maintaining output quality. It utilizes smaller models to handle simpler tasks, reserving larger models for complex queries. By combining these techniques, speculative cascades achieve faster results at lower costs, as demonstrated in tests with Gemma and T5 models. #AI #LLM #MachineLearning #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smarter nucleic acid design with NucleoBench and AdaBeam</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9561/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9561/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in nucleic acid design! Researchers have developed NucleoBench, an open-source benchmark for evaluating nucleic acid sequence design algorithms. This tool runs over 400,000 experiments across various biological challenges to improve therapeutic development. Alongside NucleoBench, they introduced AdaBeam, a new algorithm that outperforms existing methods on 11 out of 16 tasks, showing better scalability for complex models. Both NucleoBench and AdaBeam are available for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating scientific discovery with AI-powered empirical software</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9498/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9498/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in scientific research! A new AI system has been developed to assist scientists in writing empirical software, achieving expert-level results across six challenging benchmarks. This system addresses the bottleneck in hypothesis evaluation by generating high-quality custom software. By leveraging large language models, the AI can propose and implement novel concepts, optimizing performance through extensive code iteration. This innovation spans diverse fields including&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Google’s AI can help transform health professions education</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7291/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7291/</guid>
      <description>Google’s AI is shaping the future of health professions education. 🌍 With a projected shortage of over 11 million healthcare workers by 2030, AI tools are being explored to enhance medical learning. Two studies reveal how Google’s AI models can serve as personalized learning aids for medical students. The first study focused on using generative AI to support clinical reasoning, while the second assessed LearnLM, an AI model tailored for education. Results show strong interest in AI that&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A scalable framework for evaluating health language models</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7250/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7250/</guid>
      <description>Introducing a new framework for evaluating health language models! 🏥 This adaptive methodology improves efficiency and inter-rater reliability, reducing the reliance on costly human experts. By using simple boolean questions, it streamlines the evaluation process for complex health queries. The framework focuses on personalized health data and is validated in the metabolic health domain, covering conditions like diabetes and obesity. Learn more about this innovative approach! 🔍🤖 #HealthTech&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From massive models to mobile magic: The tech behind YouTube real-time generative AI effects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5179/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 18:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5179/</guid>
      <description>YouTube is enhancing user experience on mobile with real-time generative AI effects. 📱✨ By utilizing knowledge distillation and MediaPipe, YouTube has developed a solution to deliver over 20 effects directly on creators&amp;rsquo; phones. This process involves creating smaller, efficient models tailored for specific tasks, allowing for seamless video processing. These advancements make features like cartoon style transfer not only possible but also fun and interactive for creators on YouTube Shorts. 🎨🎥&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing private data at scale with differentially private partition selection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5180/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5180/</guid>
      <description>🔒 New algorithms are advancing user privacy in data sharing through differentially private partition selection. This approach allows for safe sharing of large datasets, crucial for AI and machine learning innovation. It ensures individual contributions remain confidential by adding controlled noise during selection. Parallel algorithms enhance efficiency, enabling the processing of vast datasets while maintaining robust privacy guarantees. Explore more in the publication “Scalable Private&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond billion-parameter burdens: Unlocking data synthesis with a conditional generator</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5181/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5181/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking data synthesis in AI just got easier! 🌐 A new algorithm, CTCL, enables the generation of synthetic data while preserving privacy, using a lightweight 140 million parameter model. This approach avoids the complexities of fine-tuning billion-scale models, making it accessible for resource-constrained applications. CTCL conditions data on topic information, ensuring better topic distribution matching. It also allows for unlimited synthetic data generation without additional privacy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling physician-centered oversight for AMIE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5182/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5182/</guid>
      <description>Introducing guardrailed-AMIE (g-AMIE), a new AI diagnostic tool designed for history-taking in healthcare. 🩺 g-AMIE operates under strict guidelines, preventing it from giving personalized medical advice. Instead, it generates summaries for physicians to review, ensuring patient safety and oversight. This system allows primary care physicians to maintain accountability while leveraging AI for efficiency. The recent study demonstrated g-AMIE&amp;rsquo;s performance being preferred over nurse&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving 10,000x training data reduction with high-fidelity labels</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5183/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5183/</guid>
      <description>A new method in active learning significantly reduces the training data needed for fine-tuning large language models (LLMs). 📉 This innovative approach addresses the challenges in classifying unsafe ad content, which requires deep contextual understanding. Traditional methods are costly and often ineffective with evolving safety policies. The new curation process can cut training data from 100,000 examples to under 500, while improving model alignment with human experts by up to 65%. This is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insulin resistance prediction from wearables and routine blood biomarkers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5184/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5184/</guid>
      <description>New research highlights a promising method for predicting insulin resistance using wearable data and routine blood tests. This approach makes early screening for type 2 diabetes more accessible and scalable. Early detection of insulin resistance is crucial, as timely lifestyle changes can reverse the condition. Traditional testing methods can be invasive and costly, creating barriers for many. The study utilized machine learning models to analyze data from wearables and common blood tests,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly accurate genome polishing with DeepPolisher: Enhancing the foundation of genomic research</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5185/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5185/</guid>
      <description>Introducing DeepPolisher, a new deep learning tool that enhances the accuracy of genome assemblies by correcting base-level errors. 🧬 This advancement plays a crucial role in refining the Human Pangenome Reference, making it easier to study heredity, disease, and evolution. DeepPolisher reduces assembly errors by 50% and indel errors by 70%, improving gene identification significantly. This open-source method was developed in collaboration with UC Santa Cruz Genomics Institute, marking a step&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLE-STAR: A state-of-the-art machine learning engineering agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-5186/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-5186/</guid>
      <description>Introducing MLE-STAR, a cutting-edge machine learning engineering agent designed to automate various ML tasks across different data types. 📊🤖 This innovative agent streamlines the complex process of developing machine learning models by using large language models (LLMs) to transform task descriptions into executable code. This approach enhances efficiency for machine learning engineers. While MLE-STAR shows great potential, it still faces challenges that impact its overall effectiveness&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
