<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Google-Research on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/google-research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Google-Research on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:04:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/google-research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A collaborative approach to image generation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10390/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 17:04:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10390/</guid>
      <description>Introducing PASTA, a new reinforcement learning agent designed to enhance text-to-image generation by learning user preferences through interactive refinement. 🎨🤖 This innovative approach transforms the process from trial-and-error to a collaborative conversation, making it easier for users to achieve their ideal images. PASTA outperformed traditional models in user satisfaction during evaluations. A dataset of over 7,000 interactions has been released to support this research. 📊✨&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing interactive on-device segmentation in Snapseed</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10329/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:05:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10329/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Snapseed users! The app now features a new Object Brush tool for iOS, enabling real-time image segmentation. This allows for easier and more intuitive selective edits, such as brightening a subject or enhancing the sky. Simply draw on the object you want to adjust without affecting the rest of the image. Try it out as this feature rolls out in the coming week! 📸✨ #Snapseed #PhotoEditing #MobilePhotography #TechUpdate #UserExperience</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI as a research partner: Advancing theoretical computer science with AlphaEvolve</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10274/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:57:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10274/</guid>
      <description>Discover how AlphaEvolve, a coding agent powered by LLMs, is advancing theoretical computer science. This innovative tool helps find and verify combinatorial structures that enhance our understanding of optimization problems. The study highlights AlphaEvolve&amp;rsquo;s iterative process to improve code snippets, resulting in significant findings in complexity theory. Learn more about the potential of AI in mathematical discovery! 🤖📊 #TheoreticalComputerScience #AI #AlphaEvolve #Mathematics #Research</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The anatomy of a personal health agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10288/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 14:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10288/</guid>
      <description>Discover the potential of a new research prototype: the Personal Health Agent (PHA). This LLM-powered tool analyzes data from wearable devices and health metrics to provide tailored health insights and coaching. The PHA uses a multi-agent system to address diverse health inquiries, ensuring personalized support. Extensive evaluations involved data from over 1,200 users, marking a significant advancement in health technology. This framework is intended for research and not a market-ready&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Towards better health conversations: Research insights on a “wayfinding” AI agent based on Gemini</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10112/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 10:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10112/</guid>
      <description>A new research article explores a “Wayfinding AI” agent that enhances health conversations. This AI helps users navigate health information by asking clarifying questions, understanding individual goals, and providing tailored responses. User studies revealed challenges in articulating health concerns, indicating a need for more personalized guidance. The findings suggest that proactive engagement from AI can lead to a better user experience. 🤖💬 #HealthTech #AI #UserExperience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AfriMed-QA: Benchmarking large language models for global health</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10039/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 19:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10039/</guid>
      <description>Introducing AfriMed-QA! 🌍 This new initiative focuses on evaluating large language models (LLMs) for health-related questions in Africa. It aims to bridge the gap in medical knowledge and support across diverse contexts. Developed with multiple partners, the dataset includes questions from medical schools in 16 African countries. This effort addresses the need for localized benchmarks in healthcare AI. Find out more about how this could enhance clinical decision support in low-resource&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time series foundation models can be few-shot learners</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9951/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 18:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9951/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in time-series forecasting! A new approach allows time-series foundation models to learn from just a few examples, enhancing prediction accuracy without the need for extensive training. This builds on the existing TimesFM model, which previously functioned as a zero-shot learner. The method, highlighted in &amp;ldquo;In-Context Fine-Tuning for Time-Series Foundation Models,&amp;rdquo; simplifies the forecasting process, making it more efficient for businesses to adapt to various needs&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deep researcher with test-time diffusion</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9847/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 20:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9847/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Test-Time Diffusion Deep Researcher (TTD-DR), a groundbreaking framework in machine intelligence. 🤖📚 TTD-DR utilizes a Deep Research agent to draft and refine research reports using high-quality information. This method leads to state-of-the-art results in long-form writing and complex reasoning tasks. Unlike traditional DR agents, TTD-DR emulates the iterative human research process, enhancing drafts through research and revision. This innovative approach mirrors the retrieval-&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sensible Agent: A framework for unobtrusive interaction with proactive AR agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9800/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 20:10:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9800/</guid>
      <description>Introducing Sensible Agent, a pioneering framework for proactive AR interaction. 🌟 This research prototype adapts its suggestions based on real-time context like gaze and hand availability, addressing limitations of current AR agents that rely on verbal commands. Sensible Agent aims to provide seamless, unobtrusive assistance in everyday situations, enhancing user experience. Learn more about this innovative approach at UIST 2025! #AugmentedReality #HumanComputerInteraction #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making LLMs more accurate by using all of their layers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9743/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9743/</guid>
      <description>Introducing SLED, a new decoding strategy aimed at improving the accuracy of large language models (LLMs) by utilizing all model layers. This method aligns outputs with intrinsic knowledge, tackling the issue of &amp;ldquo;hallucination,&amp;rdquo; where models generate incorrect information. SLED enhances factuality without requiring external data or additional fine-tuning. Learn more about this innovative approach presented at NeurIPS 2024! 📊💡✨ #AI #MachineLearning #LLMs #SLED #NeurIPS2024</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Your Way: Reimagining textbooks with generative AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9699/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9699/</guid>
      <description>📚 Exciting developments in education are here! New research on generative AI (GenAI) reveals innovative ways to transform textbooks into personalized learning experiences. Google&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Learn Your Way,&amp;rdquo; now in Google Labs, aims to enhance engagement by allowing students to tailor their learning paths with diverse formats. Early studies show that students using this approach scored 11 percentage points higher on retention tests compared to traditional methods. Explore how GenAI can reshape&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VaultGemma: The world&#39;s most capable differentially private LLM</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9617/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 08:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9617/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing VaultGemma, the largest differentially private language model trained from scratch! As AI becomes more integrated into daily life, ensuring privacy is essential. VaultGemma uses differential privacy (DP) to protect user data by adding calibrated noise that prevents memorization. Our research with Google DeepMind highlights the trade-offs of applying DP in large language models, including increased computation costs and altered training dynamics. We are excited to release&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speculative cascades — A hybrid approach for smarter, faster LLM inference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9597/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9597/</guid>
      <description>Introducing &amp;ldquo;speculative cascades,&amp;rdquo; a new method enhancing the efficiency of LLMs by merging speculative decoding with standard cascades. This approach aims to reduce inference costs while maintaining output quality. It utilizes smaller models to handle simpler tasks, reserving larger models for complex queries. By combining these techniques, speculative cascades achieve faster results at lower costs, as demonstrated in tests with Gemma and T5 models. #AI #LLM #MachineLearning #TechInnovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Smarter nucleic acid design with NucleoBench and AdaBeam</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9561/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 17:18:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9561/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in nucleic acid design! Researchers have developed NucleoBench, an open-source benchmark for evaluating nucleic acid sequence design algorithms. This tool runs over 400,000 experiments across various biological challenges to improve therapeutic development. Alongside NucleoBench, they introduced AdaBeam, a new algorithm that outperforms existing methods on 11 out of 16 tasks, showing better scalability for complex models. Both NucleoBench and AdaBeam are available for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating scientific discovery with AI-powered empirical software</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9498/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:08:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9498/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in scientific research! A new AI system has been developed to assist scientists in writing empirical software, achieving expert-level results across six challenging benchmarks. This system addresses the bottleneck in hypothesis evaluation by generating high-quality custom software. By leveraging large language models, the AI can propose and implement novel concepts, optimizing performance through extensive code iteration. This innovation spans diverse fields including&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Google’s AI can help transform health professions education</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7291/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 17:19:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7291/</guid>
      <description>Google’s AI is shaping the future of health professions education. 🌍 With a projected shortage of over 11 million healthcare workers by 2030, AI tools are being explored to enhance medical learning. Two studies reveal how Google’s AI models can serve as personalized learning aids for medical students. The first study focused on using generative AI to support clinical reasoning, while the second assessed LearnLM, an AI model tailored for education. Results show strong interest in AI that&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A scalable framework for evaluating health language models</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7250/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7250/</guid>
      <description>Introducing a new framework for evaluating health language models! 🏥 This adaptive methodology improves efficiency and inter-rater reliability, reducing the reliance on costly human experts. By using simple boolean questions, it streamlines the evaluation process for complex health queries. The framework focuses on personalized health data and is validated in the metabolic health domain, covering conditions like diabetes and obesity. Learn more about this innovative approach! 🔍🤖 #HealthTech&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From massive models to mobile magic: The tech behind YouTube real-time generative AI effects</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5179/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 18:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5179/</guid>
      <description>YouTube is enhancing user experience on mobile with real-time generative AI effects. 📱✨ By utilizing knowledge distillation and MediaPipe, YouTube has developed a solution to deliver over 20 effects directly on creators&amp;rsquo; phones. This process involves creating smaller, efficient models tailored for specific tasks, allowing for seamless video processing. These advancements make features like cartoon style transfer not only possible but also fun and interactive for creators on YouTube Shorts. 🎨🎥&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing private data at scale with differentially private partition selection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5180/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5180/</guid>
      <description>🔒 New algorithms are advancing user privacy in data sharing through differentially private partition selection. This approach allows for safe sharing of large datasets, crucial for AI and machine learning innovation. It ensures individual contributions remain confidential by adding controlled noise during selection. Parallel algorithms enhance efficiency, enabling the processing of vast datasets while maintaining robust privacy guarantees. Explore more in the publication “Scalable Private&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond billion-parameter burdens: Unlocking data synthesis with a conditional generator</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5181/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 19:06:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5181/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking data synthesis in AI just got easier! 🌐 A new algorithm, CTCL, enables the generation of synthetic data while preserving privacy, using a lightweight 140 million parameter model. This approach avoids the complexities of fine-tuning billion-scale models, making it accessible for resource-constrained applications. CTCL conditions data on topic information, ensuring better topic distribution matching. It also allows for unlimited synthetic data generation without additional privacy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enabling physician-centered oversight for AMIE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5182/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 17:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-5182/</guid>
      <description>Introducing guardrailed-AMIE (g-AMIE), a new AI diagnostic tool designed for history-taking in healthcare. 🩺 g-AMIE operates under strict guidelines, preventing it from giving personalized medical advice. Instead, it generates summaries for physicians to review, ensuring patient safety and oversight. This system allows primary care physicians to maintain accountability while leveraging AI for efficiency. The recent study demonstrated g-AMIE&amp;rsquo;s performance being preferred over nurse&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieving 10,000x training data reduction with high-fidelity labels</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5183/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-5183/</guid>
      <description>A new method in active learning significantly reduces the training data needed for fine-tuning large language models (LLMs). 📉 This innovative approach addresses the challenges in classifying unsafe ad content, which requires deep contextual understanding. Traditional methods are costly and often ineffective with evolving safety policies. The new curation process can cut training data from 100,000 examples to under 500, while improving model alignment with human experts by up to 65%. This is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insulin resistance prediction from wearables and routine blood biomarkers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5184/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 20:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5184/</guid>
      <description>New research highlights a promising method for predicting insulin resistance using wearable data and routine blood tests. This approach makes early screening for type 2 diabetes more accessible and scalable. Early detection of insulin resistance is crucial, as timely lifestyle changes can reverse the condition. Traditional testing methods can be invasive and costly, creating barriers for many. The study utilized machine learning models to analyze data from wearables and common blood tests,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Highly accurate genome polishing with DeepPolisher: Enhancing the foundation of genomic research</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5185/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-5185/</guid>
      <description>Introducing DeepPolisher, a new deep learning tool that enhances the accuracy of genome assemblies by correcting base-level errors. 🧬 This advancement plays a crucial role in refining the Human Pangenome Reference, making it easier to study heredity, disease, and evolution. DeepPolisher reduces assembly errors by 50% and indel errors by 70%, improving gene identification significantly. This open-source method was developed in collaboration with UC Santa Cruz Genomics Institute, marking a step&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MLE-STAR: A state-of-the-art machine learning engineering agent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-5186/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-5186/</guid>
      <description>Introducing MLE-STAR, a cutting-edge machine learning engineering agent designed to automate various ML tasks across different data types. 📊🤖 This innovative agent streamlines the complex process of developing machine learning models by using large language models (LLMs) to transform task descriptions into executable code. This approach enhances efficiency for machine learning engineers. While MLE-STAR shows great potential, it still faces challenges that impact its overall effectiveness&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
