<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Signal-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/signal-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Signal-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/signal-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Put a pin in it</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-29-15029/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-29-15029/</guid>
      <description>📌 Signal&amp;rsquo;s latest update introduces a pinning feature for important messages in chats! Users can now pin up to 3 messages in both 1-1 and group conversations, making it easier to keep track of key information like dinner plans or itineraries. Admins can manage who can pin messages, and pinned items can stay for 24 hours to forever. Join the Signal beta program to test new features and provide feedback! #SignalUpdate #MessagingApp #TechNews #PinnedMessages #ChatFeatures</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal Polls: Yes, no, maybe (yes!)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12874/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12874/</guid>
      <description>🗳️ Discover the new Signal polling feature! You can now easily gather opinions in group chats. Whether scheduling a meeting or checking preferences, creating a poll is straightforward. Just tap the + button, set your question, and add up to 10 options. Polls are encrypted for privacy, but responses are visible to all participants. This feature is rolling out on Android, Desktop, and iOS. #Signal #GroupChat #Polling #Privacy #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Signal Protocol and Post-Quantum Ratchets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10378/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10378/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in secure communication! The Signal Protocol now features the Sparse Post Quantum Ratchet (SPQR), enhancing its defense against future quantum threats. This upgrade maintains important security measures like Forward Secrecy and Post-Compromise Security. 🔒 As a Signal user, your experience remains unchanged. Your conversations will automatically transition to this new protocol, ensuring ongoing protection for your communications. Learn more about this advancement in quantum&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Signal Secure Backups</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9434/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9434/</guid>
      <description>📱 Signal has introduced secure backups, addressing a long-standing user request. This new opt-in feature allows users to back up their message history, ensuring important conversations are not lost if a phone is damaged or lost. Currently available in beta for Android, it will soon roll out to iOS and Desktop. Secure backups are end-to-end encrypted and refresh daily for added security. #Signal #SecureBackups #Privacy #Messaging #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
