<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elastic-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/elastic-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Elastic-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/elastic-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 8.18.7 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9722/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9722/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for users of the Elastic Stack! Version 8.18.7 has been released, with improvements over 8.18.6. Users are encouraged to upgrade to benefit from the latest fixes and changes. For a detailed list of updates, refer to the release notes. #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 9.0.7 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9721/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9721/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Elastic Stack has just launched version 9.0.7! This new release includes important fixes and improvements over version 9.0.6. Users are encouraged to upgrade for the best performance. For a detailed list of changes and fixes, check the release notes. #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews #VersionRelease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Shai-Hulud Worm: Elastic&#39;s proactive defense against npm supply chain compromise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9753/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9753/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The software development community is responding to compromised npm packages linked to the Shai-Hulud worm. Elastic emphasizes the importance of supply chain integrity, noting that while its products don’t ship with npm, they rely on it for package retrieval. In their latest blog, Elastic details their analysis of code, mitigation strategies, and detection rules to combat these threats. Stay informed and secure! 🔒📦 #CyberSecurity #NPMCompromise #ElasticSecurity #ShaiHulud #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powering Zero Trust Networking with Elastic and Gigamon AMI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9747/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9747/</guid>
      <description>The cybersecurity landscape is evolving with the adoption of Zero Trust Networking (ZTN). This model emphasizes that no transaction is inherently trustworthy; every connection must be verified continuously. 🔒 Elastic and Gigamon&amp;rsquo;s Application Metadata Intelligence (AMI) play a crucial role in this framework. They enable intelligent data processing to support real-time decision-making and enhance security posture. 📊 As traditional perimeter defenses become obsolete, ZTN acknowledges modern&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent threat detection for defence SOCs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9665/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9665/</guid>
      <description>The Ministry of Defence highlights a critical cyber risk for defence security operations centres (SOCs), amid rising malicious activities. To counter these threats, the MoD&amp;rsquo;s Digital Strategy prioritizes rapid detection and response. Effective SOCs aim to reduce mean time to detect (MTTD) and mean time to respond (MTTR) significantly. Elastic Security supports this through AI-driven analytics, automating tasks to enhance SOC efficiency and visibility. Improvements in MTTD and MTTR have been&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Defend now supports macOS Tahoe 26</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9562/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9562/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for macOS users! Elastic Defend now supports macOS Tahoe 26, ensuring your endpoint protection is ready from day one. This means organizations can confidently roll out new machines and upgrade existing devices without delay. With full compatibility, Elastic Defend helps bridge visibility gaps, offering consistent coverage across Windows, Linux, and macOS environments. Stay secure and streamlined with this latest update! 🔒💻 #macOSTahoe26 #ElasticDefend #EndpointSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 practical concepts for building trust in government digital strategies with Elastic</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9471/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9471/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Explore how Elastic is enhancing digital strategies in the public sector. The article outlines five key concepts: 1. Open source and open standards 2. Sovereign infrastructure 3. Responsible AI 4. Cybersecurity and resilience 5. Data-driven government Elastic supports organizations in managing their data securely and efficiently. Learn how to build trust with these strategies! #DigitalGovernment #PublicSector #Elastic #DataSecurity #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guide to the OWASP Top 10 for LLMs: Vulnerability mitigation with Elastic</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9470/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9470/</guid>
      <description>🌐 As industries adopt large language models (LLMs) and generative AI, new security challenges arise. The OWASP Top 10 for LLM Applications offers a framework to navigate these risks effectively. 🔍 Elastic&amp;rsquo;s unified platform combines observability and security analytics, providing comprehensive protection across the entire LLM application stack. ✨ This guide highlights how to use Elastic to mitigate vulnerabilities identified by OWASP, ensuring robust security in complex AI ecosystems&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starless: How we accidentally vanished our most popular GitHub repos</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-9382/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-9382/</guid>
      <description>In October 2024, a significant incident occurred where Elastic&amp;rsquo;s key public repositories on GitHub were mistakenly marked as private. This was due to automation changes aimed at enhancing internal source code security. The incident led to an outage for customers and highlighted the risks of making assumptions in automated processes. Elastic&amp;rsquo;s engineering teams are sharing insights from this experience to prevent future occurrences. Learn more about the importance of supply chain security and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JVM essentials for Elasticsearch: Metrics, memory, and monitoring</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7272/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7272/</guid>
      <description>Understanding JVM essentials is crucial for effectively running Elasticsearch, a Java-based search and analytics engine. The Java Virtual Machine (JVM) provides a platform-independent environment, crucial for troubleshooting memory issues like OutOfMemoryError. The blog outlines how to monitor memory usage and garbage collection for optimal performance. Default JVM settings are typically sufficient for most use cases, and any changes should be approached with caution. For more insights, check&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The business impact of Elasticsearch logsdb index mode and TSDS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7401/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7401/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Elasticsearch team has rolled out enhancements in versions 8.19 and 9.1, focusing on storage efficiency and performance. 📊 Key features include the logsdb index mode and time series data streams (TSDS), which address challenges faced by DevOps and security teams. 📈 Benchmark results show a storage efficiency improvement of ~16% and an indexing throughput boost of ~19%. For users not yet on logsdb, storage reductions could exceed 70%. 🔍 Remember, logsdb is available for both Basic and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Tipalti mastered Elasticsearch performance with AutoOps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6300/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6300/</guid>
      <description>Tipalti, a leader in payables automation, has transformed its approach to Elasticsearch performance. By switching from manual monitoring to the automated AutoOps system, they achieved a 10% annual cost saving while managing a complex database ecosystem with a small team. Oz Levy, a data operations manager at Tipalti, shared insights on this transition and its impact on operational efficiency. #Tipalti #Elasticsearch #AutoOps #Efficiency #CostSaving 💼📈🔍</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to reduce alert overload in defence SOCs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-4721/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-4721/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Analysts in defense SOCs are facing significant alert overload, with many notifications being false positives. A recent study shows that 71% of SOC personnel feel overwhelmed, and 62% of alerts go ignored. This impacts both efficiency and security. Using AI tools like Elastic&amp;rsquo;s Attack Discovery, organizations have seen daily alerts drop dramatically, enhancing analyst focus and operational efficiency. Learn more about transforming your SOC operations in our upcoming webinar! 📊💻&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building effective threat hunting and detection rules in Elastic Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5056/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5056/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Learn how to build effective threat hunting and detection rules in Elastic Security! This blog provides step-by-step guidance on creating custom detection rules using Elasticsearch Query Language (ES|QL) and the Elastic AI Assistant. Key highlights include best practices for refining detection logic, testing rules, and automating responses to enhance security operations. Explore how to categorize API calls and streamline your queries for better analysis. #ElasticSecurity #ThreatHunting&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic’s capabilities in the world of Zero Trust operations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5058/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5058/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exploring Zero Trust Operations with Elastic The article discusses the essential pillars of Zero Trust (ZT) based on the US Department of Defense&amp;rsquo;s framework. Key elements include user identity, device characteristics, network integrity, data protection, application vulnerabilities, and automation. Challenges exist in implementing ZT, such as system complexity, operational speed, and fragility from disparate integrations. Elastic’s Search AI Platform is highlighted for its role in enhancing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traditional AI vs. generative AI: A guide for IT leaders</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5057/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5057/</guid>
      <description>🌐 The AI landscape is rapidly changing, presenting challenges for IT leaders. This article outlines the key differences between traditional AI and generative AI. Traditional AI has supported enterprise operations for years, while generative AI is redefining creativity and innovation. Key considerations for choosing the right AI include task complexity, creativity needs, and data requirements. Understanding these factors is essential for strategic decision-making. 🔍 #ArtificialIntelligence&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Traditional AI vs. generative AI: A guide for IT leaders</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-6301/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-6301/</guid>
      <description>AI is evolving rapidly, presenting new challenges for IT leaders. This article outlines the key differences between traditional AI and generative AI. Traditional AI excels in structured tasks, while generative AI is suited for creative applications. Understanding your organization&amp;rsquo;s needs is crucial for choosing the right AI approach. Explore more about their applications and impact on technology. 🤖💡 #ArtificialIntelligence #TechTrends #ITLeadership #GenerativeAI #BusinessStrategy</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic response to blog ‘EDR 0-Day Vulnerability’</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5059/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5059/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Elastic’s Security team has responded to claims of a vulnerability in Elastic Defend. After comprehensive investigation, no evidence was found to support the alleged bypass of EDR monitoring or remote code execution. The demonstrations provided were not from unprivileged processes. Elastic remains committed to transparency and encourages researchers to share any valid findings at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:security@elastic.co&#34;&gt;security@elastic.co&lt;/a&gt;. Updates will be provided as necessary. #CyberSecurity #Elastic #Vulnerability #EDR #InfoSec</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Generative AI fields now available in ECS allowing parity and compatibility with OTel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5060/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5060/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Elastic! The Elastic Common Schema (ECS) now supports generative AI (GenAI) fields, enhancing compatibility with OpenTelemetry (OTel). This allows for better normalization of data from diverse GenAI vendors. Key use cases include observability, security, and log normalization for GenAI applications. Users can seamlessly integrate ECS and OTel for improved monitoring. Stay informed and explore how these advancements can benefit your workflows! #Elastic #GenerativeAI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming IT Help Desk: How Elastic’s Search AI Platform supercharges Salesforce Service Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5061/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5061/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Transforming IT support with Elastic&amp;rsquo;s Search AI Platform in Salesforce Service Cloud is a game-changer. The platform enhances internal IT operations by providing real-time, accurate assistance. It allows users to choose between instant AI support or traditional ticket submissions for complex issues. This dual approach improves ticket quality and accelerates resolution times. By integrating with tools like JIRA and Google Docs, it ensures responses are grounded in enterprise-specific&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Community, consulting, and chili sauce: Top Down with Dominik Toepfer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5062/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5062/</guid>
      <description>Meet Dominik “Dom” Toepfer, a principal software engineer at Elastic, where he focuses on generative AI and Search. His engineering journey began with a book on Elasticsearch, leading him through various roles at the company. Dom emphasizes the importance of collaboration, stating, “We build better together.” He balances work and family life, ensuring he’s present for his kids while pursuing his passion for tech. His workspace is carefully designed for inspiration, featuring tools and an&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic joins AWS Zero Trust Accelerator for Government (ZTAG) program</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4998/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4998/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Elastic has joined the AWS Zero Trust Accelerator for Government (ZTAG) program. This partnership aims to enhance the security of US federal agencies by integrating Elastic’s data-centric approach with AWS’s Zero Trust framework. 🔐 The collaboration focuses on improving security information and event management (SIEM) tailored for the government&amp;rsquo;s Zero Trust architecture. This is crucial as cyber threats continue to evolve. 📈 Together, they aim to support federal agencies in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic wins 2025 Google Cloud DORA Award for Architecting for the Future with AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4897/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4897/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Elastic has won the 2025 Google Cloud DORA Award for Architecting for the Future with AI. This recognition highlights our commitment to enhancing software delivery and operational performance using DORA principles. By adopting a data-driven approach, we&amp;rsquo;ve improved the velocity and reliability of our services for customers. AI is transforming software development, with 76% of technologists relying on it daily. Our focus remains on innovation and smart operations in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 8.17.10 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4898/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4898/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Elastic Stack 8.17.10 has officially been released! This new version comes with important updates and fixes compared to 8.17.9. Users are encouraged to upgrade to enhance their experience. For a complete list of changes and resolved issues, check out the release notes. #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews #VersionRelease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 8.18.5 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4899/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4899/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for Elastic Stack users! Version 8.18.5 has been officially released today. Users are encouraged to upgrade from version 8.18.4 to benefit from the latest improvements. For a comprehensive list of issues fixed and changes made, check the release notes. #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews #Upgrade</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 8.19.2 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4901/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4901/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Elastic Stack 8.19.2 has been released today. The new version offers improvements over 8.19.1, and users are encouraged to upgrade. For a detailed overview of fixed issues and changes, check the release notes. Stay updated! #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews #Upgrade #VersionRelease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 9.0.5 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4900/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4900/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Elastic Stack has officially launched version 9.0.5! This update is recommended over version 9.0.4 for improved performance and fixes. For a complete list of changes and resolved issues, check out the release notes. Stay updated and enhance your experience! 🔧📊 #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 9.1.2 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4902/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4902/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Elastic Stack version 9.1.2 has been officially released! This update brings several important fixes and improvements over version 9.1.1. For a complete list of changes and resolved issues, please check the release notes. Upgrade today to enhance your experience! #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews #VersionRelease</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating creativity with Elasticsearch vector database and the Dell AI Data Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4836/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4836/</guid>
      <description>Unlock creativity in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced industries! 🚀 The collaboration between Dell and NVIDIA is enhancing the Dell AI Data Platform with Elasticsearch, streamlining access to unstructured data for teams in media, gaming, and design. This partnership enables natural language searches, global collaboration, and AI-generated insights, ensuring efficient workflows and quick decision-making. Discover how this innovative platform can transform your creative processes! 💡🌍 #AI #Elasticsearch #Dell&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise of intelligent banking: Unifying fraud, security, and compliance in the era of AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4835/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4835/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving financial landscape, security, compliance, and customer trust are interconnected. The IDC Spotlight report, sponsored by Elastic and AWS, highlights the need for financial institutions to adopt AI-powered platforms that unify fraud prevention, cybersecurity, and regulatory compliance. As threats grow more sophisticated, institutions must move beyond siloed risk functions to ensure operational resilience and regulatory readiness. This shift is critical for maintaining customer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Security: Announcing Agentic Query validation, Attack Discovery persistence, and automated scheduling and actions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4720/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4720/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Elastic Security has unveiled updates to Attack Discovery and the Elastic AI Assistant, enhancing security operations with AI support. 🔍 The new agentic query validation ensures reliable queries, reducing errors during investigations. Analysts can focus on critical tasks with functional queries provided right away. 📅 The AI Assistant is now time-aware, streamlining incident management by providing real-time on-call information. 📊 Additionally, Attack Discovery saves historical findings and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 8.19.1 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4723/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4723/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New Release Alert! 🚨 Elastic Stack 8.19.1 has officially launched! This version includes important fixes and improvements over 8.19.0. For a detailed overview of the changes and resolved issues, check the release notes. Upgrade your systems for enhanced performance! 🔄 #ElasticStack #TechUpdate #SoftwareRelease #UpgradeNow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic Stack 9.1.1 released</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4722/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4722/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Elastic Stack has officially released version 9.1.1. This update includes important fixes and improvements compared to version 9.1.0. Users are encouraged to upgrade to benefit from these enhancements. For a complete list of changes and resolved issues, check the release notes. #ElasticStack #SoftwareUpdate #TechNews #UpgradeNow</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hash, store, join: A modern solution to log deduplication with ES|QL LOOKUP JOIN</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4692/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4692/</guid>
      <description>In the realm of cybersecurity, the challenge of balancing data fidelity with budget constraints is critical, especially with PowerShell logging. 📊 Comprehensive logging is essential for threat hunting, yet it can lead to massive data storage costs. This article introduces an innovative approach using the Elastic Stack and ES|QL LOOKUP JOIN to optimize log management. The strategy focuses on intelligent data deduplication, allowing organizations to store references rather than full logs,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expose hidden threats with EASE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4115/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4115/</guid>
      <description>Introducing the Elastic AI SOC Engine (EASE)! 🚀 EASE is designed to enhance security operations by integrating AI capabilities into existing SIEM and EDR systems. It helps analysts detect complex threats faster and reduces investigation time. With features like centralized alert summaries and automated attack discovery, EASE enables better prioritization and response to high-risk alerts. 🛡️ This solution is especially beneficial for organizations looking to improve their threat detection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leaning into AI, ML, and observability to manage your ever-growing infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-520/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-520/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The landscape of IT infrastructure is rapidly changing with AI and ML enhancing software development and orchestration. As systems scale, the need for advanced observability tools has become crucial. This transformation reveals gaps in current tools, affecting data volume, fidelity, and root cause analysis. To address these challenges, the article outlines four key technologies essential for modern observability. #AI #MachineLearning #Observability #ITInfrastructure #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Harnessing Elastic APIs for custom AI-driven SOAR</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-521/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-521/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Security teams face challenges with alerts and investigations. Elastic Security offers an API-first approach, enabling custom workflows for efficient threat response. 🛠️ The article highlights how Elastic&amp;rsquo;s APIs can automate security orchestration, integrating AI and tools like Slack for improved operations. 💡 Key steps include monitoring for critical alerts, leveraging the Elastic AI Assistant, and executing commands seamlessly. #CyberSecurity #ElasticSecurity #Automation #AI #SOAR</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the model: A data foundation for a trustworthy AI future in the US</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-522/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-522/</guid>
      <description>The White House&amp;rsquo;s “Winning the Race: America’s AI Action Plan” emphasizes AI as key to the U.S. economy and security. It highlights the need for a transparent data foundation to govern and trust AI technologies. The success of this plan relies on addressing data challenges related to evaluation, bias detection, and cybersecurity. Building a unified data ecosystem is crucial for innovation and accountability. #AIActionPlan #DataGovernance #Innovation #TrustworthyAI #USAI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Transforming digital experiences: How Liferay&#39;s partnership with Elastic drives revenue and efficiency</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-523/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-523/</guid>
      <description>Liferay partners with Elastic to enhance digital experiences for complex business needs. Since 2015, Liferay has integrated Elasticsearch into its platform, enabling tailored search solutions that improve user interactions across marketing, sales, and services. This OEM partnership simplifies procurement by allowing clients to manage everything through a single agreement. The collaboration not only boosts efficiency but also supports revenue growth for Liferay, making it easier for clients to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
