<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GitLab-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/gitlab-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GitLab-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/gitlab-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Claude Sonnet 3.7 deprecation notice for GitLab Duo</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11555/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11555/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for GitLab Duo Users! 🚨 Anthropic is deprecating Claude Sonnet 3.7. As a result, GitLab will remove support for this model in version 18.8, scheduled for January 15, 2026. 📅 Current Status: Claude Sonnet 3.7 is still available. 🔄 Action Needed: Migrate to Claude 4.0+ models now. For further details, check the resources or contact GitLab Support for assistance. #GitLab #AI #ClaudeSonnet #Migration #TechUpdates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is a YAML file? A complete guide from basics to practical use</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11544/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11544/</guid>
      <description>📄 YAML is a widely used data serialization format, known for its clarity and simplicity. It&amp;rsquo;s often utilized in configuration files and playbooks, especially in tools like Kubernetes and Ansible. 🔍 Key comparisons include YAML vs. JSON, highlighting YAML&amp;rsquo;s use of indentation for better readability. The article also discusses YAML vs. CUE, emphasizing CUE&amp;rsquo;s schema validation features. ✏️ Understanding YAML syntax, such as indentation and data structures, is crucial for effective use. The&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ace your planning without the context-switching</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11340/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11340/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Software development teams often juggle multiple tasks under tight deadlines. The planning overhead can hinder strategic thinking, leading to missed opportunities. Introducing &lt;strong&gt;GitLab Duo Planner&lt;/strong&gt;, an AI tool designed to streamline planning workflows right within GitLab. This tool helps product managers reduce overhead, improve alignment, and enhance predictability in their projects. Key features include: - Prioritization using frameworks like RICE and MoSCoW. - Efficient work breakdown&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modernize Java applications quickly with GitLab Duo with Amazon Q</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11158/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11158/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Modernizing Java applications just got easier with GitLab Duo and Amazon Q! Upgrading from Java 8 to Java 17, which once took weeks, can now be done in minutes. Simply create an issue in GitLab and trigger the transformation with a command. The automated process analyzes your code, updates dependencies, and generates merge requests for review—all while maintaining functionality. This means less time on upgrades and more on new features! For more details, check out the full walkthrough!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delivering faster and smarter scans with Advanced SAST</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11105/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11105/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab&amp;rsquo;s Advanced SAST is enhancing static application security testing to improve developer workflows. With the latest updates, teams can expect faster scans, increased accuracy, and the ability to create custom detection rules. 🔍 These enhancements, like multi-core and diff-based scanning, significantly reduce scan times, making security integration seamless. 💡 By prioritizing both speed and accuracy, GitLab aims to drive SAST adoption and secure software development. #DevSecOps #GitLab&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab 18.5: Intelligence that moves software development forward</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11106/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11106/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab 18.5 has been released, focusing on improving usability and integrating AI for software development teams. The new panel-based UI enhances user experience, allowing easy access to GitLab Duo Chat for contextual assistance. Purpose-built agents support vulnerability triage and backlog management, streamlining workflows. Key updates include advanced security features for identifying exploitable vulnerabilities, alongside tools for backlog organization and simplified API configurations&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Haiku 4.5 now available in GitLab Duo Agentic Chat</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11066/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11066/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for GitLab users! Claude Haiku 4.5, Anthropic&amp;rsquo;s latest and fastest model, is now available in the GitLab Duo model selector. With a performance score of 73.3% on SWE-bench Verified and over 2x the speed of Claude Sonnet 4.5, this model enhances coding workflows for developers. Claude Haiku 4.5 enables multi-agent orchestration, allowing efficient parallel task execution. This integration supports faster iterations and improved AI assistance within GitLab&amp;rsquo;s ecosystem. Access&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Variable and artifact sharing in GitLab parent-child pipelines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11008/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11008/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In the world of software development, adapting to evolving needs is essential. The article discusses the significance of CI/CD pipelines, specifically the parent-child pipeline model in GitLab. 🔗 This approach breaks complex pipelines into smaller, manageable child pipelines, improving functionality and efficiency. It also covers how to share variables and artifacts between these pipelines for streamlined operations. 📊 Key benefits include conditional execution, parallel processing, and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we built a structured Streamlit Application Framework in Snowflake</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10619/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10619/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The GitLab Data team has unified scattered Streamlit applications into a structured framework for Snowflake. This framework improves security, simplifies deployment, and enhances collaboration across roles: Maintainers, Creators, and Viewers. Key takeaways include the importance of governance, automation, and compliance from day one. Learn how to streamline your applications today! #DataEngineering #Streamlit #Snowflake #DevOps #Automation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Optimize GitLab object storage for scale and performance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10569/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10569/</guid>
      <description>Managing GitLab at scale requires careful object storage setup for optimal performance and security. Utilize a consolidated form for GitLab components to streamline configurations and enable encrypted S3 buckets. For container registries, a separate setup with the new s3_v2 driver is necessary. Ensure you disable proxy downloads for better performance and adopt identity-based authentication methods for improved security. #GitLab #ObjectStorage #CloudComputing #DevOps #DataSecurity 🌐🔐📦</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Streamline enterprise artifact management with GitLab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10556/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10556/</guid>
      <description>Managing artifacts has become increasingly complex and costly for organizations. A recent article highlights the significant challenges faced by platform engineers, including high licensing fees and productivity loss due to fragmented systems. GitLab offers a strategic solution by focusing on key artifact formats, helping to reduce operational overhead and improve efficiency. Their capabilities include lifecycle management, security integration, and deep CI/CD support. For teams looking to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Atlassian ending Data Center as GitLab maintains deployment choice</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10496/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10496/</guid>
      <description>Atlassian has announced that its Data Center products will reach end-of-life by March 28, 2029. This shift requires many organizations to rethink their DevSecOps strategies. GitLab offers a range of deployment options, including self-managed, cloud, and hybrid solutions, ensuring flexibility and compliance for diverse business needs. For companies relying on self-managed deployments, this change poses challenges, particularly in regulated industries where compliance and data security are&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How GitLab transforms embedded systems testing cycles</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10368/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10368/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Embedded developers face long waits for testing cycles, often leading to delays in bug fixes and product releases. GitLab addresses these challenges with managed lifecycle environments, which automate virtual testing without the complexities of traditional setups. This innovative approach ties testing environments to merge requests, ensuring persistence throughout feature development while eliminating unnecessary rebuilds and reducing costs. Discover how GitLab transforms embedded systems&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Greater AI choice in GitLab Duo: Claude Sonnet 4.5 arrives</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10233/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10233/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab introduces Claude Sonnet 4.5, Anthropic’s advanced coding model, now available in the GitLab Duo model selector. Users can enhance their experience with improved tool orchestration and domain-specific capabilities. This model excels in cybersecurity, finance, and research workflows. 👩‍💻 GitLab Duo Pro and Enterprise customers can access it now. Check out GitLab&amp;rsquo;s documentation for more details! #GitLab #AI #Coding #SoftwareDevelopment #ClaudeSonnet4.5</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic AI guides and resources</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10201/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10201/</guid>
      <description>Discover the potential of Agentic AI! 🤖 This advanced AI type operates independently, breaking complex tasks into manageable steps and adapting to challenges. Unlike traditional AI, it understands requests and executes plans without constant human input. GitLab’s latest updates enhance development with tools like GitLab Duo, enabling seamless collaboration between developers and AI agents. Learn how Agentic AI is shaping the future of software development! 🚀 #AgenticAI #SoftwareDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab Duo Agent Platform adds support for Model Context Protocol</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10127/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10127/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab Duo Agent Platform now supports the Model Context Protocol (MCP), enhancing the integration of AI in development. MCP provides AI secure access to internal systems, enabling developers to retrieve real-time information directly within their IDE. This reduces context switching and allows for a smoother workflow. With MCP, AI tools can connect reliably to various systems while maintaining security and privacy. Explore the capabilities of GitLab’s MCP in your development environment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab named a Leader in the 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for DevOps Platforms</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10081/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10081/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab has been recognized as a Leader in the 2025 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for DevOps Platforms for the third year in a row! This acknowledgment reflects GitLab&amp;rsquo;s strong platform strategy, essential for modern software development. Organizations are increasingly leveraging AI-driven capabilities while ensuring security and compliance. GitLab&amp;rsquo;s unified platform enhances collaboration, enabling teams to deliver software efficiently and securely. Key features include: - Automated code reviews&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab 18.4: AI-native development with automation and insight</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9911/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9911/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab 18.4 is here, enhancing AI-native development! The latest update expands your capabilities with custom agents through the AI Catalog, improving collaboration via Agentic Chat, and refining code navigation using the Knowledge Graph. Plus, the new Fix Failed Pipelines Flow ensures your pipelines remain efficient and aligned with business needs. Join The Developer Show on Sept. 23 for insights on these features! #GitLab #AIDevelopment #DevOps #SoftwareEngineering #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A comprehensive guide to GitLab DAST</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9748/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9748/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Modern businesses rely heavily on web applications, making security essential. GitLab&amp;rsquo;s Dynamic Application Security Testing (DAST) helps identify runtime vulnerabilities that static analysis misses. 📊 DAST integrates into CI/CD pipelines, providing automated security testing to enhance compliance and risk management. It detects issues like authentication flaws, input validation vulnerabilities, and more. 🔄 By adopting DAST, teams can reduce costs, speed up deployment, and empower&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab named a Leader in the 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for AI Code Assistants</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9736/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9736/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab has been recognized as a Leader in the 2025 Gartner Magic Quadrant for AI Code Assistants for the second time. The evaluation highlights GitLab Duo&amp;rsquo;s generative AI capabilities, which integrate into the DevSecOps platform. This allows teams to automate tasks and enhance collaboration through AI agents. 🔐 The GitLab Duo Agent Platform prioritizes security and compliance, ensuring all actions are visible and reviewable. It helps developers focus on high-impact work while maintaining&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How GitLab Duo Agent Platform transforms DataOps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9711/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9711/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Discover how the GitLab Duo Agent Platform can streamline DataOps! Creating dbt models manually can take hours, but this platform automates the process in under 10 minutes. By extracting data from Reddit Ads to Snowflake, it generates models, configurations, and test queries—all without writing code. Key steps include preparing data structures, utilizing GitLab Duo&amp;rsquo;s features, and validating outcomes with automated tests. This approach significantly enhances developer efficiency and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab and Accenture announce Global Reseller Agreement</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9645/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9645/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab and Accenture have announced a global reseller agreement, making Accenture an authorized reseller of GitLab&amp;rsquo;s DevSecOps platform. This collaboration aims to enhance digital transformation for organizations. Key focus areas include: - &lt;strong&gt;Enterprise-scale DevSecOps Transformation&lt;/strong&gt; for modernizing development practices - &lt;strong&gt;Mainframe Modernization&lt;/strong&gt; to assist customers in migrating from legacy systems - &lt;strong&gt;GitLab Duo with Amazon Q&lt;/strong&gt; for AI-driven software development ensuring security and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How we supercharged GitLab CI statuses with WebSockets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9666/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9666/</guid>
      <description>🚀 We&amp;rsquo;ve made significant improvements to GitLab&amp;rsquo;s CI job status updates by reducing API calls by 92.56%! In 2025, we&amp;rsquo;ve shifted from legacy polling to WebSockets, allowing real-time updates without unnecessary network traffic. This change means users now see job status updates instantly instead of waiting up to 30 seconds. With GraphQL subscriptions, we’ve transformed how data is fetched, resulting in just 3.4 million calls per day, down from 45 million. Stay tuned as we work on implementing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supercharge your Git workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9531/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9531/</guid>
      <description>Struggling with slow Git clone times? ⏳ Introducing &lt;strong&gt;Git Much Faster&lt;/strong&gt;! This optimization script helps developers reduce clone times significantly, with improvements of up to 93%. By utilizing various benchmarking techniques, it transforms workflows for large repositories. Key benefits include: - Reduced CI/CD pipeline delays - Lower infrastructure costs - Enhanced developer productivity 🚀 Learn how to implement these optimizations for both development and CI/CD environments. #Git #DevOps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A developer&#39;s guide to building secure retail apps with GitLab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7741/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7741/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Retailers face unique security challenges as modern commerce expands. With mobile apps, AI, and IoT, each touchpoint increases the risk of vulnerabilities that can impact customer trust and revenue. Traditional security methods often fall short in this complex landscape. An integrated DevSecOps platform, like GitLab, embeds security into the development lifecycle, allowing teams to innovate while maintaining customer experience. Discover how to address these challenges effectively through&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe coding with GitLab Duo Agent Platform: Issue to MR Flow</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7686/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7686/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing the GitLab Duo Agent Platform! Available now in Beta, this tool enables AI agents to streamline complex tasks with GitLab resources like issues and merge requests. The &amp;ldquo;Issue to MR&amp;rdquo; Flow simplifies turning well-scoped issues into draft merge requests, saving developers time and effort. By automating the process, it reduces the overhead associated with common development tasks. To get started, ensure you have a clear issue with requirements and the necessary permissions. Then,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab achieves ISO/IEC 42001 certification for AI governance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7617/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7617/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab has achieved the ISO/IEC 42001 certification for AI governance! This certification establishes a framework for responsible AI management within organizations. The certification covers GitLab Duo and the Duo Agent Platform, enhancing collaboration and efficiency in software development. Key features include code suggestions, vulnerability explanations, and automated test generation. This achievement promotes trust, transparency, and aligns with evolving AI regulations. GitLab is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure Rust development with GitLab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7618/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7618/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Rust developers, GitLab is here to enhance your workflow! The platform offers strong CI/CD capabilities tailored to Rust&amp;rsquo;s emphasis on safety and performance. With GitLab, you can easily set up automated testing, cross-platform builds, and effective documentation generation. Explore how to build a mortgage calculator app in Rust while leveraging GitLab&amp;rsquo;s features for efficient development! #GitLab #RustProgramming #CICD #DevSecOps #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why enterprise independence matters more than ever in DevSecOps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7635/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7635/</guid>
      <description>GitLab emphasizes the importance of enterprise independence in its latest release, GitLab 18.3. Key features include enhanced AI transparency and governance, ensuring that your code and data are not locked into vendor systems. The GitLab AI Transparency Center details data usage, providing clarity in an evolving landscape. 🛠️✨ Deployment options are flexible, allowing organizations to adapt to regulatory challenges without vendor constraints. Security and compliance are built-in, reducing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fine-grained permissions for job tokens is now GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7209/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7209/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab 18.3 has launched fine-grained permissions for job tokens, now in GA! This update enhances security by allowing maintainers to set specific permissions for job tokens, following the principle of least privilege. 🔒 Key resources include Repositories, Deployments, and Pipelines, with more API endpoints planned for future releases. This capability aims to reduce security risks in CI/CD pipelines. 👥 DevOps teams should assess this opt-in feature for projects with automated deployments&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom admin roles are now GA</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6337/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6337/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab has rolled out custom admin roles for Self-Managed and Dedicated instances! These roles enable organizations to apply granular permissions, ensuring the principle of least privilege is upheld while enhancing operational efficiency. Key features include centralized management, LDAP integration, and purpose-built roles for various teams. This aligns with GitLab&amp;rsquo;s mission to boost software supply chain security. For more details, check out the custom roles documentation. #GitLab&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedded views: The future of work tracking in GitLab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5775/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5775/</guid>
      <description>📊 Tired of switching tabs in GitLab to track your projects? Introducing &lt;strong&gt;Embedded Views&lt;/strong&gt;! This feature, available in version 18.3, allows you to access live, relevant data directly within your workflow. No more outdated reports or endless context switching. With &lt;strong&gt;GitLab Query Language (GLQL)&lt;/strong&gt;, you can pull real-time data right where you need it, enhancing collaboration and maintaining context. Learn how this can transform your team&amp;rsquo;s work tracking! 🚀 #GitLab #ProjectManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab 18.3: Expanding AI orchestration in software engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5063/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5063/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab 18.3 is here, enhancing AI orchestration in software engineering! The platform now integrates AI at three levels: a unified data repository, a control plane for software delivery, and a streamlined user experience. This aims to boost productivity and simplify workflows. Key updates include the introduction of AI agents, expanded integrations, and enhanced context awareness for improved collaboration. Explore the future of DevSecOps with GitLab! 🌟 #GitLab #DevSecOps #AIIntegration&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab 18.3: Expanding AI orchestration in software engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-6302/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-6302/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab 18.3 is here, enhancing software engineering with integrated AI capabilities! The platform now serves as a comprehensive system of record, control plane, and user experience hub. Key updates include a Knowledge Graph for better data context, an Orchestration Layer for multi-agent workflows, and first-class agent integration across the development lifecycle. This evolution promotes seamless human-AI collaboration, boosting productivity for over 50 million users. Explore the future of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GitLab documentation site gets a major design overhaul</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5064/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5064/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The GitLab documentation site has undergone a major redesign! Key updates include: 🌙 Dark mode for improved readability. 🎨 Enhanced brand alignment with GitLab&amp;rsquo;s marketing site. 👍 Simplified feedback options with thumbs up/down directly on pages. 📚 Redesigned navigation for easier access to over 2,300 pages. 🔧 Addressed technical debt for a more polished experience. These changes stem from a recent platform migration, enhancing overall performance. #GitLab #Documentation #UXDesign&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s new in Git 2.51.0?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5065/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5065/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Git has released version 2.51, with key updates aimed at improving performance and user experience. 🔧 Notable changes include enhanced git-push(1) and git-fetch(1) commands, which now use batched updates for reference synchronization, resulting in up to 22x speed improvements. 📦 The release also introduces the &amp;ldquo;reftable&amp;rdquo; format as the default reference backend, addressing limitations of the previous &amp;ldquo;files&amp;rdquo; backend. 🔑 Additionally, SHA-256 is now the default hash function, enhancing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why financial services choose single-tenant SaaS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5066/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5066/</guid>
      <description>Financial institutions face unique challenges with shared infrastructure, which heightens systemic risks. As highlighted by JPMorgan Chase&amp;rsquo;s CISO, incidents on multi-tenant platforms can lead to widespread disruptions. GitLab Dedicated offers a solution, providing isolated environments for development while ensuring compliance and security. This approach enables institutions to manage risks more effectively, ensuring their source code is treated as a critical asset. Learn more about how&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom rules in GitLab Duo Agentic Chat for greater developer efficiency</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4903/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4903/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of GitLab Duo with custom rules to enhance developer efficiency! 🚀 Transform your AI assistant into a tailored coding expert. Set version controls for Java, enforce coding styles, and automate DevSecOps processes. This guide covers practical steps, use cases, and examples to streamline your coding standards. Explore how to implement custom rules in GitLab projects today! #GitLab #DeveloperEfficiency #CustomRules #DevSecOps #AIInDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get started with GitLab Duo Agentic Chat in the web UI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4837/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4837/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab has introduced the Duo Agentic Chat feature, enhancing user interaction with the GitLab API directly from the web UI. This tool allows users to manage issues, track statuses, and take actions based on conversations. Access is available for Duo Pro or Enterprise users, streamlining workflows across projects. To start, navigate to your Group or Project, open the chat panel, and toggle to Agentic mode. Explore how Agentic Chat can simplify your development tasks! #GitLab #DuoAgenticChat&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Own your AI: Self-Hosted GitLab Duo models with AWS Bedrock</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4724/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4724/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of AI with GitLab Duo Self-Hosted! 🚀 This article outlines how organizations can implement AI models while maintaining control over data and security. Key benefits include data privacy, model flexibility, and compliance adherence. Learn about the architecture, prerequisites, and step-by-step implementation using AWS Bedrock. For detailed guidance, check out the full article! 📊🔐 #AI #GitLab #DataPrivacy #AWS #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab uncovers Bittensor theft campaign via PyPI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4678/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4678/</guid>
      <description>🚨 GitLab&amp;rsquo;s Vulnerability Research team has uncovered a cryptocurrency theft campaign targeting the Bittensor ecosystem via typosquatted Python packages on PyPI. Multiple malicious packages mimicked legitimate ones, published within a 25-minute window. These were designed to steal funds during staking operations, bypassing user confirmations and draining wallets silently. The attackers used a typosquatting strategy, exploiting common errors to increase the likelihood of installation. GitLab is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Measuring AI ROI at scale: A practical guide to GitLab Duo Analytics</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4116/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4116/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the value of AI with GitLab Duo Analytics! 📊 This practical guide emphasizes the importance of measuring AI investments to understand usage and ROI. GitLab&amp;rsquo;s Duo Accelerator program offers a specialized tool that converts usage data into actionable insights. Organizations can optimize license allocation and identify high-value use cases, enhancing AI adoption across teams. Learn how to implement a hybrid analytics solution for measuring AI productivity and make informed decisions for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Action Hackathon:  Celebrating the GitLab innovations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-3190/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-3190/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The AI in Action Hackathon, held from May 6 to June 17, 2025, invited developers to explore AI solutions for a chance at a $50,000 prize pool. This collaboration between Google Cloud, MongoDB, and GitLab aimed to enhance DevSecOps practices, allowing participants to leverage powerful tools for innovative projects. 🌟 Notable winners included: - &lt;strong&gt;Pipeline Doctor&lt;/strong&gt;: Uses AI for root cause analysis, improving CI/CD reliability. - &lt;strong&gt;Agentic CICD&lt;/strong&gt;: Automates DevSecOps tasks, enhancing software&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating by direct transfer is generally available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3191/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3191/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab 18.3 introduces direct transfer for migrating groups and projects, making it easier for users to copy resources between instances. This feature simplifies the migration process, allowing you to move entire top-level groups with sub-groups and projects without manual file exports. It supports user contribution mapping and works reliably with large projects. For those using GitLab.com, the feature is enabled by default. Self-managed users should check their application settings. 🌐&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing AI together: GitLab’s partnership with security researchers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3192/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3192/</guid>
      <description>GitLab is enhancing security in AI with the support of external researchers. As AI evolves, so do the challenges, like prompt injection attacks. Our collaboration with organizations like Persistent Security helps us identify vulnerabilities and implement fast solutions. By engaging with the security research community, we aim to protect customers and ensure a secure development environment. Join us in our mission at GitLab! 🤝🔒 #AISecurity #CyberSecurity #GitLab #Collaboration #SoftwareSafety</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
