<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uber-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/uber-engineering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uber-Engineering on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/uber-engineering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Open-Sourcing Starlark Worker: Define Cadence Workflows with Starlark</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9550/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9550/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in workflow management! The recently open-sourced Starlark Worker integrates the Starlark scripting language with Cadence workflow orchestration. This collaboration aims to simplify the execution of workflows, enhancing user experience and efficiency. Explore the potential of Starlark in defining Cadence workflows! #OpenSource #WorkflowManagement #Starlark #Cadence #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Uber’s Data Lake: Batch Data Replication Using HiveSync</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7734/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7734/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Dive into how Uber efficiently manages batch data replication using HiveSync! This technology ensures their data lake remains consistent, reliable, and high-performing. The article highlights the engineering efforts behind maintaining data integrity at scale. Learn more about Uber&amp;rsquo;s innovative approach to data management! 📊💻 #DataEngineering #Uber #HiveSync #DataManagement #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Controlling the Rollout of Large-Scale Monorepo Changes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7472/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7472/</guid>
      <description>Uber is enhancing its deployment strategy by managing the impact of large-scale changes through effective orchestration. As the company moves towards fully automated continuous deployment, implementing robust safety practices is essential to minimize risks. This approach ensures smoother transitions and maintains system integrity during significant updates. #Deployment #Uber #TechUpdates #ContinuousIntegration #SoftwareEngineering 🚀🔧📈</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Uber Serves over 150 Million Reads per Second from Integrated Cache with Stronger Consistency Guarantees</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7249/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7249/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Uber&amp;rsquo;s integrated cache, CacheFront, now handles over 150 million reads per second, achieving impressive hit rates exceeding 99.9%. Recent enhancements have strengthened the consistency guarantees of this infrastructure, ensuring reliable performance for users. For more insights, check out the full article. #Uber #CacheFront #TechInnovation #DataInfrastructure #Performance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightweight Office Infrastructure: Transitioning from Backbone to SD-WAN</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5164/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5164/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Uber is enhancing its global office network by adopting SD-WAN technology. This transition has resulted in an 89% reduction in latency, improved automation, and more efficient connectivity worldwide. Such advancements are set to make operations faster and more cost-effective. #SDWAN #Uber #TechInnovation #GlobalNetwork #Connectivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forecasting Models to Improve Driver Availability at Airports</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5165/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5165/</guid>
      <description>Uber is enhancing driver availability at airports through advanced forecasting models. 📊 These models aim to reduce wait times and minimize queues for passengers. By analyzing data patterns, Uber optimizes driver deployment to meet demand effectively. 🚖 Stay tuned for more updates on innovations in transportation! #Uber #DataScience #AirportTravel #DriverAvailability #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locking Down the Fleet: Encryption at Rest and Disk Isolation at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5015/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Managing encryption at rest and ensuring disk isolation for numerous stateful workloads presents significant challenges. In a recent article, the focus is on how effective logical volume management was implemented to secure a large fleet of servers. This approach enhances data security while maintaining operational efficiency. #DataSecurity #Encryption #LogicalVolumeManagement #TechInnovation #CyberSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>uReview: Scalable, Trustworthy GenAI for Code Review at Uber</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4963/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4963/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Uber has introduced uReview, a GenAI-powered tool designed to enhance code review efficiency. This innovative solution automates the review process, helping developers save thousands of hours while maintaining high-quality standards. uReview aims to improve trust in code reviews without compromising on quality for every commit. #CodeReview #GenAI #UberTech #DeveloperTools #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Restaurants to Retail: Scaling Uber Eats for Everything</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4767/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4767/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting developments are on the horizon for Uber Eats with the introduction of its new catalog system, INCA (INventory and CAtalog). This innovative system is designed to process billions of updates daily from retailers globally, enhancing the efficiency of service delivery. Stay tuned as Uber Eats expands its offerings beyond restaurants! 🍽️🌍 #UberEats #INCA #RetailInnovation #TechNews #DeliveryServices</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
