<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sketch-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/sketch-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sketch-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/sketch-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>9 reasons to choose Sketch in 2026</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2026-01-26-14855/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2026-01-26-14855/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Thinking of a new design tool in 2026? Check out Sketch! 🖥️ Sketch has undergone a major redesign, enhancing usability for designers. Features like a new Inspector and focus mode elevate the design experience. 💡 Expect robust tools like Stacks, frames, and unique additions like a minimap for navigation. 🤝 Enjoy the flexibility to collaborate in real-time or work offline, plus connect with AI tools for enhanced functionality. Explore more at sketch.com/features! #DesignTools #Sketch2026&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everything we shipped at Sketch in 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13601/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13601/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Sketch in 2025! This year, we launched three major releases: Athens, Barcelona, and Copenhagen, each packed with new features. Highlights include the introduction of Stacks and Frames, enhancing layout flexibility and design capabilities. The Command Bar now supports quick component access, streamlining your workflow. With the Barcelona update, we introduced a new glass effect for designing on iOS and macOS 26, along with progressive blurs and fade effects. Stay tuned&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A guided tour of Copenhagen</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12836/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12836/</guid>
      <description>🎨 Exciting updates in the latest Sketch release, Copenhagen! The redesign brings a modern UI aligned with macOS Tahoe, enhancing both aesthetics and functionality. Key changes include a custom sidebar layout and document tabs now integrated within the sidebar for better usability. Focus mode has been introduced in the layer list, helping users manage complex documents by displaying only relevant layers. Explore these features and more in the new Copenhagen update! #Sketch #macOSTahoe&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Ben McCarthy is bringing Obscura’s vision to photo editing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7577/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7577/</guid>
      <description>📸 Ben McCarthy, creator of Obscura, has launched Obscura Studio, a new photo editing app focused on simplicity and efficiency. The app emerged from the need to adapt to Apple&amp;rsquo;s Lock Screen Camera extension, prompting a redesign of Obscura. This standalone editor allows for streamlined editing without launching the camera first. McCarthy emphasizes thoughtful design that prioritizes ease of use, aiming to create a product that meets user needs effectively. #PhotoEditing #AppDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
