<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code-as-Craft on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/code-as-craft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Code-as-Craft on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:40:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/code-as-craft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building Etsy Buyer Profiles with LLMs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7694/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 21:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7694/</guid>
      <description>Etsy is enhancing buyer experiences by using large language models (LLMs) to create detailed buyer profiles based on shopping behaviors. 🛍️ These profiles capture individual interests, helping to tailor search results for nearly 90 million users while maintaining privacy compliance. Users have the option to opt-out of profile generation. 🔍 Technical improvements have reduced the time for profile generation from 21 days to just 3 days, making personalization more efficient and cost-effective&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context engineering case studies: Etsy-specific question answering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5133/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 20:04:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5133/</guid>
      <description>Exploring prompt engineering in AI-assisted onboarding at Etsy reveals both benefits and limitations. The study focused on how well LLMs provide reliable answers to Etsy-specific questions, particularly in the Travel &amp;amp; Entertainment domain. Initial findings indicate that concise prompts improve answer accuracy. However, some instances showcased LLM &amp;ldquo;hallucinations,&amp;rdquo; emphasizing the need for careful prompt design. For more insights, check out the full article! 📝🤖 #AIEducation #Etsy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
