<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DigitalOcean-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/digitalocean-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DigitalOcean-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:36:21 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/digitalocean-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Powered by DigitalOcean Hatch: How Ex-human uses GPU Droplets to Build Empathetic AI that Serves Customers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-8382/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:36:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-8382/</guid>
      <description>🌐 DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s Hatch program has revamped its support for AI startups in 2024, offering discounts on GPU Droplets and premium support. 💡 Ex-human, a startup focused on empathetic AI, benefits from the program to enhance customer interactions through AI models. Their technology aims to create meaningful connections between humans and digital characters. 💰 With access to on-demand NVIDIA H100 GPU Droplets at $1.90/hour, Ex-human finds DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s services reliable and affordable, allowing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktoberfest 2025 Comes to a Close</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12950/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12950/</guid>
      <description>🎉 Hacktoberfest 2025 has wrapped up, marking its 12th year of bringing open-source communities together! This year&amp;rsquo;s event welcomed over 56,000 participants from 176 countries, with a new requirement of 6 pull requests to enhance engagement and impact. Participants made 87,929 contributions, showcasing the growth of the community. 🌍✨ In-person hackathons were held in seven cities, and online events supported newcomers in their open-source journey. Digital badges were awarded, including a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPU Observability: Get Deeper Insights into Your Droplets and DOKS Clusters</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12028/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 20:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12028/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New GPU observability metrics are now available for DigitalOcean GPU Droplets and DOKS clusters! These features provide real-time insights into GPU utilization, temperature, power consumption, throttle conditions, and interconnect performance. This allows users to optimize AI workloads efficiently. 🔍 No setup is required, and these metrics are included for free with AI/ML Ready images. Explore your GPU metrics in the DigitalOcean Insights UI today! #GPUObservability #DigitalOcean #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leading the Cloud With Curiosity : Spotlight on Pranav Nambiar, SVP, AI/ML &amp; PaaS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11716/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 04:01:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11716/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Pranav Nambiar, SVP of AI/ML &amp;amp; PaaS at DigitalOcean, shares his journey and vision for innovation. He joined to be closer to builders and to work in a fast-moving, humble environment. He values DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s strong fundamentals, the opportunity for impact, and its unique culture. His teams focus on generative AI and reliable PaaS solutions, helping customers innovate effectively. 🌐 DigitalOcean is recognized for its strong developer community and commitment to simplifying cloud computing&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helping Startups Build Faster with an AI Startup Ecosystem</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11439/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:59:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11439/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DigitalOcean is enhancing support for AI startups with its new AI Startup Ecosystem. This initiative combines tools, resources, and partnerships to help founders build and scale their businesses efficiently. 🤝 Collaborating with partners like Techstars, the ecosystem offers discounted infrastructure, technical support, and go-to-market resources, making it easier for startups to thrive. 🌐 If you&amp;rsquo;re an AI startup looking for support, apply today! #DigitalOcean #AIStartups #StartupEcosystem&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pros and Cons of Crowdfunding Your Startup | DigitalOcean (migrated)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11320/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 20:37:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11320/</guid>
      <description>💡 Crowdfunding is a popular way to raise capital, generating $17.2 billion annually in North America. It allows individuals and businesses to gather funds from many donors, either through donation-based or investment models. 📊 Donation-based crowdfunding helps fund projects without giving equity, while investment crowdfunding converts donors into shareholders. 🤔 Startups should consider the benefits, like market testing and centralized communication, but also the effort required and potential&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image and audio models from fal now available on DigitalOcean</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11194/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11194/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! Four new multimodal AI models from fal are now live on the DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform. These models enable seamless image and audio generation via API, simplifying the development of AI-powered applications. 📸🎵 Models available include: - &lt;strong&gt;Stable Diffusion XL fast&lt;/strong&gt; for high-res images - &lt;strong&gt;FLUX.1&lt;/strong&gt; for quick prototypes - &lt;strong&gt;Stable Audio&lt;/strong&gt; for text-to-speech conversion - &lt;strong&gt;ElevenLabs TTS&lt;/strong&gt; for multilingual audio Start using them today through the Serverless Inference&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OAuth App Based Workload Identity for Droplets</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11169/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 18:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11169/</guid>
      <description>🚀 New Series Alert: Workload Identity Federation! In our first post, we explore workload identity federation and its implementation using DigitalOcean’s OAuth API. This series includes parts on architecture, deployment, and usage with Droplets and GitHub Actions. Workload identity helps reduce secret management by using asymmetric cryptography for secure authentication. The PoC will demonstrate how to enable secretless access to databases and Spaces from Droplets. Stay tuned for more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is DigitalOcean Your Next Career Spot? A 5-Year Insider on Why It Should Be</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10574/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 04:41:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10574/</guid>
      <description>🌟 Akanksha Kapoor, a Manager at DigitalOcean, highlights her 5-year journey with the company. She emphasizes the support and opportunities for personal and professional growth. At DigitalOcean, customer needs drive innovation and product development, creating a unique, customer-first culture. 🚀 The collaborative environment encourages open communication and shared guidance among team members. Explore career opportunities with a team that values continuous learning and innovation!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing GPU Droplets accelerated by NVIDIA HGX H100 in the EU</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10554/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 20:57:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10554/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers in Europe! NVIDIA HGX H100s are now available as GPU Droplets in DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s Amsterdam data center. This means easier access to high-performance computing for training and inference workloads. 🔍 WindBorne Systems is already utilizing these GPUs for real-time forecasting, benefiting from faster training times and cost efficiency. 💻 GPU Droplets are designed for simplicity, allowing quick launches and include an Inference-Optimized Image for streamlined&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the DigitalOcean AI Ecosystem</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10470/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 20:07:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10470/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Last week at Deploy London, DigitalOcean unveiled its expanded AI Ecosystem and the new AI Partner Program. This platform aims to support startups and developers in creating next-gen AI applications. Key features include: - Access to powerful AMD and NVIDIA GPUs - Leading models from OpenAI, DeepSeek, and others - Popular AI tools like LangChain and LiteLLM DigitalOcean emphasizes collaboration as crucial for AI advancement. Stay tuned for upcoming integrations, including voice and image&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing cost-efficient storage with Network file storage, cold storage, and usage-based backups</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10363/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 08:05:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10363/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates in data storage! Starting October 20, our Network File Storage (NFS) will be available, tailored for high-performance AI workloads. This fully managed solution simplifies access and management of large datasets across multiple nodes. 🌐 Additionally, Spaces cold storage is in public preview, offering low-cost storage for infrequently accessed data. 💾 We&amp;rsquo;re also introducing usage-based backups, allowing flexible backup scheduling to meet strict recovery objectives. Learn more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing per-sec billing, new Droplet plans, BYOIP, and NAT gateway preview to reduce scaling costs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10364/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 08:03:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10364/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from DigitalOcean! Starting January 1, 2026, Droplets will transition to per-second billing, helping users save costs on short-lived workloads. This new model ensures you only pay for the compute time used, with a minimum charge of 60 seconds. Additionally, new dedicated Droplet plans are now available for seamless upgrades, and the Bring Your Own IP (BYOIP) feature enables businesses to preserve their IP reputation during migrations. Lastly, the VPC NAT gateway is in&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing DigitalOcean Organizations, a new and comprehensive account layer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10365/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10365/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DigitalOcean has launched a new account layer called Organizations, designed to streamline team management. This feature consolidates multiple teams under one account, simplifying billing and user access. Users can now enjoy unified invoicing, centralized user management, and an intuitive dashboard for better oversight. Say goodbye to fragmented accounts and hello to a more organized cloud experience! 🌐 #DigitalOcean #CloudManagement #AccountOrganization #TechUpdates #Teamwork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Storage that thinks for itself: Introducing Storage autoscaling, the newest feature for Managed Databases</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10366/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10366/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! DigitalOcean has launched Storage autoscaling for Managed Databases. This feature automatically increases your database storage when needed, preventing common issues like &amp;ldquo;disk full&amp;rdquo; errors. Key benefits include: - Improved performance and reliability - Reduced manual checks and operational tasks - Cost optimization by scaling storage as needed Access this feature across MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, and more! Get started today! 🌟 #DatabaseManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build Smarter Agents with Image Generation, Auto-Indexing, VPC Security, and new AI Tools on DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10367/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 07:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10367/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Deploy London 2025! The Gradient AI Platform has introduced new features to enhance AI application development. 🖼️ With Image Model Support, developers can now generate images using text prompts via the Serverless Inference API. This expands capabilities to include text-to-image generation. 📚 The new Knowledge Base Auto-Indexing feature keeps your agents updated by automatically syncing new documents from sources like Google Drive and Amazon S3. 🔒 Plus, VPC integration&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktoberfest 2025: How to Participate</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10194/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 07:06:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10194/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Hacktoberfest 2025 registrations are now open! Join the global celebration of open source this October. To participate, register before October 31 and contribute to projects on GitHub or GitLab with the hacktoberfest topic. Aim for at least 6 accepted pull/merge requests to earn rewards, including digital badges and a limited edition t-shirt for the first 10,000 participants. 👕 Ways to contribute include coding, maintaining projects, or even supporting with documentation and user experience&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build faster, debug smarter, and make AI safer with new DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform features</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9880/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 15:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9880/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from the DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform! This month, four new features are enhancing AI development: 1️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Knowledge Base Activity Logs&lt;/strong&gt;: Gain visibility into indexing jobs and debug issues effectively. 2️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Agent Templates&lt;/strong&gt;: Start projects quickly with pre-built templates available on GitHub. 3️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;n8n Integration&lt;/strong&gt;: Automate workflows with ease, adding AI features without coding. 4️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Enhanced Guardrails&lt;/strong&gt;: Improved security to protect AI agents from harmful&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacktoberfest 2025: Celebrate All Things Open Source!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9828/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 16:23:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9828/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Hacktoberfest 2025 is coming soon! Starting October 1, join a global celebration of open-source contributions. Register now and help support various projects by completing 6 pull requests this month. The first 10,000 contributors will receive a t-shirt and a tree planted in their name! 🌳 Get ready for fun activities, including partnering with Major League Hacking for events worldwide. Visit Hacktoberfest.com for details and mark your calendars! 🗓️ #Hacktoberfest #OpenSource #CodingCommunity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Gateway API Support for DigitalOcean Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9479/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 21:28:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9479/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for DigitalOcean Kubernetes users! The Kubernetes Gateway API is now pre-installed in all DOKS clusters at no extra cost. This new traffic management solution offers advanced routing capabilities and superior performance using Cilium’s eBPF technology. Key benefits include zero configuration, header-based routing, and seamless integration with DigitalOcean Load Balancers. The Gateway API also enhances team collaboration by separating infrastructure management from application&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharks of DigitalOcean: Archana Kamath, Senior Director, IaaS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7654/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 04:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7654/</guid>
      <description>Archana Kamath, Senior Director of IaaS at DigitalOcean, shares insights from her six years at the company. She highlights the importance of simplifying complex cloud solutions and fostering a collaborative culture focused on customer needs. DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s mission is to disrupt cloud computing, especially in AI/ML, with a customer-first approach. Archana emphasizes an iterative innovation process driven by customer feedback. Learn more about Archana&amp;rsquo;s views and DigitalOcean&amp;rsquo;s journey! 🎥&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New on DigitalOcean App Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7636/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 23:01:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7636/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from DigitalOcean App Platform! This week, the platform has integrated AI-powered coding assistants like Claude Code and VS Code MCP plugins with the new DigitalOcean MCP Server. Now, you can deploy apps, manage databases, and check billing—all from your coding environment. 💻 Ready to streamline your workflow? DigitalOcean offers tutorials to help you quickly go from code to production using just a few prompts. Explore more with the Claude Code Tutorial and GitHub repo!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Single Sign-On is Now Available, Strengthening Security and Simplifying Authentication</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7637/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 15:43:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7637/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for DigitalOcean users! Single Sign-On (SSO) is now available via Okta OpenID Connect (OIDC). SSO simplifies user access, reduces IT workload, and strengthens security. Teams can log in securely with corporate credentials, eliminating multiple passwords. Key benefits include streamlined onboarding, enhanced security, and a seamless login experience. Get started today and empower your team! #SingleSignOn #DigitalOcean #Okta #Cybersecurity #Productivity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DigitalOcean MCP Server is now available</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7176/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 02:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7176/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The new DigitalOcean MCP Server is here! This tool allows developers to manage cloud resources using natural language commands through AI tools like Cursor and Claude. It connects to 9 services, streamlining operations. 👨‍💻 With simple commands, you can deploy apps, manage databases, and optimize costs—all without extensive scripting. 🔗 Get started by following the configuration guidelines on GitHub. #DigitalOcean #CloudManagement #AI #MCP #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stop Building SaaS from Scratch: Meet the SeaNotes Starter Kit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5049/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 14:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5049/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing SeaNotes, a SaaS Starter Kit by DigitalOcean! Designed for indie hackers and developers, it offers a ready-to-use framework for building SaaS applications quickly. With built-in features like user authentication, Stripe billing, and AI integrations, you can focus on your product instead of setup. 🔗 Check it out on GitHub and start building with best practices in mind! #SaaS #DigitalOcean #SeaNotes #OpenSource #DevTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing OpenAI gpt-oss Models on the DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5050/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 16:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5050/</guid>
      <description>🚀 OpenAI has launched its first open-source GPT models (20b and 120b) on the Gradient AI Platform! These models offer flexibility for developers to create AI applications, from prototypes to production agents. Users can access them through the Serverless Inference API or the Gradient dashboard. With integrated billing and monitoring features, building AI apps is now simpler than ever. Get started today! 🔗 #OpenAI #GradientAI #AIDevelopment #TechNews #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing langchain-gradient: Seamless LangChain Integration with DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5051/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 17:37:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5051/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! We&amp;rsquo;ve launched &lt;strong&gt;langchain-gradient&lt;/strong&gt;, an open-source integration connecting LangChain to the DigitalOcean Gradient AI Platform. This innovative package simplifies the development of AI applications with tools for chaining prompts and managing data. Key features include: - Seamless integration for quick deployment. - Access to multiple AI models with GPU-accelerated performance. - Full open-source compatibility. Use cases range from chatbots to automated workflows, enhancing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build smarter AI agents: new tools now available for the DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4995/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 14:37:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4995/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates are here for the Gradient AI Platform! The new tools enable faster and easier AI app development. Key features include: - &lt;strong&gt;Unified Gradient AI Python SDK:&lt;/strong&gt; Access all major services in one place. - &lt;strong&gt;Log Stream Insights:&lt;/strong&gt; Real-time analysis improves agent performance. - &lt;strong&gt;Dropbox Data Connector:&lt;/strong&gt; Ingest knowledge directly from Dropbox. These enhancements support building production-ready AI applications efficiently. #AI #GradientAI #PythonSDK #TechUpdates #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing GPU Droplets accelerated by NVIDIA HGX H200</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4996/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4996/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for AI developers! DigitalOcean has launched NVIDIA HGX H200 GPU Droplets, offering up to 2x faster inference speeds and double the memory capacity compared to the H100. These droplets are designed for simplicity and scalability, priced at just $3.44/GPU/hr. With 141 GB of memory and HBM3e technology, they enhance performance for demanding tasks in AI and HPC. All droplets are HIPAA-eligible and SOC 2 compliant, ensuring security. Start accelerating your AI projects today!&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sharks of DigitalOcean: Darian Wilkin, Senior Manager, Solutions Engineering</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4997/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 04:29:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4997/</guid>
      <description>Meet Darian Wilkin, Senior Manager of Solutions Engineering at DigitalOcean, who has been with the company for over eight years. He has witnessed its evolution from a startup to a public company. 🌟 Darian emphasizes the importance of a supportive culture and talented team, which enhances collaboration and keeps him motivated. He plays a key role in helping customers build efficient cloud solutions. ☁️ He values the quick decision-making process at DigitalOcean, allowing ideas to turn into&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Now Live: GPT-5 on the DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4719/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 23:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4719/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news! GPT-5 is now live on the DigitalOcean Gradient™ AI Platform. Developers can access this advanced model via serverless inference APIs or the Gradient AI Platform SDK. You can also use your own OpenAI API key for integration. GPT-5 enhances reasoning and performance, making it ideal for tasks like financial planning, medical analysis, and creative content generation. Get started today! 🌟 #GPT5 #DigitalOcean #AIPlatform #Developers #OpenAI</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
