<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Heroku-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/sources/heroku-blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Heroku-Blog on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:00:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/sources/heroku-blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Faster Agents with Automatic Prompt Caching</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13436/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13436/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Heroku! Starting December 18, 2025, they will introduce automatic prompt caching for Managed Inference and Agents. This feature, enabled by default, aims to enhance response times for common workloads without any extra effort. Currently, caching focuses on system prompts and tool definitions, excluding user messages. You can disable caching for specific requests if needed. Prompt caching works by securely storing and reusing processed components, leading to faster&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleash the Power of IaC on Heroku’s Next Generation: Terraform for Fir is Here!</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12998/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 17:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12998/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! The Heroku Terraform Provider is now fully optimized for Fir, enabling Infrastructure as Code (IaC) on Heroku’s next-generation platform. Fir combines cloud-native standards with the Heroku experience, allowing for better control, consistency, and scalability. With over 9.6 million downloads, Terraform is an essential tool for managing resources efficiently. This integration simplifies Kubernetes complexities while enhancing your provisioning process. #Heroku&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incident Review: Intermittent Disruption and Degradation of Heroku Services on October 20, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12188/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 23:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12188/</guid>
      <description>On October 20, 2025, Heroku experienced significant service disruptions due to a database service outage from its cloud infrastructure provider in Virginia. The incident unfolded in two phases. Phase 1 involved database issues leading to provisioning delays and degraded performance of key Heroku services. Phase 2 saw further complications with networking issues and control plane failures, affecting customer applications and causing errors. Recovery efforts were implemented, but some users&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heroku Support for .NET 10 LTS: What Developers Need to Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12027/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 08:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12027/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for .NET developers! Heroku now supports .NET 10, released at .NET Conf 2025, along with ASP.NET Core 10, C# 14, and F# 10. This new Long Term Support (LTS) version will be supported for three years, making it a reliable choice for development and migration. With .NET 10, you can deploy file-based apps effortlessly, enabling quick setups without complex configurations. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget, .NET 8 and 9 will reach End of Support on November 10, 2026. Now is the time to plan your&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn How to Lower Heroku Dyno Latency through Persistent Connections (Keep-alive)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11715/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:27:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11715/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Learn how to enhance your Heroku app&amp;rsquo;s performance by reducing latency! The article explains the impact of TCP slow start on web applications and introduces keep-alive connections as a solution. Keep-alives allow multiple requests to reuse a single connection, improving response times by maximizing bandwidth. Understanding these concepts can significantly benefit developers working with HTTP. #Heroku #WebDevelopment #TCP #PerformanceOptimization #KeepAlive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heroku Connect: Faster, More Reliable Data Sync with Salesforce CDC</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11517/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:45:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11517/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Heroku Connect has upgraded its Accelerated Polling feature to now support Salesforce Change Data Capture (CDC). This enhancement allows for faster and more reliable data synchronization, addressing previous limitations with legacy technology. With support for over 170 new Salesforce standard objects, your critical data, such as Opportunity Line Items, can now sync more efficiently. To get started, simply enable CDC in Salesforce and select the “Uses&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heroku Introduces New Innovations to Expand the Capabilities of Every Salesforce Org</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10902/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:05:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10902/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates from Heroku at Dreamforce! Heroku introduces innovations to its AI PaaS, enhancing Salesforce orgs with improved pro-code capabilities, data foundations, and AI integration. Key highlights include enhanced security, increased scalability, and streamlined app development processes. These updates aim to simplify the complexities developers face, making it easier to build modern applications. #Heroku #Salesforce #AI #Dreamforce #AppDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing the Next Generation of Heroku Postgres – Unlocking Performance, Scale, and Zero-Friction Ops</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10903/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 15:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10903/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Heroku! The next generation of Heroku Postgres is here, introducing an Advanced tier designed for intelligent applications. This update prioritizes performance and scalability, allowing for seamless growth and handling of massive workloads. Key features include high throughput, flexible compute and storage options, and a unique follower pool architecture for better read performance. Join the pilot to experience these advancements firsthand! 🌟 #Heroku #Postgres&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Heroku Vibes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10543/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:45:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10543/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news from Heroku! Introducing the pilot of Heroku Vibes, designed to turn your ideas into running apps effortlessly. This new platform builds on the nostalgia of Heroku Garden, aiming to simplify app creation for everyone, not just developers. With AI-powered capabilities, you can now describe your app in natural language, and Heroku Vibes will handle the rest—from code generation to deployment. Say goodbye to complex setups and hello to a seamless experience! 🌐💻 #HerokuVibes&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heroku AI Studio is Your Workspace for Smarter, Faster AI Apps</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9735/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9735/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Introducing Heroku AI Studio, a new workspace designed to enhance your AI app development! This tool streamlines the process from prompt to production, allowing developers to focus on building rather than troubleshooting. Key features include real-time model interaction, efficient prompt tuning, and seamless integration into your codebase. Getting started is simple – just access your Heroku Dashboard and click “Open Playground” to begin exploring! #HerokuAI #AIDevelopment #TechTools&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Salesforce Integrations with Heroku AppLink</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9523/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9523/</guid>
      <description>Salesforce customers often use third-party services through Connected Apps and External Services. However, security risks persist in the integration landscape. 🔒 Heroku AppLink enhances security by providing a managed bridge between Salesforce and Heroku. It handles authentication, service discovery, and request validation, reducing reliance on stored credentials. This allows developers to reuse existing code and improves visibility and trust boundaries for admins and security teams. For&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Triage and Fix with Confidence: heroku run and OTel on Heroku Fir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9446/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 21:33:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9446/</guid>
      <description>🚨 When production issues arise, Heroku’s new capabilities can help. With the heroku run command, developers can launch a dedicated dyno for troubleshooting without risking the stability of live applications. This interactive session allows for real-time diagnostics and efficient problem resolution. 🛠️ Additionally, OpenTelemetry (OTel) enhancements provide valuable insights into application performance after fixes are applied. #Heroku #DevOps #Troubleshooting #OpenTelemetry #DatabaseMigration</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corrective Action Update for the Heroku June 10th Outage</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7784/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7784/</guid>
      <description>🚨 &lt;strong&gt;Heroku Outage Update&lt;/strong&gt; 🚨 On June 10, 2025, Heroku experienced a service disruption due to an unintended system update. This affected not only platform performance but also the Heroku Status site, leading to confusion among users. 🛠️ On June 15, we outlined our remediation objectives, focusing on: - Immutable infrastructure - Improved communication resilience - Faster investigation and recovery 🔧 Key actions taken include halting unattended vendor upgrades, auditing system images, and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corrective Action Update for the Heroku June 10th Outage</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7910/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7910/</guid>
      <description>🚨 &lt;strong&gt;Heroku Outage Update&lt;/strong&gt; 🚨 On June 10, 2025, Heroku faced a service disruption due to an unintended system update by a vendor. The outage also affected the Heroku Status site, leading to communication challenges. 📅 A summary of our root cause analysis was shared on June 15. Key remediation goals include enhancing infrastructure resilience, improving communication channels, and speeding up recovery processes. 🔧 &lt;strong&gt;Current Actions:&lt;/strong&gt; - Permanent halt on unattended vendor OS upgrades - Audit of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover How Heroku’s AI PaaS Delivers Real-World Results at Dreamforce</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7743/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7743/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Heroku has transformed at Dreamforce into an AI PaaS, designed to enhance the shift from experimentation to production. Key highlights include new features like AppLink, Managed Inference, and Agents, all aimed at speeding up the delivery of AI-powered applications. Discover how companies like Workday and AT&amp;amp;T; are achieving significant results with Heroku’s solutions. Explore more at Dreamforce! #Heroku #Dreamforce #AI #TechInnovation #BusinessGrowth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Discover How Heroku’s AI PaaS Delivers Real-World Results at Dreamforce</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7911/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 15:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7911/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Heroku has transformed into an AI PaaS, addressing the challenge of moving AI from experimentation to production. This evolution includes features like AppLink and Managed Inference, designed to speed up the development of AI-powered applications. Join us at Dreamforce 2025 to see how businesses like Workday and AT&amp;amp;T; leverage Heroku for impactful results! #Heroku #AI #Dreamforce #CloudComputing #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Nova Models: Now Available on Heroku</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7214/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 15:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7214/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! Amazon&amp;rsquo;s Nova models are now available on Heroku. Provisioning these advanced AI models is as easy as adding an add-on to your Heroku app. This allows businesses to access powerful, cost-effective AI with simplicity. The Nova family includes nova-pro, designed for accuracy and deep reasoning, and nova-lite, optimized for speed and high-throughput applications. Explore the capabilities of these models today! #AmazonNova #Heroku #AI #MachineLearning #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heroku AI Expands Model Offering with OpenAI’s gpt-oss-120b</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5054/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5054/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for developers! OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s new model, gpt-oss-120b, is now available on Heroku Managed Inference and Agents. This open-weight model allows for easy integration into existing applications through an OpenAI-compatible API. With its Mixture-of-Experts architecture, gpt-oss-120b is efficient and designed for a variety of text generation tasks. Early benchmarks show it performs competitively with other models. Explore the future of AI application development on Heroku! 🌟 #AI #OpenAI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Data-Aware AI Applications with Heroku AI and LlamaIndex</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5055/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5055/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Organizations aim to build AI applications that access private data, but connecting large language models (LLMs) to proprietary datasets can be challenging. Heroku Managed Inference and LlamaIndex offer a solution for creating retrieval-augmented generation (RAG) applications. LlamaIndex helps orchestrate data, while Heroku AI simplifies deployment. Use cases include financial analysis and insurance claim assessments, enhancing efficiency and accuracy in data retrieval. 📊🤖 #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Agents With Heroku AI and Pydantic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4718/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 16:33:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-08-4718/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the potential of AI with Heroku and Pydantic AI! 🚀 Developers can easily integrate advanced AI capabilities using Heroku Managed Inference and Agents. A simple click attaches powerful models like Anthropic&amp;rsquo;s Claude 4 Sonnet to your applications. Pydantic AI enhances this by providing a Python framework for building production-grade agents, ensuring a smooth development experience. 🐍 Together, they support advanced workflows through the Model Context Protocol and Agent2Agent Protocol,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AppLink Fundamentals III: Building with AppLink – Development Flow and Language Choices</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-350/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 15:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-350/</guid>
      <description>🌟 The latest article in the AppLink Fundamentals series focuses on the practical aspects of building with AppLink. It covers the development workflow, local testing, and managing changes to the OpenAPI specification. Key considerations for choosing programming languages for Salesforce extensions are also discussed. Additionally, the article highlights Agentforce integration, showcasing its ability to enhance agent capabilities beyond standard Salesforce functions. A real-world example&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
