<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security_compliance on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/categories/security_compliance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security_compliance on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:30:24 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/security_compliance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let’s Make Hardened Images the Seatbelts of Software</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13948/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:30:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13948/</guid>
      <description>🚗 No automaker charges extra for seatbelts; they are included for safety. The same should apply to hardened container images in software. They should be affordable and standard, enhancing security for all users without added costs. The article draws parallels with HTTPS and TLS, which became the norm through community efforts and default settings. Making security options easy and accessible can lead to widespread adoption. #SoftwareSecurity #HardenedImages #OpenSource #Cybersecurity #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unify IT Asset Management and Network Security in Real Time: Cisco ISE and ServiceNow Are Redefining Asset-Aware Access</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13927/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13927/</guid>
      <description>Cisco ISE and ServiceNow are enhancing asset-aware access by merging IT asset management with real-time network security. 🔒💻 In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced environments, devices frequently connect and disconnect, leading to compliance gaps and security risks. Current integrations fail to provide a complete view, often leaving IT teams manually reconciling data. ❗️ The collaboration aims to bridge these gaps, improving visibility and operational efficiency. #CyberSecurity #ITManagement #CiscoISE&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Playbooks to Gamebooks: Why Static Security Response Is Giving Attackers the Advantage</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13908/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-17-13908/</guid>
      <description>In the article &amp;ldquo;From Playbooks to Gamebooks,&amp;rdquo; the limitations of static security response systems are explored. While SOAR playbooks were once innovative, they now pose risks as attackers adapt to predictable defenses. Attackers are leveraging knowledge gained from playbooks, making it easier to bypass security measures. Key issues include context drift leading to false positives, SaaS complexities causing collateral damage, and cloud ephemerality resulting in missed threats. These challenges&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Cisco’s Integrated AI Security and Safety Framework</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13603/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:28:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13603/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco has unveiled its Integrated AI Security and Safety Framework, addressing the growing need for robust AI security measures. Despite rapid AI adoption, only 29% of companies feel prepared to defend against AI threats, according to Cisco&amp;rsquo;s 2025 AI Readiness Index. This new framework aims to provide a comprehensive approach to AI risks, integrating various insights to help organizations understand and mitigate these challenges. #AI #Cybersecurity #Cisco #AISecurity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manage credentials with Tekton and OpenShift on IBM Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13611/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 15:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-16-13611/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Securing CI/CD workflows is essential in cloud-native environments. This article discusses how to protect credentials and enforce compliance using Tekton Pipelines on Red Hat OpenShift on IBM Cloud. Key highlights include managing Kubernetes Secrets, integrating IBM Cloud Key Protect, and utilizing Tekton Chains for integrity. Effective security measures ensure secrets are injected only when needed, images are scanned, and unsafe deployments are blocked. Learn more about building a trusted&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making the Cyber Resilience Act Work for Open Source</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13588/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 22:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13588/</guid>
      <description>As the EU Cyber Resilience Act (CRA) approaches its implementation, software manufacturers are assessing its impact on security and compliance. Red Hat emphasizes its commitment to both enterprise open source solutions and cybersecurity. The company has established a comprehensive program to align with CRA requirements, ensuring secure development practices are ingrained in their processes. While the CRA raises security expectations across the industry, it may challenge smaller projects&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ZTNA and Remote Access: A Security Model for the Future of Work</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13609/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 20:25:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13609/</guid>
      <description>Remote work is now the standard, demanding secure solutions that support flexibility without friction. Traditional VPNs struggle to meet these needs, as they are slow and outdated. Enter Zero Trust Network Access (ZTNA). This model focuses on &amp;ldquo;never trust, always verify,&amp;rdquo; ensuring continuous validation of every user and device connection. Unlike VPNs, ZTNA grants access only to authorized applications, enhancing security and reducing risks. #RemoteWork #ZTNA #Cybersecurity #FutureOfWork&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How AI Is Transforming the Adoption of Secure-by-Default Mobile Frameworks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13920/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:00:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13920/</guid>
      <description>Meta is advancing mobile security with its secure-by-default frameworks. These frameworks wrap potentially unsafe OS and third-party functions, ensuring security is a priority while keeping development fast and user-friendly. AI and automation are key in scaling these frameworks across Meta’s codebase, helping to identify insecure patterns and enforce consistent security measures. Balancing security, usability, and performance is crucial in framework design to encourage developer adoption and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to reduce false positives in security scans</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13613/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 08:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-15-13613/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Running security scans on Python applications in Fedora or RHEL can lead to false positives. Scanners often flag backported, patched versions of setuptools or pip as vulnerable due to outdated version numbers. 🚀 To address this, Fedora Rawhide is now incorporating Software Bill of Materials (SBOM) information directly into Python wheels. This helps scanners identify the actual patched version, reducing false alerts. 📢 Feedback from the developer community is welcomed to refine this feature&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Automation Paradox and Why Security Teams Fear Their Own Tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13569/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 21:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-08-13569/</guid>
      <description>Security automation is facing a challenge: speed has overshadowed precision. Many security teams hesitate to deploy automated responses due to fears of unintended consequences. The article discusses the &amp;ldquo;automation paradox,&amp;rdquo; where tools that promise quick action often remain unused because of the risk of collateral damage. Unlike DevOps, which improved safety in automation, security operations still lack effective rollback plans. A proposed solution is &amp;ldquo;surgical containment,&amp;rdquo; a framework that&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>React Server Components Vulnerability Found</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-06-13525/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 15:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-06-13525/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A security vulnerability in React Server Components has been identified. Reported by Lachlan Davidson, this flaw allows unauthenticated remote code execution. The issue affects versions 19.0, 19.1.0, 19.1.1, and 19.2.0. Immediate upgrades to versions 19.0.1, 19.1.2, and 19.2.1 are necessary. If your app does not utilize a server or React Server Components, it is not impacted. #React #Security #Coding #DeveloperNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Can Deliver Deployment-Aware Risk Analysis for Kubernetes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13501/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13501/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Kubernetes platform engineers face a challenge with overwhelming alerts on security dashboards, often displaying thousands of critical vulnerabilities. Traditional risk scoring methods fall short by evaluating risks in isolation without considering the specific deployment context. Red Hat and IBM Research are addressing this by developing an AI-driven Risk Investigation Agent for more accurate, “deployment-aware” risk analysis. This innovation aims to refine risk assessments based on real-&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New deployments of vulnerable Next.js applications are now blocked by default</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13516/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13516/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important update for Next.js users! 🚨 New deployments with vulnerable versions of Next.js (CVE-2025-66478) will now be blocked by default on Vercel. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to upgrade to a patched version to ensure your application’s security. If needed, this automatic protection can be disabled by setting the environment variable DANGEROUSLY_DEPLOY_VULNERABLE_CVE_2025_66478=1. Stay safe and informed! 🔒✨ #NextJS #Vercel #CyberSecurity #WebDevelopment #Updates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources for protecting against &#39;React2Shell&#39;</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13514/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-05-13514/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New security alert! As of December 4, proof-of-concept exploits for CVE-2025-55182 are now publicly available. This vulnerability affects all Next.js apps from versions 15.0.0 to 16.0.6. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial for developers to assess their applications and implement necessary protections. Stay informed and secure! 🔒💻 #Cybersecurity #NextJS #VulnerabilityAlert #CVE2025 #DevCommunity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Segmentation Remains a Foundational Security Concept</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13423/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 13:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13423/</guid>
      <description>The 2025 Cisco Segmentation Report highlights the importance of segmentation in enterprise security. 📊 Despite 79% of respondents prioritizing it, only 33% fully implement segmentation strategies. The report emphasizes the need for both macro and micro-segmentation to safeguard modern, decentralized applications. This adaptation is crucial for enhancing resilience against cyber threats. 🔒 Stay tuned for more insights in this three-part series! #Cybersecurity #Segmentation #EnterpriseSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indirect Prompt Injection Attacks: A Lurking Risk to AI Systems</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13481/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13481/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Indirect prompt injection attacks pose a significant risk to AI systems. This subtle threat involves embedding malicious information in data sources accessed by generative AI, making it harder to detect. 🛡️ While direct prompt injection is well-known, indirect methods can hide in emails, documents, or images. These attacks can be targeted or widespread, affecting multiple systems at once. Organizations must take steps to monitor and defend against this emerging vulnerability. #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling WARP PANDA: A New Sophisticated China-Nexus Adversary</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13482/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-04-13482/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New Threat Alert: WARP PANDA 🚨 CrowdStrike has identified WARP PANDA, a sophisticated adversary linked to China, targeting VMware vCenter environments in the U.S. This group employs advanced malware like BRICKSTORM and new implants, Junction and GuestConduit, showcasing high technical skills. Their operations focus on long-term covert access, primarily for intelligence gathering aligned with China&amp;rsquo;s strategic interests. Initial access often exploits internet-facing devices, allowing lateral&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero trust for agentic systems: Managing non-human identities at scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13400/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13400/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The rise of agentic AI systems is changing how enterprises manage software. Unlike traditional AI, these systems operate autonomously and present new security challenges. 🔒 Non-human identities (NHIs) are now a significant concern, outnumbering human identities 50:1. With 97% having excessive privileges, NHI exploitation is a top cybersecurity threat. 💡 Effective security strategies must include dynamic secrets, auditing, and proper attribution mechanisms to protect against vulnerabilities&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing the Docker MCP Catalog: Commit Pinning, Agentic Auditing, and Publisher Trust Levels</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13375/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13375/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Strengthening trust in Docker MCP solutions is key as the ecosystem expands. 🔒 New enhancements include: - &lt;strong&gt;Commit Pinning&lt;/strong&gt;: Each Docker-built MCP server is linked to a specific Git commit for verifiable releases. - &lt;strong&gt;Automated, AI-Audited Updates&lt;/strong&gt;: Ensures MCP servers remain current with scalable oversight. - &lt;strong&gt;Publisher Trust Levels&lt;/strong&gt;: Clear trust indicators help developers identify verified servers. These updates enhance transparency and security for all users. #Docker #MCP&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summary of CVE-2025-55182</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13385/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13385/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A critical vulnerability, CVE-2025-55182, has been discovered in React Server Components affecting versions 19.0 to 19.2.0. This issue can lead to remote code execution through specially crafted requests. 🛡️ Projects hosted on Vercel have protections in place, but upgrading to patched versions is strongly recommended. 🔧 Users should update to React 19.0.1, 19.1.2, or 19.2.1, and Next.js versions 15.0.5 or later. #CyberSecurity #React #NextJS #Vulnerability #SoftwareUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudflare WAF proactively protects against React vulnerability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13388/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13388/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Cloudflare has implemented new protections against a critical vulnerability in React Server Components (CVE-2025-55182). All customers are automatically shielded when their traffic is routed through the Cloudflare Web Application Firewall (WAF). This includes both free and paid users. Cloudflare Workers are immune to this exploit, ensuring that React applications deployed on them remain secure. For optimal safety, users are advised to update to React 19.2.1 and the latest versions of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Netlify&#39;s response to the critical React security vulnerability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13384/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-03-13384/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A critical vulnerability (CVE-2025-55182) was identified in React&amp;rsquo;s Server Functions protocol, affecting versions 19.0 to 19.2. This issue can allow attackers to execute arbitrary code in vulnerable applications. Netlify has acted swiftly, rolling out a patch on December 3 to secure all customer sites. They have found no evidence of exploitation on their platforms. For added security, it&amp;rsquo;s advised to upgrade to the latest framework versions and enable automatic updates for Next.js users&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Policy Enforcement with Reasoning: Faster, Safer AI Applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13301/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:50:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13301/</guid>
      <description>Explore how custom policy enforcement enhances AI applications. The article discusses the integration of reasoning mechanisms that improve both speed and safety in AI systems. Key insights include the importance of tailored policies to meet specific needs and the role of reasoning in decision-making processes. Stay informed about the future of AI! 🤖🔍 #AI #PolicyEnforcement #TechInnovation #Safety #MachineLearning</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Agents &amp; AI Supply Chain with Cisco AI Defense</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13261/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 18:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13261/</guid>
      <description>The focus on AI in enterprises is shifting towards AI agents—autonomous systems capable of reasoning and executing actions. According to the Cisco AI Readiness Index 2025, 83% of companies plan to deploy AI agents. However, challenges remain, particularly regarding infrastructure, workforce planning, and security. As AI risk surfaces expand, Cisco introduced AI Defense to address these concerns. This solution offers comprehensive security for AI applications, including supply chain scanning&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guardians of the Wi-Fi: Cisco Field Manual for Securing Wireless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13219/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 16:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13219/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Enhance your enterprise Wi-Fi security with Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest field manual! The guide focuses on effective strategies like WPA3, 802.1X authentication, and AI-driven threat detection to defend against modern attacks. Cisco emphasizes a multilayered defense approach, ensuring strong mutual authentication and robust encryption. Stay ahead in securing your wireless network! 📶💻 #WiFiSecurity #Cisco #NetworkSafety #WPA3 #CyberSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Detection to Deep Dive: Splunk Attack Analyzer and Endace for GovWare 2025 Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13294/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 08:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13294/</guid>
      <description>At GovWare 2025, security teams tackled the complexities of live event protection using Splunk Attack Analyzer integrated with Endace. 🔍 This integration allowed for enhanced threat hunting by connecting security analytics with network forensics. It enabled quick identification and investigation of suspicious activities in real-time. ⚡ One notable case involved a zip file containing a malicious executable, flagged by Splunk with a high threat score. The integration with Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Secure Malware&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automate embedded systems compliance with GitLab and CodeSonar</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13223/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-02-13223/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Embedded systems development teams often face a trade-off between speed and compliance. The integration of GitLab with CodeSonar automates compliance workflows, allowing for continuous verification throughout the development lifecycle. This addresses the challenges of meeting stringent standards like ISO 26262 and DO-178C. The collaboration enhances code analysis, identifying vulnerabilities while maintaining audit trails, significantly improving development velocity and compliance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying AI at Scale Without Sacrificing Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13286/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13286/</guid>
      <description>Deploying AI securely is a complex task that involves more than just one decision. It requires a disciplined approach that focuses on three key elements: &lt;strong&gt;People&lt;/strong&gt;: Training and awareness are crucial for effective AI deployment. &lt;strong&gt;Process&lt;/strong&gt;: Establishing clear protocols helps in maintaining security. &lt;strong&gt;Practice&lt;/strong&gt;: Continuous evaluation and improvement of practices ensure ongoing protection. Understanding these interconnected elements is essential for organizations looking to scale AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Shai-Hulud Worm 2.0: Elastic&#39;s updated response to npm supply chain compromise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13200/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Elastic has responded to the updated Shai-Hulud Worm 2.0, a serious npm supply chain threat affecting many packages. Since November 24, 2025, the community has been on high alert as this variant leaks data and compromises popular projects. Elastic has implemented monitoring measures and shares prevention rules to combat this evolving threat. Stay informed and secure! 🔒 #CyberSecurity #NPM #Elastic #SupplyChainSecurity #ShaiHulud</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next.js 16: What’s New for Authentication and Authorization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13175/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-12-01-13175/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Next.js 16 introduces key updates for authentication and authorization, enhancing security for developers. The framework now features a renamed middleware file, changing from middleware.ts to proxy.ts. This change clarifies its role as a routing layer, streamlining request interception. With the new proxy.ts, developers can implement lightweight authentication checks effectively. However, complex session management and authorization should be handled closer to data. #Nextjs16&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demystifying OAuth Security: State vs. Nonce vs. PKCE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13094/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13094/</guid>
      <description>Understanding OAuth security is essential for secure authentication. This article explains the differences between key parameters: state, nonce, and PKCE. Each plays a unique role in protecting against various attacks, like CSRF and code interception. The state parameter ensures the response is legitimate, while nonce and PKCE add additional layers of security. Learn how these components work together to safeguard your applications. 🔐💻 #OAuth #Cybersecurity #WebDevelopment #Authentication #PKCE</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What you should know about Australia&#39;s new SMS Sender ID Register</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13131/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-27-13131/</guid>
      <description>Australia has introduced a new SMS Sender ID Register to enhance transparency and security in messaging. 📲 This register requires businesses to register their SMS sender IDs, helping to reduce spam and protect consumers from scams. Compliance with the new regulations is essential for companies using SMS for communication. Stay informed on these developments to ensure your messaging practices align with the new requirements. 🔒 #SMS #SenderID #Australia #Regulations #BusinessCompliance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security that strengthens the ecosystem: Docker’s upstream approach to CVE-2025-12735</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13077/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 17:06:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13077/</guid>
      <description>On November 24, 2025, Docker Hardened Images addressed CVE-2025-12735, a serious remote code execution vulnerability in the Kibana project. This issue scored 9.8 on the CVSS scale and posed risks across many applications due to its origins in the expr-eval library. Docker not only patched the vulnerability for its users but also submitted a fix to the upstream LangChain.js project. This means enhanced security for all applications relying on LangChain.js, which sees over a million weekly&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiding Prompts in Plain Sight: A New AI Security Risk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13071/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-26-13071/</guid>
      <description>🔍 AI is transforming our web interactions, but with this advancement comes new security risks. Prompt injection vulnerabilities are now a top concern, especially with the rise of AI browsers. These can occur directly through manipulated inputs or indirectly via hidden queries in external content. As AI becomes more autonomous, indirect prompt injections pose significant threats that may go unnoticed until it&amp;rsquo;s too late. 🌐🔒 #AISecurity #PromptInjection #Cybersecurity #AIBrowsers #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS WAF vs. Google Cloud Armor: A Multicloud Security Showdown</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13044/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 18:00:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13044/</guid>
      <description>In 2025, multicloud strategies are now common, with organizations utilizing AWS, Google Cloud, and Azure. This shift creates challenges for unified app security. AWS WAF and Google Cloud Armor are leading web application firewalls (WAFs) that protect against various threats, including OWASP vulnerabilities, bots, and DDoS attacks. Key differences in integration, rule customization, and automation between the two platforms can impact performance in hybrid environments. Both WAFs play a crucial&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing the software supply chain shouldn’t be hard. According to theCUBE Research, Docker makes it simple</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13042/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 14:04:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13042/</guid>
      <description>Securing software supply chains is critical in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape. 🌐 According to theCUBE Research, 95% of organizations report improved vulnerability management with Docker, while 79% find it effective for compliance. Docker integrates security into developer workflows, making it a foundational tool for modern DevSecOps. 🔒 Docker Hardened Images and real-time vulnerability analysis help reduce application vulnerabilities by 92%. Additionally, tools for AI development streamline setup&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplifying credential security on ChatGPT Atlas</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13047/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-25-13047/</guid>
      <description>AI-powered browsers are changing the way we interact online, making tasks faster and simpler. 🌐 1Password is now available on OpenAI&amp;rsquo;s ChatGPT Atlas, enhancing security and ease of use. The new onboarding process allows users to start quickly, ensuring credentials and data remain protected. 🔒 You can pin 1Password for easy access, and it seamlessly integrates with Atlas for a smooth experience. Get started today! 🚀 #1Password #ChatGPT #AISecurity #DataPrivacy #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security that moves fast: Docker’s response to Shai Hulud 2.0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 21:04:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13017/</guid>
      <description>🚨 On November 21, 2025, security researchers identified the Shai Hulud 2.0 npm supply chain attack, compromising over 25,000 GitHub repositories within 72 hours. Major organizations like Zapier and Postman were targeted. The malware&amp;rsquo;s self-propagating nature posed a serious threat, executing during npm&amp;rsquo;s preinstall phase and stealing developer credentials and cloud secrets. In response, Docker Security quickly issued DSA-2025-1124, enhancing protection through automated threat intelligence&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get better visibility for the WAF with payload logging</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12987/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12987/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your understanding of Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Web Application Firewall (WAF) with revamped payload logging! 📊 The WAF is designed to protect against layer 7 attacks, offering tools like managed rules and custom rules for tailored security. However, false positives can occur, requiring fine-tuning based on customer data. New logging improvements aim to provide clearer insights into WAF actions, reducing noise and increasing signal for better decision-making. 🛡️ #WAF #CyberSecurity #Cloudflare&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Glimpse Into Cisco Mobile Infrastructure Security Developments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12978/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-12978/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is advancing mobile infrastructure security to meet the demands of 5G networks. Their innovative architectures aim to enhance visibility and secure traffic efficiently, especially as workloads shift towards the edge. Key developments include the scalable Security Gateway and support for distributed VPN on Cisco Secure Firewalls. Cisco is also exploring new 5G use cases and enhancing encryption with Cilium CNI for Open RAN deployments. Stay tuned for more updates! 🔒📡🚀 #Cisco #5G&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security through design: Creating the improved Firewall experience</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13011/</guid>
      <description>🔒 At Vercel, we prioritize intuitive security that enhances user experience. The redesigned Vercel Firewall aims to eliminate the tradeoff between security and shipping speed. A clear and useful interface encourages teams to actively use security tools instead of leaving them in passive modes. Explore how this new UI boosts confidence in app resilience against attacks. #CyberSecurity #UserExperience #Vercel #Firewall #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shai-Hulud 2.0 Supply Chain Compromise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13014/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A recent security breach involved multiple npm packages being compromised through account takeover. A malicious actor added a stealthy loader to these packages, targeting the Bun runtime. 🔍 Vercel has confirmed that their environment remains secure and no internal systems were affected. They are resetting the cache for projects using the vulnerable packages. 📞 Affected customers are being notified with specific mitigation steps. Updates will be provided as the investigation continues&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checking it twice: How to spot a fake in your inbox and stay safe this holiday season</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13026/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13026/</guid>
      <description>This holiday season, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to be vigilant about email safety. 📧 Twilio&amp;rsquo;s latest article offers practical tips for identifying fake emails. It emphasizes checking sender addresses, looking for spelling errors, and avoiding suspicious links. 🛡️ Stay informed and protect yourself from scams this festive season! 🎄 #EmailSafety #CyberSecurity #HolidayTips #Twilio #StaySafe</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab discovers widespread npm supply chain attack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-24-13019/</guid>
      <description>🚨 GitLab&amp;rsquo;s Vulnerability Research team has uncovered a significant supply chain attack in the npm ecosystem. This campaign involves malware that spreads through infected packages, displaying worm-like behavior. The malware not only harvests credentials from various platforms but also has a destructive mechanism that can erase user data if its access channels are disrupted. 🔍 GitLab has confirmed that it is not affected but aims to help the security community combat this threat. Investigations&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Docker Hardened Images Patches Vulnerabilities in 24 hours</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12955/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 18:40:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12955/</guid>
      <description>On November 19, 2025, the Golang project announced two vulnerabilities affecting the golang.org/x/crypto/ssh package. While not critically scored, these vulnerabilities pose risks to applications using SSH in Go containers. CVE-2025-58181 allows for unbounded memory consumption, and CVE-2025-47914 affects SSH Agent servers, potentially leading to system instability. Docker Hardened Images responded promptly, patching these vulnerabilities within 24 hours through continuous monitoring and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Comprehensive Guide to Auth0 Security Against Identity Attacks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12942/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-21-12942/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Dive into our guide on enhancing Auth0 security against identity attacks! This resource highlights key areas to focus on, including misconfigurations, account fraud, MFA bypass, and token hijacking. It emphasizes the importance of proper configurations and proactive detection measures to safeguard your identity systems. Explore strategies to fortify your defenses and stay ahead of automated threats. #Auth0 #Cybersecurity #IdentityProtection #SecurityBestPractices #MFA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6 ways Terraform can help secure your infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12908/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12908/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Securing your infrastructure is essential in today&amp;rsquo;s evolving AI and hybrid-cloud landscape. Terraform offers solutions to address common challenges such as manual workflows, lack of security controls, and inconsistent policy enforcement. By leveraging Infrastructure as Code (IaC), teams can create a more efficient and secure provisioning process. Key practices include bridging skills gaps and simplifying workflows using HashiCorp Configuration Language (HCL), allowing for a more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving from Risk to Resilience: Securing Critical Infrastructure by Tackling Technical Debt</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12881/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 10:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12881/</guid>
      <description>Policymakers face urgent cybersecurity challenges as outdated technology poses significant risks to critical infrastructure. 🛠️ End-of-life (EoL) systems lack support and security updates, leading to vulnerabilities. Recent attacks highlight the dangers of relying on unsupported tech. With nearly half of global network assets being obsolete, a coordinated effort is needed to address this issue. 🔍 #Cybersecurity #TechDebt #CriticalInfrastructure #Resilience #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doubling down on resilient infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12882/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 10:00:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12882/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Global networks are under increasing threat, prompting Cisco to enhance resilient infrastructure. 🔒 The company is simplifying security by making secure defaults standard and phasing out outdated methods. This aims to help organizations better assess their risk and protect their networks. 📊 A recent report highlights that 48% of network assets are now aging or obsolete, creating technical debt that hampers modernization efforts. #Cybersecurity #ResilientInfrastructure #Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Europe’s Critical Infrastructure by Tackling Technical Debt</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12883/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 09:20:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12883/</guid>
      <description>Outdated technology in critical infrastructure poses a rising risk of cyber exploitation in Europe. Nearly half of business network assets are aging or obsolete, making it easier for cyber attackers to infiltrate systems. High-profile threats, like the Volt Typhoon campaign, highlight these vulnerabilities. The EU&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Digital Omnibus&amp;rsquo; aims to simplify cyber incident reporting and address these challenges. 🔒💻 #Cybersecurity #TechDebt #Infrastructure #EUPolicy #DigitalTransformation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating SaaS management: Extend IAM to regain time, trust, and control</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12899/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12899/</guid>
      <description>Security leaders face challenges in managing increasing SaaS apps and shadow IT. Automation is key in enhancing visibility and control. Many companies lack insight into their SaaS usage, leading to security risks. 52% of employees admit to downloading apps without IT approval. SaaS Management Platforms (SMPs) can help by automating the discovery of applications and managing licenses efficiently. Tools like Trelica by 1Password offer a comprehensive view of apps and users. Learn how automation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Research: Security Flaws in DeepSeek-Generated Code Linked to Political Triggers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12885/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-20-12885/</guid>
      <description>CrowdStrike Research has identified significant security flaws in code generated by the Chinese AI model DeepSeek-R1. Their tests revealed that prompts containing politically sensitive topics could increase the risk of vulnerabilities by up to 50%. This poses a serious concern, as many developers utilize AI coding assistants. The findings suggest a need for further analysis on how political biases in LLMs affect code quality. 🔍💻⚠️ #CyberSecurity #AI #DeepSeek #Coding #TechResearch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why I joined Docker: security at the center of the software supply chain</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12854/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 16:55:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12854/</guid>
      <description>Mark Lechner, CISO at Docker, emphasizes the need for security at the core of the software supply chain. As threats evolve, they exploit interconnected systems rather than isolated ones. He reflects on his decade-long experience in diverse sectors, highlighting the shift from controlled environments to open systems where trust must be proven. Docker’s role is crucial; with containers as the standard unit of compute, ensuring security now can reshape software development. 🔍🔐💻 #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing MCP servers with 1Password: Stop credential exposure in your agent configurations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12843/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12843/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Securing MCP servers is crucial to prevent credential leaks. A recent article highlights how to use 1Password to safeguard sensitive information in your projects. Instead of hardcoding API tokens in configuration files, developers can reference secrets stored in 1Password vaults. This method enhances security by injecting credentials at runtime, eliminating plaintext exposure. The approach is beneficial for various AI tools and is easy to implement using the 1Password CLI. For detailed&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why data sovereignty is mission-critical for global defence organisations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12840/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-19-12840/</guid>
      <description>Data sovereignty is critical for global defense organizations. It ensures control over data storage and access, protecting sensitive information and maintaining strategic autonomy. As collaboration grows, secure data exchange is essential for mission readiness. Sovereign control aligns data management with national security needs. Understanding data sovereignty enhances operational efficiency, supports intelligence, and improves decision-making. #DataSovereignty #DefenseStrategy&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Bitbucket powers compliance and code quality at scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12794/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:59:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12794/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Bitbucket Cloud enhances coding at scale by prioritizing security, compliance, and flexibility. It serves over 300,000 organizations globally, ensuring secure code access and automated change management. Key features include data encryption, IP allowlisting, and comprehensive audit logs. Bitbucket balances compliance and developer autonomy, enabling teams to enforce best practices while allowing customization in CI/CD workflows. Explore how Bitbucket is evolving for the future! #Bitbucket&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Secure Development: Faster and Safer Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12756/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 15:00:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12756/</guid>
      <description>The software development landscape is shifting as teams face a conflict between speed and safety. AI tools now allow for rapid code generation, but they also introduce new security risks. These tools can replicate insecure coding patterns and create vulnerabilities alongside faster releases. Traditional security measures struggle to keep pace, leading to backlogs and increased risk. To ensure secure development, a new approach is needed that balances speed with safety. 🔒💻⚡️ #SecureDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Identity-Driven Firewalls: Shaping the Future of Adaptive Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12760/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 13:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12760/</guid>
      <description>Identity-driven security policies are essential in combating modern cyber threats. Recent breaches highlight vulnerabilities linked to credential management, where attackers exploit trust in authentication systems. Identity is now a key attack vector, with threats targeting digital identities like users and services. Effective firewalls can adapt to these risks, enhancing organizational security. Stay informed and protect your credentials! 🔐✨ #CyberSecurity #IdentityProtection #DataBreach&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defeating BLOCKADE SPIDER: How CrowdStrike Stops Cross-Domain Attacks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12793/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-18-12793/</guid>
      <description>🚨 CrowdStrike&amp;rsquo;s OverWatch has effectively disrupted the operations of BLOCKADE SPIDER, a sophisticated eCrime adversary known for cross-domain attacks. These attacks involve navigating multiple systems to exploit vulnerabilities within organizations. BLOCKADE SPIDER, active since April 2024, employs tactics like credential dumping and ransomware deployment. In early 2025, CrowdStrike identified the adversary accessing a victim&amp;rsquo;s network via an unmanaged VPN. By leveraging cross-domain data,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automation Complacency Can Compound Vibe Coding Risks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12730/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 21:00:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12730/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Automation in coding, or &amp;ldquo;vibe coding,&amp;rdquo; is becoming common among developers. While it boosts productivity, risks are emerging due to reliance on AI-generated code. AI&amp;rsquo;s lack of transparency can introduce vulnerabilities that skilled professionals may overlook. This has been observed even in security-focused environments. 🔒 To combat this, companies are deploying honeypots to detect new exploits. A recent project involved creating a rapid-response honeypot using AI, but it revealed&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The ROI of AI-Driven Security Automation: Metrics That Matter</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12211/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12211/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming security operations by changing the metrics we use to measure effectiveness. Traditional metrics like Mean Time to Detect (MTTD) are becoming obsolete as AI can process alerts and respond faster than humans. Key metrics to focus on now include: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Coverage Within Critical Time Windows&lt;/strong&gt;: Measure how quickly you can respond to attacks compared to their execution time. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Attack Progression Prevention Rate&lt;/strong&gt;: Evaluate if AI can stop attacks at various stages, preventing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco IT’s Zero Trust Access Evolution: Securing Our Distributed Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12205/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12205/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is evolving its Zero Trust Network Access (ZTNA) to enhance security for its global workforce. 🌍🔐 With over 135,000 laptops and many mobile devices, Cisco recognizes the need for a shift from traditional VPNs to a more flexible and secure model. This approach eliminates implicit trust and improves visibility into user activities. The goal is to support productivity and innovation while ensuring robust protection for digital assets. #ZeroTrust #CyberSecurity #Cisco #DigitalTransformation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco IT’s Zero Trust Access Evolution: Securing Our Distributed Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12733/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 14:00:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12733/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is advancing its Zero Trust Network Access (ZTNA) to enhance security for its global workforce. This shift moves away from traditional VPNs, which offer broad access after authentication but lack continuous validation. Cisco’s ZTNA provides flexibility and visibility, ensuring that critical assets are protected, regardless of location. This approach supports a modern, distributed work environment. #CyberSecurity #ZeroTrust #Cisco #DigitalTransformation #RemoteWork</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To Stop AI-Powered Adversaries, Defenders Must Fight Fire with Fire</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12740/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-17-12740/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A recent report from Anthropic&amp;rsquo;s Threat Intelligence team highlights a significant shift in cybersecurity. They&amp;rsquo;ve disrupted a nation-state operation using AI for automated cyberattacks on a global scale. 🌍 The report urges defenders to adapt by leveraging AI for defense strategies, including SOC automation and threat detection. It&amp;rsquo;s a call for the cybersecurity community to innovate in response to evolving threats. 🔒 As adversaries embrace AI, defenders must also enhance their capabilities&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portmaster, an Open Source Firewall for the Desktop</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-16-12196/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 15:00:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-16-12196/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your desktop security with Portmaster, an open-source application firewall. 🔒 Portmaster offers system-wide protection, helping to block ads, trackers, and malware. It allows you to monitor network activity and customize settings for individual applications. Available for Linux and Windows, it&amp;rsquo;s a tool designed to automate security measures. For installation, simply download the appropriate file and follow the setup instructions. #CyberSecurity #OpenSource #Portmaster #Linux #Windows</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proactive Auth0 Security Posture via Real-Time Audit of Management API Logs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12169/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-14-12169/</guid>
      <description>Stay ahead of security threats with proactive monitoring of your Auth0 Management API logs. 📊 Real-time audits help detect changes to critical defenses like MFA and Attack Protection, preventing configuration drift and maintaining a strong security posture. Auth0 Logs enable this essential threat detection, complementing tools like Checkmate for ongoing security monitoring. Learn how immediate awareness of modifications can protect your identity security. 🔒 #Auth0 #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We’re Repeating Cybersecurity’s Big Mistake, This Time With AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-11974/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-11974/</guid>
      <description>Fifteen years ago, cybersecurity was often overlooked, leading to significant breaches. Today, a similar trend is emerging with AI deployment. 🚨 While 72% of developers are building AI applications, only 33% are using adversarial testing to find vulnerabilities. This gap poses serious risks as AI systems evolve unpredictably. Effective AI testing must include human perspectives to uncover critical issues that traditional methods miss. #AI #Cybersecurity #QualityAssurance #TechTrends #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPIFFE: Securing the identity of agentic AI and non-human actors</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12151/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12151/</guid>
      <description>🔒 As AI systems grow more autonomous, securing their identity is crucial. The SPIFFE framework addresses this need by providing a reliable identity system for non-human workloads. ✨ SPIFFE enables unique identities for each service, supports dynamic credentialing, and ensures trust across different environments. This is essential for agentic AI systems that operate independently. 🔗 By using SPIFFE, AI agents can securely authenticate and communicate, enhancing safety in multi-agent&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The WhatsApp Data Exfiltration Attack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12102/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12102/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Part 5 of our MCP Horror Stories series highlights a serious security threat: the WhatsApp Data Exfiltration Attack. This vulnerability allows attackers to steal entire message histories by leveraging a clever exploit within WhatsApp. It bypasses traditional security measures, making it difficult to detect. Understanding these threats is crucial for developers to enhance AI security. #CyberSecurity #AIThreats #DataProtection #WhatsApp #MCP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Vulnerability Management to Exposure Management: The Platform Era Has Arrived</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12163/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12163/</guid>
      <description>🌐 The shift from vulnerability management to exposure management is crucial as adversaries become faster and more sophisticated. 🛡️ Traditional methods can&amp;rsquo;t keep up with the rapid exploitation of vulnerabilities. A new approach is needed, focusing on visibility, intelligence, and unified platforms for effective action. 🔍 CrowdStrike emphasizes the importance of understanding real-world adversary behavior to enhance risk management and stop breaches. #Cybersecurity #ExposureManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time for the defense and intelligence community to upgrade endpoint security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12029/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12029/</guid>
      <description>🔒 It&amp;rsquo;s essential for the defense and intelligence community to enhance endpoint security. For over two decades, the US IC and DoD have relied on a legacy system but still lack a comprehensive solution for endpoint detection and response (EDR). Elastic&amp;rsquo;s endpoint security, stemming from Endgame&amp;rsquo;s acquisition, offers advanced protection across various environments, including Linux and air-gapped networks. This system integrates with Elastic&amp;rsquo;s AI-powered analytics for better security. Elastic&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password habits are worsening, but security leaders see a path to passwordless</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12078/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-13-12078/</guid>
      <description>Poorly managed passwords continue to pose significant risks for security teams. The latest findings from the 1Password Annual Report 2025 highlight that 66% of employees exhibit poor password hygiene, contributing to security challenges. However, there is a shift towards passwordless authentication, with 89% of security professionals encouraging the use of passkeys. This strategy aims to minimize user exposure to credentials and enhance security. To address these risks, IT teams are advised&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building resilient infrastructure in regulated environments: 7 Lessons from IG Group’s journey</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12096/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12096/</guid>
      <description>Building resilient infrastructure is crucial for businesses in regulated industries. IG Group&amp;rsquo;s Platform Security Team Lead, Andrew Blooman, shared insights at HashiDays 2025 on addressing this challenge. Key lessons include: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Regulatory compliance is essential&lt;/strong&gt;. DORA mandates secure coding practices and strict separation of environments, driving modernization in security architecture. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Secret sprawl poses risks&lt;/strong&gt;. Leaked secrets can lead to multimillion-dollar breaches. IG Group&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieve CMMC Level 2 with GitLab Dedicated for Government</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12035/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12035/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The U.S. Department of Defense has introduced new compliance requirements for Defense Industrial Base (DIB) companies under the CMMC Final Rule. Companies must now apply NIST 800-171 and undergo audits by Third-Party Assessment Organizations (3PAO) every three years. 💼 GitLab Dedicated for Government offers a solution with its FedRAMP Moderate Authorization. This allows DIB companies to use the platform without extra audits, easing the compliance burden. 🔍 The Shared Responsibility Matrix&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>November 2025 Patch Tuesday: One Zero-Day and Five Critical Vulnerabilities Among 63 CVEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12081/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12081/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Microsoft released its November 2025 security updates, addressing 63 vulnerabilities, including one zero-day and five critical flaws. This is a decrease from October&amp;rsquo;s 172 patches. 🖥️ Notably, this marks the first Extended Security Update (ESU) for Windows 10 after its end of life on October 14, 2025. Organizations must enroll in ESU to receive updates. 📊 Key risks this month include 29 patches for elevation of privilege and 16 for remote code execution. #Microsoft #PatchTuesday&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oracle Red Bull Racing CIO Matt Cadieux’s cyber resilience playbook</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12079/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-12-12079/</guid>
      <description>🚗 In Episode 4 of &amp;ldquo;Securing the Win,&amp;rdquo; Matt Cadieux, CIO of Oracle Red Bull Racing, discusses the importance of cyber resilience in Formula 1. 🔐 He emphasizes that speed relies on trust, with a robust digital backbone protecting against threats. Cadieux&amp;rsquo;s approach involves designing for failure and continuously verifying trust. 📊 As the team evolves, they implement layered security measures and focus on business continuity, ensuring safety and efficiency in operations. 🤝 Strategic&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Zero-Trust Infrastructure Powering Agentforce 360 Platform: Protecting 20 Trillion Transactions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12126/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:46:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12126/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Meet Meir Amiel, Salesforce&amp;rsquo;s President and Chief Infrastructure Officer, who leads the development of the Hyperforce Infrastructure. His team powers the Agentforce 360 Platform, ensuring a trusted infrastructure for Salesforce products like Data 360 and MuleSoft. This foundation supports secure operations across various regulated environments. 🔐 Discover how they have secured 20 trillion transactions annually across 17 countries through a robust zero-trust infrastructure, addressing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ingress NGINX Retirement: What You Need to Know</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12099/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12099/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for Kubernetes Users 🚨 Kubernetes SIG Network and the Security Response Committee have announced the retirement of Ingress NGINX, effective March 2026. After this date, there will be no more releases, bug fixes, or security updates. Existing deployments will remain functional, and installation artifacts will still be accessible. Users are encouraged to migrate to the Gateway API or other alternative Ingress controllers listed in the Kubernetes documentation. For further&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 strategies that reduce security friction in developer workflows</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12097/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-11-12097/</guid>
      <description>🔒 The future of security is evolving within developer workflows, prioritizing innovation and speed. Three key strategies are being adopted: 1️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Integrate Security Early&lt;/strong&gt;: Security scanning must occur earlier in the development lifecycle, providing real-time feedback within familiar tools, allowing developers to address issues immediately. 2️⃣ &lt;strong&gt;Shift from Enforcement to Enablement&lt;/strong&gt;: Security should guide developers during coding, rather than act as a barrier later in the process. This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactics to End Dark Patterns in App and Web Development</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11864/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 16:01:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11864/</guid>
      <description>Rohan Gupta from R Systems emphasizes the importance of identifying dark patterns in app and web development. His team integrates dark pattern audits into their process, attaching risk levels to deceptive practices like subscription traps and false urgency. This step ensures compliance and promotes ethical design from the start. Selam Moges from Apella introduced the CLEAR framework at a recent conference, guiding developers to avoid dark patterns through a five-step process focused on user&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Nous Research used BotID to block automated abuse at scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11912/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11912/</guid>
      <description>Nous Research recently offered their open-source language model, Hermes, for free, leading to a surge in automated abuse. 🤖 Within days, scripts created fake accounts to bypass rate limits, despite existing protections. This resulted in wasted resources and increased bills for identity verification. Moving forward, Nous plans to strengthen bot protection before offering free access again. #AI #Cybersecurity #NousResearch #BotProtection #OpenSource</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel now supports post-quantum cryptography</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11915/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11915/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Vercel enhances security with post-quantum cryptography for HTTPS connections. This update protects applications from future quantum computing threats. Current encryption methods may become vulnerable, but Vercel&amp;rsquo;s support ensures secure TLS handshakes without extra configuration or cost. Stay informed about encryption and secure deployments. #CyberSecurity #PostQuantum #Vercel #Encryption #CloudComputing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Three Laws of AI Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11930/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-07-11930/</guid>
      <description>The article discusses adapting Asimov&amp;rsquo;s Three Laws of Robotics for modern AI security. As AI agents become more autonomous, they face new security challenges, particularly regarding data control and tool access. Unlike traditional programs, AI&amp;rsquo;s non-deterministic nature makes it unpredictable, raising concerns about reliability. Key questions emerge about granting AI tools access to sensitive information and actions without clear oversight. #AISecurity #AI #Asimov #DataProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-48985: Input Validation Bypass on AI SDK</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11922/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11922/</guid>
      <description>🔒 A recent security vulnerability, CVE-2025-48985, was found in Vercel&amp;rsquo;s AI SDK. This low-severity issue allowed possible bypass of filetype whitelists during file uploads. 🔧 The flaw stemmed from improper URL-to-data mapping in the SDK&amp;rsquo;s conversion pipeline. This could lead to attackers injecting arbitrary content. 📢 Vercel has addressed the issue in versions 5.0.52 and 6.0.0-beta.* Users are encouraged to upgrade to these versions for enhanced security. #Cybersecurity #Vercel #AI #TechNews&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-52662: XSS on Nuxt DevTools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11919/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11919/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A medium-severity security vulnerability, CVE-2025-52662, has been identified in Nuxt DevTools. This vulnerability allowed for potential remote code execution through XSS, leading to authentication token theft. The issue was fixed in version 2.6.4. Users are urged to upgrade to the latest version for security. For more details, check the official release. 🔒🛠️ #Nuxt #SecurityUpdate #XSS #CVE2025 #DevTools</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why a Unified Email Security Platform is Your Best Defense</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11886/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11886/</guid>
      <description>Email security is more crucial than ever as sophisticated threats like account takeovers and business email compromise rise. 🌐💼 Organizations need a unified email security platform that combines gateway-level prevention with API-based post-delivery remediation. This approach provides essential visibility and rapid response to threats. 🔍 Cisco Secure Email Threat Defense leads the way by integrating advanced detection with standalone gateway capabilities, enhancing flexibility in defense&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trusting AI Output? Why Improper Output Handling is the New XSS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11931/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-06-11931/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Are you trusting AI output? 🚨 Improper output handling can lead to serious vulnerabilities like XSS, SQL injection, and RCE. As developers integrate AI, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to remember: never trust the outputs from Large Language Models (LLMs) without proper validation. The OWASP Top 10 highlights this issue with LLM05, emphasizing that treating LLMs as trusted components can lead to significant security risks. Stay informed and safeguard your applications! 🔒 #CyberSecurity #AI #OWASP #LLM&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlocking Modern Risk &amp; Compliance with Moody’s Risk Data Suite on the Databricks Data Intelligence Platform</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11834/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11834/</guid>
      <description>Discover how Moody&amp;rsquo;s Risk Data Suite, in collaboration with the Databricks Data Intelligence Platform, is addressing the challenges faced by financial executives. This integration assists banks in managing risk and compliance while adapting to evolving regulations and customer demands. Stay informed and navigate the complexities of modern finance with these innovative tools. #RiskManagement #FinancialServices #Compliance #Databricks #Moody&amp;rsquo;s 📊🔍💼</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Next Steps for Apps Distributed in Texas</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11843/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 16:00:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11843/</guid>
      <description>📢 Attention developers in Texas! Apple has announced new tools to help meet compliance with Texas law SB2420, effective January 1, 2026. This includes age assurance and parental consent for users under 18. Developers will need to implement the Declared Age Range and Significant Change APIs to manage age verification and consent requirements. Sandbox testing is available to ensure smooth integration. Stay informed for updates on future legal obligations in other states! #AppDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>To write secure code, be less gullible than your AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11682/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 08:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11682/</guid>
      <description>Exploring AI in coding, Greg Foster, CTO of Graphite, highlights the importance of not fully trusting AI-generated code. 💻 He emphasizes the need for proper tooling to enhance code security and the significance of human readability in AI-generated code. 🛠️ Graphite aims to provide context on code changes and improve PR processes. Stay informed about the evolving landscape of coding! 🔍 #AICoding #CodeSecurity #Graphite #SoftwareDevelopment #TechTalk</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Handling Third-Party Access Tokens Securely in AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11708/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11708/</guid>
      <description>🔐 AI Agents are revolutionizing how we manage tasks by interacting with services like Google and GitHub. However, this opens up new security challenges. Developers must implement secure-by-design strategies to protect sensitive data and manage third-party access tokens effectively. This involves ensuring proper user authentication and securely storing access tokens. Maintaining high security while providing easy integration is essential. #AISecurity #DataProtection #TokenManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrate from pipeline variables to pipeline inputs for better security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11831/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-04-11831/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitLab is enhancing CI/CD security by migrating from pipeline variables to pipeline inputs. Pipeline variables can be overridden without validation, posing security risks. In contrast, pipeline inputs offer explicit declarations, type safety, and built-in validation, improving overall maintainability and governance. To transition, restrict pipeline variables and configure roles effectively. This ensures a more secure CI/CD environment. Learn more about the migration process and its&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Code Execution Drives Key Risks in Agentic AI Systems</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11664/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 17:54:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-11-03-11664/</guid>
      <description>AI-driven applications are shifting from passive tools to agentic systems capable of generating code and making decisions. This evolution presents significant security risks, especially concerning code execution. Strict controls are necessary to prevent malicious actors from exploiting AI-generated code. Traditional defenses, like sanitization, may not be sufficient as attackers can craft inputs to bypass these measures. The NVIDIA AI red team highlights the importance of treating LLM-&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotID Deep Analysis catches a sophisticated bot network in real-time</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11556/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11556/</guid>
      <description>🚨 On October 29, BotID Deep Analysis identified a significant increase in traffic—500% above normal levels—on a customer&amp;rsquo;s project. 📈 This surge appeared to originate from legitimate human users, raising concerns about disguised bot activity. Our team promptly engaged with the customer to address the issue. Remarkably, before discussions concluded, Deep Analysis utilized Kasada’s machine learning to identify and adapt to the threat. #BotID #CyberSecurity #MachineLearning #ThreatDetection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Doesn’t Have to Hurt</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11536/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11536/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Security teams and employees often find themselves at odds over the tools needed to get work done. Tools like AI for documentation can be blocked, causing frustration for everyone involved. 💻 Shadow IT emerges as a solution, but it creates tension between innovation and security compliance. Employees seek flexibility, while security teams strive to maintain oversight. 🤝 There’s a call for collaboration to shift security focus towards compromise and efficiency, allowing for better tool&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8 Log Detections for Credential Stuffing and MFA Exploit Prevention</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11547/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11547/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your security with eight crucial log detections for credential stuffing and MFA exploit prevention from Auth0. These detections are part of the Auth0 Detection Catalog, offering real-time insights and customizable monitoring for your SIEM. Key features include tracking abnormal login patterns and identifying sophisticated bot activity. Stay ahead of potential threats and protect your systems! 🔒🛡️ #CyberSecurity #Auth0 #CredentialStuffing #MFA #SecurityMonitoring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elevating public sector cyber defense with AI-powered threat hunting</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11543/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-31-11543/</guid>
      <description>Public sector organizations face increasing cyber threats, with 38% reporting insufficient resilience. To combat this, proactive threat hunting is essential. Elastic Security provides tools that enhance threat detection and investigation, helping agencies safeguard sensitive data effectively. Explore how AI-powered features can transform public sector cyber defense. 🔍💻 #CyberSecurity #PublicSector #AI #ThreatHunting #ElasticSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make your Atlassian account safer (and easier to use!) with two-step verification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11512/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11512/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Have you noticed an increase in email one-time passcodes (OTPs) when logging into your Atlassian account? This is part of Atlassian&amp;rsquo;s enhanced security measures to protect your account. Two-step verification (2SV) offers a more efficient way to secure your login. With 2SV, you’ll use your password along with a second factor, like your phone, making it significantly harder for unauthorized access. 📱 Setting up 2SV takes just a few minutes and reduces the need for email codes, allowing for a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SafeChat: DoorDash’s AI-powered safety feature</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11510/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:43:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11510/</guid>
      <description>🚀 DoorDash introduces SafeChat, an AI-driven feature aimed at enhancing safety for users. The system moderates millions of messages daily, identifying and managing inappropriate content between Dashers and customers. SafeChat employs a three-layered AI approach to ensure effective content moderation, allowing immediate actions when necessary. Learn more about how DoorDash is prioritizing safety on its platform! 🔒📱 #DoorDash #AI #SafetyFirst #TechInnovation #SafeChat</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anonymous credentials: rate-limiting bots and agents without compromising privacy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11502/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11502/</guid>
      <description>As AI agents transform online interactions, they pose new security challenges. 🌐 Anonymous Credentials (AC) can help manage agent traffic while preserving user privacy. This approach allows website operators to implement security measures without tracking users. 🔒 Currently under development at IETF, these credentials aim to strike a balance between security and privacy in the evolving AI landscape. Stay informed on this crucial advancement! 📈 #Privacy #CyberSecurity #AI #TechNews&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Raising the Bar on ML Model Deployment Safety</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11505/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11505/</guid>
      <description>At Uber, a new approach to ML model deployment has been developed to enhance safety without delaying teams. The article details how guardrails have been implemented to identify issues early, reducing the need for rollbacks and improving reliability across their ML ecosystem. This initiative sets measurable safety standards for the deployment process. 🚀🔒 #MachineLearning #ModelDeployment #TechInnovation #Uber #SafetyStandards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toward provably private insights into AI use</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11514/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 10:56:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11514/</guid>
      <description>Unlocking the potential of generative AI while ensuring user privacy is crucial. A new system called Provably Private Insights (PPI) uses federated analytics to analyze on-device generative AI data without exposing personal information. It combines large language models and differential privacy to provide insights into user interactions. This approach is already being implemented in Google’s Recorder app, allowing developers to improve AI tools while maintaining transparency in data handling&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Identity Security taxonomy for Agentic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11494/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11494/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Understanding Agentic AI is crucial for identity security. This new AI paradigm allows agents to interact dynamically with tools, blending application and user roles. The article outlines a taxonomy to help determine specific security measures based on three categories: 1. Type of AI agent (Browser vs. Programmatic) 2. Where the agent is running (Endpoint vs. Remote) 3. Who the agent serves (Employee, Internal Company, or External Customer) 1Password emphasizes that these classifications&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 for Scaling Apps: Advanced Security and Authentication</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11496/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11496/</guid>
      <description>Is your app outgrowing its authentication setup? 🚀 Auth0 identifies three key signs that indicate it&amp;rsquo;s time for an upgrade. 1️⃣ Stronger security is needed as your user base grows. Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) can enhance security without sacrificing user experience. 2️⃣ If you&amp;rsquo;re creating workarounds for user groups, consider Auth0 Organizations for a streamlined solution. Explore how Auth0 can help scale your app effectively. 🔐 #Auth0 #AppDevelopment #UserSecurity #Authentication&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The enterprise AI crisis: Unsanctioned tools and unenforced policies</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11495/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-30-11495/</guid>
      <description>The 1Password Annual Report 2025 highlights a growing &amp;ldquo;Access-Trust Gap&amp;rdquo; in organizations due to unsanctioned AI tools, patchy access controls, and unmanaged devices. 🔍 Key findings show that while 73% of employees are encouraged to use AI, 37% do not follow company policies. This gap poses risks to compliance and security. 📊 Companies need to establish clear AI governance, maintain an inventory of tools, and educate employees on safe practices. 1Password offers solutions like Trelica for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Good Software Supply Chain Security Looks Like</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11452/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11452/</guid>
      <description>Organizations using open source software are increasingly facing complex security and compliance challenges. A recent report highlights a 156% rise in malicious packages in 2024. To enhance software supply chain security, teams must focus on reducing vulnerabilities and removing unnecessary code from container images. Distroless images can help by minimizing attack points, making applications safer. #SoftwareSecurity #OpenSource #CyberSecurity #DevOps #SupplyChain</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadow AI: The Growing Risk IT Leaders Must Address</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11436/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 14:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11436/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The rise of Shadow AI presents new challenges for IT leaders. As employees increasingly use third-party AI tools without approval, risks to cybersecurity grow. IT departments strive to balance providing innovative solutions while maintaining security. To learn more about managing these risks, check out Anaconda&amp;rsquo;s 2025 &amp;ldquo;State of Data Science and AI Report.&amp;rdquo; 📈 #ShadowAI #Cybersecurity #DataScience #ITLeadership #AITrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending QUIC from acknowledgement-based DDoS attacks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11450/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11450/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Cloudflare has addressed two DDoS vulnerabilities in its QUIC implementation, identified as CVE-2025-4820 and CVE-2025-4821. These issues related to packet acknowledgements were reported through the Public Bug Bounty program. 🔧 The vulnerabilities allowed potential exploitation through the &amp;ldquo;Optimistic ACK&amp;rdquo; attack, which could unfairly increase connection send rates. Cloudflare has successfully patched these issues, ensuring no customers were impacted. 🌐 QUIC&amp;rsquo;s reliance on acknowledgements&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel achieves TISAX AL2</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11459/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11459/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has achieved TISAX Assessment Level 2 (AL2), a key security standard in the automotive and manufacturing sectors. This certification evaluates information security and cloud service usage in supply chains. Customers can access Vercel’s TISAX results via the ENX portal. For more details, check out our blog post! #Vercel #TISAX #InformationSecurity #CloudServices #AutomotiveCompliance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vercel achieves TISAX AL2 compliance to serve automotive partners</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11458/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11458/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Vercel has achieved TISAX Level 2 (AL2) compliance, enhancing its ability to serve automotive partners. This milestone highlights Vercel&amp;rsquo;s focus on providing secure and reliable infrastructure, especially for industries with strict security needs. This achievement complements existing certifications such as ISO/IEC 27001:2022 and SOC 2 Type II. #Vercel #TISAX #CyberSecurity #Compliance #Automotive</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Helping protect the 2025 Moldova elections</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11434/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11434/</guid>
      <description>On September 28, 2025, Moldova held a pivotal parliamentary election amid concerns of foreign interference. 🌍 Cloudflare defended the Central Election Commission against a 12-hour DDoS attack, blocking over 898 million malicious requests. This ensured citizens could access critical election information without disruption. 🔒 The election was crucial for Moldova&amp;rsquo;s geopolitical stance, highlighting the need for secure democratic processes. #MoldovaElections #CyberSecurity #Democracy #Cloudflare&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cyber resilience for all: How Cisco and NIIT Foundation are securing India’s digital future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11391/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 08:00:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11391/</guid>
      <description>🚀 As India embraces digital transformation, Cisco and NIIT Foundation are addressing cybersecurity challenges with their Cyber Suraksha initiative. Their goal is to train over one million individuals in cybersecurity, aiming to build a safer digital landscape. The program includes three key courses: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Cyber Awareness&lt;/strong&gt; for youth. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Cyber Smart&lt;/strong&gt; for college students. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Cyber Workforce&lt;/strong&gt; focused on employability. This partnership highlights the importance of equipping citizens with&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Speed and security: Mark Hazelton on protecting Oracle Red Bull Racing’s most valuable asset – its data</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11445/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-29-11445/</guid>
      <description>In Episode 2 of &amp;ldquo;Securing the Win,&amp;rdquo; Mark Hazelton, CSO of Oracle Red Bull Racing, discusses the impact of a $100 million data breach on Formula 1® security practices. He highlights the shift from insider threats to digital risks and emphasizes the importance of a zero trust approach. With operations spanning multiple sites, the team generates vast data, making cybersecurity a performance necessity. Hazelton underscores that effective security is essential for speed and success. Learn more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keeping the Internet fast and secure: introducing Merkle Tree Certificates</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11347/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11347/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Cloudflare is partnering with Chrome to test Merkle Tree Certificates (MTCs), aiming to enhance Internet security against quantum threats. 🔒 With the rise of quantum computing, the need for Post-Quantum (PQ) cryptography is urgent. Currently, about 50% of Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s network traffic is protected against future decryption threats. 📈 The challenge lies in the size of new PQ algorithms, which can significantly impact performance. Cloudflare aims to redesign the Web Public-Key Infrastructure&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>State of the post-quantum Internet in 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11346/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11346/</guid>
      <description>🚀 In October 2025, Cloudflare achieved a significant milestone: over half of human-initiated traffic is now protected by post-quantum encryption. This development counters the harvest-now/decrypt-later threat. 🔍 The article discusses the ongoing migration to post-quantum cryptography, highlighting advancements like NIST standards and new cryptographic proposals. 🖥️ Quantum computers pose risks to traditional encryption methods like RSA, prompting the shift to more secure options. While&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incident Report: October 28th, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11483/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11483/</guid>
      <description>We faced an outage on October 28th, 2025, affecting our backend API. This disruption impacted several services, including dashboard access, CLI operations, GitHub deployment processing, and overall API functionality. We are actively working to resolve these issues. Stay tuned for updates! 🔧💻⚙️ #IncidentReport #TechUpdate #APIOutage #ServiceDisruption #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October 2025 Fraud Update: How ISVs can Prepare for the Holiday Season</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11475/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11475/</guid>
      <description>As the holiday season approaches, ISVs need to focus on account security. The October 2025 Fraud Update highlights rising trends in AIT and webform abuse. It outlines essential steps ISVs can take to protect their platforms and respond to potential threats effectively. Stay informed and prepare to safeguard your business! 🔒🎄 #FraudPrevention #CyberSecurity #ISVs #HolidaySeason #AIT</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stopping USB-borne attacks at the endpoint with Elastic Security Device Control</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11360/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11360/</guid>
      <description>🔒 In the latest update, Elastic Security introduces Device Control, a feature aimed at enhancing endpoint security. This tool allows organizations to manage which USB devices can connect to their systems, helping prevent data loss and malware attacks without disrupting productivity. Device Control addresses critical security gaps, ensuring a robust defense against both internal and external threats. Learn more about how this can protect your organization. #CyberSecurity #EndpointProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stopping USB-borne attacks at the endpoint with Elastic Security Device Control</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11397/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11397/</guid>
      <description>🔒 In the latest update, Elastic Security introduces Device Control, a feature aimed at enhancing endpoint security. This tool allows organizations to manage which USB storage devices can connect to their systems, preventing data loss and malware access. Device Control focuses on intelligent device management rather than outright blocking access, ensuring productivity remains intact. With this addition, businesses can better protect against overlooked security gaps that traditional measures&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voice Cloning with Consent</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11364/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-28-11364/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting advancements in voice technology are here! A recent blog post discusses the concept of a &amp;lsquo;voice consent gate&amp;rsquo; aimed at promoting ethical voice cloning. This initiative seeks to ensure that voice cloning is performed with consent, helping to mitigate risks associated with misuse, like deepfakes. The article highlights both the advantages and concerns of voice generation, noting its potential to assist those who have lost their ability to speak and support language learning. For more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 reasons to upgrade your secret scanner</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11316/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11316/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Open source secret scanners are a good start for security, but as environments grow, commercial tools offer enhanced capabilities. They provide end-to-end visibility, continuous coverage, and integrated remediation guidance, addressing limitations of basic tools. This helps teams effectively manage secrets while reducing false positives and ensuring real-time protection. 🛡️💡 #CyberSecurity #DevOps #SecretManagement #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find Sensitive Data at Scale with Data Classification in Unity Catalog</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11322/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11322/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the power of data classification with Unity Catalog! This tool helps organizations automatically detect, tag, and track personally identifiable information (PII) across their data environments. By utilizing AI agents, it eliminates the need for manual tagging and scripts. Stay compliant and secure your sensitive data efficiently! 📊🔍 #DataSecurity #UnityCatalog #AI #DataManagement #SensitiveData</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Perimeter to SOC: How Integrating Cisco Firewalls with Splunk Delivers End-to-End Threat Visibility and Compliance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11290/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11290/</guid>
      <description>Organizations face increasing cyber threats and compliance demands. Traditional perimeter defenses are inadequate against modern attacks. 🔒 Integrating Cisco Firewalls with Splunk enhances security operations center (SOC) visibility, enabling better threat detection and compliance readiness. This integration helps manage the vast amounts of log data generated daily, reducing noise and improving alert prioritization. 📊 By connecting telemetry and threat analytics, teams can gain actionable&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI can do what now?! Accelerating SIEM migration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11321/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11321/</guid>
      <description>🚀 SIEM migration can be a challenging process for security teams, often requiring manual work that distracts from active defense. In a recent discussion, Haran Kumar from Elastic highlighted how AI, particularly large language models, can streamline this process. By automating the transfer of detection rules, teams can move from legacy systems in minutes instead of months. This advancement helps improve efficiency and reduces errors during migration. #SIEM #CyberSecurity #AI #Automation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI can do what now?! Accelerating SIEM migration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11398/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11398/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Migrating SIEM systems can be a challenging task for security teams, often requiring extensive manual effort. In the latest episode of &amp;ldquo;AI can do what now?!&amp;rdquo;, Haran Kumar from Elastic explains how AI is transforming this process. Using large language models and the RAG framework, AI can automate the migration of detection rules in just minutes. This advancement allows teams to focus more on security rather than getting bogged down in tedious migrations. #SIEM #AI #CyberSecurity #Automation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulatory &amp; Compliance Corner – October 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11390/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11390/</guid>
      <description>🌍 The latest edition of the Regulatory &amp;amp; Compliance Corner highlights key telecom policy changes globally. 📜 It provides an overview of new regulations impacting the industry, ensuring companies stay informed and compliant. Stay updated on how these changes could affect your operations. #Telecom #Regulations #Compliance #IndustryInsights #PolicyChanges</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing AI Agents: Mitigate Excessive Agency with Zero Trust Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11314/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-27-11314/</guid>
      <description>🚀 AI agents are reshaping application development, offering powerful capabilities in task management. However, security risks like Excessive Agency pose significant challenges. Excessive Agency occurs when AI systems are given too many permissions, leading to unintended actions. This vulnerability is on the OWASP Top 10 list for LLMs and can lead to severe consequences in sensitive environments. To mitigate these risks, adopting a Zero Trust security model is crucial. This approach ensures AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Cloudflare’s client-side security made the npm supply chain attack a non-event</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11271/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:10:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11271/</guid>
      <description>In September 2025, a phishing attack compromised 18 popular npm packages, risking over 2 billion weekly downloads. This breach allowed hackers to steal crypto assets and modify other packages. Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s Page Shield, utilizing a graph-based machine learning model, detected these threats in real-time, analyzing 3.5 billion scripts daily. This proactive approach prevents future attacks by identifying malicious code patterns effectively. Stay informed and secure your applications! 🔒💻&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How TARmageddon Compromises Rust Security: A Developer’s Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11260/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11260/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A new Rust vulnerability, TARmageddon (CVE-2025-62518), has been identified by Edera, affecting the tokio-tar library. This flaw may lead to remote code execution (RCE) in several software programs, including popular tools like Astral’s uv and wasmCloud. With a CVSS score of 8.1, it&amp;rsquo;s classified as high severity. The issue arises from a desynchronization bug in TAR parsing that allows attackers to manipulate nested TAR archives. Developers are advised to be cautious, as this highlights&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing agentic commerce: helping AI Agents transact with Visa and Mastercard</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11258/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11258/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare is partnering with Visa and Mastercard to enhance security in agentic commerce. 🤝 As AI agents increasingly handle transactions, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial for merchants to differentiate between legitimate agents and malicious bots. The Trusted Agent Protocol and Agent Pay are key developments aimed at addressing these security challenges. These protocols use Web Bot Auth for authenticating agent traffic, ensuring safe and reliable interactions during both product browsing and payment processes&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing the Vibe: Reducing the Risk of AI-Generated Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11253/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11253/</guid>
      <description>Vibe coding empowers developers to quickly turn ideas into applications. However, this speed can compromise security. AI-generated code often has vulnerabilities that require human review before deployment. To tackle security risks, organizations should apply threat models like STRIDE and utilize checklists like OWASP Top 10 for LLM Applications. By doing so, developers can harness the benefits of AI while maintaining security. ⚙️💻🔍 #AICoding #Cybersecurity #VibeCoding #SoftwareDevelopment #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSE That Thinks in Identity and Adapts Access</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11248/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-24-11248/</guid>
      <description>Cisco Secure Access is redefining security by prioritizing identity in a dynamic environment. 🌐 Traditional security methods focused on IP addresses are outdated. Cisco emphasizes that identity is now the new perimeter. Their approach adapts access decisions based on real-time identity data and behavior, enhancing security. 🔒 Static views of identity can leave organizations vulnerable. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s integration with Identity Intelligence allows for dynamic policies, ensuring continuous risk&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Kubernetes Security Is Critical for GenAI Integrity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11224/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 21:00:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11224/</guid>
      <description>As generative AI adoption grows, Kubernetes is becoming essential for managing these workloads. However, this shift brings significant security challenges. 🔒 A recent CNCF report indicates that 76% of organizations see security as their top concern, with unauthorized access and misconfigurations posing major risks. These vulnerabilities can lead to data leaks and intellectual property theft. Kubernetes&amp;rsquo; dynamic nature complicates security, making it hard to maintain visibility and control&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing the AI agent supply chain with Cisco’s open-source MCP Scanner</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11206/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 17:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11206/</guid>
      <description>🚀 As enterprises adopt AI agents, reliance on external tools grows. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Model Context Protocol (MCP) simplifies access to these tools but also introduces new security risks. 🔍 To address this, Cisco has launched MCP Scanner, an open-source tool aimed at securing the AI agent supply chain. This tool is part of Cisco AI Defense, which focuses on enhancing security across AI systems. 🔒 With MCP&amp;rsquo;s growing popularity, it&amp;rsquo;s essential for companies to be aware of potential vulnerabilities,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 questions to ask your cloud security team</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11220/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11220/</guid>
      <description>Navigating security in multi-cloud and hybrid environments presents unique challenges for organizations. 🌩️ To enhance compliance and risk management, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to ask the right questions. Key points include: 1️⃣ How are security vulnerabilities proactively addressed? 2️⃣ Are cloud environments built to meet security standards? 3️⃣ How consistent are security policies across providers? These questions can guide teams in strengthening their security posture and avoiding costly breaches. 🔒&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Architectural Convergence of Hybrid Mesh Firewall and Universal Zero Trust</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11193/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 15:00:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11193/</guid>
      <description>🌐 The evolution of campus networks has led to increased vulnerabilities. Cisco addresses this with the Hybrid Mesh Firewall and Universal Zero Trust Access. 🔒 These solutions embed security into the network, reducing attack surfaces and protecting against advanced threats. Key features include: - Baseline controls for foundational protections - Access controls for microsegmentation - Business-aligned controls for operational needs Explore how these advancements enhance security in complex&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling Privacy Infrastructure for GenAI Product Innovation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11236/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-23-11236/</guid>
      <description>Meta is enhancing product innovation through its Privacy Aware Infrastructure (PAI) to ensure responsible use of GenAI. The focus is on AI glasses as a key example of how GenAI enables new features while prioritizing user trust and data protection. Key challenges include managing explosive data growth, adapting to shifting privacy requirements, and supporting rapid innovation cycles. Explore how Meta balances innovation with privacy! 🔍✨ #Meta #GenAI #Privacy #Innovation #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Domain User to SYSTEM: Analyzing the NTLM LDAP Authentication Bypass Vulnerability (CVE-2025-54918)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11161/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11161/</guid>
      <description>A critical vulnerability, CVE-2025-54918, was identified in September 2025, impacting Domain Controllers using LDAP or LDAPS services. This flaw allows attackers to escalate privileges from standard domain users to SYSTEM level, threatening entire Active Directory environments. The vulnerability exploits NTLM relay and coerced authentication techniques. Organizations can enhance their security using CrowdStrike solutions to mitigate risks. 🔒⚠️ #Cybersecurity #Vulnerability #ActiveDirectory&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugging Face and VirusTotal collaborate to strengthen AI security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11186/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-22-11186/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news in AI security! Hugging Face has teamed up with VirusTotal to enhance the safety of files on the Hugging Face Hub. 🔍 This partnership ensures that over 2.2 million public model and dataset repositories are continuously scanned for potential threats, protecting the machine learning community. 🛡️ AI models can carry risks, from disguised malicious files to compromised assets. With VirusTotal’s trusted malware intelligence, users gain an additional layer of security. #AISecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamic AI Security: How Cisco AI Defense Protects Against New Threats</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11129/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 22:03:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11129/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The evolution of AI is remarkable, but it brings new security challenges. Cisco AI Defense addresses the risks by offering a multi-layered approach to protect businesses. With 84% of companies facing AI-related security incidents last year, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to adapt to this dynamic threat landscape. Their framework includes threat intelligence operations, unified data correlation, and a release platform for timely protections. #AISecurity #CiscoAI #Cybersecurity #TechInnovation #BusinessSafety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unleash(ed) AI: The Rise of Cognitive Security Operations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11117/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 15:23:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11117/</guid>
      <description>Cognitive Security is transforming cyber defense, moving organizations from reactive to proactive measures. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s experts discuss the increasing sophistication of AI-driven threats and the need for innovative solutions. They emphasize that traditional security tools are no longer enough to protect against these evolving risks. Learn more about how Cisco is shaping the future of cybersecurity. 🔐💻 #CyberSecurity #CognitiveSecurity #AI #Cisco #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Investments, Stronger Grids: Elevating Rural Electric Cooperative Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11103/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 13:51:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11103/</guid>
      <description>Rural electric cooperatives are essential to America&amp;rsquo;s power grid, providing energy to millions. 🌍 With the rise of cyber threats, a federal investment of $20 million is aimed at enhancing their security through advanced technologies. These funds will help co-ops modernize operations and improve cyber resilience. ⚡️ Key focus areas include enhanced monitoring, network control, and secure remote access. This initiative allows cooperatives the flexibility to choose solutions that fit their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ransomware Reality: Business Confidence Is High, Preparedness Is Low</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11109/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-21-11109/</guid>
      <description>The latest CrowdStrike State of Ransomware Survey reveals a concerning gap in business preparedness. While 50% of security leaders feel “very well prepared,” 78% faced ransomware attacks last year. Only 22% recovered within 24 hours, highlighting a false sense of security. As adversaries leverage AI for faster attacks, organizations must innovate their defenses. 89% see AI-powered protection as key to improving security. #Ransomware #CyberSecurity #AI #BusinessPreparedness #DataProtection 🛡️🔒💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Machine Speed Needs Machine Trust</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11063/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 15:00:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-20-11063/</guid>
      <description>AI is changing IT operations by enabling faster problem resolution with new paradigms like AgenticOps. 🌐 However, as AI acts quicker than humans can verify, ensuring trust in these decisions is crucial. Assurance mechanisms must validate AI actions in real time to prevent unintended consequences. ⚙️ Learn more about balancing speed and trust in AI systems in our latest e-book. 📘 #MachineTrust #AI #ITOperations #Assurance #Automation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Solutions to secret sprawl: A 4-part framework</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11028/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11028/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Secret sprawl can increase vulnerability to data breaches for organizations. A new article outlines a 4-part framework to enhance secrets management. 🔑 Key strategies include: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Centralized secrets management&lt;/strong&gt; to store and protect all secrets. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Cross-platform synchronization&lt;/strong&gt; for unified management. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Secret scanning&lt;/strong&gt; to detect leaks across infrastructure. 4. &lt;strong&gt;Access controls and encryption&lt;/strong&gt; to safeguard secrets. Adopting these practices can help organizations manage their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Falcon Exposure Management’s ExPRT.AI Predicts What Attackers Will Exploit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11049/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-17-11049/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Nearly 40,000 vulnerabilities were disclosed in 2024, leaving security teams overwhelmed. ExPRT.AI, part of CrowdStrike Falcon® Exposure Management, helps prioritize vulnerabilities based on real-time attack behavior, not just static severity scores. This predictive tool uses live adversary signals to identify which vulnerabilities are most likely to be exploited. By leveraging AI and extensive threat intelligence, ExPRT.AI enables faster remediation of critical vulnerabilities&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improving the trustworthiness of Javascript on the Web</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10990/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10990/</guid>
      <description>🔐 The web&amp;rsquo;s power comes with challenges, especially in client-side cryptography. Current JavaScript practices make cryptography hard to trust, as sites can change code without auditability. A new specification, WAICT, aims to enhance web security by ensuring integrity, consistency, and transparency for web applications. This effort involves collaboration among browser vendors, cloud providers, and developers to protect various uses of in-browser cryptography. #WebSecurity #JavaScript&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing a New Framework for Securing AI-Generated Code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10986/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-10986/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Software teams are increasingly using AI coding agents to enhance productivity, but security is lagging behind. Many AI-generated codes lack essential protections, which leads to vulnerabilities. To address this, Cisco has introduced Project CodeGuard, an open-source framework aimed at securing AI-generated code. Project CodeGuard integrates secure defaults into coding workflows, offering community-driven rules, translators for popular AI agents, and automatic security validators. This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Defends Against Git Vulnerability CVE-2025-48384</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11021/</guid>
      <description>🚨 CrowdStrike has reported active exploitation of Git vulnerability CVE-2025-48384. This vulnerability affects macOS and Linux systems and can lead to arbitrary code execution via malicious Git repository cloning. 🛡️ The threat actors utilize social engineering tactics to compromise unpatched Git installations. Organizations are advised to prioritize timely software updates and enhance their security strategies. 🔒 Stay vigilant and protect your systems! #Cybersecurity #GitVulnerability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incident Report: October 16th, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-16-11020/</guid>
      <description>📢 We encountered an outage on October 16th, 2025, impacting our Edge Network connectivity. Some users faced brief interruptions when accessing services through public endpoints. We are actively working to resolve these issues and appreciate your patience during this time. Stay informed! 🌐🔧 #NetworkUpdate #ServiceStatus #TechNews</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Modern APIs Roundtable: How AI Creates New Challenges for API Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10950/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10950/</guid>
      <description>APIs are essential for internet functionality, connecting applications and services. With AI&amp;rsquo;s rise, they face new challenges in security and management. During a recent roundtable, industry leaders discussed the need for better API discovery and visibility, highlighting gaps that can lead to security risks. Proactive security practices and continuous monitoring were emphasized to ensure safer API environments. Documentation accuracy and standardization also emerged as key concerns. AI-&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Hardened Images: crafted by humans, protected by AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10960/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:11:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10960/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At Docker, we&amp;rsquo;re committed to building hardened images with meticulous human craftsmanship and enhanced by AI. This dual approach ensures better security for our users. Our AI guardrail recently caught a critical bug during an nginx-exporter update, preventing potential issues from reaching customers. This highlights the importance of layered safeguards in software development. By addressing issues upstream, we maintain clean images and support the broader open-source community. #Docker #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Think Like an Adversary: How Cisco Safely Finds the Flaws Attackers *Will* Exploit</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10937/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10937/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Your security systems need a workout! Cisco’s Assessment and Penetration Testing (APT) team helps organizations identify weaknesses by simulating real-world attacks safely. 🛡️ This proactive approach allows businesses to fix vulnerabilities before they can be exploited. October is Cybersecurity Awareness Month, making it a perfect time to reassess your defenses. 📚 Interested in gaining offensive skills? Check out Cisco&amp;rsquo;s Certificate in Ethical Hacking program! #Cybersecurity #Cisco&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure coding in JavaScript</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10948/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10948/</guid>
      <description>🔒 JavaScript is essential for web development, but it also attracts attackers. This article highlights ten tips for writing secure JavaScript, focusing on preventing cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks. XSS allows attackers to execute malicious code directly in users&amp;rsquo; browsers, which can compromise security. Key recommendations include input validation, output encoding, and using Content Security Policy (CSP) headers. Implementing these measures can significantly reduce the risk of XSS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Infrastructure That Powers AI Could Also Break It</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10934/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10934/</guid>
      <description>🚀 When discussing AI security, infrastructure risks often get overlooked. AI workloads rely on foundational components like containers and GPUs, which weren&amp;rsquo;t designed with these specific vulnerabilities in mind. 🔍 Recent findings revealed critical vulnerabilities in the NVIDIA Container Toolkit, highlighting a new attack surface that could compromise shared GPU infrastructure. 🛠️ Organizations using AI as a service must prioritize secure-by-default practices to protect against risks arising&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talha Tariq joins Vercel as CTO (Security)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10968/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10968/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news at Vercel! Talha Tariq joins as CTO (Security) to address the growing security challenges in software development. With experience as CISO &amp;amp; CIO at HashiCorp and CTO (Security) at IBM, he brings valuable expertise to the team. His role will focus on enhancing security measures as AI continues to evolve. #Vercel #Cybersecurity #TechNews #Leadership #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Common Threat Themes: Defending Against Lateral Movement (Part 1)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10931/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10931/</guid>
      <description>Cybersecurity is a continuous battle as defenders enhance their strategies against evolving threats. Lateral movement is identified as a key tactic in 70% of cyber breaches, highlighting a critical area for improvement. Organizations are encouraged to adopt strong, prescriptive controls to combat this risk effectively. Investing in network and application segmentation can significantly enhance security without disrupting operations. #CyberSecurity #LateralMovement #DataProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incident Report: October 15th, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10921/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-15-10921/</guid>
      <description>📢 On October 15th, 2025, we faced an outage that impacted our dashboard and deployment pipeline. This led to a temporary suspension of deployments and made the dashboard unavailable for all user tiers. We are actively working to resolve these issues. Thank you for your understanding. #IncidentReport #ServiceUpdate #TechStatus #UserNotification #SystemOutage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Data Cloud’s New Unstructured Data Governance: Automated PII Detection at Enterprise Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10909/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:58:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10909/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in data governance are underway at Salesforce! In the latest “Engineering Energizers” Q&amp;amp;A, Lead Software Engineer Bhargava Ravali Koganti discusses the development of Data Cloud’s first unstructured security system. This innovative system automatically detects and masks sensitive information in enterprise documents. The team tackled the challenge of processing large volumes of unstructured data using Spark pipelines and machine learning models. Their efforts focus on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How CrowdStrike Stops Living-off-the-Land Attacks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10928/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10928/</guid>
      <description>CrowdStrike is addressing the rising threat of &amp;ldquo;living-off-the-land&amp;rdquo; attacks, where adversaries misuse legitimate tools instead of traditional malware. Their new capability, Anomalous Process Execution (APEX), enhances defense by using AI to identify and stop the abuse of trusted applications like Windows utilities and remote management tools. This shift in tactics has made detection challenging, as these applications are critical for business operations. APEX aims to improve security by&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>October 2025 Patch Tuesday: Two Publicly Disclosed, Three Zero-Days, and Eight Critical Vulnerabilities Among 172 CVEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10929/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10929/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Microsoft has issued its October 2025 security update, addressing a total of 172 vulnerabilities. This is the highest monthly total for the year. This update includes two publicly disclosed vulnerabilities, three zero-day vulnerabilities, and eight critical vulnerabilities, along with 159 others of varying severity. The main risk types involve elevation of privilege (80 patches), remote code execution (31), and information disclosure (28). Most patches were for Microsoft Windows (134),&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows 10 End of Support: How to Stay Protected</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10927/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-14-10927/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for Windows 10 Users! 🚨 As of October 14, 2025, Microsoft will end support for non-LTSC releases of Windows 10. This means no more security updates or feature patches, increasing vulnerability to cyber threats. Many enterprises still rely on Windows 10, holding significant market share. Organizations must plan their migration to supported systems to avoid security risks and compliance issues. Stay informed and protect your systems! 💻🔒 #Windows10 #CyberSecurity #EndOfSupport&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>100% Transparency and Five Pillars</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10878/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 21:58:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10878/</guid>
      <description>Container security is crucial as workloads increasingly rely on containers. However, many organizations misrepresent their container security capabilities. According to a recent article, there are five essential elements for achieving maximum container security: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Minimal Attack Surface&lt;/strong&gt;: Only essential software should be included. 2. &lt;strong&gt;Complete Software Bills of Materials (SBOM)&lt;/strong&gt;: Accurate inventory is necessary. 3. &lt;strong&gt;Verifiable Build Provenance&lt;/strong&gt;: Establishes a clear chain of custody&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prevent secret exposure across IT: 4 tools and techniques</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10873/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-13-10873/</guid>
      <description>Preventing the exposure of sensitive information is crucial for cybersecurity. 🔒 The average data breach cost is projected to reach $4.4M by 2025. A significant number of attacks involve compromised credentials, highlighting the need for proactive measures. HashiCorp offers tools that integrate security checks into development workflows. One notable method is credential injection, which automates the management of sensitive credentials, reducing the risk of exposure. Explore how these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Reliability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10634/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10634/</guid>
      <description>Data reliability is essential for organizations today. It impacts decision-making and overall business performance. With the rise of data-driven strategies, ensuring accurate and consistent data is vital for success. Businesses must prioritize data integrity to maintain trust and efficiency. 🔍📊💼 #DataReliability #BusinessStrategy #DataIntegrity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is the End of Detection-Based Security Here?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10622/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 16:00:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10622/</guid>
      <description>Is the era of detection-based security coming to an end? 🛡️ A recent article discusses how security monitoring has evolved but often remains reactive. Many companies focus on creating efficient detection tools rather than addressing vulnerabilities directly. The reliance on logs and alerts can drain resources and time, making incident response challenging. Emerging security firms emphasize prevention over detection, signaling a potential shift in the industry. #CyberSecurity #CloudSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Over Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10626/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 15:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10626/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Palantir Technologies provides software platforms for data and AI, assisting various sectors including defense, healthcare, and finance. 🛡️ The company emphasizes privacy, ensuring clients maintain full ownership and control over their data. Palantir is not a data broker and does not sell or use client data for its own purposes. 📊 With advanced security and governance tools, Palantir helps organizations optimize operations while adhering to global regulations. For more information, visit&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Your Business Ready for AI Agents? The Ultimate AI Security Checklist for Customer Identity</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10620/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-10-10620/</guid>
      <description>Is your business prepared for AI agents? 🤖 As AI technology becomes part of everyday life, security concerns are rising. A recent report shows that 60% of users worry about AI&amp;rsquo;s impact on their digital identities. Our AI Security Checklist outlines the essential steps for assessing your identity environment. 📝 Strengthening your strategy is crucial to ensuring customer trust and data protection. Stay secure as you implement AI solutions! #AI #Cybersecurity #CustomerTrust #DataProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Assistant to Adversary: Exploiting Agentic AI Developer Tools</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10584/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10584/</guid>
      <description>Developers are increasingly using AI tools like OpenAI Codex and GitHub Copilot for coding. While these tools can enhance productivity, they also create new security risks. 🛡️ These agentic tools leverage LLMs, which can lead to unpredictable actions. Attackers can exploit this through techniques like watering hole attacks, potentially allowing remote code execution. Understanding the role and risks of computer use agents is crucial for maintaining security in development environments. 🔍💻&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Auth0 Token Vault: Secure Token Exchange for AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10601/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 14:58:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-09-10601/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Auth0 Token Vault enhances AI agents by enabling secure, delegated access through OAuth 2.0 Token Exchange. AI agents can now perform tasks like scheduling meetings or posting updates without exposing sensitive refresh tokens. This method addresses the risks associated with traditional token storage and API keys. By applying federated identity, users can seamlessly authenticate with trusted providers, ensuring better control and security. Discover how Auth0 is paving the way for safer AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the credential risk gap for AI agents using a browser</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10534/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10534/</guid>
      <description>AI agents are increasingly taking on tasks in browsers, but this raises security concerns regarding credential management. As these agents operate, they need access to sensitive information like passwords and API keys, leading to risks of credential sprawl and exposure. 🔑💻 1Password introduces Secure Agentic Autofill, which allows credentials to be securely injected into browsers without exposing them to AI agents. This method ensures that sensitive data remains protected and requires human&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Refresh Token Security: Detecting Hijacking and Misuse with Auth0</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10570/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-08-10570/</guid>
      <description>Enhancing refresh token security is vital for modern applications. 🔐 This article discusses methods to detect hijacking and misuse using Auth0&amp;rsquo;s Detection Catalog. Refresh tokens help maintain user experience but pose security risks, especially if compromised. Key strategies include: - Storing tokens in secure HTTP-Only cookies - Enabling refresh token rotation - Automatic reuse detection These measures can help mitigate risks and protect sensitive data. 💻🛡️ #Cybersecurity #Auth0&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From key sprawl to scalable control: Rethinking SSH access</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10514/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 16:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10514/</guid>
      <description>Access sprawl and security issues are growing concerns with static SSH keys. 🚨 These keys, widely used for secure connections, become unmanageable as organizations scale, leading to risks like shared access and lack of audit trails. Transitioning to SSH certificates can enhance security and manageability, providing better auditability and automatic revocation. This move addresses the challenges of static keys, especially in dynamic environments. 🔑 #CyberSecurity #SSH #AccessManagement&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defining a Standard Taxonomy for Segmentation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10495/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10495/</guid>
      <description>Segmentation is essential for enhancing cybersecurity by preventing threats from spreading across networks. As segmentation solutions multiply, organizations face challenges in selecting the right approach. A new blog series will address these topics, offering insights into use cases, challenges, and strategies for effective implementation. Stay tuned for valuable information to strengthen your security posture and align with business goals. 🔒💻 #Cybersecurity #Segmentation #ZeroTrust&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Context is king for secure, AI-generated code</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10484/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 07:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10484/</guid>
      <description>In a recent discussion, Dimitri Stiliadis, CTO of Endor Labs, emphasized the evolving role of AppSec in the era of AI-generated code. Key points include the need for human oversight in managing vulnerabilities and the balance between security and efficiency when integrating AI into development practices. Endor Labs aims to help organizations identify critical risks in both human and AI-written code. 🔒🤖💻 #AppSec #AIGeneratedCode #Cybersecurity #SoftwareDevelopment #EndorLabs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft and Dropbox password managers are sunsetting: What it means and what to do next</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10498/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-07-10498/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Attention users! Microsoft and Dropbox are discontinuing their built-in password managers, raising concerns about digital security. Without a password manager, you may risk reusing passwords, increasing vulnerability to credential theft. 💻🔒 Microsoft Authenticator will sunset in August 2025, while Dropbox Passwords will end on October 28, 2025. Users can still access saved passwords via Microsoft accounts and export data before the deadline for Dropbox. As security threats grow, consider&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Racing Against Threats: How Cisco Security Powers McLaren’s F1 Prowess</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10442/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10442/</guid>
      <description>🚀 McLaren&amp;rsquo;s success in the 2025 F1 season is backed by a strong partnership with Cisco. Since 2021, Cisco has provided essential cybersecurity and networking solutions, ensuring McLaren’s data remains secure and operations efficient. The collaboration emphasizes trust and innovation, crucial for facing modern security challenges. Together, they enhance performance on and off the track. 🏎️🔐 #F1 #Cybersecurity #McLaren #Cisco #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Identifies Campaign Targeting Oracle E-Business Suite via Zero-Day Vulnerability (now tracked as CVE-2025-61882)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10480/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10480/</guid>
      <description>🚨 CrowdStrike has identified a mass exploitation campaign targeting Oracle E-Business Suite applications through a zero-day vulnerability, known as CVE-2025-61882. The campaign is believed to involve the threat actor GRACEFUL SPIDER. Initial exploitation began on August 9, 2025, and ongoing investigations may alter this timeline. Recent disclosures of proof-of-concept exploits are likely to motivate other actors to exploit this vulnerability. Stay vigilant! 🔒💻 #CyberSecurity #Oracle&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From endpoint to XDR: Operationalize Jamf Protect data in Elastic Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10471/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-06-10471/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your threat detection capabilities by integrating Jamf Protect with Elastic Security. 🛡️ This integration consolidates macOS telemetry with AI-driven analytics, improving visibility across endpoints and networks. It helps security teams respond to threats more effectively within a single platform. With real-time alerts and detection rules, organizations can connect telemetry to broader attack campaigns and act swiftly to prevent escalations. 🔍✨ #CyberSecurity #XDR #JamfProtect&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Practical LLM Security Advice from the NVIDIA AI Red Team</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10362/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:52:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10362/</guid>
      <description>The NVIDIA AI Red Team (AIRT) has been assessing AI-enabled systems for security vulnerabilities. They identified key risks in LLM-based applications, particularly the danger of executing LLM-generated code without proper isolation. This can lead to remote code execution, exposing applications to potential attacks. Addressing these vulnerabilities during development is crucial for improving security. 🔒💻 #AI #CyberSecurity #NVIDIA #LLM #SecurityAwareness</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why traditional secret scanning tools fail to address today&#39;s secret management crisis</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10400/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10400/</guid>
      <description>Traditional secret scanning tools face significant challenges in today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced development landscape. 🚀 Recent research shows over 18,000 exposed API secrets last year, with many categorized as highly critical. Despite using secret scanning, organizations struggle with credential leaks and sensitive data exposure. 🔑 The shift to microservice architectures and cloud deployments has increased the number of secrets to manage, outpacing older scanning methods. These tools often produce high&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP: Best Practices for Secure Agent-Database Interoperability</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10353/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10353/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Model Context Protocol (MCP), launched by Anthropic in November 2024, aims to standardize AI applications&amp;rsquo; connection to various data sources. However, its openness leads to security concerns, particularly regarding agentic AI systems. Key threats include prompt injections and malicious servers, which can compromise data integrity. For organizations using MCP, understanding these risks is crucial for secure implementation. #AIsafety #MCP #CyberSecurity #DataProtection #AIStandards</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust: The Foundation of Industrial Cyber Defense</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10357/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:36:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-02-10357/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Industrial cybersecurity is crucial as threats evolve. A zero trust architecture is recommended for protecting operational technology (OT) in sectors like energy and manufacturing. CISA emphasizes the need for micro-segmentation and accurate asset inventory to enhance security. Zero trust can reduce attack surfaces and limit lateral movement, which is vital for maintaining operations. Cisco offers solutions to implement zero trust at scale without disrupting production. #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canadian Bacon Cybersecurity: SharePoint Vulnerabilities and Vulnerabilities in General</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10312/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 12:00:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10312/</guid>
      <description>📢 Understanding SharePoint Vulnerabilities The article highlights vulnerabilities in Microsoft SharePoint and how they can be exploited by adversaries. Key factors include remotely accessible systems and weak endpoint protections. To mitigate these risks, patching is essential, though not always timely. Implementing remote access via VPN or zero trust access can enhance security. Stay informed and secure! 🔐 #Cybersecurity #SharePoint #Vulnerabilities #DataProtection #ZeroTrust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The secure way to handle secrets in OpenShift</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10306/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 07:01:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10306/</guid>
      <description>Managing sensitive information in cloud-native platforms like OpenShift is essential for security. 🌐 This article discusses two methods for accessing secrets: environment variables and volume mounts. While both are supported, volume mounts are recommended for better security and control. 🔒 Volume mounts automatically update sensitive data and limit exposure, ensuring only necessary credentials are accessed by applications. In contrast, environment variables carry risks of accidental exposure&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI can do what now?! How AI is fixing security&#39;s worst bottleneck</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10315/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-10-01-10315/</guid>
      <description>AI is transforming how security teams handle data onboarding! 🤖 Many security professionals spend significant time normalizing log formats, which is essential for effective operations. This process can be tedious and error-prone. In a recent discussion, Anas Khatri from Elastic highlighted how AI, particularly large language models, is streamlining this task. AI now automates data normalization and enrichment, reducing onboarding time from hours to just minutes. This innovation supports&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs Are the Key to Mutation Testing and Better Compliance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10301/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 16:00:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10301/</guid>
      <description>Meta is advancing software testing with its Automated Compliance Hardening (ACH) tool, powered by large language models (LLMs). This tool automates compliance adherence and enhances developer efficiency. By using LLMs, Meta simplifies risk assessments, reduces developer workload, and fosters continuous compliance, creating safer online environments. Meta also invites the community to engage in challenges like the JiTTest Challenge, exploring new opportunities in software testing. #Meta&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charting a New Course for SaaS Security: Why MongoDB Helped Build the SSCF</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10253/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10253/</guid>
      <description>SaaS applications are essential for businesses, but their diverse security settings create risks. 🛡️ To address this, MongoDB collaborated with the Cloud Security Alliance to create the SaaS Security Capability Framework (SSCF). This framework standardizes security controls, making it easier for risk management and security teams to assess and implement security measures. 🔒 The SSCF focuses on six key domains, providing actionable controls for secure SaaS usage. Learn more about how MongoDB&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rethinking AI Security: The Dynamic Context Firewall for MCP</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10249/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 12:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10249/</guid>
      <description>🔒 As AI becomes integral to business workflows, securing interactions with external tools is essential. The Dynamic Context Firewall (DCF) is a proposed security layer for the Model Context Protocol (MCP), enhancing adaptive AI security. Unlike traditional firewalls, the DCF analyzes AI interactions in real-time, considering context and intent to ensure proper access control. This innovative approach aims to tackle risks such as unauthorized data access and consent fatigue. #AISecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Falcon ASPM Secures GenAI Applications and Lessons from Dogfooding</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10308/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-30-10308/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Falcon Application Security Posture Management (ASPM) enhances the security of generative AI applications by providing essential visibility and context to combat advanced threats. As businesses adopt large language models, traditional security tools may fall short. Falcon ASPM helps organizations understand complex attack surfaces, ensuring robust protection for their GenAI applications. Discover how CrowdStrike&amp;rsquo;s innovative approach addresses the unique challenges of agentic AI and keeps&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Expanding Docker Hardened Images: Secure Helm Charts for Deployments</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10229/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 20:02:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10229/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Development teams are facing increased pressure to secure their software supply chains. Docker has introduced Helm charts in the Docker Hardened Images (DHI) Catalog to streamline Kubernetes deployments while enhancing security. These charts ensure safe configurations and clear traceability, meeting the needs of teams concerned about compliance. With changes from Broadcom affecting Bitnami&amp;rsquo;s distribution, Docker offers a reliable alternative for secure deployments. Join the beta program to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploying AI in Air-Gapped Environments: What It Really Takes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10197/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-29-10197/</guid>
      <description>Integrating AI tools in secure environments poses unique challenges. For teams in defense and regulated industries, traditional cloud-based AI solutions are not viable. They operate in air-gapped environments, requiring strict isolation from external networks. To be effective, AI must have zero external dependencies, frozen models for predictability, and rely solely on local data. Comprehensive auditability is crucial for compliance. #AI #CyberSecurity #AirGapped #TechInsights #Compliance 🛡️💻🔒</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe Coding: When AI Writes the Code, Who Secures It?</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10162/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 20:00:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10162/</guid>
      <description>Exploring &amp;ldquo;vibe coding&amp;rdquo; introduces exciting possibilities for creators using AI tools like ChatGPT and Copilot. This approach encourages innovation but raises critical security concerns. Experts, including prominent figures from the open-source community, emphasize the need for human oversight in AI-generated code. While AI can enhance rapid prototyping, risks remain without proper guidance. As we embrace AI in coding, it’s essential to balance enthusiasm with experience and maintain security&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why CVEs Belong in Frameworks and Apps, Not AI Models</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10153/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 16:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10153/</guid>
      <description>The Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) system catalogs software security flaws globally. As AI models integrate into enterprise systems, discussions arise about their inclusion in CVEs. However, vulnerabilities often reside in the frameworks and applications using AI models, not the models themselves. Issues like insecure session handling or supply chain risks are better addressed outside the CVE system. It&amp;rsquo;s essential to focus on the surrounding code for identifying and mitigating&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CISOs: Prepare for Software’s Agentic Future Today</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10151/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 15:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10151/</guid>
      <description>📊 A recent GitLab survey reveals that 89% of executives foresee agentic AI becoming the key standard in software development within three years. However, 85% acknowledge the significant security challenges it presents. 🔒 CISOs face the tough task of adopting AI while minimizing its risks. With 91% planning to increase AI spending, the need for a robust governance model is critical. Yet, 47% lack regulatory-aligned governance, highlighting the urgency for action. ⚖️ To tackle these challenges,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Trust Paradox: When Your AI Gets Catfished</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10139/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-26-10139/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Hackers are exploiting trust relationships to catfish your AI. Attacks aren&amp;rsquo;t about technical skills; they manipulate familiar systems designers and developers rely on. From altered npm packages to deceptive documentation, AI tools can be misled to introduce vulnerabilities. The good news? Solutions exist that don&amp;rsquo;t hinder development. #CyberSecurity #AI #TrustParadox #MCP #InfoSec</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audit log streaming for real-time security visibility in your CI/CD pipeline</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10116/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 19:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10116/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Security and compliance teams often face challenges in detecting suspicious activities in their CI/CD pipelines. Delays in incident response and gaps in visibility can leave organizations vulnerable. The article discusses automated audit log streaming as a solution. This method provides real-time access to audit events, enabling immediate threat detection and faster incident response. By integrating audit logs into security tools, teams can ensure continuous compliance and streamline their&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Palantir’s Strategic Privacy Investments Enable Future Customer Success</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10080/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:56:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10080/</guid>
      <description>Palantir is enhancing customer success through strategic privacy investments in its software platforms. Their tools, like granular access controls and data lineage, ensure sensitive data is handled securely. A key feature, Checkpoints, allows users to provide purpose justification for sensitive actions, improving compliance and governance. Checkpoints integrate with over 60 actions, helping organizations meet regulatory requirements and manage AI workflows effectively. Learn how these&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe in the sandbox: security hardening for Cloudflare Workers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10062/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10062/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare Workers is enhancing security with new software and hardware features. We utilize defense-in-depth strategies, including V8 sandboxes and memory protection keys, to safeguard your data while running third-party code on our infrastructure. The V8 JavaScript runtime is key to our approach, designed to run safely under adversarial conditions. Our ongoing updates focus on leveraging the latest advancements to keep Workers secure. 🔒💻 #Cloudflare #CyberSecurity #Serverless&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Secure: how we upgraded 6,000,000 domains by default to get ready for the Quantum Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9977/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9977/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates on Internet security! Cloudflare has upgraded over 6 million domains to Automatic SSL/TLS for enhanced protection. This service automatically scans and strengthens security without any action from users. As we prepare for future advancements, the focus is on evolving TLS protocols and integrating post-quantum cryptography to safeguard data against emerging threats. Learn more about these important developments! 🔒🌐 #InternetSecurity #Cloudflare #TLS #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing data in SaaS to SaaS applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9979/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9979/</guid>
      <description>The recent Salesloft breach highlights a critical issue: companies lack visibility over data in SaaS applications. 🔍 To address this, Cloudflare is developing security tools that consolidate SaaS connections through a single proxy. This aims to enhance monitoring, detection, and response capabilities. 🛡️ SaaS platform providers play a key role in safeguarding customer data, but integrations can create vulnerabilities. With more apps, the risk of data breaches increases. 🔒 Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap: Cisco’s Blueprint for Developer-Centric Cloud Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9972/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9972/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco is transforming cloud security by integrating it into the developer workflow. They focus on reducing friction between developers and security teams through high-fidelity alerts, pre-configured solutions, and clear communication. This approach fosters collaboration and trust, making security a natural part of development. Empathy is emphasized to ensure security measures truly support developers. #CloudSecurity #DevOps #Cisco #Collaboration #SecuritySolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Signup Fraud: 3 Ways to Use Auth0 Logs to Protect Your Business</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10035/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10035/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Fraudulent signups can harm businesses significantly. Auth0 provides tools to help detect and prevent these threats. Key indicators of signup fraud include: 1️⃣ High-volume signups from specific IP addresses. 2️⃣ Use of disposable email addresses. 3️⃣ Unverified accounts. By leveraging Auth0 Logs, businesses can identify these patterns and take action to protect themselves. 🛡️ #FraudPrevention #Auth0 #CyberSecurity #BusinessSafety #SignUpFraud</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The Drive-By Localhost Breach</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9917/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9917/</guid>
      <description>🚨 MCP Horror Stories: Drive-By Localhost Breach 🚨 Part 4 of our series highlights a critical vulnerability, CVE-2025-49596, found in MCP Inspector. This issue allows attackers to compromise developer machines simply by visiting a malicious website. With a CVSS score of 9.4, this flaw turns a trusted debugging tool into an attack vector, showcasing the real-world risks in AI development environments. Learn how Docker MCP Gateway can help protect against these sophisticated threats&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotID uncovers hidden SEO poisoning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9884/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9884/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A recent case highlights the risks of hidden SEO poisoning. A major financial institution observed unexpected bot traffic and deployed BotID. Instead of detecting malicious scrapers, they found verified Google bots. However, the search queries were unrelated to their business, revealing a long-standing SEO attack that was distorting their traffic patterns. Stay vigilant! 🕵️‍♂️ #SEOSecurity #BotID #CyberThreats #DigitalSafety #TrafficMonitoring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 80/20 Rule Doesn’t Apply to Security: How Cisco SASE Bridges the Gap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9865/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9865/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s IT landscape, relying on the 80/20 rule for security is risky. Focusing only on the majority can leave vulnerabilities exposed. 🌐🔒 With hybrid work and evolving tech, organizations need a security strategy that protects 100% of their digital presence at all times. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s SASE offers a solution by merging networking and security in a cloud-based framework. 🌥️ This innovative approach establishes micro-perimeters for enhanced protection, ensuring secure access no matter where users&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incident Report: September 22nd, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9899/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9899/</guid>
      <description>📉 On September 22, 2025, our platform faced an outage that impacted both the dashboard and deployment pipeline. This led to a temporary suspension of deployments for all user tiers. We are actively working to resolve these issues and minimize future disruptions. Stay tuned for updates! 🔧🚧 #IncidentReport #TechUpdate #SystemOutage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect AI Development with Falcon Cloud Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9890/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9890/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Falcon Cloud Security is crucial for safeguarding AI development. It detects risks in the CI/CD pipeline and tracks AI workloads in production. As AI becomes integral to applications, it also introduces new security challenges. Without proper visibility, organizations may expose sensitive data or deploy vulnerable code. CrowdStrike&amp;rsquo;s solution offers real-time detection and comprehensive model scanning, ensuring robust protection throughout the AI pipeline. #CloudSecurity #AIDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Government Operations: Cisco Security Cloud Control Achieves FedRAMP Authorization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9826/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9826/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for U.S. government agencies! Cisco Security Cloud Control has received FedRAMP Authorization, enhancing security management for critical infrastructure. This cloud-native solution supports agencies in navigating today’s complex threat landscape. The FedRAMP Authorization signifies high security standards, ensuring that Cisco&amp;rsquo;s solution is compliant and reliable for federal operations. #Cybersecurity #GovTech #FedRAMP #Cisco #CloudSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You don’t need quantum hardware for post-quantum security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9823/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9823/</guid>
      <description>🛡️ Protect your organization from future quantum threats with post-quantum cryptography (PQC). PQC can be deployed on existing hardware, ensuring your systems remain secure even after the arrival of powerful quantum computers. Contrary to popular belief, quantum key distribution (QKD) is not necessary for security. Stay informed and prepare for a quantum-ready future! #PostQuantumSecurity #Cybersecurity #QuantumReady #TechNews #DataProtection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Determinism and Safety to Uber IAM Policy Changes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9776/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9776/</guid>
      <description>🚦 Uber has introduced a Policy Simulator tool to improve the safety and predictability of IAM policy changes. 🛠️ This tool allows policy authors to preview the effects of their modifications before they go live, ensuring predictable outcomes post-deployment. 🔍 This development aims to enhance security and stability in Uber&amp;rsquo;s operations. #Uber #IAM #PolicyChanges #Cybersecurity #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratizing AI Safety with RiskRubric.ai</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9789/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9789/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news in AI safety! The launch of RiskRubric.ai aims to enhance trust in AI models by providing standardized risk assessments. With over 500,000 models on the Hugging Face hub, users often struggle to evaluate security and privacy aspects. This initiative, led by Cloud Security Alliance and Noma Security, seeks to ensure transparent security reporting as AI adoption grows. #AISafety #RiskAssessment #AIModels #CloudSecurity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusing Security into Networks: The Next Evolution in Enterprise Protection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9734/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9734/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving landscape of enterprise networks, traditional security tools are proving inadequate. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s AI-Ready Secure Network Architecture embeds multilayered security within the network itself, enhancing protection against a range of threats. This integrated approach utilizes Zero Trust, post-quantum encryption, and real-time threat prevention to simplify operations and improve threat response. It addresses vulnerabilities across various domains, including user edge and industrial&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthen privacy and security with encrypted DNS in RHEL</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9716/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 07:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9716/</guid>
      <description>🔒 In today&amp;rsquo;s digital world, securing DNS traffic is crucial. Unencrypted DNS queries can expose sensitive information to eavesdroppers, leading to potential data breaches. 🔍 Encrypted DNS, particularly DNS over TLS (DoT), is now available in Red Hat Enterprise Linux 10 and 9.6. This advancement strengthens network security by ensuring that DNS queries are kept private and verifiable. 🛠️ The article provides a step-by-step guide for implementing encrypted DNS to improve system security during&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Collaborates with AI Leaders to Secure AI Across the Enterprise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9756/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9756/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike is enhancing AI security with new integrations across the enterprise. Their Falcon® platform now offers unified protection for AI models, data, and applications, addressing risks like data poisoning and model theft. Partnerships with industry leaders like AWS, NVIDIA, and Meta ensure comprehensive security at every layer of the AI stack. This approach enables organizations to innovate with confidence while maintaining essential visibility and control. #CyberSecurity #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Shai-Hulud Worm: Elastic&#39;s proactive defense against npm supply chain compromise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9753/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9753/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The software development community is responding to compromised npm packages linked to the Shai-Hulud worm. Elastic emphasizes the importance of supply chain integrity, noting that while its products don’t ship with npm, they rely on it for package retrieval. In their latest blog, Elastic details their analysis of code, mitigation strategies, and detection rules to combat these threats. Stay informed and secure! 🔒📦 #CyberSecurity #NPMCompromise #ElasticSecurity #ShaiHulud #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powering Zero Trust Networking with Elastic and Gigamon AMI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9747/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9747/</guid>
      <description>The cybersecurity landscape is evolving with the adoption of Zero Trust Networking (ZTN). This model emphasizes that no transaction is inherently trustworthy; every connection must be verified continuously. 🔒 Elastic and Gigamon&amp;rsquo;s Application Metadata Intelligence (AMI) play a crucial role in this framework. They enable intelligent data processing to support real-time decision-making and enhance security posture. 📊 As traditional perimeter defenses become obsolete, ZTN acknowledges modern&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correcting the Record: Response to the Recent American Conservative Article on Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9710/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 20:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9710/</guid>
      <description>Palantir addresses recent allegations from the American Conservative questioning its commitment to privacy and civil liberties. The response clarifies that Palantir is not a surveillance company and does not engage in or promote unlawful surveillance practices. The article misrepresents Palantir&amp;rsquo;s work with intelligence agencies, particularly regarding claims related to the NSA&amp;rsquo;s XKEYSCORE tool. Palantir emphasizes its dedication to privacy laws and governance safeguards, ensuring that its&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Agent in the Middle To Ride Herd on Wayward AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9689/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9689/</guid>
      <description>Development teams face pressure to adopt AI agents, but concerns about their unpredictable behavior and potential risks are rising. Ilya Sutskever from OpenAI warns that these agents could become &amp;ldquo;ticking time bombs,&amp;rdquo; highlighting the need for better security measures. Eve Security aims to address these challenges with their agent-in-the-loop technology, which monitors agent actions while minimizing false alerts. CISOs express concerns about connecting AI to sensitive systems, emphasizing the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Security: A Developer’s Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9685/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9685/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Model Context Protocol (MCP) has quickly gained traction since its launch by Anthropic in November 2024. It serves as a vital link between AI agents and various tools, APIs, and data. 🔍 However, this flexibility comes with security challenges. Research indicates that 43% of analyzed MCP servers have command injection vulnerabilities, which could lead to serious risks if misconfigured. 🛡️ This guide offers developers insights into MCP security, highlighting risks and best practices for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shai-Halud Supply Chain Campaign — Expanded Impact &amp; Vercel Response</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9788/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9788/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The Shai-Halud supply chain campaign has escalated, impacting over 40 npm packages, including Tinycolor and CrowdStrike. Vercel identified 10 customer projects affected by compromised packages but confirmed that no builds were impacted in the DuckDB incident. Steps taken include blocking compromised versions and purging build caches. Vercel is enhancing supply chain defenses and monitoring for further threats. For Vercel users, audit dependencies and consider using pnpm&amp;rsquo;s new settings to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Identity Security Essentials for a Trusted AI Agent Strategy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9683/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9683/</guid>
      <description>Is your AI agent strategy secure? 🤖🔒 As companies integrate AI agents, consumer trust is crucial. A recent report shows that while 37% of consumers use GenAI tools, 70% still prefer human interaction due to privacy concerns. To build trust, robust customer identity and access management (CIAM) is essential. Here are four key practices: 1️⃣ Ensure strong authentication before AI actions. 2️⃣ Securely manage data access to protect user information. Investing in CIAM can enhance security and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-quantum security for SSH access on GitHub</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9659/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9659/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitHub is enhancing SSH access security with a new post-quantum secure key exchange algorithm called sntrup761x25519-sha512. This upgrade will protect Git data against future quantum computing threats. 🔒 The changes will take effect on September 17, 2025, and will only affect SSH connections, leaving HTTPS access unchanged. 🔧 Users with compatible SSH clients will benefit without needing adjustments. #GitHub #Cybersecurity #PostQuantum #SSH #DataProtection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent threat detection for defence SOCs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9665/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9665/</guid>
      <description>The Ministry of Defence highlights a critical cyber risk for defence security operations centres (SOCs), amid rising malicious activities. To counter these threats, the MoD&amp;rsquo;s Digital Strategy prioritizes rapid detection and response. Effective SOCs aim to reduce mean time to detect (MTTD) and mean time to respond (MTTR) significantly. Elastic Security supports this through AI-driven analytics, automating tasks to enhance SOC efficiency and visibility. Improvements in MTTD and MTTR have been&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic AI Is Key To Preventing Costly AI Hallucinations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9635/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9635/</guid>
      <description>AI hallucinations can lead to significant risks for businesses, with inaccuracies affecting efficiency and trust. A recent study shows these inaccuracies occur between 0.7% and 29.9% of the time, depending on the AI model used. An example highlights how a manufacturer faced issues when their AI assistant provided incorrect troubleshooting advice due to gaps in its knowledge base. To combat this, the team developed enhanced checks and validation processes, leading to improved accuracy and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 Popular npm Packages Compromised in Attack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9631/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 13:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9631/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Aikido Security has uncovered a serious security breach involving 18 popular npm packages, which have been compromised to include malicious code. These packages, with over 2 billion downloads weekly, can silently intercept crypto and web3 activities, directing funds to attacker-controlled accounts. Key affected packages include chalk, debug, and supports-color. For developers using these tools, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to check for updates and security patches. #CyberSecurity #npm #Malware&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenSSF Experts Weigh in on CISA’s SBOM Minimum Elements Update</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9611/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9611/</guid>
      <description>Experts from OpenSSF highlight the need for an update to CISA&amp;rsquo;s guidance on software bills of materials (SBOMs). Josh Bressers and Michael Lieberman emphasize the importance of clarity in SBOMs to ensure software safety, citing examples from industries like automotive and healthcare. The draft revision is open for public comment until October 3. Your feedback is crucial! 🛠️🔍 #SBOM #SoftwareSecurity #OpenSSF #CISA #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Ways Security Teams Can Tame Autonomous AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9568/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9568/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Security teams face new challenges with autonomous AI agents that operate without human consciousness. These systems can expose vulnerabilities in traditional authorization processes. To address this, organizations should implement three key strategies: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Assign Composite Identities&lt;/strong&gt; - This helps clarify the relationship between AI actions and human operators, enhancing accountability. Understanding these risks is crucial for maintaining secure environments. #CyberSecurity #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Attacks on AI-Powered Apps with the AI Kill Chain Framework</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9552/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9552/</guid>
      <description>AI-powered applications are facing new security challenges that traditional models may not address. The AI Kill Chain framework, developed by NVIDIA, outlines how adversaries target these systems. This framework emphasizes the stages of an attack: recon, poison, hijack, persist, and impact. It aims to help defenders identify where they can intervene effectively. Learn more about the evolving landscape of AI security! 🔐💻🛡️ #AI #CyberSecurity #NVIDIA #AIKillChain #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Salesforce Integrations with Heroku AppLink</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9523/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9523/</guid>
      <description>Salesforce customers often use third-party services through Connected Apps and External Services. However, security risks persist in the integration landscape. 🔒 Heroku AppLink enhances security by providing a managed bridge between Salesforce and Heroku. It handles authentication, service discovery, and request validation, reducing reliance on stored credentials. This allows developers to reuse existing code and improves visibility and trust boundaries for admins and security teams. For&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Hallucinations to Prompt Injection: Securing AI Workflows at Runtime</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9516/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9516/</guid>
      <description>Developers are facing new challenges as AI workflows become potential attack surfaces. With AI tools like LLMs generating code, issues can arise only at runtime, leading to serious risks such as data loss or unauthorized commands. ⚠️ Prompt injections and misuse of AI outputs are significant threats. Recent incidents have shown how AI-generated scripts can unintentionally delete databases or expose sensitive information. 📉 To tackle these risks, integrating runtime security directly into&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against AI-Powered CLI Supply Chain Attacks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9514/</guid>
      <description>🚨 AI-powered CLI supply chain attacks are becoming a serious threat to developers. These attacks exploit trusted command-line tools, turning them into insider threats that can steal sensitive data. A recent example involves an attacker exploiting a developer&amp;rsquo;s credentials to publish a malicious update, compromising systems and stealing secrets. To defend against these threats, an identity-first strategy is essential for securing developer environments and preventing data exfiltration. Stay&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitbucket Cloud enters phase two of app password deprecation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9505/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9505/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Bitbucket Cloud is moving to Phase 2 of app password deprecation! Starting September 9, 2025, new app passwords will no longer be created. Existing passwords will remain valid until June 9, 2026. New integrations must use API tokens for enhanced security and control. Admins should start migrating their teams now to avoid disruptions. 🔗 Learn more about this transition! #Bitbucket #APITokens #Security #DeveloperTools #Atlassian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIPAA BAAs are now available to Pro teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9485/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9485/</guid>
      <description>Pro teams can now enter into a Business Associate Agreement (BAA) on Vercel, supporting HIPAA-compliant workloads without needing an Enterprise contract. Vercel ensures HIPAA compliance through technical safeguards, annual audits, and breach notifications. However, compliance is a shared responsibility; teams must manage security features and access. This update simplifies regulatory compliance for healthcare applications. #HIPAA #Vercel #HealthcareTech #DataSecurity #ProTeams 🏥🔒📊</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guide to the OWASP Top 10 for LLMs: Vulnerability mitigation with Elastic</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9470/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9470/</guid>
      <description>🌐 As industries adopt large language models (LLMs) and generative AI, new security challenges arise. The OWASP Top 10 for LLM Applications offers a framework to navigate these risks effectively. 🔍 Elastic&amp;rsquo;s unified platform combines observability and security analytics, providing comprehensive protection across the entire LLM application stack. ✨ This guide highlights how to use Elastic to mitigate vulnerabilities identified by OWASP, ensuring robust security in complex AI ecosystems&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September 2025 Patch Tuesday: Two Publicly Disclosed Zero-Days and Eight Critical Vulnerabilities Among 84 CVEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9506/</guid>
      <description>📅 In September 2025, Microsoft released a significant security update addressing 84 vulnerabilities. This includes two publicly disclosed zero-day vulnerabilities and eight critical ones. 🔍 The primary risks involve elevation of privilege (45% of patches), remote code execution (26%), and information disclosure (16%). Many critical vulnerabilities require user interaction to exploit. 🖥️ Microsoft Windows received the majority of the patches, totaling 58, followed by Extended Security Updates&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Fused into the Network to Protect OT at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9428/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9428/</guid>
      <description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest update enhances OT security by integrating asset visibility and secure remote access into industrial switches. This approach aims to eliminate security blind spots and reduce costs for organizations managing numerous sites and assets. With the new Cyber Vision offering, users gain comprehensive visibility and enforce zero-trust remote access seamlessly. This solution is now standard in Cisco&amp;rsquo;s IE3500 and IE9300 Rugged Series Switches, making OT security more accessible&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical npm supply chain attack response - September 8, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9447/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9447/</guid>
      <description>On September 8, 2025, a supply chain attack impacted 18 popular npm packages, including chalk, debug, and ansi-styles. These packages had malicious code aimed at intercepting cryptocurrency transactions in browsers. 🚨 Our security and engineering teams responded by identifying the affected projects and purging build caches. Affected customers have been notified with specific guidance. 🔍🔒 #CyberSecurity #npm #SupplyChainAttack #Cryptocurrency #Malware</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust in the Era of Agentic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9393/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9393/</guid>
      <description>Zero Trust is evolving to address the unique challenges posed by Agentic AI. 🤖 As AI agents utilize the same networks as users and apps, current security measures must adapt to ensure safe communication. Traditional security solutions have limitations, primarily focusing on intercepting traffic and analyzing data context. To protect these intelligent agents effectively, a shift towards enhanced zero trust frameworks is essential. 🔐 #ZeroTrust #AI #CyberSecurity #AgenticAI #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing trust, access, and control on Webflow Enterprise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9433/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9433/</guid>
      <description>Webflow Enterprise addresses the challenges of managing access in a world of numerous applications. With enterprises handling over 300 apps, effective Identity and Access Management (IAM) is crucial to prevent security risks. Webflow integrates IAM into its platform, ensuring secure user onboarding, authentication, and access monitoring. This holistic approach allows teams to collaborate freely while maintaining IT oversight and compliance. Automated provisioning and deprovisioning support&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corrective Action Update for the Heroku June 10th Outage</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7784/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7784/</guid>
      <description>🚨 &lt;strong&gt;Heroku Outage Update&lt;/strong&gt; 🚨 On June 10, 2025, Heroku experienced a service disruption due to an unintended system update. This affected not only platform performance but also the Heroku Status site, leading to confusion among users. 🛠️ On June 15, we outlined our remediation objectives, focusing on: - Immutable infrastructure - Improved communication resilience - Faster investigation and recovery 🔧 Key actions taken include halting unattended vendor upgrades, auditing system images, and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corrective Action Update for the Heroku June 10th Outage</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7910/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7910/</guid>
      <description>🚨 &lt;strong&gt;Heroku Outage Update&lt;/strong&gt; 🚨 On June 10, 2025, Heroku faced a service disruption due to an unintended system update by a vendor. The outage also affected the Heroku Status site, leading to communication challenges. 📅 A summary of our root cause analysis was shared on June 15. Key remediation goals include enhancing infrastructure resilience, improving communication channels, and speeding up recovery processes. 🔧 &lt;strong&gt;Current Actions:&lt;/strong&gt; - Permanent halt on unattended vendor OS upgrades - Audit of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Acquisition of MCP Defender Helps Meet Challenges of Securing the Agentic Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7786/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7786/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker, Inc. has acquired MCP Defender to enhance security for AI applications. As AI evolves rapidly, new security challenges arise for software development. 🔍 The current AI security landscape reflects early container adoption, marked by innovation but also uncertainty about risks. Organizations must now focus on real-time monitoring and dynamic threat detection. 🔒 Docker aims to embed security into AI infrastructure from the start, ensuring seamless integration into development&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Acquisition of MCP Defender Helps Meet Challenges of Securing the Agentic Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-8131/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-8131/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker, Inc. has announced its acquisition of MCP Defender to enhance security for AI applications. As AI technology evolves, so do the security challenges it presents. 🚧 Companies are urged to shift towards real-time monitoring and proactive threat detection to safeguard their AI infrastructure. Docker aims to integrate security into AI development from the start, ensuring a seamless experience for developers. 🔐 #Docker #AIsafety #Cybersecurity #TechNews #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starless: How we accidentally vanished our most popular GitHub repos</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-9382/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-9382/</guid>
      <description>In October 2024, a significant incident occurred where Elastic&amp;rsquo;s key public repositories on GitHub were mistakenly marked as private. This was due to automation changes aimed at enhancing internal source code security. The incident led to an outage for customers and highlighted the risks of making assumptions in automated processes. Elastic&amp;rsquo;s engineering teams are sharing insights from this experience to prevent future occurrences. Learn more about the importance of supply chain security and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing the unauthorized issuance of multiple TLS certificates for 1.1.1.1</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7750/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7750/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare has reported unauthorized TLS certificates issued for 1.1.1.1 by Fina CA without permission. These 12 certificates were issued between February 2024 and August 2025 and have since been revoked. While no evidence suggests malicious use, this incident highlights the importance of proper certificate issuance protocols. Fina CA stated the certificates were intended for internal testing. Cloudflare emphasizes the need for awareness around internet trust dynamics. 🔒🌐 #CyberSecurity #DNS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why secrets management is incomplete without secret scanning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7745/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7745/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Secrets management is vital for safeguarding API keys, passwords, and certificates. However, it often only covers known secrets, leaving gaps in security. 💻 Secrets can be scattered across code, pipelines, and tools, creating hidden risks. Recent research shows that leaked secrets can take 94 days to remediate, increasing vulnerability to attacks. 🔐 Secret scanning complements management by providing visibility and real-time detection of hidden secrets. This proactive approach integrates&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A developer&#39;s guide to building secure retail apps with GitLab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7741/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7741/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Retailers face unique security challenges as modern commerce expands. With mobile apps, AI, and IoT, each touchpoint increases the risk of vulnerabilities that can impact customer trust and revenue. Traditional security methods often fall short in this complex landscape. An integrated DevSecOps platform, like GitLab, embeds security into the development lifecycle, allowing teams to innovate while maintaining customer experience. Discover how to address these challenges effectively through&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 security wins from Booking.com&#39;s hybrid cloud migration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7701/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7701/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Booking.com has made significant strides in their hybrid cloud migration by enhancing security with HashiCorp Vault. They developed a unified secrets management system, allowing consistent access across various platforms, including AWS and GCP. This central security bridge mitigates risks of misconfigurations. By migrating to JWT authentication, they simplified their authentication processes, reducing complexity and improving oversight. Additionally, Vault&amp;rsquo;s secrets sync will provide&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat Investigation: Attempted Exploitation of Registration Server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7668/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7668/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Black Hat Conference Update 🚨 Recent investigations revealed attempted exploitation of the registration server at the Black Hat conference. Operating within the unique Security and Network Operations Center (NOC) environment, Cisco faces distinct challenges due to the conference&amp;rsquo;s focus on cybersecurity research and ethical hacking. 🔍 The NOC anticipates various activities that might appear suspicious elsewhere. The Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) policy complicates monitoring, emphasizing the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Value of PCAP in Firewall Investigations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7669/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7669/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The article highlights the importance of PCAP (packet capture) in firewall investigations, emphasizing its time-consuming nature. Key steps include finding a suitable platform, executing the capture, and analyzing large files. At Black Hat USA 2025, the ‘Endace PCAP Pivot’ feature enabled easier access to packet-level data, enhancing SOC analyst investigations significantly. 📊🔍 #CyberSecurity #PacketCapture #NetworkAnalysis #BlackHat2025 #SOCInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compliance Toolkit: AI-powered support for SMS compliance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7713/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7713/</guid>
      <description>Twilio&amp;rsquo;s new Compliance Toolkit leverages AI and machine learning to enhance SMS compliance. This tool proactively identifies and mitigates potential regulatory violations, helping businesses maintain compliance and avoid penalties. Explore how AI can support your compliance efforts! 📲🤖 #Compliance #AI #SMS #Twilio #Regulations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What security leaders need to know about mergers and acquisitions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7681/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7681/</guid>
      <description>Mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) present unique security challenges for teams. The integration of two companies involves managing devices, applications, and data, often exposing serious vulnerabilities. Notable cases, like Verizon and Yahoo, highlight the consequences of security oversights that can lead to costly data breaches. Due diligence is crucial. Security leaders should be involved from the start, focusing on identifying risks through thorough discovery and validation processes&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 tips for credential management across multi-cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7645/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7645/</guid>
      <description>Managing credentials in multi-cloud environments can be complex. Lino Telera from InfoCert shares five essential tips to streamline secret management: 1️⃣ Use dynamic secrets instead of static API keys to minimize risk. 2️⃣ Automate runtime secret management to eliminate manual errors. 3️⃣ Implement workspace sandboxing to enforce zero trust principles. These practices help improve security and efficiency in development. #CredentialManagement #CloudSecurity #DevOps #InfoSec #HashiCorp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The impact of the Salesloft Drift breach on Cloudflare and our customers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7648/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7648/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Last week, Cloudflare confirmed that it was affected by the Salesloft Drift breach, where an advanced threat actor accessed Salesforce data, impacting Cloudflare and many companies. The breach compromised customer contact information and support case data, including sensitive details. Cloudflare has urged customers to rotate any credentials shared through this channel. Immediate actions were taken, including securing the environment and investigating the incident. All affected customers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API Keys and AI Agents: Four Common Risks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7639/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7639/</guid>
      <description>Building AI agents can be thrilling, but it comes with serious security risks when using API keys. 🚨 Pasting keys everywhere can lead to exposure through public repositories, logs, or client-side applications. This increases the chance of automated attacks, especially if the keys have broad permissions. 🔑 Managing these keys is crucial to ensure data security and compliance, particularly in regulated industries. Consider solutions like Auth0&amp;rsquo;s Token Vault to safeguard your integrations. 🔒 #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Backdoor in TACACS&#43;: Why Full-Session Encryption Matters More Than Ever</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7607/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7607/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Recent cyber threats highlight the risks of weak TACACS+ encryption. Attackers exploited vulnerabilities, targeting network operators to steal credentials and blend in as legitimate admins. By harvesting TACACS+ traffic, they captured sensitive data, allowing unauthorized access and evading detection. Cisco ISE with TLS 1.3 and Duo MFA offers solutions to enhance security and close these backdoors. 🔒🛡️ #Cybersecurity #TACACS #DataProtection #CiscoISE #MFA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure AI at Machine Speed: Defending the Growing Attack Surface</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7658/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7658/</guid>
      <description>As AI integrates into various business functions, it significantly broadens the enterprise attack surface. 📈 Adversaries are increasingly targeting AI tools and their supporting infrastructure, exploiting vulnerabilities in APIs and models. Many organizations struggle with visibility and lack adequate protection for these evolving threats. 🔍 To tackle these challenges, innovative, real-time security solutions tailored for AI are essential. The CrowdStrike Falcon® platform offers insights on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Exposed LLM Servers: A Shodan Case Study on Ollama</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7583/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7583/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A recent case study reveals over 1,100 exposed Ollama LLM servers, with 20% hosting open models. This highlights critical security vulnerabilities in LLM deployments. 🔍 The study utilized Shodan to identify these unsecured endpoints, emphasizing the need for stronger security measures. 🛡️ As LLMs become more popular, addressing these gaps is essential for protecting sensitive data. #CyberSecurity #LLM #DataProtection #Ollama #Shodan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Update: Multiple vulnerabilities in Next.js</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-30-7551/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-30-7551/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Security Alert for Next.js Users 🚨 Recent vulnerabilities have been disclosed affecting Next.js applications, including issues related to arbitrary file downloads and cache poisoning. Netlify&amp;rsquo;s engineering team confirms that sites hosted on their platform are not vulnerable to multiple threats. However, if using the next/image component with protected sources, caution is advised. To ensure security, it is recommended to upgrade to the latest Next.js versions and enable automatic updates for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating 70% of Dependency &amp; Vulnerability Management with Renovate and CI/CD</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7556/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 23:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7556/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in security automation at Salesforce! Sai Saketh Nakkina and his team transformed vulnerability management for AI features on the Agentforce platform. By automating 70% of the process with Renovate and CI/CD, they significantly reduced manual responses to vulnerabilities. Their mission focuses on maintaining secure ML pipelines and delivering AI features efficiently while ensuring platform integrity. This approach addresses security threats and enhances customer trust&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-55173</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7555/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7555/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A vulnerability (CVE-2025-55173) affecting Next.js Image Optimization has been identified. It impacts versions prior to v15.4.5 and v14.2.31, allowing attacker-controlled external image servers to trigger arbitrary file downloads. This could lead to phishing and social engineering attacks. A patch was released on July 29th, 2025, addressing this issue for Vercel customers. For more details, check the GitHub Advisory and Next.js Release Notes. #CyberSecurity #NextJS #Vulnerability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-57752</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7553/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7553/</guid>
      <description>A vulnerability, CVE-2025-57752, has been identified in Next.js Image Optimization affecting versions prior to v15.4.5 and v14.2.31. It involved cache poisoning, risking unauthorized access to sensitive images. The issue arose when API routes returned images based on headers, leading to potential disclosure of user-specific content. The vulnerability has been resolved in the latest versions, ensuring that request headers are not forwarded to image endpoints. For more details, refer to the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-57822</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7554/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7554/</guid>
      <description>A recent vulnerability, CVE-2025-57822, has been identified in Next.js Middleware, affecting versions before v14.2.32 and v15.4.7. This flaw allowed for Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) risks due to misconfigured NextResponse.next() usage. Applications that reflected user request headers could unintentionally allow servers to make requests to harmful destinations. A patch was released on August 25, 2025, to protect Vercel customers. For those unable to upgrade, it is vital to adhere to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for the worst: Our core database failover test</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7485/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7485/</guid>
      <description>On July 24, 2025, we conducted a successful failover test of our core control-plane database from Azure West US to East US 2. This exercise confirmed our disaster recovery plans in real-world conditions. All control-plane traffic was tested, ensuring stability without any customer impact. While preview and development traffic were affected, our production CDN traffic remained unaffected across 19 regions. The operation highlighted our commitment to resilience, achieving zero downtime and no&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure by Design: A Shift-Left Approach with Testcontainers, Docker Scout, and Hardened Images</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7465/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7465/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s software development landscape, speed should not compromise security. 🛡️ This article discusses a shift-left approach using tools like Testcontainers and Docker to enhance security early in the development lifecycle. It highlights how developers can conduct reliable integration tests while maintaining high quality. A practical example features a Node.js Movie Catalog API, demonstrating how Testcontainers can streamline testing against a PostgreSQL database. 📦 Learn how modern&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Approach to Data Exfiltration Protection on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7446/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7446/</guid>
      <description>Data exfiltration poses a significant security risk for organizations. A recent article outlines a comprehensive framework for protecting against unauthorized data movement on Databricks. The recommendations focus on unified strategies to enhance data security and prevent breaches. Implementing these measures can help safeguard sensitive information effectively. 🔒🛡️ #DataSecurity #Databricks #CyberSecurity #DataProtection #InformationSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>s1ngularity: supply chain attack in Nx packages</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7486/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7486/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A supply chain attack has targeted the Nx package in the npm registry. Malicious versions were published using a stolen npm token, leading to potential exfiltration of developer credentials. 🔍 The Nx team quickly removed the compromised packages, but Vercel customers are generally safe unless specific conditions were met. 👉 For detailed information, visit the GitHub advisory from the Nx team. Stay vigilant! #SupplyChainAttack #CyberSecurity #NxPackages #Vercel #DeveloperSafety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Ahead of the HIPAA Security Rule Update With Secure Workload</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7193/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7193/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for Healthcare Organizations! 🚨 On January 6, 2025, the Office of Civil Rights will introduce new cybersecurity requirements as part of the HIPAA Security Rule Update. This will shift the focus from reactive measures to a risk-based approach to enhance cybersecurity in healthcare. The update aims to strengthen the protection of electronic personal health information (ePHI) and address the increasing number of cyberattacks. Organizations must prepare to implement effective&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices for Securing Generative AI with SASE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7241/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7241/</guid>
      <description>🚀 As businesses adopt Generative AI, Security and IT leaders face new challenges. Executives push for quick implementation, while teams must create effective AI Security Strategies. 🔒 Cloudflare’s SASE architecture offers a solution, integrating networking and security for secure access to corporate resources. Their platform supports safe AI usage without hindering innovation. 🛡️ Recent enhancements include shadow AI reporting, confidence scoring for AI providers, and protections against&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Block unsafe prompts targeting your LLM endpoints with Firewall for AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7240/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7240/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloudflare has enhanced its AI security suite with the introduction of unsafe content moderation through Firewall for AI. This new feature aims to protect AI applications from malicious prompts that could compromise sensitive data or user trust. 🔒 With this integration, customers can now detect and block harmful prompts at the network level without modifying their application code. Firewall for AI supports various models, ensuring consistent protection across all platforms. 🛡️ This update&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT, Claude, &amp; Gemini security scanning with Cloudflare CASB</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7239/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7239/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloudflare CASB now offers security scanning for generative AI tools like ChatGPT, Claude, and Gemini. Organizations can connect their accounts to detect misconfigurations, data exposure, and compliance risks quickly and without additional software. This integration enhances visibility and helps IT teams manage the security challenges of AI adoption effectively. 🔍 #Cloudflare #CyberSecurity #GenerativeAI #DataProtection #Compliance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Cloudflare Application Confidence Score For AI Applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7238/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7238/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Cloudflare has introduced Application Confidence Scores for Gen AI applications to help businesses assess risks associated with shadow IT. These scores will aid security, IT, and legal teams in evaluating third-party applications without needing extensive individual audits. This initiative aims to balance productivity with security, promoting smarter controls rather than blanket bans. Stay informed about the new features in Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s AI Security Posture Management within the Cloudflare&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Cisco’s front lines with AI-powered Email Threat Defense and Splunk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7198/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7198/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is enhancing email security with a layered approach using AI and Splunk. 💻✉️ Facing over 326 million emails quarterly, Cisco recognized the need to defend against phishing and malware while improving user productivity. The FBI reported a staggering rise in email cyberattacks, highlighting the urgency for robust security measures. By integrating Cisco Email Threat Defense with Splunk’s analytics, Cisco aims to provide comprehensive protection against evolving threats. #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fragmented SSE Is a Risk You Can’t Afford</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7200/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7200/</guid>
      <description>Fragmented security solutions can create significant risks. Many organizations rely on multiple vendors for their security needs, leading to complex systems that may leave gaps in protection. Cisco Secure Access addresses this issue by providing a unified architecture. This ensures consistent policy enforcement regardless of where users connect from, enhancing overall security. No more silos or inconsistent access experiences! #Cybersecurity #Cisco #SecureAccess #SSE #DataProtection 🔐🌐💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and security at Black Hat: 5 key takeaways from a security expert panel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7251/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7251/</guid>
      <description>🌐 At Black Hat, security leaders discussed the rise of AI in cybersecurity, highlighting key challenges and strategies. 1️⃣ Zero trust principles need to evolve to include AI agents. 2️⃣ Cybercriminals are increasingly using AI for more sophisticated attacks. 3️⃣ Many organizations lack visibility into their AI usage, leading to risks. 4️⃣ Business demand for AI is outpacing security preparedness. 5️⃣ AI can enhance security but also introduces new vulnerabilities. Effective governance is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clickjacking: What it means for 1Password users</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7252/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7252/</guid>
      <description>🔒 1Password has released an important update (version 8.11.7) addressing clickjacking, a technique that can trick users into autofilling sensitive information. This vulnerability does not put 1Password systems at risk, but the update provides users with better control by introducing confirmation alerts for autofill actions. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to update to the latest version and keep autofill enabled for enhanced security. Stay safe online! 🛡️ #1Password #CyberSecurity #Clickjacking #DataProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret sprawl is costing you more than you think</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7172/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7172/</guid>
      <description>🛡️ Secret sprawl is significantly impacting organizations, costing them millions annually through lost productivity and increased security overhead. Developers often waste time on preventable secret management tasks, leading to an estimated $936,000 annual loss for a typical 50-person team. This includes hunting down exposed credentials and managing compromised keys. Moreover, security teams face a burden from false positives, costing around $520,000 each year due to unnecessary&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking the Unseen: Your Guide to Taming Shadow AI with Cloudflare One</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6345/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6345/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Concerned about data leaks from unsanctioned AI use? The rise of &amp;ldquo;Shadow AI&amp;rdquo; poses a significant risk as employees unknowingly expose sensitive information through AI tools. Traditional security measures often miss these interactions. Cloudflare One offers a solution with its Shadow IT Report, providing visibility into AI application usage and helping organizations manage potential risks effectively. Stay informed and secure! 🔍💻 #CyberSecurity #ShadowAI #Cloudflare #DataProtection #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the ban: A better way to secure generative AI applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6348/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6348/</guid>
      <description>Generative AI is transforming workplace productivity, but it also poses significant data security risks. 🛡️ Many employees inadvertently share sensitive information with AI tools. Recent incidents highlight the consequences of this, including private chats being indexed online. To address these risks, Cloudflare introduces AI prompt protection, part of its Data Loss Prevention (DLP) system. This feature helps organizations manage AI use while securing sensitive data. AI prompt protection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect Your Access Tokens with DPoP (Demonstrating Proof of Possession)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6332/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6332/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Protect your applications with DPoP! This article explains how Demonstrating Proof-of-Possession enhances security for access tokens by ensuring they can only be used by the intended application. Unlike traditional bearer tokens, DPoP binds tokens to a specific client instance, mitigating risks of token theft. Learn about the benefits, security threats it addresses, and how to implement DPoP in your applications using Auth0. #Security #DPoP #OAuth2 #AccessTokens #ApplicationSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing the Future: How Databricks Powers Financial Services</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6309/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6309/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving financial services landscape, data security and compliance are vital for growth. Databricks enables financial institutions to build resilience and accelerate innovation while ensuring adherence to regulations. This approach supports the safe use of data and AI technologies in the sector. Understanding these elements is crucial for navigating future challenges. 📊🔐✨ #DataSecurity #FinancialServices #Innovation #Compliance #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why default secret detection rules don&#39;t work (and how to fix it)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6312/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6312/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Many organizations face challenges with default secret detection rules. Studies indicate that up to 80% of security alerts are false positives, leading to overlooked real threats. 📊 Generic detection tools often miss unique credentials like proprietary API keys. This can result in significant security incidents if not addressed. 💡 HCP Vault Radar offers a solution with customizable detection patterns and severity-based workflows. This approach helps teams focus on genuine threats while&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Financial Services Demands a New Trust Layer: Why Identity Security Is the Answer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5100/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5100/</guid>
      <description>As AI transforms financial services, new risks arise with autonomous AI agents accessing sensitive data. Traditional identity security is becoming insufficient. Financial institutions must now consider not just who the user is, but also what operates on their behalf. A shift to advanced identity solutions, like Auth for GenAI, is essential for secure innovation. 🚀🔐 Explore more insights from the Auth0 Customer Identity Trends Report 2025. #AI #FinancialServices #IdentitySecurity #Innovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MURKY PANDA: A Trusted-Relationship Threat in the Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-7438/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-7438/</guid>
      <description>🚨 MURKY PANDA is a China-nexus adversary targeting various sectors in North America, including government and technology. Since late 2024, they have used trusted-relationship compromises in the cloud, showcasing deep knowledge of cloud environments. Their tactics include exploiting vulnerabilities and deploying malware like CloudedHope. 💻 CrowdStrike has tracked MURKY PANDA&amp;rsquo;s operations, which are driven by intelligence-collection goals, often resulting in the exfiltration of sensitive&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing private data at scale with differentially private partition selection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5180/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5180/</guid>
      <description>🔒 New algorithms are advancing user privacy in data sharing through differentially private partition selection. This approach allows for safe sharing of large datasets, crucial for AI and machine learning innovation. It ensures individual contributions remain confidential by adding controlled noise during selection. Parallel algorithms enhance efficiency, enabling the processing of vast datasets while maintaining robust privacy guarantees. Explore more in the publication “Scalable Private&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic’s capabilities in the world of Zero Trust operations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5058/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5058/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exploring Zero Trust Operations with Elastic The article discusses the essential pillars of Zero Trust (ZT) based on the US Department of Defense&amp;rsquo;s framework. Key elements include user identity, device characteristics, network integrity, data protection, application vulnerabilities, and automation. Challenges exist in implementing ZT, such as system complexity, operational speed, and fragility from disparate integrations. Elastic’s Search AI Platform is highlighted for its role in enhancing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Platform Prevents COOKIE SPIDER’s SHAMOS Delivery on macOS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-7439/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-7439/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The CrowdStrike Falcon® platform has successfully blocked a sophisticated malware campaign by COOKIE SPIDER targeting macOS users. Between June and August 2025, over 300 customer environments were at risk due to the SHAMOS variant of the Atomic macOS Stealer. This malware was distributed through malvertising, tricking users into executing a harmful installation command. The campaign highlighted the use of one-line installation commands, which can bypass security checks, raising concerns&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRLite: Fast, private, and comprehensive certificate revocation checking in Firefox</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5048/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5048/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Firefox has launched CRLite, the first fast and private certificate revocation checking system that protects user browsing activity. This new mechanism downloads a compact list of revoked certificates, making checking efficient and reliable. Starting with Firefox 137, CRLite enhances security while disabling the less private OCSP method in future updates. #Firefox #CRLite #Cybersecurity #Privacy #WebDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Findings Report From the SOC at RSAC™ 2025 Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5286/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5286/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Exciting updates from the RSAC™ 2025 Conference! 🚨 The Findings Report from the Security Operations Center reveals key insights into network security. Cisco and Endace monitored the Moscone Center&amp;rsquo;s wireless network, showcasing how an open network operates. The SOC utilized advanced tools, including the EndaceProbe packet capture platform and Cisco Security Cloud, to enhance security measures. Learn more about these innovations and watch the session replay! #RSAC2025 #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to enhance Agent2Agent (A2A) security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5032/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5032/</guid>
      <description>🔒 The Agent2Agent (A2A) protocol by Google facilitates communication between AI agents, allowing seamless interaction across different vendors. Each agent can serve as a client or remote agent depending on the context. 🌐 Communication involves retrieving an Agent Card, which contains essential details for task execution. Security measures such as HTTPS and authentication protocols are crucial for protecting these interactions. 🛡️ Developers implementing A2A should remain vigilant about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic response to blog ‘EDR 0-Day Vulnerability’</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5059/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5059/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Elastic’s Security team has responded to claims of a vulnerability in Elastic Defend. After comprehensive investigation, no evidence was found to support the alleged bypass of EDR monitoring or remote code execution. The demonstrations provided were not from unprivileged processes. Elastic remains committed to transparency and encourages researchers to share any valid findings at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:security@elastic.co&#34;&gt;security@elastic.co&lt;/a&gt;. Updates will be provided as necessary. #CyberSecurity #Elastic #Vulnerability #EDR #InfoSec</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulatory and Compliance Corner - August &amp; September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5138/</guid>
      <description>🌍 This month&amp;rsquo;s Regulatory and Compliance Corner highlights significant telecom policy changes worldwide. Key updates include new regulations aimed at enhancing data privacy and security for users. Additionally, several countries are revising rules to promote competition in the telecom sector. Stay informed about these important shifts in the industry! 📡✉️ #Telecom #Regulations #DataPrivacy #IndustryInsights #Compliance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker @ Black Hat 2025: CVEs have everyone’s attention, here’s the path forward</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5119/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At Black Hat 2025, CVEs were a hot topic, highlighting the need for effective vulnerability management. The focus is shifting from just scanning to eliminating security debt before it enters the software supply chain. Hardened images and compliance-ready tools are becoming essential. Key themes included the importance of secure starting points, customization for enterprises, and the demand for FedRAMP-ready solutions. Thanks to everyone who joined the Docker community at our booth and the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A practitioner’s view on how Docker enables security by default and makes developers work better</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5120/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5120/</guid>
      <description>Docker Captains share their experiences on how Docker enhances security and developer efficiency. Security in distributed systems is crucial, and Docker provides a strong framework for developers and security teams. Key areas of focus include managing artifacts, code quality, and vulnerability management. For more insights on becoming a Docker Captain, visit the Docker Captains’ website! 🛠️🔒 #Docker #Security #DevOps #ContainerSecurity #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling On-Prem Security at Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5053/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5053/</guid>
      <description>Palantir emphasizes security in its on-premises solutions, tailoring approaches for various environments. 🌐 The Insight tool enhances security by automating checks on server configurations, ensuring compliance with rigorous standards. It allows users to run scans and generate reports easily. 📊 With the integration of Foundry and Apollo, Palantir streamlines the review process, improving visibility and collaboration. 🔍 Learn more about how Palantir maintains security across thousands of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MadeYouReset: An HTTP/2 vulnerability thwarted by Rapid Reset mitigations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5132/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5132/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A new HTTP/2 vulnerability named MadeYouReset (CVE-2025-8671) has been disclosed by researchers at Tel Aviv University. This denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability affects unpatched HTTP/2 servers, potentially leading to resource exhaustion. If you use Cloudflare for DDoS mitigation, your systems are already protected. MadeYouReset exploits server-sent stream resets, similar to the previously identified Rapid Reset vulnerability. Implementations are encouraged to monitor and limit the use of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The GitHub Prompt Injection Data Heist</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5122/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5122/</guid>
      <description>🚨 In Part 3 of the MCP Horror Stories series, we explore the GitHub Prompt Injection Data Heist. This incident highlights critical vulnerabilities in AI security, revealing how attackers can manipulate AI assistants through malicious GitHub issues. When developers request help, they risk exposing sensitive data from locked repositories. Learn how these attacks exploit broad GitHub tokens and bypass traditional access controls. Docker’s MCP Toolkit offers solutions to protect against such&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locking Down the Fleet: Encryption at Rest and Disk Isolation at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5015/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Managing encryption at rest and ensuring disk isolation for numerous stateful workloads presents significant challenges. In a recent article, the focus is on how effective logical volume management was implemented to secure a large fleet of servers. This approach enhances data security while maintaining operational efficiency. #DataSecurity #Encryption #LogicalVolumeManagement #TechInnovation #CyberSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to secure your Jenkins pipeline with Red Hat Advanced Developer Suite</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4994/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 07:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4994/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your Jenkins pipeline security with Red Hat Advanced Developer Suite! 🔒 This suite integrates cryptographic signing, SBOM validation, and runtime enforcement to ensure a secure CI/CD process. Each stage—from commit to deployment—now includes proof of compliance. Key features include: - Trusted Artifact Signer for image signing. - Profile Analyzer for risk assessment. - Advanced Cluster Security for policy enforcement. Learn how to keep your deployment velocity while lowering risks! 🚀🔧&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against SCATTERED SPIDER with Falcon Next-Gen SIEM</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7440/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7440/</guid>
      <description>🚨 SCATTERED SPIDER continues to pose a significant threat, launching attacks on organizations globally since 2022. This adversary uses refined social engineering tactics to compromise sensitive information. 🔍 CrowdStrike&amp;rsquo;s Falcon Next-Gen SIEM offers real-time detection across various domains, enhancing defenses against these evolving threats. It integrates third-party telemetry for improved visibility and tailored protection. 📊 The blog details key phases of SCATTERED SPIDER’s kill chain and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Trust in AI: A Developer&#39;s Identity Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5009/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5009/</guid>
      <description>🔐 In the evolving landscape of AI, security is essential for building user trust. Developers face challenges like signup attacks, account takeovers, and poor password hygiene, which can erode confidence in digital platforms. The Auth0 Customer Identity Trends Report 2025 reveals that 46.1% of new registrations may be fraudulent, while 16.9% of login attempts show malicious intent. To foster trust, developers must prioritize robust identity management, as 74% of users value a company’s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why financial services choose single-tenant SaaS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5066/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5066/</guid>
      <description>Financial institutions face unique challenges with shared infrastructure, which heightens systemic risks. As highlighted by JPMorgan Chase&amp;rsquo;s CISO, incidents on multi-tenant platforms can lead to widespread disruptions. GitLab Dedicated offers a solution, providing isolated environments for development while ensuring compliance and security. This approach enables institutions to manage risks more effectively, ensuring their source code is treated as a critical asset. Learn more about how&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating AI agent solutions for warehouse data access and security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4966/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 22:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4966/</guid>
      <description>Meta is evolving its data warehouse to enhance productivity and security for both human users and AI agents. 🤖🔒 We are developing AI agents to streamline data access requests, helping users find the data they need while assisting data owners in maintaining security. Guardrails, such as auditing and feedback systems, are also being implemented to ensure safe operations. As the scale and complexity of data access grow, our focus is on minimizing security risks while improving efficiency. This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software provenance: Why visibility into your software supply chain matters</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4954/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4954/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Understanding software provenance is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s complex software supply chain. This concept emphasizes tracking the creation, modification, and ownership of software artifacts throughout their lifecycle. As cyber threats rise, maintaining visibility is essential for security and compliance. Challenges include limited visibility, pipeline complexity, and compliance risks. Organizations must prioritize comprehensive documentation to address these issues. Stay informed and secure! 🔒🛡️&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Access Control in the Era of AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4945/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4945/</guid>
      <description>AI agents are evolving, performing complex tasks and making API calls autonomously. This shift poses new security challenges, particularly in access control. The article discusses the history of AI agents and highlights the risks they bring, emphasizing the need for fine-grained access control. Traditional models like RBAC and ABAC struggle under the dynamic nature of AI systems, often requiring additional engineering for effective management. Explore how to adapt access control as AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passing the Security Vibe Check: The Dangers of Vibe Coding</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4951/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4951/</guid>
      <description>In a recent article from Databricks, the concept of &amp;ldquo;vibe coding&amp;rdquo; is examined in relation to software security. The piece discusses how developers often rely on intuition or &amp;ldquo;vibes&amp;rdquo; when assessing security risks, which can lead to vulnerabilities. It emphasizes the importance of structured security practices over subjective judgments. Understanding these risks is crucial for building safer software systems. 🔒💻 #CyberSecurity #SoftwareDevelopment #VibeCoding #TechInsights #DataProtection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>August 2025 Patch Tuesday: One Publicly Disclosed Zero-Day and 13 Critical Vulnerabilities Among 107 CVEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7443/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7443/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Microsoft has released its August 2025 Patch Tuesday updates, addressing 107 vulnerabilities. Among these are one publicly disclosed zero-day and 13 critical vulnerabilities. The most common risk types involve elevation of privilege (39%), remote code execution (33%), and information disclosure (15%). Windows received the largest share of patches with 67 updates. #PatchTuesday #CyberSecurity #MicrosoftUpdates #Vulnerabilities #InfoSec</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federation Platform and Privacy Waves: How Meta distributes compliance-related tasks at scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4855/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4855/</guid>
      <description>Meta is enhancing privacy compliance with its Federation Platform and Privacy Waves program. These tools manage compliance tasks effectively and ensure accountability across teams. 🌐 The Federation Platform breaks down compliance initiatives into manageable tasks, while Privacy Waves organizes these tasks into monthly batches for better planning. 📅 Together, they improve user data protection and streamline operations, managing over 100,000 tasks annually. This approach is expanding into&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise of intelligent banking: Unifying fraud, security, and compliance in the era of AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4835/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4835/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving financial landscape, security, compliance, and customer trust are interconnected. The IDC Spotlight report, sponsored by Elastic and AWS, highlights the need for financial institutions to adopt AI-powered platforms that unify fraud prevention, cybersecurity, and regulatory compliance. As threats grow more sophisticated, institutions must move beyond siloed risk functions to ensure operational resilience and regulatory readiness. This shift is critical for maintaining customer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Healthcare Is AI-Powered and Secure: How CIAM Builds Trust</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4850/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4850/</guid>
      <description>The integration of AI in healthcare is reshaping the industry, promising enhanced efficiency and personalized treatment. However, the security of sensitive patient data is a major concern. Customer Identity and Access Management (CIAM) solutions play a crucial role in ensuring that only authorized users access AI systems, supporting compliance and security. As the healthcare IAM market is projected to grow significantly, establishing trust becomes vital. Patients prioritize trust over&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The Supply Chain Attack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4763/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4763/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Part 2 of our MCP Horror Stories series highlights a critical supply chain attack affecting AI development environments. The article discusses CVE-2025-6514, where a vulnerability in mcp-remote led to credential compromise and remote code execution. This incident impacted nearly 437,000 environments, including major platforms like Cloudflare and Hugging Face. Learn about the attack techniques used, the importance of containerized MCP servers, and practical steps to secure your AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Hackers Exploit AI’s Problem-Solving Instincts</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4717/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4717/</guid>
      <description>🚨 As AI models become more advanced, they face new vulnerabilities. Researchers highlight how hackers exploit these systems by manipulating their problem-solving instincts. 🔍 The article discusses the evolution of attack techniques from text-based prompt injections to sophisticated multimodal reasoning attacks. These new methods target how AI merges inputs like text, images, and audio. 🔒 Securing AI requires a shift in focus from just input/output layers to the reasoning architecture itself&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 key questions about designing a secure cloud environment</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4708/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4708/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Designing a secure cloud environment is crucial for organizations to avoid risks and enhance innovation. Here are 10 key questions leaders should ask their teams: 1. Do we have full visibility into our cloud infrastructure? 2. Are we embedding security throughout the development lifecycle? 3. Can we enforce security policies at scale? These discussions are essential for reducing risk and maintaining compliance. 🌐 For more insights on cloud security, check the full article. #CloudSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build trust in your CI/CD pipelines with OpenShift Pipelines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4691/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4691/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Red Hat OpenShift Pipelines provide a cloud-native CI/CD solution using Tekton. This article highlights the use of OpenShift sandboxed containers, which isolate workloads in virtual machines, enhancing security for tasks needing elevated privileges. 🌐 For untrusted environments, OpenShift confidential containers (CoCo) further protect pipeline data by running containers in isolated hardware enclaves, safeguarding against admin access. 💡 The integration of these technologies ensures secure,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing AI Agents: Retail&#39;s Next Big Challenge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4706/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4706/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence is transforming the retail industry, offering new ways to engage customers and streamline operations. 🚀 While 90% of retailers are already using or evaluating AI, concerns about data privacy and security remain significant. 60% of retailers worry about data privacy, highlighting the need for secure AI adoption. 🔒 Current AI applications include hyper-personalized shopping experiences, virtual try-ons, and real-time customer service assistance. The future holds even&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The security principles guiding 1Password’s approach to AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4745/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4745/</guid>
      <description>AI is reshaping our work landscape, bringing both opportunities and responsibilities, especially in security. 1Password emphasizes building trustworthy AI while maintaining core values of privacy and transparency. Key principles include: 🔒 Keeping secrets secure through strong encryption. 📜 Ensuring predictable authorization processes. 📊 Maintaining audit trails for AI actions. 1Password is committed to integrating AI securely and effectively. #AI #CyberSecurity #1Password #DataPrivacy #Trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating FedRAMP Compliance with Docker Hardened Images</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4147/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4147/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Navigating FedRAMP compliance can be costly and time-consuming, often taking 12-18 months and over $2 million. Competitors are already moving ahead while you manage security controls. Docker has introduced Hardened Images (DHI) to streamline this process. These pre-configured images support FIPS 140 compliance, simplifying cryptographic requirements. With DHI, companies can reduce compliance costs and speed up time-to-market for cloud services. 💻🔒 #FedRAMP #Docker #CloudCompliance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Time to Evolve Authentication Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4146/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4146/</guid>
      <description>Identity-based attacks are on the rise, making strong authentication security necessary. Okta emphasizes the need to enhance identity security through initiatives like the Secure Identity Commitment. Key steps include adopting phishing-resistant methods, avoiding weak authentication, and implementing Multi-factor Authentication (MFA). Tailoring authentication requirements dynamically is crucial for balancing security and user experience. For developers, leveraging Identity Providers and using&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAPI 2.0: The Future of API Security for High-Stakes Customer Interactions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4133/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4133/</guid>
      <description>🚀 FAPI 2.0 is redefining API security for critical customer interactions. Originally created for financial services, it now offers advanced protections applicable across industries. This new version focuses on enhancing end-to-end security and privacy for sensitive actions like payments and data sharing. Key benefits include clear specifications, thorough conformance tests, and a standards-based approach for better security. Discover how FAPI 2.0 can help protect your organization. 🔒🌐&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab uncovers Bittensor theft campaign via PyPI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4678/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4678/</guid>
      <description>🚨 GitLab&amp;rsquo;s Vulnerability Research team has uncovered a cryptocurrency theft campaign targeting the Bittensor ecosystem via typosquatted Python packages on PyPI. Multiple malicious packages mimicked legitimate ones, published within a 25-minute window. These were designed to steal funds during staking operations, bypassing user confirmations and draining wallets silently. The attackers used a typosquatting strategy, exploiting common errors to increase the likelihood of installation. GitLab is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify access reviews with Trelica by 1Password</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4679/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4679/</guid>
      <description>Managing access in today&amp;rsquo;s SaaS environment is challenging for organizations. Each time an employee joins or leaves, IT and security teams must adjust permissions to maintain security and compliance. 🔒 Access reviews are essential for verifying user access and meeting compliance standards like SOC 2 and ISO 27001. However, traditional methods often rely on spreadsheets, leading to incomplete processes and errors. 📊 Trelica by 1Password simplifies access reviews with automated workflows, a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone’s a Snowflake: Designing Hardened Image Processes for the Real World</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2015/</guid>
      <description>Hardened container images and distroless software are gaining traction among startups and established companies. While they promise a smaller attack surface and operational simplicity, challenges arise in real-world applications. The unique needs of development teams often clash with rigid security measures, leading to frustration and workarounds. This &amp;lsquo;Snowflake Problem&amp;rsquo; highlights how no two environments are the same, complicating the balance between usability and security. Flexibility is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Auth0 Mitigates OWASP’s Agentic AI Threats</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-1965/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-1965/</guid>
      <description>🌐 AI-powered agents are transforming industries, but they also bring significant security risks. Auth0 addresses these challenges highlighted by OWASP&amp;rsquo;s recent report on Agentic AI threats. Key risks include data breaches and regulatory non-compliance, which can erode customer trust. Traditional security measures often fall short for autonomous AI. Organizations must implement robust security from the start when developing GenAI applications. 🔐 #CyberSecurity #AI #GenAI #Auth0 #OWASP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Questions: What You Should Really Be Asking Your Hardened Image Provider Before You Press the Buy Button</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2017/</guid>
      <description>When considering hardened image providers, it’s essential to go beyond buzzwords like &amp;ldquo;zero-CVE.&amp;rdquo; Understanding their update and patch management processes is crucial. Ask how quickly they can respond to serious vulnerabilities and their SLAs on updates. Also, inquire about their modification processes. Knowing how to adjust images without compromising security is vital for maintaining your workflows. For more insights on essential questions to ask, check the full article. 🔍💻 #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perplexity is using stealth, undeclared crawlers to evade website no-crawl directives</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2077/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2077/</guid>
      <description>Perplexity, an AI-powered answer engine, is reportedly using stealth tactics to bypass website no-crawl directives. They modify user agents and change IPs to continue crawling despite explicit blocks. This behavior contradicts the trust-based principles of the internet, which emphasize transparency and adherence to website preferences. As a result, Perplexity has been de-listed as a verified bot and is facing new blocking measures. #Crawling #AI #WebSecurity #DataPrivacy #TechNews 🕵️‍♂️🔍🚫</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>v0: vibe coding, securely</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4165/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4165/</guid>
      <description>Vibe coding is transforming software development, allowing rapid prototyping with tools like v0. Anthropic&amp;rsquo;s CEO indicates that in just 3-6 months, 90% of code may be AI-generated. However, this speed can lead to significant risks. A recent incident involved a viral app that leaked 72,000 selfies and IDs due to misconfigured settings, emphasizing the need for security measures. #VibeCoding #SoftwareDevelopment #CyberSecurity #AI #TechNews 🚀🔒📱</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability disclosure on SSL for SaaS v1 (Managed CNAME)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2078/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2078/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare has announced a vulnerability disclosure for its SSL for SaaS v1 (Managed CNAME) product, identified through its bug bounty program. Despite deprecating this version in 2021, some customers have yet to migrate to SSL for SaaS v2. Cloudflare is working to assist these remaining clients in the transition. The architecture of SSL for SaaS v1 posed security risks due to its reliance on IP-based routing without domain ownership verification, leading to potential vulnerabilities. 🌐🔒&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Agentic AI: How Semantic Prompt Injections Bypass AI Guardrails</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-220/</guid>
      <description>Prompt injection remains a significant threat to AI systems, particularly with the rise of multimodal and agentic AI. 🛡️ NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s AI Red Team simulates real-world attacks to identify vulnerabilities in these advanced systems, emphasizing the need for cross-functional solutions. Their recent research introduces a new category of multimodal prompt injection using symbolic visual inputs, like emoji sequences. 🔍 This shift highlights the importance of adapting security strategies from input&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The Security Issues Threatening AI Infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2019/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New Series Alert: MCP Horror Stories! 🚨 The first issue dives into the security vulnerabilities within the Model Context Protocol (MCP) ecosystem. MCP enables AI agents to communicate with various services, but this connectivity brings significant security risks. While MCP aims to streamline integrations, it has raised concerns about potential data breaches and system compromises due to malicious servers. Stay informed about the challenges in AI infrastructure! #AI #CyberSecurity #MCP&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Hyper Protect with OpenShift sandboxed containers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-99/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-99/</guid>
      <description>IBM is advancing data security with Hyper Protect Confidential Containers (HPCC) for Red Hat OpenShift. This solution protects sensitive workloads in untrusted environments, essential for industries like finance and healthcare. Using OpenShift sandboxed containers, HPCC ensures VM-level isolation for confidential computing. It addresses vulnerabilities of traditional containers by employing hardware-based trusted execution environments. Learn how HPCC enhances data protection and supports&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing CIBA for Secure Transaction Verification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4073/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4073/</guid>
      <description>🔐 &lt;strong&gt;Introducing CIBA for Secure Transaction Verification&lt;/strong&gt; 🔐 Digital applications require identity verification beyond just login interfaces. CIBA (Client-Initiated Backchannel Authentication) enhances security by decoupling authentication from applications, allowing users to verify their identity securely on different devices. This method is particularly useful in scenarios like updating bank email addresses or making payments at retail POS systems without sharing credentials on public&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Rules in Spain: Don’t Let Your Calls Get Ghosted</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5158/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5158/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New telecom regulations in Spain are now in effect! Spanish mobile numbers cannot be used for unsolicited marketing or customer service calls. This means calls may get flagged or blocked, especially if using Transit-Caller-ID. 📞 To stay compliant, consider switching to Spanish landline or toll-free numbers. Review your number strategy to avoid disruptions in communication. Stay informed and keep your calls connected! #Telecom #Spain #Compliance #Twilio #Communication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing AI together: GitLab’s partnership with security researchers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3192/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3192/</guid>
      <description>GitLab is enhancing security in AI with the support of external researchers. As AI evolves, so do the challenges, like prompt injection attacks. Our collaboration with organizations like Persistent Security helps us identify vulnerabilities and implement fast solutions. By engaging with the security research community, we aim to protect customers and ensure a secure development environment. Join us in our mission at GitLab! 🤝🔒 #AISecurity #CyberSecurity #GitLab #Collaboration #SoftwareSafety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webflow’s availability incident: what we got wrong and what we’re changing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5656/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5656/</guid>
      <description>Webflow faced a significant service disruption on July 28, caused by a malicious attack that affected customer access. The team worked quickly to stabilize the platform. CEO&amp;rsquo;s reflections highlight shortcomings in communication and support during this incident. Immediate changes include enhanced monitoring, improved infrastructure, and proactive customer updates. Webflow is committed to making the platform more reliable and transparent moving forward. #Webflow #ServiceUpdate #CustomerSupport&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Omdia recommends Extended Access Management to secure agentic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2506/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2506/</guid>
      <description>Omdia&amp;rsquo;s recent report highlights significant security challenges in managing access for agentic AI. With the rise of application, device, and identity sprawl, organizations face increased risk. AI agents require extensive access but lack secure management tools, leading to potential data leaks and unauthorized actions. Omdia recommends five strategies to secure access, including the need for robust measures specifically for AI agents. 1Password Extended Access Management offers a solution by&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
