<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security_compliance on Daily Tech Articles Feed</title>
    <link>/categories/security_compliance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security_compliance on Daily Tech Articles Feed</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/categories/security_compliance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Safe in the sandbox: security hardening for Cloudflare Workers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10062/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-25-10062/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare Workers is enhancing security with new software and hardware features. We utilize defense-in-depth strategies, including V8 sandboxes and memory protection keys, to safeguard your data while running third-party code on our infrastructure. The V8 JavaScript runtime is key to our approach, designed to run safely under adversarial conditions. Our ongoing updates focus on leveraging the latest advancements to keep Workers secure. 🔒💻 #Cloudflare #CyberSecurity #Serverless&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automatically Secure: how we upgraded 6,000,000 domains by default to get ready for the Quantum Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9977/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9977/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting updates on Internet security! Cloudflare has upgraded over 6 million domains to Automatic SSL/TLS for enhanced protection. This service automatically scans and strengthens security without any action from users. As we prepare for future advancements, the focus is on evolving TLS protocols and integrating post-quantum cryptography to safeguard data against emerging threats. Learn more about these important developments! 🔒🌐 #InternetSecurity #Cloudflare #TLS #Cybersecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing data in SaaS to SaaS applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9979/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9979/</guid>
      <description>The recent Salesloft breach highlights a critical issue: companies lack visibility over data in SaaS applications. 🔍 To address this, Cloudflare is developing security tools that consolidate SaaS connections through a single proxy. This aims to enhance monitoring, detection, and response capabilities. 🛡️ SaaS platform providers play a key role in safeguarding customer data, but integrations can create vulnerabilities. With more apps, the risk of data breaches increases. 🔒 Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bridging the Gap: Cisco’s Blueprint for Developer-Centric Cloud Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9972/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-9972/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cisco is transforming cloud security by integrating it into the developer workflow. They focus on reducing friction between developers and security teams through high-fidelity alerts, pre-configured solutions, and clear communication. This approach fosters collaboration and trust, making security a natural part of development. Empathy is emphasized to ensure security measures truly support developers. #CloudSecurity #DevOps #Cisco #Collaboration #SecuritySolutions</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Signup Fraud: 3 Ways to Use Auth0 Logs to Protect Your Business</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10035/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-24-10035/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Fraudulent signups can harm businesses significantly. Auth0 provides tools to help detect and prevent these threats. Key indicators of signup fraud include: 1️⃣ High-volume signups from specific IP addresses. 2️⃣ Use of disposable email addresses. 3️⃣ Unverified accounts. By leveraging Auth0 Logs, businesses can identify these patterns and take action to protect themselves. 🛡️ #FraudPrevention #Auth0 #CyberSecurity #BusinessSafety #SignUpFraud</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The Drive-By Localhost Breach</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9917/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-23-9917/</guid>
      <description>🚨 MCP Horror Stories: Drive-By Localhost Breach 🚨 Part 4 of our series highlights a critical vulnerability, CVE-2025-49596, found in MCP Inspector. This issue allows attackers to compromise developer machines simply by visiting a malicious website. With a CVSS score of 9.4, this flaw turns a trusted debugging tool into an attack vector, showcasing the real-world risks in AI development environments. Learn how Docker MCP Gateway can help protect against these sophisticated threats&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BotID uncovers hidden SEO poisoning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9884/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9884/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A recent case highlights the risks of hidden SEO poisoning. A major financial institution observed unexpected bot traffic and deployed BotID. Instead of detecting malicious scrapers, they found verified Google bots. However, the search queries were unrelated to their business, revealing a long-standing SEO attack that was distorting their traffic patterns. Stay vigilant! 🕵️‍♂️ #SEOSecurity #BotID #CyberThreats #DigitalSafety #TrafficMonitoring</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 80/20 Rule Doesn’t Apply to Security: How Cisco SASE Bridges the Gap</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9865/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 12:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9865/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s IT landscape, relying on the 80/20 rule for security is risky. Focusing only on the majority can leave vulnerabilities exposed. 🌐🔒 With hybrid work and evolving tech, organizations need a security strategy that protects 100% of their digital presence at all times. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s SASE offers a solution by merging networking and security in a cloud-based framework. 🌥️ This innovative approach establishes micro-perimeters for enhanced protection, ensuring secure access no matter where users&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Incident Report: September 22nd, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9899/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9899/</guid>
      <description>📉 On September 22, 2025, our platform faced an outage that impacted both the dashboard and deployment pipeline. This led to a temporary suspension of deployments for all user tiers. We are actively working to resolve these issues and minimize future disruptions. Stay tuned for updates! 🔧🚧 #IncidentReport #TechUpdate #SystemOutage</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect AI Development with Falcon Cloud Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9890/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-22-9890/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Falcon Cloud Security is crucial for safeguarding AI development. It detects risks in the CI/CD pipeline and tracks AI workloads in production. As AI becomes integral to applications, it also introduces new security challenges. Without proper visibility, organizations may expose sensitive data or deploy vulnerable code. CrowdStrike&amp;rsquo;s solution offers real-time detection and comprehensive model scanning, ensuring robust protection throughout the AI pipeline. #CloudSecurity #AIDevelopment&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Government Operations: Cisco Security Cloud Control Achieves FedRAMP Authorization</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9826/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 17:03:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9826/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting news for U.S. government agencies! Cisco Security Cloud Control has received FedRAMP Authorization, enhancing security management for critical infrastructure. This cloud-native solution supports agencies in navigating today’s complex threat landscape. The FedRAMP Authorization signifies high security standards, ensuring that Cisco&amp;rsquo;s solution is compliant and reliable for federal operations. #Cybersecurity #GovTech #FedRAMP #Cisco #CloudSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You don’t need quantum hardware for post-quantum security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9823/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 13:44:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-19-9823/</guid>
      <description>🛡️ Protect your organization from future quantum threats with post-quantum cryptography (PQC). PQC can be deployed on existing hardware, ensuring your systems remain secure even after the arrival of powerful quantum computers. Contrary to popular belief, quantum key distribution (QKD) is not necessary for security. Stay informed and prepare for a quantum-ready future! #PostQuantumSecurity #Cybersecurity #QuantumReady #TechNews #DataProtection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adding Determinism and Safety to Uber IAM Policy Changes</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9776/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9776/</guid>
      <description>🚦 Uber has introduced a Policy Simulator tool to improve the safety and predictability of IAM policy changes. 🛠️ This tool allows policy authors to preview the effects of their modifications before they go live, ensuring predictable outcomes post-deployment. 🔍 This development aims to enhance security and stability in Uber&amp;rsquo;s operations. #Uber #IAM #PolicyChanges #Cybersecurity #TechInnovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Democratizing AI Safety with RiskRubric.ai</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9789/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-18-9789/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exciting news in AI safety! The launch of RiskRubric.ai aims to enhance trust in AI models by providing standardized risk assessments. With over 500,000 models on the Hugging Face hub, users often struggle to evaluate security and privacy aspects. This initiative, led by Cloud Security Alliance and Noma Security, seeks to ensure transparent security reporting as AI adoption grows. #AISafety #RiskAssessment #AIModels #CloudSecurity #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fusing Security into Networks: The Next Evolution in Enterprise Protection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9734/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9734/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving landscape of enterprise networks, traditional security tools are proving inadequate. Cisco&amp;rsquo;s AI-Ready Secure Network Architecture embeds multilayered security within the network itself, enhancing protection against a range of threats. This integrated approach utilizes Zero Trust, post-quantum encryption, and real-time threat prevention to simplify operations and improve threat response. It addresses vulnerabilities across various domains, including user edge and industrial&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strengthen privacy and security with encrypted DNS in RHEL</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9716/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 07:01:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9716/</guid>
      <description>🔒 In today&amp;rsquo;s digital world, securing DNS traffic is crucial. Unencrypted DNS queries can expose sensitive information to eavesdroppers, leading to potential data breaches. 🔍 Encrypted DNS, particularly DNS over TLS (DoT), is now available in Red Hat Enterprise Linux 10 and 9.6. This advancement strengthens network security by ensuring that DNS queries are kept private and verifiable. 🛠️ The article provides a step-by-step guide for implementing encrypted DNS to improve system security during&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CrowdStrike Collaborates with AI Leaders to Secure AI Across the Enterprise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9756/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9756/</guid>
      <description>🚀 CrowdStrike is enhancing AI security with new integrations across the enterprise. Their Falcon® platform now offers unified protection for AI models, data, and applications, addressing risks like data poisoning and model theft. Partnerships with industry leaders like AWS, NVIDIA, and Meta ensure comprehensive security at every layer of the AI stack. This approach enables organizations to innovate with confidence while maintaining essential visibility and control. #CyberSecurity #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating the Shai-Hulud Worm: Elastic&#39;s proactive defense against npm supply chain compromise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9753/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9753/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The software development community is responding to compromised npm packages linked to the Shai-Hulud worm. Elastic emphasizes the importance of supply chain integrity, noting that while its products don’t ship with npm, they rely on it for package retrieval. In their latest blog, Elastic details their analysis of code, mitigation strategies, and detection rules to combat these threats. Stay informed and secure! 🔒📦 #CyberSecurity #NPMCompromise #ElasticSecurity #ShaiHulud #SoftwareDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Powering Zero Trust Networking with Elastic and Gigamon AMI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9747/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-17-9747/</guid>
      <description>The cybersecurity landscape is evolving with the adoption of Zero Trust Networking (ZTN). This model emphasizes that no transaction is inherently trustworthy; every connection must be verified continuously. 🔒 Elastic and Gigamon&amp;rsquo;s Application Metadata Intelligence (AMI) play a crucial role in this framework. They enable intelligent data processing to support real-time decision-making and enhance security posture. 📊 As traditional perimeter defenses become obsolete, ZTN acknowledges modern&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Correcting the Record: Response to the Recent American Conservative Article on Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9710/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 20:56:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9710/</guid>
      <description>Palantir addresses recent allegations from the American Conservative questioning its commitment to privacy and civil liberties. The response clarifies that Palantir is not a surveillance company and does not engage in or promote unlawful surveillance practices. The article misrepresents Palantir&amp;rsquo;s work with intelligence agencies, particularly regarding claims related to the NSA&amp;rsquo;s XKEYSCORE tool. Palantir emphasizes its dedication to privacy laws and governance safeguards, ensuring that its&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using Agent in the Middle To Ride Herd on Wayward AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9689/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9689/</guid>
      <description>Development teams face pressure to adopt AI agents, but concerns about their unpredictable behavior and potential risks are rising. Ilya Sutskever from OpenAI warns that these agents could become &amp;ldquo;ticking time bombs,&amp;rdquo; highlighting the need for better security measures. Eve Security aims to address these challenges with their agent-in-the-loop technology, which monitors agent actions while minimizing false alerts. CISOs express concerns about connecting AI to sensitive systems, emphasizing the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Security: A Developer’s Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9685/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:00:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9685/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The Model Context Protocol (MCP) has quickly gained traction since its launch by Anthropic in November 2024. It serves as a vital link between AI agents and various tools, APIs, and data. 🔍 However, this flexibility comes with security challenges. Research indicates that 43% of analyzed MCP servers have command injection vulnerabilities, which could lead to serious risks if misconfigured. 🛡️ This guide offers developers insights into MCP security, highlighting risks and best practices for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shai-Halud Supply Chain Campaign — Expanded Impact &amp; Vercel Response</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9788/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9788/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The Shai-Halud supply chain campaign has escalated, impacting over 40 npm packages, including Tinycolor and CrowdStrike. Vercel identified 10 customer projects affected by compromised packages but confirmed that no builds were impacted in the DuckDB incident. Steps taken include blocking compromised versions and purging build caches. Vercel is enhancing supply chain defenses and monitoring for further threats. For Vercel users, audit dependencies and consider using pnpm&amp;rsquo;s new settings to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Identity Security Essentials for a Trusted AI Agent Strategy</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9683/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-16-9683/</guid>
      <description>Is your AI agent strategy secure? 🤖🔒 As companies integrate AI agents, consumer trust is crucial. A recent report shows that while 37% of consumers use GenAI tools, 70% still prefer human interaction due to privacy concerns. To build trust, robust customer identity and access management (CIAM) is essential. Here are four key practices: 1️⃣ Ensure strong authentication before AI actions. 2️⃣ Securely manage data access to protect user information. Investing in CIAM can enhance security and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post-quantum security for SSH access on GitHub</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9659/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9659/</guid>
      <description>🚀 GitHub is enhancing SSH access security with a new post-quantum secure key exchange algorithm called sntrup761x25519-sha512. This upgrade will protect Git data against future quantum computing threats. 🔒 The changes will take effect on September 17, 2025, and will only affect SSH connections, leaving HTTPS access unchanged. 🔧 Users with compatible SSH clients will benefit without needing adjustments. #GitHub #Cybersecurity #PostQuantum #SSH #DataProtection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent threat detection for defence SOCs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9665/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-15-9665/</guid>
      <description>The Ministry of Defence highlights a critical cyber risk for defence security operations centres (SOCs), amid rising malicious activities. To counter these threats, the MoD&amp;rsquo;s Digital Strategy prioritizes rapid detection and response. Effective SOCs aim to reduce mean time to detect (MTTD) and mean time to respond (MTTR) significantly. Elastic Security supports this through AI-driven analytics, automating tasks to enhance SOC efficiency and visibility. Improvements in MTTD and MTTR have been&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Agentic AI Is Key To Preventing Costly AI Hallucinations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9635/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 16:00:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-14-9635/</guid>
      <description>AI hallucinations can lead to significant risks for businesses, with inaccuracies affecting efficiency and trust. A recent study shows these inaccuracies occur between 0.7% and 29.9% of the time, depending on the AI model used. An example highlights how a manufacturer faced issues when their AI assistant provided incorrect troubleshooting advice due to gaps in its knowledge base. To combat this, the team developed enhanced checks and validation processes, leading to improved accuracy and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>18 Popular npm Packages Compromised in Attack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9631/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 13:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-13-9631/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Aikido Security has uncovered a serious security breach involving 18 popular npm packages, which have been compromised to include malicious code. These packages, with over 2 billion downloads weekly, can silently intercept crypto and web3 activities, directing funds to attacker-controlled accounts. Key affected packages include chalk, debug, and supports-color. For developers using these tools, it&amp;rsquo;s crucial to check for updates and security patches. #CyberSecurity #npm #Malware&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenSSF Experts Weigh in on CISA’s SBOM Minimum Elements Update</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9611/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 16:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-12-9611/</guid>
      <description>Experts from OpenSSF highlight the need for an update to CISA&amp;rsquo;s guidance on software bills of materials (SBOMs). Josh Bressers and Michael Lieberman emphasize the importance of clarity in SBOMs to ensure software safety, citing examples from industries like automotive and healthcare. The draft revision is open for public comment until October 3. Your feedback is crucial! 🛠️🔍 #SBOM #SoftwareSecurity #OpenSSF #CISA #TechUpdate</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3 Ways Security Teams Can Tame Autonomous AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9568/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 19:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9568/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Security teams face new challenges with autonomous AI agents that operate without human consciousness. These systems can expose vulnerabilities in traditional authorization processes. To address this, organizations should implement three key strategies: 1. &lt;strong&gt;Assign Composite Identities&lt;/strong&gt; - This helps clarify the relationship between AI actions and human operators, enhancing accountability. Understanding these risks is crucial for maintaining secure environments. #CyberSecurity #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modeling Attacks on AI-Powered Apps with the AI Kill Chain Framework</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9552/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-11-9552/</guid>
      <description>AI-powered applications are facing new security challenges that traditional models may not address. The AI Kill Chain framework, developed by NVIDIA, outlines how adversaries target these systems. This framework emphasizes the stages of an attack: recon, poison, hijack, persist, and impact. It aims to help defenders identify where they can intervene effectively. Learn more about the evolving landscape of AI security! 🔐💻🛡️ #AI #CyberSecurity #NVIDIA #AIKillChain #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Salesforce Integrations with Heroku AppLink</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9523/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 15:00:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9523/</guid>
      <description>Salesforce customers often use third-party services through Connected Apps and External Services. However, security risks persist in the integration landscape. 🔒 Heroku AppLink enhances security by providing a managed bridge between Salesforce and Heroku. It handles authentication, service discovery, and request validation, reducing reliance on stored credentials. This allows developers to reuse existing code and improves visibility and trust boundaries for admins and security teams. For&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Hallucinations to Prompt Injection: Securing AI Workflows at Runtime</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9516/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9516/</guid>
      <description>Developers are facing new challenges as AI workflows become potential attack surfaces. With AI tools like LLMs generating code, issues can arise only at runtime, leading to serious risks such as data loss or unauthorized commands. ⚠️ Prompt injections and misuse of AI outputs are significant threats. Recent incidents have shown how AI-generated scripts can unintentionally delete databases or expose sensitive information. 📉 To tackle these risks, integrating runtime security directly into&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against AI-Powered CLI Supply Chain Attacks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9514/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-10-9514/</guid>
      <description>🚨 AI-powered CLI supply chain attacks are becoming a serious threat to developers. These attacks exploit trusted command-line tools, turning them into insider threats that can steal sensitive data. A recent example involves an attacker exploiting a developer&amp;rsquo;s credentials to publish a malicious update, compromising systems and stealing secrets. To defend against these threats, an identity-first strategy is essential for securing developer environments and preventing data exfiltration. Stay&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bitbucket Cloud enters phase two of app password deprecation</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9505/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 23:52:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9505/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Bitbucket Cloud is moving to Phase 2 of app password deprecation! Starting September 9, 2025, new app passwords will no longer be created. Existing passwords will remain valid until June 9, 2026. New integrations must use API tokens for enhanced security and control. Admins should start migrating their teams now to avoid disruptions. 🔗 Learn more about this transition! #Bitbucket #APITokens #Security #DeveloperTools #Atlassian</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HIPAA BAAs are now available to Pro teams</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9485/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9485/</guid>
      <description>Pro teams can now enter into a Business Associate Agreement (BAA) on Vercel, supporting HIPAA-compliant workloads without needing an Enterprise contract. Vercel ensures HIPAA compliance through technical safeguards, annual audits, and breach notifications. However, compliance is a shared responsibility; teams must manage security features and access. This update simplifies regulatory compliance for healthcare applications. #HIPAA #Vercel #HealthcareTech #DataSecurity #ProTeams 🏥🔒📊</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Guide to the OWASP Top 10 for LLMs: Vulnerability mitigation with Elastic</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9470/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9470/</guid>
      <description>🌐 As industries adopt large language models (LLMs) and generative AI, new security challenges arise. The OWASP Top 10 for LLM Applications offers a framework to navigate these risks effectively. 🔍 Elastic&amp;rsquo;s unified platform combines observability and security analytics, providing comprehensive protection across the entire LLM application stack. ✨ This guide highlights how to use Elastic to mitigate vulnerabilities identified by OWASP, ensuring robust security in complex AI ecosystems&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>September 2025 Patch Tuesday: Two Publicly Disclosed Zero-Days and Eight Critical Vulnerabilities Among 84 CVEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9506/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-09-9506/</guid>
      <description>📅 In September 2025, Microsoft released a significant security update addressing 84 vulnerabilities. This includes two publicly disclosed zero-day vulnerabilities and eight critical ones. 🔍 The primary risks involve elevation of privilege (45% of patches), remote code execution (26%), and information disclosure (16%). Many critical vulnerabilities require user interaction to exploit. 🖥️ Microsoft Windows received the majority of the patches, totaling 58, followed by Extended Security Updates&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Fused into the Network to Protect OT at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9428/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:28:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9428/</guid>
      <description>Cisco&amp;rsquo;s latest update enhances OT security by integrating asset visibility and secure remote access into industrial switches. This approach aims to eliminate security blind spots and reduce costs for organizations managing numerous sites and assets. With the new Cyber Vision offering, users gain comprehensive visibility and enforce zero-trust remote access seamlessly. This solution is now standard in Cisco&amp;rsquo;s IE3500 and IE9300 Rugged Series Switches, making OT security more accessible&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical npm supply chain attack response - September 8, 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9447/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9447/</guid>
      <description>On September 8, 2025, a supply chain attack impacted 18 popular npm packages, including chalk, debug, and ansi-styles. These packages had malicious code aimed at intercepting cryptocurrency transactions in browsers. 🚨 Our security and engineering teams responded by identifying the affected projects and purging build caches. Affected customers have been notified with specific guidance. 🔍🔒 #CyberSecurity #npm #SupplyChainAttack #Cryptocurrency #Malware</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zero Trust in the Era of Agentic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9393/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 12:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9393/</guid>
      <description>Zero Trust is evolving to address the unique challenges posed by Agentic AI. 🤖 As AI agents utilize the same networks as users and apps, current security measures must adapt to ensure safe communication. Traditional security solutions have limitations, primarily focusing on intercepting traffic and analyzing data context. To protect these intelligent agents effectively, a shift towards enhanced zero trust frameworks is essential. 🔐 #ZeroTrust #AI #CyberSecurity #AgenticAI #TechTrends</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balancing trust, access, and control on Webflow Enterprise</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9433/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-08-9433/</guid>
      <description>Webflow Enterprise addresses the challenges of managing access in a world of numerous applications. With enterprises handling over 300 apps, effective Identity and Access Management (IAM) is crucial to prevent security risks. Webflow integrates IAM into its platform, ensuring secure user onboarding, authentication, and access monitoring. This holistic approach allows teams to collaborate freely while maintaining IT oversight and compliance. Automated provisioning and deprovisioning support&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corrective Action Update for the Heroku June 10th Outage</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7784/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7784/</guid>
      <description>🚨 &lt;strong&gt;Heroku Outage Update&lt;/strong&gt; 🚨 On June 10, 2025, Heroku experienced a service disruption due to an unintended system update. This affected not only platform performance but also the Heroku Status site, leading to confusion among users. 🛠️ On June 15, we outlined our remediation objectives, focusing on: - Immutable infrastructure - Improved communication resilience - Faster investigation and recovery 🔧 Key actions taken include halting unattended vendor upgrades, auditing system images, and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Corrective Action Update for the Heroku June 10th Outage</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7910/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 15:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7910/</guid>
      <description>🚨 &lt;strong&gt;Heroku Outage Update&lt;/strong&gt; 🚨 On June 10, 2025, Heroku faced a service disruption due to an unintended system update by a vendor. The outage also affected the Heroku Status site, leading to communication challenges. 📅 A summary of our root cause analysis was shared on June 15. Key remediation goals include enhancing infrastructure resilience, improving communication channels, and speeding up recovery processes. 🔧 &lt;strong&gt;Current Actions:&lt;/strong&gt; - Permanent halt on unattended vendor OS upgrades - Audit of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Acquisition of MCP Defender Helps Meet Challenges of Securing the Agentic Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7786/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-7786/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker, Inc. has acquired MCP Defender to enhance security for AI applications. As AI evolves rapidly, new security challenges arise for software development. 🔍 The current AI security landscape reflects early container adoption, marked by innovation but also uncertainty about risks. Organizations must now focus on real-time monitoring and dynamic threat detection. 🔒 Docker aims to embed security into AI infrastructure from the start, ensuring seamless integration into development&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker Acquisition of MCP Defender Helps Meet Challenges of Securing the Agentic Future</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-8131/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-8131/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Docker, Inc. has announced its acquisition of MCP Defender to enhance security for AI applications. As AI technology evolves, so do the security challenges it presents. 🚧 Companies are urged to shift towards real-time monitoring and proactive threat detection to safeguard their AI infrastructure. Docker aims to integrate security into AI development from the start, ensuring a seamless experience for developers. 🔐 #Docker #AIsafety #Cybersecurity #TechNews #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Starless: How we accidentally vanished our most popular GitHub repos</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-05-9382/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-05-9382/</guid>
      <description>In October 2024, a significant incident occurred where Elastic&amp;rsquo;s key public repositories on GitHub were mistakenly marked as private. This was due to automation changes aimed at enhancing internal source code security. The incident led to an outage for customers and highlighted the risks of making assumptions in automated processes. Elastic&amp;rsquo;s engineering teams are sharing insights from this experience to prevent future occurrences. Learn more about the importance of supply chain security and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Addressing the unauthorized issuance of multiple TLS certificates for 1.1.1.1</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7750/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 17:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7750/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare has reported unauthorized TLS certificates issued for 1.1.1.1 by Fina CA without permission. These 12 certificates were issued between February 2024 and August 2025 and have since been revoked. While no evidence suggests malicious use, this incident highlights the importance of proper certificate issuance protocols. Fina CA stated the certificates were intended for internal testing. Cloudflare emphasizes the need for awareness around internet trust dynamics. 🔒🌐 #CyberSecurity #DNS&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why secrets management is incomplete without secret scanning</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7745/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7745/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Secrets management is vital for safeguarding API keys, passwords, and certificates. However, it often only covers known secrets, leaving gaps in security. 💻 Secrets can be scattered across code, pipelines, and tools, creating hidden risks. Recent research shows that leaked secrets can take 94 days to remediate, increasing vulnerability to attacks. 🔐 Secret scanning complements management by providing visibility and real-time detection of hidden secrets. This proactive approach integrates&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A developer&#39;s guide to building secure retail apps with GitLab</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7741/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-04-7741/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Retailers face unique security challenges as modern commerce expands. With mobile apps, AI, and IoT, each touchpoint increases the risk of vulnerabilities that can impact customer trust and revenue. Traditional security methods often fall short in this complex landscape. An integrated DevSecOps platform, like GitLab, embeds security into the development lifecycle, allowing teams to innovate while maintaining customer experience. Discover how to address these challenges effectively through&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 security wins from Booking.com&#39;s hybrid cloud migration</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7701/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7701/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Booking.com has made significant strides in their hybrid cloud migration by enhancing security with HashiCorp Vault. They developed a unified secrets management system, allowing consistent access across various platforms, including AWS and GCP. This central security bridge mitigates risks of misconfigurations. By migrating to JWT authentication, they simplified their authentication processes, reducing complexity and improving oversight. Additionally, Vault&amp;rsquo;s secrets sync will provide&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black Hat Investigation: Attempted Exploitation of Registration Server</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7668/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7668/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Black Hat Conference Update 🚨 Recent investigations revealed attempted exploitation of the registration server at the Black Hat conference. Operating within the unique Security and Network Operations Center (NOC) environment, Cisco faces distinct challenges due to the conference&amp;rsquo;s focus on cybersecurity research and ethical hacking. 🔍 The NOC anticipates various activities that might appear suspicious elsewhere. The Bring Your Own Device (BYOD) policy complicates monitoring, emphasizing the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Value of PCAP in Firewall Investigations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7669/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 12:00:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7669/</guid>
      <description>🚀 The article highlights the importance of PCAP (packet capture) in firewall investigations, emphasizing its time-consuming nature. Key steps include finding a suitable platform, executing the capture, and analyzing large files. At Black Hat USA 2025, the ‘Endace PCAP Pivot’ feature enabled easier access to packet-level data, enhancing SOC analyst investigations significantly. 📊🔍 #CyberSecurity #PacketCapture #NetworkAnalysis #BlackHat2025 #SOCInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Compliance Toolkit: AI-powered support for SMS compliance</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7713/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7713/</guid>
      <description>Twilio&amp;rsquo;s new Compliance Toolkit leverages AI and machine learning to enhance SMS compliance. This tool proactively identifies and mitigates potential regulatory violations, helping businesses maintain compliance and avoid penalties. Explore how AI can support your compliance efforts! 📲🤖 #Compliance #AI #SMS #Twilio #Regulations</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What security leaders need to know about mergers and acquisitions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7681/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-03-7681/</guid>
      <description>Mergers and acquisitions (M&amp;amp;A) present unique security challenges for teams. The integration of two companies involves managing devices, applications, and data, often exposing serious vulnerabilities. Notable cases, like Verizon and Yahoo, highlight the consequences of security oversights that can lead to costly data breaches. Due diligence is crucial. Security leaders should be involved from the start, focusing on identifying risks through thorough discovery and validation processes&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 tips for credential management across multi-cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7645/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7645/</guid>
      <description>Managing credentials in multi-cloud environments can be complex. Lino Telera from InfoCert shares five essential tips to streamline secret management: 1️⃣ Use dynamic secrets instead of static API keys to minimize risk. 2️⃣ Automate runtime secret management to eliminate manual errors. 3️⃣ Implement workspace sandboxing to enforce zero trust principles. These practices help improve security and efficiency in development. #CredentialManagement #CloudSecurity #DevOps #InfoSec #HashiCorp</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The impact of the Salesloft Drift breach on Cloudflare and our customers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7648/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7648/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Last week, Cloudflare confirmed that it was affected by the Salesloft Drift breach, where an advanced threat actor accessed Salesforce data, impacting Cloudflare and many companies. The breach compromised customer contact information and support case data, including sensitive details. Cloudflare has urged customers to rotate any credentials shared through this channel. Immediate actions were taken, including securing the environment and investigating the incident. All affected customers&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API Keys and AI Agents: Four Common Risks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7639/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 16:26:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7639/</guid>
      <description>Building AI agents can be thrilling, but it comes with serious security risks when using API keys. 🚨 Pasting keys everywhere can lead to exposure through public repositories, logs, or client-side applications. This increases the chance of automated attacks, especially if the keys have broad permissions. 🔑 Managing these keys is crucial to ensure data security and compliance, particularly in regulated industries. Consider solutions like Auth0&amp;rsquo;s Token Vault to safeguard your integrations. 🔒 #AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing the Backdoor in TACACS&#43;: Why Full-Session Encryption Matters More Than Ever</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7607/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7607/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Recent cyber threats highlight the risks of weak TACACS+ encryption. Attackers exploited vulnerabilities, targeting network operators to steal credentials and blend in as legitimate admins. By harvesting TACACS+ traffic, they captured sensitive data, allowing unauthorized access and evading detection. Cisco ISE with TLS 1.3 and Duo MFA offers solutions to enhance security and close these backdoors. 🔒🛡️ #Cybersecurity #TACACS #DataProtection #CiscoISE #MFA</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure AI at Machine Speed: Defending the Growing Attack Surface</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7658/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-02-7658/</guid>
      <description>As AI integrates into various business functions, it significantly broadens the enterprise attack surface. 📈 Adversaries are increasingly targeting AI tools and their supporting infrastructure, exploiting vulnerabilities in APIs and models. Many organizations struggle with visibility and lack adequate protection for these evolving threats. 🔍 To tackle these challenges, innovative, real-time security solutions tailored for AI are essential. The CrowdStrike Falcon® platform offers insights on&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Exposed LLM Servers: A Shodan Case Study on Ollama</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7583/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-09-01-7583/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A recent case study reveals over 1,100 exposed Ollama LLM servers, with 20% hosting open models. This highlights critical security vulnerabilities in LLM deployments. 🔍 The study utilized Shodan to identify these unsecured endpoints, emphasizing the need for stronger security measures. 🛡️ As LLMs become more popular, addressing these gaps is essential for protecting sensitive data. #CyberSecurity #LLM #DataProtection #Ollama #Shodan</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Update: Multiple vulnerabilities in Next.js</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-30-7551/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 01:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-30-7551/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Security Alert for Next.js Users 🚨 Recent vulnerabilities have been disclosed affecting Next.js applications, including issues related to arbitrary file downloads and cache poisoning. Netlify&amp;rsquo;s engineering team confirms that sites hosted on their platform are not vulnerable to multiple threats. However, if using the next/image component with protected sources, caution is advised. To ensure security, it is recommended to upgrade to the latest Next.js versions and enable automatic updates for&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating 70% of Dependency &amp; Vulnerability Management with Renovate and CI/CD</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7556/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 23:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7556/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Exciting advancements in security automation at Salesforce! Sai Saketh Nakkina and his team transformed vulnerability management for AI features on the Agentforce platform. By automating 70% of the process with Renovate and CI/CD, they significantly reduced manual responses to vulnerabilities. Their mission focuses on maintaining secure ML pipelines and delivering AI features efficiently while ensuring platform integrity. This approach addresses security threats and enhances customer trust&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-55173</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7555/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7555/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A vulnerability (CVE-2025-55173) affecting Next.js Image Optimization has been identified. It impacts versions prior to v15.4.5 and v14.2.31, allowing attacker-controlled external image servers to trigger arbitrary file downloads. This could lead to phishing and social engineering attacks. A patch was released on July 29th, 2025, addressing this issue for Vercel customers. For more details, check the GitHub Advisory and Next.js Release Notes. #CyberSecurity #NextJS #Vulnerability&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-57752</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7553/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7553/</guid>
      <description>A vulnerability, CVE-2025-57752, has been identified in Next.js Image Optimization affecting versions prior to v15.4.5 and v14.2.31. It involved cache poisoning, risking unauthorized access to sensitive images. The issue arose when API routes returned images based on headers, leading to potential disclosure of user-specific content. The vulnerability has been resolved in the latest versions, ensuring that request headers are not forwarded to image endpoints. For more details, refer to the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-57822</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7554/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-29-7554/</guid>
      <description>A recent vulnerability, CVE-2025-57822, has been identified in Next.js Middleware, affecting versions before v14.2.32 and v15.4.7. This flaw allowed for Server-Side Request Forgery (SSRF) risks due to misconfigured NextResponse.next() usage. Applications that reflected user request headers could unintentionally allow servers to make requests to harmful destinations. A patch was released on August 25, 2025, to protect Vercel customers. For those unable to upgrade, it is vital to adhere to&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preparing for the worst: Our core database failover test</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7485/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7485/</guid>
      <description>On July 24, 2025, we conducted a successful failover test of our core control-plane database from Azure West US to East US 2. This exercise confirmed our disaster recovery plans in real-world conditions. All control-plane traffic was tested, ensuring stability without any customer impact. While preview and development traffic were affected, our production CDN traffic remained unaffected across 19 regions. The operation highlighted our commitment to resilience, achieving zero downtime and no&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secure by Design: A Shift-Left Approach with Testcontainers, Docker Scout, and Hardened Images</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7465/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-28-7465/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s software development landscape, speed should not compromise security. 🛡️ This article discusses a shift-left approach using tools like Testcontainers and Docker to enhance security early in the development lifecycle. It highlights how developers can conduct reliable integration tests while maintaining high quality. A practical example features a Node.js Movie Catalog API, demonstrating how Testcontainers can streamline testing against a PostgreSQL database. 📦 Learn how modern&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Unified Approach to Data Exfiltration Protection on Databricks</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7446/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 20:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7446/</guid>
      <description>Data exfiltration poses a significant security risk for organizations. A recent article outlines a comprehensive framework for protecting against unauthorized data movement on Databricks. The recommendations focus on unified strategies to enhance data security and prevent breaches. Implementing these measures can help safeguard sensitive information effectively. 🔒🛡️ #DataSecurity #Databricks #CyberSecurity #DataProtection #InformationSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>s1ngularity: supply chain attack in Nx packages</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7486/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7486/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A supply chain attack has targeted the Nx package in the npm registry. Malicious versions were published using a stolen npm token, leading to potential exfiltration of developer credentials. 🔍 The Nx team quickly removed the compromised packages, but Vercel customers are generally safe unless specific conditions were met. 👉 For detailed information, visit the GitHub advisory from the Nx team. Stay vigilant! #SupplyChainAttack #CyberSecurity #NxPackages #Vercel #DeveloperSafety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Ahead of the HIPAA Security Rule Update With Secure Workload</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7193/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-27-7193/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Important Update for Healthcare Organizations! 🚨 On January 6, 2025, the Office of Civil Rights will introduce new cybersecurity requirements as part of the HIPAA Security Rule Update. This will shift the focus from reactive measures to a risk-based approach to enhance cybersecurity in healthcare. The update aims to strengthen the protection of electronic personal health information (ePHI) and address the increasing number of cyberattacks. Organizations must prepare to implement effective&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices for Securing Generative AI with SASE</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7241/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7241/</guid>
      <description>🚀 As businesses adopt Generative AI, Security and IT leaders face new challenges. Executives push for quick implementation, while teams must create effective AI Security Strategies. 🔒 Cloudflare’s SASE architecture offers a solution, integrating networking and security for secure access to corporate resources. Their platform supports safe AI usage without hindering innovation. 🛡️ Recent enhancements include shadow AI reporting, confidence scoring for AI providers, and protections against&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Block unsafe prompts targeting your LLM endpoints with Firewall for AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7240/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7240/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloudflare has enhanced its AI security suite with the introduction of unsafe content moderation through Firewall for AI. This new feature aims to protect AI applications from malicious prompts that could compromise sensitive data or user trust. 🔒 With this integration, customers can now detect and block harmful prompts at the network level without modifying their application code. Firewall for AI supports various models, ensuring consistent protection across all platforms. 🛡️ This update&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT, Claude, &amp; Gemini security scanning with Cloudflare CASB</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7239/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7239/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Cloudflare CASB now offers security scanning for generative AI tools like ChatGPT, Claude, and Gemini. Organizations can connect their accounts to detect misconfigurations, data exposure, and compliance risks quickly and without additional software. This integration enhances visibility and helps IT teams manage the security challenges of AI adoption effectively. 🔍 #Cloudflare #CyberSecurity #GenerativeAI #DataProtection #Compliance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Cloudflare Application Confidence Score For AI Applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7238/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7238/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Cloudflare has introduced Application Confidence Scores for Gen AI applications to help businesses assess risks associated with shadow IT. These scores will aid security, IT, and legal teams in evaluating third-party applications without needing extensive individual audits. This initiative aims to balance productivity with security, promoting smarter controls rather than blanket bans. Stay informed about the new features in Cloudflare&amp;rsquo;s AI Security Posture Management within the Cloudflare&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protecting Cisco’s front lines with AI-powered Email Threat Defense and Splunk</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7198/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7198/</guid>
      <description>Cisco is enhancing email security with a layered approach using AI and Splunk. 💻✉️ Facing over 326 million emails quarterly, Cisco recognized the need to defend against phishing and malware while improving user productivity. The FBI reported a staggering rise in email cyberattacks, highlighting the urgency for robust security measures. By integrating Cisco Email Threat Defense with Splunk’s analytics, Cisco aims to provide comprehensive protection against evolving threats. #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fragmented SSE Is a Risk You Can’t Afford</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7200/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7200/</guid>
      <description>Fragmented security solutions can create significant risks. Many organizations rely on multiple vendors for their security needs, leading to complex systems that may leave gaps in protection. Cisco Secure Access addresses this issue by providing a unified architecture. This ensures consistent policy enforcement regardless of where users connect from, enhancing overall security. No more silos or inconsistent access experiences! #Cybersecurity #Cisco #SecureAccess #SSE #DataProtection 🔐🌐💻</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and security at Black Hat: 5 key takeaways from a security expert panel</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7251/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7251/</guid>
      <description>🌐 At Black Hat, security leaders discussed the rise of AI in cybersecurity, highlighting key challenges and strategies. 1️⃣ Zero trust principles need to evolve to include AI agents. 2️⃣ Cybercriminals are increasingly using AI for more sophisticated attacks. 3️⃣ Many organizations lack visibility into their AI usage, leading to risks. 4️⃣ Business demand for AI is outpacing security preparedness. 5️⃣ AI can enhance security but also introduces new vulnerabilities. Effective governance is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clickjacking: What it means for 1Password users</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7252/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-26-7252/</guid>
      <description>🔒 1Password has released an important update (version 8.11.7) addressing clickjacking, a technique that can trick users into autofilling sensitive information. This vulnerability does not put 1Password systems at risk, but the update provides users with better control by introducing confirmation alerts for autofill actions. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to update to the latest version and keep autofill enabled for enhanced security. Stay safe online! 🛡️ #1Password #CyberSecurity #Clickjacking #DataProtection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secret sprawl is costing you more than you think</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7172/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-7172/</guid>
      <description>🛡️ Secret sprawl is significantly impacting organizations, costing them millions annually through lost productivity and increased security overhead. Developers often waste time on preventable secret management tasks, leading to an estimated $936,000 annual loss for a typical 50-person team. This includes hunting down exposed credentials and managing compromised keys. Moreover, security teams face a burden from false positives, costing around $520,000 each year due to unnecessary&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking the Unseen: Your Guide to Taming Shadow AI with Cloudflare One</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6345/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6345/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Concerned about data leaks from unsanctioned AI use? The rise of &amp;ldquo;Shadow AI&amp;rdquo; poses a significant risk as employees unknowingly expose sensitive information through AI tools. Traditional security measures often miss these interactions. Cloudflare One offers a solution with its Shadow IT Report, providing visibility into AI application usage and helping organizations manage potential risks effectively. Stay informed and secure! 🔍💻 #CyberSecurity #ShadowAI #Cloudflare #DataProtection #Innovation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond the ban: A better way to secure generative AI applications</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6348/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6348/</guid>
      <description>Generative AI is transforming workplace productivity, but it also poses significant data security risks. 🛡️ Many employees inadvertently share sensitive information with AI tools. Recent incidents highlight the consequences of this, including private chats being indexed online. To address these risks, Cloudflare introduces AI prompt protection, part of its Data Loss Prevention (DLP) system. This feature helps organizations manage AI use while securing sensitive data. AI prompt protection&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Protect Your Access Tokens with DPoP (Demonstrating Proof of Possession)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6332/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-25-6332/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Protect your applications with DPoP! This article explains how Demonstrating Proof-of-Possession enhances security for access tokens by ensuring they can only be used by the intended application. Unlike traditional bearer tokens, DPoP binds tokens to a specific client instance, mitigating risks of token theft. Learn about the benefits, security threats it addresses, and how to implement DPoP in your applications using Auth0. #Security #DPoP #OAuth2 #AccessTokens #ApplicationSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing the Future: How Databricks Powers Financial Services</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6309/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 18:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6309/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving financial services landscape, data security and compliance are vital for growth. Databricks enables financial institutions to build resilience and accelerate innovation while ensuring adherence to regulations. This approach supports the safe use of data and AI technologies in the sector. Understanding these elements is crucial for navigating future challenges. 📊🔐✨ #DataSecurity #FinancialServices #Innovation #Compliance #AI</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why default secret detection rules don&#39;t work (and how to fix it)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6312/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-22-6312/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Many organizations face challenges with default secret detection rules. Studies indicate that up to 80% of security alerts are false positives, leading to overlooked real threats. 📊 Generic detection tools often miss unique credentials like proprietary API keys. This can result in significant security incidents if not addressed. 💡 HCP Vault Radar offers a solution with customizable detection patterns and severity-based workflows. This approach helps teams focus on genuine threats while&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI in Financial Services Demands a New Trust Layer: Why Identity Security Is the Answer</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5100/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-5100/</guid>
      <description>As AI transforms financial services, new risks arise with autonomous AI agents accessing sensitive data. Traditional identity security is becoming insufficient. Financial institutions must now consider not just who the user is, but also what operates on their behalf. A shift to advanced identity solutions, like Auth for GenAI, is essential for secure innovation. 🚀🔐 Explore more insights from the Auth0 Customer Identity Trends Report 2025. #AI #FinancialServices #IdentitySecurity #Innovation&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MURKY PANDA: A Trusted-Relationship Threat in the Cloud</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-21-7438/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-21-7438/</guid>
      <description>🚨 MURKY PANDA is a China-nexus adversary targeting various sectors in North America, including government and technology. Since late 2024, they have used trusted-relationship compromises in the cloud, showcasing deep knowledge of cloud environments. Their tactics include exploiting vulnerabilities and deploying malware like CloudedHope. 💻 CrowdStrike has tracked MURKY PANDA&amp;rsquo;s operations, which are driven by intelligence-collection goals, often resulting in the exfiltration of sensitive&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing private data at scale with differentially private partition selection</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5180/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 19:24:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5180/</guid>
      <description>🔒 New algorithms are advancing user privacy in data sharing through differentially private partition selection. This approach allows for safe sharing of large datasets, crucial for AI and machine learning innovation. It ensures individual contributions remain confidential by adding controlled noise during selection. Parallel algorithms enhance efficiency, enabling the processing of vast datasets while maintaining robust privacy guarantees. Explore more in the publication “Scalable Private&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic’s capabilities in the world of Zero Trust operations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5058/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-5058/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Exploring Zero Trust Operations with Elastic The article discusses the essential pillars of Zero Trust (ZT) based on the US Department of Defense&amp;rsquo;s framework. Key elements include user identity, device characteristics, network integrity, data protection, application vulnerabilities, and automation. Challenges exist in implementing ZT, such as system complexity, operational speed, and fragility from disparate integrations. Elastic’s Search AI Platform is highlighted for its role in enhancing&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Falcon Platform Prevents COOKIE SPIDER’s SHAMOS Delivery on macOS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-20-7439/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-20-7439/</guid>
      <description>🚨 The CrowdStrike Falcon® platform has successfully blocked a sophisticated malware campaign by COOKIE SPIDER targeting macOS users. Between June and August 2025, over 300 customer environments were at risk due to the SHAMOS variant of the Atomic macOS Stealer. This malware was distributed through malvertising, tricking users into executing a harmful installation command. The campaign highlighted the use of one-line installation commands, which can bypass security checks, raising concerns&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CRLite: Fast, private, and comprehensive certificate revocation checking in Firefox</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5048/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5048/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Firefox has launched CRLite, the first fast and private certificate revocation checking system that protects user browsing activity. This new mechanism downloads a compact list of revoked certificates, making checking efficient and reliable. Starting with Firefox 137, CRLite enhances security while disabling the less private OCSP method in future updates. #Firefox #CRLite #Cybersecurity #Privacy #WebDevelopment</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Findings Report From the SOC at RSAC™ 2025 Conference</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5286/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 12:00:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5286/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Exciting updates from the RSAC™ 2025 Conference! 🚨 The Findings Report from the Security Operations Center reveals key insights into network security. Cisco and Endace monitored the Moscone Center&amp;rsquo;s wireless network, showcasing how an open network operates. The SOC utilized advanced tools, including the EndaceProbe packet capture platform and Cisco Security Cloud, to enhance security measures. Learn more about these innovations and watch the session replay! #RSAC2025 #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to enhance Agent2Agent (A2A) security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5032/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 07:01:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-19-5032/</guid>
      <description>🔒 The Agent2Agent (A2A) protocol by Google facilitates communication between AI agents, allowing seamless interaction across different vendors. Each agent can serve as a client or remote agent depending on the context. 🌐 Communication involves retrieving an Agent Card, which contains essential details for task execution. Security measures such as HTTPS and authentication protocols are crucial for protecting these interactions. 🛡️ Developers implementing A2A should remain vigilant about&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elastic response to blog ‘EDR 0-Day Vulnerability’</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5059/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5059/</guid>
      <description>🔍 Elastic’s Security team has responded to claims of a vulnerability in Elastic Defend. After comprehensive investigation, no evidence was found to support the alleged bypass of EDR monitoring or remote code execution. The demonstrations provided were not from unprivileged processes. Elastic remains committed to transparency and encourages researchers to share any valid findings at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:security@elastic.co&#34;&gt;security@elastic.co&lt;/a&gt;. Updates will be provided as necessary. #CyberSecurity #Elastic #Vulnerability #EDR #InfoSec</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regulatory and Compliance Corner - August &amp; September 2025</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5138/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-18-5138/</guid>
      <description>🌍 This month&amp;rsquo;s Regulatory and Compliance Corner highlights significant telecom policy changes worldwide. Key updates include new regulations aimed at enhancing data privacy and security for users. Additionally, several countries are revising rules to promote competition in the telecom sector. Stay informed about these important shifts in the industry! 📡✉️ #Telecom #Regulations #DataPrivacy #IndustryInsights #Compliance</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Docker @ Black Hat 2025: CVEs have everyone’s attention, here’s the path forward</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5119/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:05:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5119/</guid>
      <description>🚀 At Black Hat 2025, CVEs were a hot topic, highlighting the need for effective vulnerability management. The focus is shifting from just scanning to eliminating security debt before it enters the software supply chain. Hardened images and compliance-ready tools are becoming essential. Key themes included the importance of secure starting points, customization for enterprises, and the demand for FedRAMP-ready solutions. Thanks to everyone who joined the Docker community at our booth and the&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A practitioner’s view on how Docker enables security by default and makes developers work better</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5120/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5120/</guid>
      <description>Docker Captains share their experiences on how Docker enhances security and developer efficiency. Security in distributed systems is crucial, and Docker provides a strong framework for developers and security teams. Key areas of focus include managing artifacts, code quality, and vulnerability management. For more insights on becoming a Docker Captain, visit the Docker Captains’ website! 🛠️🔒 #Docker #Security #DevOps #ContainerSecurity #TechInsights</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scaling On-Prem Security at Palantir</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5053/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 13:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-15-5053/</guid>
      <description>Palantir emphasizes security in its on-premises solutions, tailoring approaches for various environments. 🌐 The Insight tool enhances security by automating checks on server configurations, ensuring compliance with rigorous standards. It allows users to run scans and generate reports easily. 📊 With the integration of Foundry and Apollo, Palantir streamlines the review process, improving visibility and collaboration. 🔍 Learn more about how Palantir maintains security across thousands of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MadeYouReset: An HTTP/2 vulnerability thwarted by Rapid Reset mitigations</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5132/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 22:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5132/</guid>
      <description>🚨 A new HTTP/2 vulnerability named MadeYouReset (CVE-2025-8671) has been disclosed by researchers at Tel Aviv University. This denial-of-service (DoS) vulnerability affects unpatched HTTP/2 servers, potentially leading to resource exhaustion. If you use Cloudflare for DDoS mitigation, your systems are already protected. MadeYouReset exploits server-sent stream resets, similar to the previously identified Rapid Reset vulnerability. Implementations are encouraged to monitor and limit the use of&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The GitHub Prompt Injection Data Heist</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5122/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5122/</guid>
      <description>🚨 In Part 3 of the MCP Horror Stories series, we explore the GitHub Prompt Injection Data Heist. This incident highlights critical vulnerabilities in AI security, revealing how attackers can manipulate AI assistants through malicious GitHub issues. When developers request help, they risk exposing sensitive data from locked repositories. Learn how these attacks exploit broad GitHub tokens and bypass traditional access controls. Docker’s MCP Toolkit offers solutions to protect against such&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Locking Down the Fleet: Encryption at Rest and Disk Isolation at Scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5015/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Managing encryption at rest and ensuring disk isolation for numerous stateful workloads presents significant challenges. In a recent article, the focus is on how effective logical volume management was implemented to secure a large fleet of servers. This approach enhances data security while maintaining operational efficiency. #DataSecurity #Encryption #LogicalVolumeManagement #TechInnovation #CyberSecurity</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to secure your Jenkins pipeline with Red Hat Advanced Developer Suite</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4994/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 07:01:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-4994/</guid>
      <description>Enhance your Jenkins pipeline security with Red Hat Advanced Developer Suite! 🔒 This suite integrates cryptographic signing, SBOM validation, and runtime enforcement to ensure a secure CI/CD process. Each stage—from commit to deployment—now includes proof of compliance. Key features include: - Trusted Artifact Signer for image signing. - Profile Analyzer for risk assessment. - Advanced Cluster Security for policy enforcement. Learn how to keep your deployment velocity while lowering risks! 🚀🔧&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Defending Against SCATTERED SPIDER with Falcon Next-Gen SIEM</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7440/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-7440/</guid>
      <description>🚨 SCATTERED SPIDER continues to pose a significant threat, launching attacks on organizations globally since 2022. This adversary uses refined social engineering tactics to compromise sensitive information. 🔍 CrowdStrike&amp;rsquo;s Falcon Next-Gen SIEM offers real-time detection across various domains, enhancing defenses against these evolving threats. It integrates third-party telemetry for improved visibility and tailored protection. 📊 The blog details key phases of SCATTERED SPIDER’s kill chain and&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Trust in AI: A Developer&#39;s Identity Guide</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5009/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5009/</guid>
      <description>🔐 In the evolving landscape of AI, security is essential for building user trust. Developers face challenges like signup attacks, account takeovers, and poor password hygiene, which can erode confidence in digital platforms. The Auth0 Customer Identity Trends Report 2025 reveals that 46.1% of new registrations may be fraudulent, while 16.9% of login attempts show malicious intent. To foster trust, developers must prioritize robust identity management, as 74% of users value a company’s&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why financial services choose single-tenant SaaS</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5066/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-14-5066/</guid>
      <description>Financial institutions face unique challenges with shared infrastructure, which heightens systemic risks. As highlighted by JPMorgan Chase&amp;rsquo;s CISO, incidents on multi-tenant platforms can lead to widespread disruptions. GitLab Dedicated offers a solution, providing isolated environments for development while ensuring compliance and security. This approach enables institutions to manage risks more effectively, ensuring their source code is treated as a critical asset. Learn more about how&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Creating AI agent solutions for warehouse data access and security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4966/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 22:05:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4966/</guid>
      <description>Meta is evolving its data warehouse to enhance productivity and security for both human users and AI agents. 🤖🔒 We are developing AI agents to streamline data access requests, helping users find the data they need while assisting data owners in maintaining security. Guardrails, such as auditing and feedback systems, are also being implemented to ensure safe operations. As the scale and complexity of data access grow, our focus is on minimizing security risks while improving efficiency. This&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software provenance: Why visibility into your software supply chain matters</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4954/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4954/</guid>
      <description>🌐 Understanding software provenance is crucial in today&amp;rsquo;s complex software supply chain. This concept emphasizes tracking the creation, modification, and ownership of software artifacts throughout their lifecycle. As cyber threats rise, maintaining visibility is essential for security and compliance. Challenges include limited visibility, pipeline complexity, and compliance risks. Organizations must prioritize comprehensive documentation to address these issues. Stay informed and secure! 🔒🛡️&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Access Control in the Era of AI Agents</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4945/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-13-4945/</guid>
      <description>AI agents are evolving, performing complex tasks and making API calls autonomously. This shift poses new security challenges, particularly in access control. The article discusses the history of AI agents and highlights the risks they bring, emphasizing the need for fine-grained access control. Traditional models like RBAC and ABAC struggle under the dynamic nature of AI systems, often requiring additional engineering for effective management. Explore how to adapt access control as AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Passing the Security Vibe Check: The Dangers of Vibe Coding</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4951/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 19:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-4951/</guid>
      <description>In a recent article from Databricks, the concept of &amp;ldquo;vibe coding&amp;rdquo; is examined in relation to software security. The piece discusses how developers often rely on intuition or &amp;ldquo;vibes&amp;rdquo; when assessing security risks, which can lead to vulnerabilities. It emphasizes the importance of structured security practices over subjective judgments. Understanding these risks is crucial for building safer software systems. 🔒💻 #CyberSecurity #SoftwareDevelopment #VibeCoding #TechInsights #DataProtection</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>August 2025 Patch Tuesday: One Publicly Disclosed Zero-Day and 13 Critical Vulnerabilities Among 107 CVEs</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7443/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-12-7443/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Microsoft has released its August 2025 Patch Tuesday updates, addressing 107 vulnerabilities. Among these are one publicly disclosed zero-day and 13 critical vulnerabilities. The most common risk types involve elevation of privilege (39%), remote code execution (33%), and information disclosure (15%). Windows received the largest share of patches with 67 updates. #PatchTuesday #CyberSecurity #MicrosoftUpdates #Vulnerabilities #InfoSec</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federation Platform and Privacy Waves: How Meta distributes compliance-related tasks at scale</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4855/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 16:00:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4855/</guid>
      <description>Meta is enhancing privacy compliance with its Federation Platform and Privacy Waves program. These tools manage compliance tasks effectively and ensure accountability across teams. 🌐 The Federation Platform breaks down compliance initiatives into manageable tasks, while Privacy Waves organizes these tasks into monthly batches for better planning. 📅 Together, they improve user data protection and streamline operations, managing over 100,000 tasks annually. This approach is expanding into&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The rise of intelligent banking: Unifying fraud, security, and compliance in the era of AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4835/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-11-4835/</guid>
      <description>In the evolving financial landscape, security, compliance, and customer trust are interconnected. The IDC Spotlight report, sponsored by Elastic and AWS, highlights the need for financial institutions to adopt AI-powered platforms that unify fraud prevention, cybersecurity, and regulatory compliance. As threats grow more sophisticated, institutions must move beyond siloed risk functions to ensure operational resilience and regulatory readiness. This shift is critical for maintaining customer&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Future of Healthcare Is AI-Powered and Secure: How CIAM Builds Trust</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4850/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 22:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4850/</guid>
      <description>The integration of AI in healthcare is reshaping the industry, promising enhanced efficiency and personalized treatment. However, the security of sensitive patient data is a major concern. Customer Identity and Access Management (CIAM) solutions play a crucial role in ensuring that only authorized users access AI systems, supporting compliance and security. As the healthcare IAM market is projected to grow significantly, establishing trust becomes vital. Patients prioritize trust over&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The Supply Chain Attack</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4763/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4763/</guid>
      <description>🚨 Part 2 of our MCP Horror Stories series highlights a critical supply chain attack affecting AI development environments. The article discusses CVE-2025-6514, where a vulnerability in mcp-remote led to credential compromise and remote code execution. This incident impacted nearly 437,000 environments, including major platforms like Cloudflare and Hugging Face. Learn about the attack techniques used, the importance of containerized MCP servers, and practical steps to secure your AI&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Hackers Exploit AI’s Problem-Solving Instincts</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4717/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4717/</guid>
      <description>🚨 As AI models become more advanced, they face new vulnerabilities. Researchers highlight how hackers exploit these systems by manipulating their problem-solving instincts. 🔍 The article discusses the evolution of attack techniques from text-based prompt injections to sophisticated multimodal reasoning attacks. These new methods target how AI merges inputs like text, images, and audio. 🔒 Securing AI requires a shift in focus from just input/output layers to the reasoning architecture itself&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10 key questions about designing a secure cloud environment</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4708/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4708/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Designing a secure cloud environment is crucial for organizations to avoid risks and enhance innovation. Here are 10 key questions leaders should ask their teams: 1. Do we have full visibility into our cloud infrastructure? 2. Are we embedding security throughout the development lifecycle? 3. Can we enforce security policies at scale? These discussions are essential for reducing risk and maintaining compliance. 🌐 For more insights on cloud security, check the full article. #CloudSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build trust in your CI/CD pipelines with OpenShift Pipelines</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4691/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 07:01:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4691/</guid>
      <description>🔒 Red Hat OpenShift Pipelines provide a cloud-native CI/CD solution using Tekton. This article highlights the use of OpenShift sandboxed containers, which isolate workloads in virtual machines, enhancing security for tasks needing elevated privileges. 🌐 For untrusted environments, OpenShift confidential containers (CoCo) further protect pipeline data by running containers in isolated hardware enclaves, safeguarding against admin access. 💡 The integration of these technologies ensures secure,&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing AI Agents: Retail&#39;s Next Big Challenge</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4706/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4706/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence is transforming the retail industry, offering new ways to engage customers and streamline operations. 🚀 While 90% of retailers are already using or evaluating AI, concerns about data privacy and security remain significant. 60% of retailers worry about data privacy, highlighting the need for secure AI adoption. 🔒 Current AI applications include hyper-personalized shopping experiences, virtual try-ons, and real-time customer service assistance. The future holds even&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The security principles guiding 1Password’s approach to AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4745/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-07-4745/</guid>
      <description>AI is reshaping our work landscape, bringing both opportunities and responsibilities, especially in security. 1Password emphasizes building trustworthy AI while maintaining core values of privacy and transparency. Key principles include: 🔒 Keeping secrets secure through strong encryption. 📜 Ensuring predictable authorization processes. 📊 Maintaining audit trails for AI actions. 1Password is committed to integrating AI securely and effectively. #AI #CyberSecurity #1Password #DataPrivacy #Trust</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Accelerating FedRAMP Compliance with Docker Hardened Images</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4147/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4147/</guid>
      <description>🚀 Navigating FedRAMP compliance can be costly and time-consuming, often taking 12-18 months and over $2 million. Competitors are already moving ahead while you manage security controls. Docker has introduced Hardened Images (DHI) to streamline this process. These pre-configured images support FIPS 140 compliance, simplifying cryptographic requirements. With DHI, companies can reduce compliance costs and speed up time-to-market for cloud services. 💻🔒 #FedRAMP #Docker #CloudCompliance&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Time to Evolve Authentication Security</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4146/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4146/</guid>
      <description>Identity-based attacks are on the rise, making strong authentication security necessary. Okta emphasizes the need to enhance identity security through initiatives like the Secure Identity Commitment. Key steps include adopting phishing-resistant methods, avoiding weak authentication, and implementing Multi-factor Authentication (MFA). Tailoring authentication requirements dynamically is crucial for balancing security and user experience. For developers, leveraging Identity Providers and using&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAPI 2.0: The Future of API Security for High-Stakes Customer Interactions</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4133/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4133/</guid>
      <description>🚀 FAPI 2.0 is redefining API security for critical customer interactions. Originally created for financial services, it now offers advanced protections applicable across industries. This new version focuses on enhancing end-to-end security and privacy for sensitive actions like payments and data sharing. Key benefits include clear specifications, thorough conformance tests, and a standards-based approach for better security. Discover how FAPI 2.0 can help protect your organization. 🔒🌐&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GitLab uncovers Bittensor theft campaign via PyPI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4678/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4678/</guid>
      <description>🚨 GitLab&amp;rsquo;s Vulnerability Research team has uncovered a cryptocurrency theft campaign targeting the Bittensor ecosystem via typosquatted Python packages on PyPI. Multiple malicious packages mimicked legitimate ones, published within a 25-minute window. These were designed to steal funds during staking operations, bypassing user confirmations and draining wallets silently. The attackers used a typosquatting strategy, exploiting common errors to increase the likelihood of installation. GitLab is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simplify access reviews with Trelica by 1Password</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4679/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-06-4679/</guid>
      <description>Managing access in today&amp;rsquo;s SaaS environment is challenging for organizations. Each time an employee joins or leaves, IT and security teams must adjust permissions to maintain security and compliance. 🔒 Access reviews are essential for verifying user access and meeting compliance standards like SOC 2 and ISO 27001. However, traditional methods often rely on spreadsheets, leading to incomplete processes and errors. 📊 Trelica by 1Password simplifies access reviews with automated workflows, a&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Everyone’s a Snowflake: Designing Hardened Image Processes for the Real World</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 18:54:38 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-2015/</guid>
      <description>Hardened container images and distroless software are gaining traction among startups and established companies. While they promise a smaller attack surface and operational simplicity, challenges arise in real-world applications. The unique needs of development teams often clash with rigid security measures, leading to frustration and workarounds. This &amp;lsquo;Snowflake Problem&amp;rsquo; highlights how no two environments are the same, complicating the balance between usability and security. Flexibility is&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Auth0 Mitigates OWASP’s Agentic AI Threats</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-05-1965/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-05-1965/</guid>
      <description>🌐 AI-powered agents are transforming industries, but they also bring significant security risks. Auth0 addresses these challenges highlighted by OWASP&amp;rsquo;s recent report on Agentic AI threats. Key risks include data breaches and regulatory non-compliance, which can erode customer trust. Traditional security measures often fall short for autonomous AI. Organizations must implement robust security from the start when developing GenAI applications. 🔐 #CyberSecurity #AI #GenAI #Auth0 #OWASP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hard Questions: What You Should Really Be Asking Your Hardened Image Provider Before You Press the Buy Button</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 19:08:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2017/</guid>
      <description>When considering hardened image providers, it’s essential to go beyond buzzwords like &amp;ldquo;zero-CVE.&amp;rdquo; Understanding their update and patch management processes is crucial. Ask how quickly they can respond to serious vulnerabilities and their SLAs on updates. Also, inquire about their modification processes. Knowing how to adjust images without compromising security is vital for maintaining your workflows. For more insights on essential questions to ask, check the full article. 🔍💻 #CyberSecurity&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Perplexity is using stealth, undeclared crawlers to evade website no-crawl directives</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2077/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-2077/</guid>
      <description>Perplexity, an AI-powered answer engine, is reportedly using stealth tactics to bypass website no-crawl directives. They modify user agents and change IPs to continue crawling despite explicit blocks. This behavior contradicts the trust-based principles of the internet, which emphasize transparency and adherence to website preferences. As a result, Perplexity has been de-listed as a verified bot and is facing new blocking measures. #Crawling #AI #WebSecurity #DataPrivacy #TechNews 🕵️‍♂️🔍🚫</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>v0: vibe coding, securely</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4165/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-04-4165/</guid>
      <description>Vibe coding is transforming software development, allowing rapid prototyping with tools like v0. Anthropic&amp;rsquo;s CEO indicates that in just 3-6 months, 90% of code may be AI-generated. However, this speed can lead to significant risks. A recent incident involved a viral app that leaked 72,000 selfies and IDs due to misconfigured settings, emphasizing the need for security measures. #VibeCoding #SoftwareDevelopment #CyberSecurity #AI #TechNews 🚀🔒📱</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability disclosure on SSL for SaaS v1 (Managed CNAME)</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2078/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-08-01-2078/</guid>
      <description>Cloudflare has announced a vulnerability disclosure for its SSL for SaaS v1 (Managed CNAME) product, identified through its bug bounty program. Despite deprecating this version in 2021, some customers have yet to migrate to SSL for SaaS v2. Cloudflare is working to assist these remaining clients in the transition. The architecture of SSL for SaaS v1 posed security risks due to its reliance on IP-based routing without domain ownership verification, leading to potential vulnerabilities. 🌐🔒&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing Agentic AI: How Semantic Prompt Injections Bypass AI Guardrails</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-220/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-220/</guid>
      <description>Prompt injection remains a significant threat to AI systems, particularly with the rise of multimodal and agentic AI. 🛡️ NVIDIA&amp;rsquo;s AI Red Team simulates real-world attacks to identify vulnerabilities in these advanced systems, emphasizing the need for cross-functional solutions. Their recent research introduces a new category of multimodal prompt injection using symbolic visual inputs, like emoji sequences. 🔍 This shift highlights the importance of adapting security strategies from input&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MCP Horror Stories: The Security Issues Threatening AI Infrastructure</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2019/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New Series Alert: MCP Horror Stories! 🚨 The first issue dives into the security vulnerabilities within the Model Context Protocol (MCP) ecosystem. MCP enables AI agents to communicate with various services, but this connectivity brings significant security risks. While MCP aims to streamline integrations, it has raised concerns about potential data breaches and system compromises due to malicious servers. Stay informed about the challenges in AI infrastructure! #AI #CyberSecurity #MCP&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBM Hyper Protect with OpenShift sandboxed containers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-99/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 07:01:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-99/</guid>
      <description>IBM is advancing data security with Hyper Protect Confidential Containers (HPCC) for Red Hat OpenShift. This solution protects sensitive workloads in untrusted environments, essential for industries like finance and healthcare. Using OpenShift sandboxed containers, HPCC ensures VM-level isolation for confidential computing. It addresses vulnerabilities of traditional containers by employing hardware-based trusted execution environments. Learn how HPCC enhances data protection and supports&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing CIBA for Secure Transaction Verification</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4073/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-4073/</guid>
      <description>🔐 &lt;strong&gt;Introducing CIBA for Secure Transaction Verification&lt;/strong&gt; 🔐 Digital applications require identity verification beyond just login interfaces. CIBA (Client-Initiated Backchannel Authentication) enhances security by decoupling authentication from applications, allowing users to verify their identity securely on different devices. This method is particularly useful in scenarios like updating bank email addresses or making payments at retail POS systems without sharing credentials on public&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Rules in Spain: Don’t Let Your Calls Get Ghosted</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5158/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5158/</guid>
      <description>🚨 New telecom regulations in Spain are now in effect! Spanish mobile numbers cannot be used for unsolicited marketing or customer service calls. This means calls may get flagged or blocked, especially if using Transit-Caller-ID. 📞 To stay compliant, consider switching to Spanish landline or toll-free numbers. Review your number strategy to avoid disruptions in communication. Stay informed and keep your calls connected! #Telecom #Spain #Compliance #Twilio #Communication</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing AI together: GitLab’s partnership with security researchers</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3192/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-3192/</guid>
      <description>GitLab is enhancing security in AI with the support of external researchers. As AI evolves, so do the challenges, like prompt injection attacks. Our collaboration with organizations like Persistent Security helps us identify vulnerabilities and implement fast solutions. By engaging with the security research community, we aim to protect customers and ensure a secure development environment. Join us in our mission at GitLab! 🤝🔒 #AISecurity #CyberSecurity #GitLab #Collaboration #SoftwareSafety</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Webflow’s availability incident: what we got wrong and what we’re changing</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5656/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-5656/</guid>
      <description>Webflow faced a significant service disruption on July 28, caused by a malicious attack that affected customer access. The team worked quickly to stabilize the platform. CEO&amp;rsquo;s reflections highlight shortcomings in communication and support during this incident. Immediate changes include enhanced monitoring, improved infrastructure, and proactive customer updates. Webflow is committed to making the platform more reliable and transparent moving forward. #Webflow #ServiceUpdate #CustomerSupport&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Omdia recommends Extended Access Management to secure agentic AI</title>
      <link>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2506/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/articles/article-2025-07-31-2506/</guid>
      <description>Omdia&amp;rsquo;s recent report highlights significant security challenges in managing access for agentic AI. With the rise of application, device, and identity sprawl, organizations face increased risk. AI agents require extensive access but lack secure management tools, leading to potential data leaks and unauthorized actions. Omdia recommends five strategies to secure access, including the need for robust measures specifically for AI agents. 1Password Extended Access Management offers a solution by&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
